<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新新增AI 消除和面对面翻译功能，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【图库】">
<feature>新增AI 消除功能，智能消除照片中的路人、杂物等，一键拯救废片，体验路径：图库>图片>编辑>AI 消除。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【面对面翻译】">
<feature>支持轮流对话场景下，中文、英语、法语、德语、西班牙语、意大利语、俄语、土耳其语、马来西亚语、阿拉伯语之间的互译。支持语音和文本输入，以及翻译结果播报，体验路径：设置>智慧助手>面对面翻译。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>合入安卓2024年9月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update brings new features, including AI Eraser and Face-to-face translation, and incorporates a security patch. It is recommended to update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>The new AI Eraser can help you intelligently remove the passers-by and other unwanted elements from images with a single tap. Try it out by going to: Gallery > Select a photo > Edit > AI Eraser.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Face-to-face translation">
<feature>In a turn-taking situation, it can provide mutual translation between Chinese, English, French, German, Spanish, Italian, Russian, Turkish, Malay, and Arabic. It also supports voice and text input, as well as translation broadcast. You can try it out by going to: Settings > Smart services > Face-to-face translation.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android Security Patch (Sept 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service center for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ የሚመከር ዝማኔ ኤአይ መደምሰሻ እና የፊት-ለፊት ትርጉምን ጨምሮ አዳዲስ ባህሪያትን ያመጣል እና የደህንነት መጠገኛን ያካትታል። እንዲያዘምኑ ይመከራሉ።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የሥነ ጥበብ ማዕከል">
<feature>አዲሱ ኤአይ መደምሰሻ መንገደኞችን እና ሌሎች አላስፈላጊ ነገሮችን በአንድ ጊዜ መታ በማድረግ ከምስሎች ላይ በብልህነት እንዲያስወግዱ ይረዳዎታል። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ የሥነ ጥበብ ማዕከል > ፎቶ ይምረጡ > አርትዕ > ኤአይ መደምሰሻ።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የፊት-ለፊት ትርጉም">
<feature>በተለዋዋጭ-ተራ ሁኔታ፣ በቻይንኛ፣ እንግሊዝኛ፣ ፈረንሳይኛ፣ ጀርመንኛ፣ ስፔንኛ፣ ጣልያንኛ፣ ሩሲያኛ፣ ቱርክኛ፣ ማላይኛ እና አረብኛ መካከል የጋራ ትርጉም መስጠት ይችላል። እንዲሁም የድምጽ እና የጽሑፍ ግብዓትን እንዲሁም የትርጉም ስርጭትን ይደግፋል። ወደዚህ በመሄድ ሊሞክሩት ይችላሉ፦ ቅንብሮች > ረዳት > የፊት-ለፊት ትርጉም።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ደህንነት">
<feature>ለስርዓት ደህንነት የአንድሮይድ የደህንነት መጠገኛን (ሴፕ 2024) ተካቷል። ስለ HONOR ደህንነት ዝማኔዎች ተጨማሪ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎን የእኛን ድር ጣቢያ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9 ይጎብኙ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ማሻሻያ መጫን የእርስዎን የግል መረጃዎን አይነካም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመን በፊት አስቀድሞ መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል።
2. በማሻሻያው ወቅት ማንኛውም አይነት ችግር ካጋጠመዎት እባክዎን ወደ HONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር ይደውሉ ወይም ድጋፍ ለማግኘት ወደ HONOR የደንበኞች የአገልግሎት ማዕከል ይሂዱ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يقدم هذا التحديث الموصى به ميزات جديدة، بما فيها الممحاة الذكية والترجمة وجهًا لوجه، ويضمّن تصحيح أمان. من المستحسن التحديث.</feature>
</features>
<features module="المعرض">
<feature>بإمكان أداة الممحاة الذكية الجديدة أن تساعدك على إزالة المارة والعناصر غير المرغوب فيها الأخرى من الصور بذكاء بضغطة واحدة. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: المعرض > تحديد صورة > تعديل > ممحاة ذكية.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ترجمة وجهًا لوجه">
<feature>في حالة تناوب الأدوار، بإمكان هذه الميزة توفير الترجمة المتبادلة بين اللغات الصينية والإنجليزية والفرنسية والألمانية والإسبانية والإيطالية والروسية والتركية والماليزية والعربية. وهي تدعم أيضًا إدخال الصوت والنص، بالإضافة إلى بث الترجمة. جرّب هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > المساعد > الترجمة وجهًا لوجه.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأمان">
<feature>تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (سبتمبر 2024) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في HONOR، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث.
2. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة HONOR أو الانتقال إلى مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR للحصول على الدعم.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই অনুমোদিত আপডেটটোৱে AI ৰবৰ আৰু পোনপটীয়া অনুবাদক অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰি নতুন ফিচাৰসমূহ লৈ আহে আৰু এটা নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰে। এইটো আপডেট কৰিবলৈ অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গেলাৰী">
<feature>নতুন AI ৰবৰে এবাৰ টিপি প্ৰতিচ্ছবিসমূহৰ পৰা পথচাৰী আৰু অন্য অবাঞ্ছিত উপাদানবোৰ বুদ্ধিমত্তাৰে আঁতৰোৱাত আপোনাক সহায় কৰিব। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাওক: গেলাৰী > এখন ফটো বাছনি কৰক > সম্পাদনা কৰক > AI ৰবৰ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="পোনপটীয়া অনুবাদ">
<feature>কথোপকথনৰ সময়ত ই চীনা, ইংৰাজী, ফ্ৰেন্স, জাৰ্মান, স্পেনিচ, ইটালীয়ান, ৰাছিয়ান, তুৰ্কী, মালয় আৰু আৰবীৰ মাজত পাৰস্পৰিক অনুবাদ প্ৰদান কৰিব পাৰে। ই লগতে ভইচ আৰু পাঠ ইনপুটৰ লগতে অনুবাদৰ ব্ৰডকাষ্ট সমৰ্থন কৰে। আপুনি ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াক ব্যৱহাৰ কৰি চাব পাৰে: ছেটিংছ > সহায়ক > পোনপটীয়া অনুবাদ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিৰাপত্তা">
<feature>ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (ছেপ্টেম্বৰ 2024) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। HONOR নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আপডেটৰ সময়ত আপুনি যদি কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হয়, তেন্তে সমৰ্থনৰ বাবে অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত ফোন কৰিব বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ যাব।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, tövsiyə edilən bu yeniləmə AI Pozan və Üz-üzə tərcümə də daxil olmaqla yeni xüsusiyyətlər təqdim edir və təhlükəsizlik paketi daxil edir. Yeniləmək tövsiyə olunur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qalereya">
<feature>Yeni AI Pozan sizə bir toxunuşla kənardan keçənləri və digər arzuolunmaz elementləri şəkillərdən ağıllı qaydada silməyə kömək edə bilər. Buraya keçərək sınayın: Qalereya > Foto seçin > Redaktə edin > AI Pozan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Üz-üzə tərcümə">
<feature>Növbəli vəziyyətdə Çin, İngilis, Fransız, Alman, İspan, İtalyan, Rus, Türk, Malay və Ərəb dilləri arasında qarşılıqlı tərcümə təmin edə bilər. O, həmçinin səs və mətn daxiletməsini, eləcə də tərcümə yayımını dəstəkləyir. Parametrlər > Yardımçı > Üz-üzə tərcümə bölməsinə keçərək bunu sınaya bilərsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Təhlükəsizlik">
<feature>Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android Təhlükəsizlik Paketi (Sentyabr 2024-cü il) daxil edilib. HONOR Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün veb-saytımıza daxil olun: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yeniləmədən əvvəl verilənlərinizin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur.
2. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlərlə qarşılaşsanız, dəstək üçün HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edin, yaxud HONOR müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə gedin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran sing disaranake iki menehi fitur anyar, kalebu Setip AI lan Pertalan adhep-adhepan, sarta nggabungake patch keamanan. Sampeyan disaranake supaya nganyarake.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Setip AI sing anyar bisa mbantu sampeyan mbusak wong liwat lan unsur sing ora dikarepake liyane kanthi wasis saka gambar kanthi nutul sepisan. Coba kanthi mbukak: Galeri > Pilih foto > Edit > Setip AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pertalan adhep-adhepan">
<feature>Ing kahanan gantian, fitur iki bisa nyedhiyakake pertalan bebarengan antarane Basa Mandarin, Basa Inggris, Basa Prancis, Basa Jerman, Basa Spanyol, Basa Italia, Basa Rusia, Basa Turki, Basa Melayu, lan Basa Arab. Fitur iki uga ndhukung input swara lan teks, sarta giyaran pertalan. Sampeyan bisa nyoba fitur iki kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Assistant > Pertalan adhep-adhepan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Patch Keamanan Android (September 2024) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan HONOR bisa dideleng ing situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging sampeyan tetep disaranake nggawe serep data sadurunge nganyarake
2. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, ubungi hotline layanan HONOR utawa tekani pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR kanggo njaluk dukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje donosi nove funkcije, uključujući AI gumicu i simultani prevod, i sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučujemo da ažurirate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Nova AI gumica može da vam pomogne da jednim dodirom pametno uklonite prolazne i ostale neželjene elemente sa slika. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na: Galerija > Izaberi fotografiju > Izmeni > AI gumica.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Simultano prevođenje">
<feature>Kada dođe red na vas da govorite, može da prevodi između kineskog, engleskog, francuskog, nemačkog, španskog, italijanskog, ruskog, turskog, malajskog i arapskog. Takođe podržava glasovne i tekstualne unose, kao i emitovanje prevoda. Možete da isprobate tako što ćete otići na: Podešavanja > Asistent > Simultano prevođenje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (sept 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje donosi nove funkcije, uključujući AI gumicu i simultani prevod, i sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučujemo da ažurirate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Nova AI gumica može da vam pomogne da jednim dodirom pametno uklonite prolazne i ostale neželjene elemente sa slika. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na: Galerija > Izaberi fotografiju > Izmeni > AI gumica.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Simultano prevođenje">
<feature>Kada dođe red na vas da govorite, može da prevodi između kineskog, engleskog, francuskog, nemačkog, španskog, italijanskog, ruskog, turskog, malajskog i arapskog. Takođe podržava glasovne i tekstualne unose, kao i emitovanje prevoda. Možete da isprobate tako što ćete otići na: Podešavanja > Asistent > Simultano prevođenje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (sept 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje donosi nove funkcije, uključujući AI gumicu i simultani prevod, i sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu. Preporučujemo da ažurirate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Nova AI gumica može da vam pomogne da jednim dodirom pametno uklonite prolazne i ostale neželjene elemente sa slika. Isprobajte tako što ćete otići na: Galerija > Izaberi fotografiju > Izmeni > AI gumica.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Simultano prevođenje">
<feature>Kada dođe red na vas da govorite, može da prevodi između kineskog, engleskog, francuskog, nemačkog, španskog, italijanskog, ruskog, turskog, malajskog i arapskog. Takođe podržava glasovne i tekstualne unose, kao i emitovanje prevoda. Možete da isprobate tako što ćete otići na: Podešavanja > Asistent > Simultano prevođenje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (sept 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта рэкамендаванае абнаўленне ўводзіць новыя функцыі, у тым ліку «Разумную гумку» і «Пераклад у рэальным часе». Таксама яно ўключае выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі. Рэкамендуецца ўстанавіць абнаўленне.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерэя">
<feature>Новая функцыя «Разумная гумка» выкарыстоўвае штучны інтэлект, каб вы маглі адным дотыкам выдаляць прахожых і іншыя непатрэбныя аб’екты са здымкаў. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Галерэя > Выбраць фота > Рэдагаваць > Разумная гумка».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Пераклад у рэальным часе">
<feature>У сітуацыі, калі людзі размаўляюць па чарзе, гэта функцыя можа забяспечваць вусны пераклад паміж наступнымі мовамі: кітайская, англійская, французская, нямецкая, іспанская, італьянская, руская, турэцкая, малайская і арабская. Таксама яна падтрымлівае галасавы і тэкставы ўвод і галасавую трансляцыю перакладу. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Памочнік > Пераклад у рэальным часе».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бяспека">
<feature>Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (верасень 2024 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі HONOR можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не паўплывае на вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію перад абнаўленнем.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, патэлефануйце на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або звярніцеся па дапамогу ў сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази препоръчителна актуализация въвежда нови функции, включително „AI гумичка“ и „Превод лице в лице“, и включва корекция за сигурност. Препоръчва се да актуализирате.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерия">
<feature>Новата „AI гумичка“ може да ви помогне да премахнете интелигентно минувачите и други нежелани елементи от изображенията с едно докосване. Изпробвайте я, като отидете на: „Галерия > Изберете снимка > Редактиране > AI гумичка“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Превод лице в лице">
<feature>В ситуация на изчакване на ред тази функция може да осигури взаимен превод между китайски, английски, френски, немски, испански, италиански, руски, турски, малайски и арабски език. Също така тя поддържа гласово и текстово въвеждане, както и излъчване на превод. Можете да я изпробвате, като отидете на: „Настройки > Асистент > Превод лице в лице“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сигурност">
<feature>Корекцията за сигурност на Android (септември 2024 г.) е включена за защита на системата. За още информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на HONOR посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да засегне личните ви данни, но е препоръчително да ги архивирате преди това.
2. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализирането, обадете се на обслужващата гореща линия на HONOR или посетете сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR за поддръжка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই সুপারিশকৃত আপডেটটি AI ইরেজার এবং মুখোমুখি অনুবাদ সহ নতুন বৈশিষ্ট্য নিয়ে এসেছে এবং এটিতে একটি নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ অন্তর্ভুক্ত আছে। এটা আপডেট করার সুপারিশ করা হয়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গ্যালারি">
<feature>নতুন AI ইরেজার আপনাকে বুদ্ধিমত্তার সাথে একবার মাত্র ট্যাপ করে ছবি থেকে পথচারীদের এবং অন্যান্য অবাঞ্ছিত উপাদানগুলি সরিয়ে দিতে সাহায্য করতে পারে। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: গ্যালারি > একটি ফটো নির্বাচন করুন > সম্পাদনা করুন > AI ইরেজার।</feature>
</features>
<features module="মুখোমুখি অনুবাদ">
<feature>পালাক্রমে কথোপকথনের পরিস্থিতিতে, এটি চীনা, ইংরেজি, ফরাসি, জার্মান, স্পেনীয়, ইতালীয়, রাশিয়ান, তুর্কি, মালয় এবং আরবি ভাষার মধ্যে পারস্পরিক অনুবাদ প্রদান করতে পারে। এটি ভয়েস এবং টেক্সট ইনপুটের পাশাপাশি অনুবাদ সম্প্রচারকেও সমর্থন করে। আপনি এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখতে পারেন: সেটিংস > সহকারী > মুখোমুখি অনুবাদ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিরাপত্তা">
<feature>সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (সেপ্টেম্বর 2024) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। HONOR-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. আপনি আপডেটের সময় কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে HONOR সার্ভিস হটলাইনে কল করুন বা সহায়তার জন্য HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে যান।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ AI གསུབ་འདོར་གདོང་ཐུག་ཡིག་སྒྱུར་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད་པ་དང་། བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཡོད་། ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་པར་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【པར་མཛོད།】">
<feature>AI གསུབ་འདོར་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། རིག་ལྡན་གྱིས་འདྲ་པར་ཁྲོད་ཀྱི་ལམ་འགྲོ་བ་དང་ཅ་ལག་སྣ་ཚོགས་སོགས་གསུབ་འདོར་བྱས་ནས། མཐེབ་གཅིག་གིས་འདྲ་པར་ཇེ་ལེགས་གཏོང་། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ་ནི། པར་མཛོད་ནས་པར་རིས། དེ་ནས་རྩོམ་སྒྲིག AI གསུབ་འདོར།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【གདོང་ཐུག་ཡིག་སྒྱུར།】">
<feature>རེས་མོས་སུ་ཁ་བརྡ་བྱེད་པའི་བཟོ་ལྗོངས་སུ། རྒྱ་ཡིག་དང་དབྱིན་ཡིག ཧྥ་རན་སེའི་སྐད། འཇར་མན་གྱི་སྐད། སི་ཕེན་གྱི་སྐད། དབྱི་ཐ་ལིའི་སྐད། ཨུ་རུ་སུའི་སྐད། ཐུར་ཁེའི་སྐད། མ་ལེ་ཞི་ཡའི་སྐད། ཨ་རབ་སྐད་བཅས་བར་ཕན་ཚུན་སྒྱུར་བར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད། སྐད་གདངས་དང་ཡིག་གཞི་ནང་འཇུག ཡིག་སྒྱུར་མཇུག་འབྲས་སྒྲོག་གཏོང་ལ་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་རིག་ལྡན་ལག་རོགས། དེ་ནས་གདོང་ཐུག་ཡིག་སྒྱུར།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【བདེ་འཇགས།】">
<feature>ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2024 ལོའི་ཟླ་བ་ 9 བའི་བདེ་འཇགས་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་སྟོབས་སྒྱུར་དུ་གཏོང་བ། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/9 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་གསར་སྒྱུར་མ་བྱས་གོང་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ཡག་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་ལ་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ་ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་སྐུ་མགྲོན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་སོང་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་རེ་ཞུ་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje donosi nove funkcije, uključujući AI brisač i Direktan prijevod, te ugrađuje sigurnosnu zakrpu. Preporučuje se da izvršite ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Novi AI brisač vam može pomoći da inteligentno uklonite prolaznike i druge neželjene elemente sa slika samo jednim dodirom. Isprobajte ga odlaskom u aplikaciju Galerija > Odaberite fotografiju > Uredi > AI brisač.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Direktan prijevod">
<feature>U situacijama kada se govornici izmjenjuju, može pružiti obostrani prijevod za kineski, engleski, francuski, njemački, španski, italijanski, ruski, turski, malajski i arapski jezik. Također podržava govorni i tekstualni unos, kao i emitiranje prijevoda. Možete ga isprobati odlaskom u Postavke > Pomoćnik > Direktan prijevod.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (sep 2024) radi sigurnosti sistema. Više informacija o HONOR sigurnosnim ažuriranjima potražite na našoj web lokaciji https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització recomanada presenta noves funcions, com ara Esborrador amb IA i Traducció directa, i incorpora un pedaç de seguretat. Recomanem que l'actualitzeu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>La nova funció Esborrador amb IA us ajuda a eliminar de manera intel·ligent els transeünts i altres elements que no voleu que apareguin de les imatges amb un sol toc. Proveu-ho des de: Galeria > Seleccioneu una foto > Editar > Esborrador amb IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traducció directa">
<feature>En una situació de torns d'intervenció, proporciona traducció mútua entre xinès, anglès, francès, alemany, castellà, italià, rus, turc, malai i àrab. També és compatible amb l'entrada de veu i text, així com la reproducció de traduccions. Proveu-ho des de: Configuració > Assistent > Traducció directa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguretat">
<feature>S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (setembre del 2024) per a la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'HONOR, consulteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però tot i així us recomanem que feu una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans de l'actualització.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o visiteu el centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážení uživatelé, tato doporučená aktualizace přináší nové funkce, včetně AI Gumy a Osobního překladu a obsahuje bezpečnostní opravu. Doporučujeme aktualizovat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Nová funkce AI Guma vám pomůže inteligentně odstranit kolemjdoucí a další nežádoucí prvky ze snímků jediným klepnutím. Vyzkoušejte si to v nabídce: Galerie > Vybrat fotografii > Upravit > AI Guma.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Osobní překlad">
<feature>Během rozhovoru dokáže zajistit vzájemný překlad mezi čínštinou, angličtinou, francouzštinou, němčinou, španělštinou, italštinou, ruštinou, turečtinou, malajštinou a arabštinou. Podporuje také hlasový a textový vstup a vysílání překladů. Můžete si to vyzkoušet v nabídce: Nastavení > Asistent > Osobní překlad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezpečnost">
<feature>Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (září 2024) pro systém Android pro zajištění bezpečnosti systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích HONOR najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Pokud se během aktualizace setkáte s nějakými problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo si vyžádejte podporu v Centru služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger, denne anbefalede opdatering bringer nye funktioner, inklusive AI-viskelæder og Oversættelse ansigt-til-ansigt, og den integrerer en sikkerhedsrettelse. Opdatering anbefales.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleri">
<feature>På en intelligent måde hjælper AI-viskelæder dig med at fjerne forbipasserende og andre uønskede elementer fra billeder med et enkelt tryk. Prøv det ved at gå til: Galleri > Vælg et foto > Rediger > AI-viskelæder.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oversættelse ansigt-til-ansigt">
<feature>I en situation, hvor personer skiftes til at tale, kan det levere gensidig oversættelse mellem kinesisk, engelsk, fransk, tysk, spansk, italiensk, russisk, tyrkisk, malajisk og arabisk. Det understøtter også stemme- og tekstinput samt oversættelsestransmission. Du kan prøve det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Assistent > Oversættelse ansigt-til-ansigt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhed">
<feature>Android sikkerhedsrettelse (sept 2024) er blevet integreret for systemsikkerhed. For yderligere oplysninger om HONOR-sikkerhedsopdateringer kan du besøge vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering vil ikke påvirke dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadig at sikkerhedskopiere dine data, før du opdaterer.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du ringe til HONORs service-hotline eller gå til HONORs kundeservicecenter for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung führt neue Funktionen wie AI-Radierer und Face-to-Face-Übersetzung ein und enthält einen Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Mit dem neuen AI-Radierer können Sie Passanten und andere unerwünschte Elemente mit einem einzigen Tippen intelligent aus Ihren Bildern entfernen. Probieren Sie es aus. Gehen Sie zu: Galerie > Foto auswählen > Bearbeiten > AI-Radierer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Face-to-Face-Übersetzung">
<feature>In einer Gesprächssituation kann die Funktion eine wechselseitige Übersetzung zwischen Chinesisch, Englisch, Französisch, Deutsch, Spanisch, Italienisch, Russisch, Türkisch, Malaiisch und Arabisch bereitstellen. Sie unterstützt außerdem die Sprach- und Texteingabe sowie die Übertragung von Übersetzungen. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Assistent > Face-to-Face-Übersetzung.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Sept. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung führt neue Funktionen wie AI-Radierer und Face-to-Face-Übersetzung ein und enthält einen Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Mit dem neuen AI-Radierer können Sie Passanten und andere unerwünschte Elemente mit einem einzigen Tippen intelligent aus Ihren Bildern entfernen. Probieren Sie es aus. Gehen Sie zu: Galerie > Foto auswählen > Bearbeiten > AI-Radierer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Face-to-Face-Übersetzung">
<feature>In einer Gesprächssituation kann die Funktion eine wechselseitige Übersetzung zwischen Chinesisch, Englisch, Französisch, Deutsch, Spanisch, Italienisch, Russisch, Türkisch, Malaiisch und Arabisch bereitstellen. Sie unterstützt außerdem die Sprach- und Texteingabe sowie die Übertragung von Übersetzungen. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Assistent > Face-to-Face-Übersetzung.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Sept. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung führt neue Funktionen wie AI-Radierer und Face-to-Face-Übersetzung ein und enthält einen Sicherheitspatch. Es wird empfohlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Mit dem neuen AI-Radierer können Sie Passanten und andere unerwünschte Elemente mit einem einzigen Tippen intelligent aus Ihren Bildern entfernen. Probieren Sie es aus. Gehen Sie zu: Galerie > Foto auswählen > Bearbeiten > AI-Radierer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Face-to-Face-Übersetzung">
<feature>In einer Gesprächssituation kann die Funktion eine wechselseitige Übersetzung zwischen Chinesisch, Englisch, Französisch, Deutsch, Spanisch, Italienisch, Russisch, Türkisch, Malaiisch und Arabisch bereitstellen. Sie unterstützt außerdem die Sprach- und Texteingabe sowie die Übertragung von Übersetzungen. Sie können es hier ausprobieren: Einstellungen > Assistent > Face-to-Face-Übersetzung.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Sept. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η προτεινόμενη ενημέρωση φέρνει νέες δυνατότητες, συμπεριλαμβανομένης της Γόμας AI και της Μετάφρασης πρόσωπο με πρόσωπο και ενσωματώνει μια ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας. Συνιστάται η ενημέρωση.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Συλλογή">
<feature>Η νέα Γόμα AI μπορεί να σας βοηθήσει να αφαιρέσετε έξυπνα τα πρόσθετα στοιχεία και άλλα ανεπιθύμητα στοιχεία από τις εικόνες με ένα μόνο πάτημα. Δοκιμάστε τη μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Συλλογή > Επιλογή φωτογραφίας > Επεξεργασία > Γόμα AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Μετάφραση πρόσωπο με πρόσωπο">
<feature>Σε μια κατάσταση εναλλασσόμενης ακρόασης/ομιλίας, μπορεί να παρέχει αμοιβαία μετάφραση μεταξύ Κινεζικών, Αγγλικών, Γαλλικών, Γερμανικών, Ισπανικών, Ιταλικών, Ρωσικών, Τουρκικών, Μαλαισιανών και Αραβικών. Υποστηρίζει επίσης την φωνητική καταχώριση και την καταχώριση κειμένου, καθώς και τη μετάδοση μετάφρασης. Μπορείτε να τη δοκιμάσετε μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Βοηθός > Μετάφραση πρόσωπο με πρόσωπο.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ασφάλεια">
<feature>Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Σεπτέμβριος 2024) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας HONOR, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση.
2. Εάν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, καλέστε την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή της HONOR ή μεταβείτε στο κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR για υποστήριξη.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update brings new features, including AI Eraser and Face-to-face translation, and incorporates a security patch. It is recommended to update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>The new AI Eraser can help you intelligently remove the passers-by and other unwanted elements from images with a single tap. Try it out by going to: Gallery > Select a photo > Edit > AI Eraser.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Face-to-face translation">
<feature>In a turn-taking situation, it can provide mutual translation between Chinese, English, French, German, Spanish, Italian, Russian, Turkish, Malay, and Arabic. It also supports voice and text input, as well as translation broadcast. You can try it out by going to: Settings > Assistant > Face-to-face translation.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android Security Patch (Sept 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service centre for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada implementa nuevas funcionalidades, como Goma de borrar de IA y Traducción cara a cara, e incorpora un parche de seguridad. Le recomendamos que actualice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galería">
<feature>El nuevo Goma de borrar de IA puede ayudarte a eliminar de forma inteligente los transeúntes y otros elementos no deseados de las imágenes con un solo toque. Pruébelo en: Galería > Seleccionar una foto > Editar > Goma de borrar de IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traducción cara a cara">
<feature>En una situación de turnos, puede proporcionar traducción mutua entre chino, inglés, francés, alemán, español, italiano, ruso, turco, malayo y árabe. También admite la introducción de voz y texto, así como la emisión de traducciones. Puede probarlo yendo a: Ajustes > Asistente > Traducción cara a cara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (septiembre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para obtener ayuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada implementa nuevas funcionalidades, como Borrador IA y Traducción cara a cara, e incorpora un parche de seguridad. Le recomendamos que actualice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galería">
<feature>La nueva Goma IA puede ayudarlo a eliminar de forma inteligente a los transeúntes y otros elementos no deseados de las imágenes con solo presionar una vez. Pruébelo accediendo a: Galería > Seleccionar una foto > Editar > Goma IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traducción cara a cara">
<feature>En una situación por turnos, puede proporcionar traducción mutua entre chino, inglés, francés, alemán, español, italiano, ruso, turco, malayo y árabe. También admite la entrada de voz y texto, así como la transmisión de traducción. Puede probarlo accediendo a: Ajustes > Servicios inteligentes > Traducción cara a cara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (septiembre de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visite el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja! See soovitatav värskendus lisab uusi funktsioone, sh AI-kustutaja ja Näost näkku tõlke, ning sisaldab turvapaika. Soovitatav on värskendada.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerii">
<feature>Uus AI-kustutaja aitab juhuslikult kaadrisse jalutajad ja muu soovimatu piltidelt ühe puudutusega eemaldada. Proovige: Galerii > valige foto > Redigeeri > AI-kustutaja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Näost näkku tõlge">
<feature>Vahelduvate kõnelejatega vestluses võib see tõlkida hiina, inglise, prantsuse, saksa, hispaania, itaalia, vene, türgi, malai ja araabia keelt. See toetab nii hääl- kui ka tekstsisestust ning tõlke teadustamist. Proovimiseks avage Sätted > Assistent > Näost näkku tõlge.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turve">
<feature>Lisati süsteemi turvalisemaks muutev Androidi turvapaik (september 2024). Lisateavet HONORi turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isikuandmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, helistage HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või minge toe saamiseks HONORi klienditeeninduskeskusesse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile agurgarria: gomendatutako eguneratze honetan ezaugarri berriak gehitu dira, AA borragoma eta aurrez aurreko itzulpena barne, eta segurtasun-adabaki bat gehitu da. Eguneratzea gomendatzen da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>AA borragoma berriari esker, modu adimendunean ezaba ditzakezu argazkietatik nahi ez dituzun pertsonak eta elementuak sakatze bakarrarekin. Hori probatzeko, joan Galeria > Hautatu argazki bat > Editatu > AA borragoma aukerara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aurrez aurrezko itzulpena">
<feature>Txanda-egoeretan, elkarren arteko itzulpenak eman ditzake txineraz, ingelesez, frantsesez, alemanaz, gaztelaniaz, italieraz, errusieraz, turkieraz, malaysieraz eta arabieraz. Halaber, ahots- eta testu-sarrerak eta itzulpenen transmisioak onartzen ditu. Hori probatzeko, joan Ezarpenak > Laguntzailea > Aurrez aurreko itzulpena aukerara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurtasuna">
<feature>Android-en segurtasun-adabakia (2024ko ira.) gehitu da sistemaren segurtasuna hobetzeko. HONOR Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago nahi izanez gero, joan gure webgunera: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzen baduzu ere, ez diezu eragingo datu pertsonalei, baina gomendagarria da datuen babeskopia bat egitea eguneratzea egin baino lehen.
2. Arazorik baduzu eguneratzea egitean, deitu HONOR zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara edo joan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora laguntza lortzeko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی پیشنهادی قابلیت‌های جدیدی را ارائه می‌کند که شامل «پاک‌کن هوش مصنوعی» و «ترجمۀ رودررو» است و یک وصله امنیتی در آن گنجانده شده است. توصیه می‌شود به‌روزرسانی را انجام دهید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="گالری">
<feature>‏‏قابلیت جدید «پاک‌کن هوش مصنوعی» می‌تواند به شما کمک کند تا رهگذران و سایر عناصر ناخواسته را فقط با یک بار ضربه زدن به‌صورت هوشمندانه از تصاویر حذف کنید. با رفتن به «گالری > انتخاب عکس > ویرایش > پاک‌کن هوش مصنوعی» می‌توانید آن را امتحان کنید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ترجمۀ رودررو">
<feature>در شرایط صحبت کردن به نوبت، قادر است ترجمه متقابل بین زبان‌های چینی، انگلیسی، فرانسوی، آلمانی، اسپانیایی، ایتالیایی، روسی، ترکی، مالایی و عربی را ارائه دهد. همچنین از ورودی گفتاری و نوشتاری و همچنین پخش ترجمه پشتیبانی می‌کند. با رفتن به «تنظیمات > دستیار > ترجمۀ رودررو» می‌توانید آن را امتحان کنید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="امنیت">
<feature>برای حفظ امنیت سیستم، وصلۀ امنیتی Android (سپتامبر ۲۰۲۴) گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر دربارۀ به‌روزرسانی‌های امنیتی HONOR، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما به این نشانی مراجعه کنید: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="نکات قابل‌توجه:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما را تحت تأثیر قرار نخواهد داد، اما همچنان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.
‏‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، لطفاً جهت دریافت پشتیبانی با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä suositeltu päivitys lisää uusia ominaisuuksia, kuten AI-pyyhekumin ja Kasvotusten suoritettavan käännöksen, sekä sisältää turvallisuus korjauksen. Päivittämistä suositellaan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleria">
<feature>Uusi AI-pyyhekumi poistaa ohikulkijat ja muut ei-toivotut kohteet älykkäästi kuvista yhdellä napautuksella. Voit kokeilla sitä kohdassa Galleria > Valitse valokuva > Muokkaa > AI-pyyhekumi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kasvotusten suoritettava käännös">
<feature>Tarjoaa vuoropuhelun aikana molemminpuolisen käännöksen kiinan, englannin, ranskan, saksan, espanjan, italian, venäjän, turkin, malaijin ja arabian välillä. Se tukee myös ääni- ja tekstisyötettä sekä käännösten lähetystä. Voit kokeilla sitä kohdassa Asetukset > Avustaja > Kasvotusten suoritettava käännös.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvallisuus">
<feature>Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (syyskuu 2024) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja HONORin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa.
2. Soita HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käy HONORin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa, jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia ja tarvitset apua.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée ajoute de nouvelles fonctionnalités, dont Gomme IA et Traduction face à face, et intègre un correctif de sécurité. Nous vous recommandons d'effectuer la mise à jour.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>La nouvelle Gomme IA peut vous aider à supprimer intelligemment les passants et les autres éléments indésirables des images d'un simple appui. Essayez-la en accédant à : Galerie > Sélectionner une photo > Retoucher > Gomme IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traduction face à face">
<feature>Dans une situation de tour de parole, elle peut fournir une traduction mutuelle entre le chinois, l'anglais, le français, l'allemand, l'espagnol, l'italien, le russe, le turc, le malais et l'arabe. Elle prend également en charge la saisie vocale et textuelle, ainsi que la diffusion de traduction. Vous pouvez l'essayer en accédant à : Paramètres > Assistant > Traduction face à face.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Un correctif de sécurité Android (septembre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée ajoute de nouvelles fonctionnalités, dont Gomme IA et Traduction face à face, et intègre un correctif de sécurité. Nous vous recommandons d'effectuer la mise à jour.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>La nouvelle Gomme IA peut vous aider à supprimer intelligemment les passants et les autres éléments indésirables des images d'un simple appui. Essayez-la en accédant à : Galerie > Sélectionner une photo > Retoucher > Gomme IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traduction face à face">
<feature>Dans une situation de tour de parole, elle peut fournir une traduction mutuelle entre le chinois, l'anglais, le français, l'allemand, l'espagnol, l'italien, le russe, le turc, le malais et l'arabe. Elle prend également en charge la saisie vocale et textuelle, ainsi que la diffusion de traduction. Vous pouvez l'essayer en accédant à : Paramètres > Assistant > Traduction face à face.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Un correctif de sécurité Android (septembre 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada engade novas funcionalidades, como Goma de borrar con IA e Tradución cara a cara, e incorpora un parche de seguranza. Recoméndase aplicar a actualización.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galería">
<feature>A nova Goma de borrar con IA pode axudarlle a quitar de xeito intelixente os espontáneos e outros elementos non desexados das imaxes cun só toque. Para probala, vaia a: Galería > Seleccionar unha foto > Editar > Goma de borrar con IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tradución cara a cara">
<feature>Ao falar por quendas, pode traducir conversas entre os seguintes idiomas: chinés, inglés, francés, alemán, español, italiano, ruso, turco, malaio e árabe. Tamén é compatible con entradas de texto e voz e coa transmisión da tradución. Para probala, vaia a: Configuración > Asistente > Tradución cara a cara.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguranza">
<feature>Incorporouse un parche de seguranza de Android (setembro de 2024) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información acerca das actualizacións de seguranza de HONOR, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar unha copia de seguranza dos datos antes da actualización.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou vaia a un centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ ભલામણ કરેલ અપડેટ નવી સુવિધાઓ લાવે છે, AI ઇરેઝર અને સામ-સામે અનુવાદ સહિત, અને સુરક્ષા પેચનો સમાવેશ કરે છે. અપડેટ કરવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ગૅલેરી">
<feature>નવું AI ઇરેઝર તમને એક જ ટૅપ વડે છબીમાંથી પસાર થતા લોકો અને અન્ય અનિચ્છનીય તત્વોને બુદ્ધિપૂર્વક દૂર કરવામાં મદદ કરી શકે છે. અહીં જઈને અજમાવી જુઓ: ગૅલેરી > ફોટો પસંદ કરો > સંપાદિત કરો > AI ઇરેઝર.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સામ-સામે અનુવાદ">
<feature>ટર્ન-ટેકિંગ પરિસ્થિતિમાં, તે ચાઇનીઝ, અંગ્રેજી, ફ્રેન્ચ, જર્મન, સ્પેનિશ, ઇટાલિયન, રશિયન, ટર્કિશ, મલય અને અરબી વચ્ચે પરસ્પર અનુવાદ પ્રદાન કરી શકે છે. તે વૉઇસ અને ટેક્સ્ટ ઇનપુટ તેમજ અનુવાદ પ્રસારણને પણ સમર્થન કરે છે. તમે તેને અહીં જઈને અજમાવી શકો છો: સેટિંગ્સ > સહાયક > સામ-સામે અનુવાદ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સુરક્ષા">
<feature>Android સુરક્ષા પેચ (સપ્ટેમ્બર 2024) સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. HONOR સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9 ની મુલાકાત લો</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલા તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો કૃપા કરીને HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરો અથવા સમર્થન માટે HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્ર પર જાઓ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, यह अनुशंसित अपडेट AI इरेज़र और फ़ेस टु फ़ेस अनुवाद सहित नई सुविधाएँ देता है, और एक सुरक्षा पैच शामिल करता है। इसे अपडेट करने की सलाह दी जाती है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गैलरी">
<feature>नए AI इरेज़र से आपको एक टैप में स्मार्ट तरीके से छवियों से अनावश्यक और अन्य अनचाही चीज़ों को निकालने में सहायता मिल सकती है। इसे यहाँ जाकर आज़माएँ: गैलरी > फ़ोटो चुनें > संपादित करें > AI इरेज़र।</feature>
</features>
<features module="आमने-सामने अनुवाद">
<feature>बारी-बारी से बातचीत वाली स्थिति में, इसमें चीनी, अंग्रेज़ी, फ़्रेंच, जर्मन, स्पैनिश, इतालवी, रूसी, तुर्की, मलय और अरबी के बीच पारस्परिक अनुवाद की सुविधा मिल सकती है। इसमें वॉइस और पाठ इनपुट के साथ-साथ अनुवाद प्रसारण का भी समर्थन किया जाता है। आप यहाँ जाकर इसे आज़मा सकते हैं: सेटिंग्स > सहायक > आमने-सामने अनुवाद।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>सिस्टम की सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (सितंबर, 2024) शामिल किया गया है। HONOR सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट पर जाएँ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो सहायता पाने के लिए, HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करें या HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाएँ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se preporučenim ažuriranjem uvode nove značajke, uključujući AI gumicu i Prijevod licem u lice i ugrađuje sigurnosna zakrpa. Preporučuje se ažuriranje.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Nova značajka AI gumica može vam pomoći jednim dodirom inteligentno ukloniti prolaznike i druge neželjene elemente sa slika. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Galerija > Odaberi fotografiju > Uredi > AI gumica.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prijevod licem u lice">
<feature>U situaciji kada se govornici izmjenjuju, može svim stranama pružiti prijevod s kineskog, engleskog, francuskog, njemačkog, španjolskog, talijanskog, ruskog, turskog, malajskog i arapskog. Podržava i glasovni i tekstualni unos te emitiranje prijevoda. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Pomoćnik > Prijevod licem u lice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (rujan 2024.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke HONOR Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako tijekom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za pomoć nazovite telefonsku korisničku službu tvrtke HONOR ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku tvrtke HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez az ajánlott frissítés új funkciókat vezet be, ilyen például az AI-radír és a Szinkrontolmácsolás, és egy biztonsági javítást is tartalmaz. Javasoljuk, hogy telepítse a frissítést.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galéria">
<feature>Az új AI-radír segítségével egyetlen koppintással intelligensen eltávolíthatja a képekről a járókelőket és más nem kívánt elemeket. Próbálja ki: Galéria > Válasszon ki egy fényképet > Szerkesztés > AI-radír.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Szinkrontolmácsolás">
<feature>Ha felváltva beszélget valakivel, ez a funkció fordítást tud biztosítani a kínai, az angol, a francia, a német, a spanyol, az olasz, az orosz, a török, a maláj és az arab nyelv között. A hang- és a szövegbevitelt egyaránt támogatja, valamint a fordítás továbbítását is. Próbálja ki: Beállítások > Asszisztens > Szinkrontolmácsolás.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biztonság">
<feature>Tartalmazza a rendszer biztonságát fokozó Android biztonsági javítást (2024. szeptember). A HONOR biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. A frissítés telepítése nem érinti az Ön személyes adatait, de a frissítés megkezdése előtt ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni az adatokról.
2. Ha problémába ütközik a frissítés során, hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini membawakan fitur-fitur baru, termasuk Penghapus AI dan Terjemahan tatap muka, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan. Anda direkomendasikan untuk memperbarui.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Penghapus AI yang baru dapat membantu Anda menghapus orang yang lewat atau elemen lainnya yang tidak diinginkan dari gambar dengan sekali ketuk. Cobalah dengan membuka: Galeri > Pilih foto > Edit > Penghapus AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Terjemahan tatap muka">
<feature>Dalam situasi bersahutan, layanan ini dapat menyediakan penerjemahan bersama antara bahasa Mandarin, Inggris, Prancis, Jerman, Spanyol, Italia, Rusia, Turki, Melayu, dan Arab. Layanan ini juga mendukung masukan suara dan teks, serta siaran penerjemahan. Anda dapat mencobanya dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Asisten > Terjemahan tatap muka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Penambal Keamanan Android (Sept 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini membawakan fitur-fitur baru, termasuk Penghapus AI dan Terjemahan tatap muka, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan. Anda direkomendasikan untuk memperbarui.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Penghapus AI yang baru dapat membantu Anda menghapus orang yang lewat atau elemen lainnya yang tidak diinginkan dari gambar dengan sekali ketuk. Cobalah dengan membuka: Galeri > Pilih foto > Edit > Penghapus AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Terjemahan tatap muka">
<feature>Dalam situasi bersahutan, layanan ini dapat menyediakan penerjemahan bersama antara bahasa Mandarin, Inggris, Prancis, Jerman, Spanyol, Italia, Rusia, Turki, Melayu, dan Arab. Layanan ini juga mendukung masukan suara dan teks, serta siaran penerjemahan. Anda dapat mencobanya dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Asisten > Terjemahan tatap muka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Penambal Keamanan Android (Sept 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato introduce nuove funzioni, incluse Gomma AI e Traduzione faccia a faccia, e incorpora una patch di sicurezza. Si consiglia di effettuare l'aggiornamento.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleria">
<feature>La nuova Gomma AI può aiutarti a rimuovere in modo intelligente intrusi e altri elementi indesiderati dalle immagini con un solo tocco. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Galleria > Seleziona una foto > Modifica > Gomma AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traduzione faccia a faccia">
<feature>In scenari di conversazione alternata, può fornire la traduzione bidirezionale tra cinese, inglese, francese, tedesco, spagnolo, italiano, russo, turco, malese e arabo. Inoltre, supporta l'immissione di voce e di testo, nonché la trasmissione di traduzioni. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Assistente > Traduzione faccia a faccia.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (settembre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato introduce nuove funzioni, incluse Gomma AI e Traduzione faccia a faccia, e incorpora una patch di sicurezza. Si consiglia di effettuare l'aggiornamento.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleria">
<feature>La nuova Gomma AI può aiutarti a rimuovere in modo intelligente intrusi e altri elementi indesiderati dalle immagini con un solo tocco. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Galleria > Seleziona una foto > Modifica > Gomma AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traduzione faccia a faccia">
<feature>In scenari di conversazione alternata, può fornire la traduzione bidirezionale tra cinese, inglese, francese, tedesco, spagnolo, italiano, russo, turco, malese e arabo. Inoltre, supporta l'immissione di voce e di testo, nonché la trasmissione di traduzioni. Per provare la funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Assistente > Traduzione faccia a faccia.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (settembre 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה מביא עימו תכונות חדשות, כולל 'מחק AI' ו'תרגום פנים אל פנים', ומשלב תיקון אבטחה. מומלץ לעדכן.</feature>
</features>
<features module="גלריה">
<feature>‏'מחק AI' החדש יכול לעזור לך להסיר בצורה חכמה את העוברים ושבים ורכיבים לא רצויים אחרים מהתמונות בהקשה אחת. נסה זאת על-ידי מעבר אל 'גלריה' > 'בחר תמונה' > 'ערוך' > 'מחק AI'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="תרגום פנים אל פנים">
<feature>במצב של לקיחת תורות, אפשרות זו יכולה לספק תרגום הדדי בין סינית, אנגלית, צרפתית, גרמנית, ספרדית, איטלקית, רוסית, טורקית, מלאית וערבית. הוא תומך גם בהזנת קול וטקסט, וכן בשידור תרגום. תוכל לנסות זאת על ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' > 'מסייע' > 'תרגום פנים אל פנים'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מספט' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה מביא עימו תכונות חדשות, כולל 'מחק AI' ו'תרגום פנים אל פנים', ומשלב תיקון אבטחה. מומלץ לעדכן.</feature>
</features>
<features module="גלריה">
<feature>‏'מחק AI' החדש יכול לעזור לך להסיר בצורה חכמה את העוברים ושבים ורכיבים לא רצויים אחרים מהתמונות בהקשה אחת. נסה זאת על-ידי מעבר אל 'גלריה' > 'בחר תמונה' > 'ערוך' > 'מחק AI'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="תרגום פנים אל פנים">
<feature>במצב של לקיחת תורות, אפשרות זו יכולה לספק תרגום הדדי בין סינית, אנגלית, צרפתית, גרמנית, ספרדית, איטלקית, רוסית, טורקית, מלאית וערבית. הוא תומך גם בהזנת קול וטקסט, וכן בשידור תרגום. תוכל לנסות זאת על ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' > 'מסייע' > 'תרגום פנים אל פנים'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מספט' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様。今回の推奨更新では、AI消しゴム、対面翻訳などの新機能が導入され、セキュリティパッチが組み込まれます。更新することをおすすめします。</feature>
</features>
<features module="ギャラリー">
<feature>新しいAI消しゴムによって、通行人やその他不要な要素を1回のタップで画面からインテリジェントに削除できます。[ギャラリー] > [写真を選択] > [編集] > [AI消しゴム]に移動して試してください。</feature>
</features>
<features module="対面翻訳">
<feature>発話交代状況で、中国語、英語、フランス語、ドイツ語、スペイン語、イタリア語、ロシア語、トルコ語、マレー語、アラビア語を交互に翻訳します。また、音声とテキストの入力、翻訳ブロードキャストもサポートされます。[設定] > [アシスタント] > [対面翻訳]に移動して試してください。</feature>
</features>
<features module="セキュリティ">
<feature>システムセキュリティのためにAndroidセキュリティパッチ（2024年9月）が組み込まれました。HONORのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報に影響はありませんが、更新前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターでサポートを受けてください。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ეს რეკომენდებული განახლება მოიცავს ახალ ფუნქციებს, მათ შორის, AI საშლელსა და პირისპირ თარგმნას. მასში ასევე ჩაშენებულია უსაფრთხოების შესწორება. გირჩევთ განახლებას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="გალერეა">
<feature>ახალი AI საშლელი დაგეხმარებათ, ერთი შეხებით, ჭკვიანურად ამოშალოთ სურათებიდან გამვლელები და სხვა არასასურველი ელემენტები. გამოსცადეთ ის მენიუდან: გალერეა > ფოტოს არჩევა > რედაქტირ. > AI საშლელი.</feature>
</features>
<features module="პირისპირ თარგმანი">
<feature>თანმიმდევრული საუბრის სიტუაციებში მას შეუძლია უზრუნველყოს ორმხრივი თარგმანი ჩინურ, ინგლისურ, ფრანგულ, გერმანულ, ესპანურ, იტალიურ, რუსულ, თურქულ, მალაიურ და არაბულ ენებს შორის. გარდა ამისა, აქვს ხმოვანი და ტექსტური შეყვანის, ასევე თარგმანის გადაცემის მხარდაჭერა. მისი ცდა შეგიძლიათ მენიუდან: პარამეტრები > ასისტენტი > პირისპირ თარგმანი.</feature>
</features>
<features module="უსაფრთხოება">
<feature>სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის ჩაირთო Android უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (2024 წლის სექტემბერი). HONOR-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ იქონიებს გავლენას თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. განახლების დროს პრობლემების წარმოქმნის შემთხვევაში, მხარდაჭერის მისაღებად დარეკეთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან მიმართეთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл ұсынылған жаңарту жаңа мүмкіндіктерді (оның ішінде «ЖИ өшіргіші» және «Бетпе-бет аудару») ұсынады және қауіпсіздік патчын біріктіреді. Жаңарту ұсынылады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерея">
<feature>Жаңа «ЖИ өшіргіші» мүмкіндігі бір рет түрту арқылы кескіндерден жүргіншілер мен басқа қажетсіз элементтерді зерделі түрде жоюға көмектеседі. «Галерея» > «Фотосуретті таңдау» > «Өңдеу» > «ЖИ өшіргіші» тармағына өту арқылы қолданып көріңіз.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бетпе-бет аудару">
<feature>Кезекті жағдайда ол қытай, ағылшын, француз, неміс, испан, итальян, орыс, түрік, малай және араб тілдері арасында өзара аударманы қамтамасыз ете алады. Сондай-ақ ол дауыстық және мәтіндік енгізілімді, сонымен бірге аударманы таратуды қолдайды. «Параметрлер» > «Көмекші» > «Бетпе-бет аудару» тармағына өту арқылы қолданып көруге болады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қауіпсіздік">
<feature>Android қауіпсіздік патчы (қыркүйек, 2024) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. HONOR қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңартпас бұрын деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту барысында мәселелер орын алса, қолдау алу үшін HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне хабарласыңыз немесе HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына барыңыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពដែលបានណែនាំនេះនាំយកមុខងារថ្មីៗ ដែលរួមមានប្រដាប់លុប AI និងការបកប្រែទល់មុខគ្នា និងរួមបញ្ចូលបំណះសន្តិសុខ។ សូមណែនាំឱ្យធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព។</feature>
</features>
<features module="វិចិត្រសាល">
<feature>ប្រដាប់លុប AI ថ្មីអាចជួយអ្នកយកអ្នកឆ្លងកាត់ និងធាតុផ្សំដែលមិនចង់បានផ្សេងទៀតចេញពីរូបភាពបានយ៉ាងឆ្លាតវៃត្រឹមមួយប៉ះ។ សាកល្បងប្រើវាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ វិចិត្រសាល > ជ្រើសរើសរូបថត > កែ > ប្រដាប់លុប AI។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ការបកប្រែ​មុខទល់មុខគ្នា">
<feature>ក្នុងស្ថានភាពប្ដូរវេនគ្នា វាអាចផ្ដល់ការបកប្រែទៅវិញទៅមករវាងភាសាចិន ភាសាអង់គ្លេស ភាសាបារាំង ភាសាអាល្លឺម៉ង់ ភាសាអេស្ប៉ាញ ភាសាអ៊ីតាលី ភាសារុស្ស៊ី ភាសាតួកគី ភាសាម៉ាឡេ និងភាសាអារ៉ាប់។ វាក៏អាចប្រើការបញ្ចូលសំឡេង និងអត្ថបទ ក៏ដូចជាការផ្សាយការបកប្រែបានផងដែរ។ អ្នកអាចសាកល្បងប្រើវាបានដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > ជំនួយការ > ការបកប្រែ​មុខទល់មុខគ្នា។</feature>
</features>
<features module="សន្តិសុខ">
<feature>បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (កញ្ញា 2024) ត្រូវបាន​រួមបញ្ចូល​សម្រាប់​សន្តិសុខ​ប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់​ព័ត៌មាន​បន្ថែម​អំពី​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​សន្តិសុខ HONOR សូមចូលទៅ​គេហទំព័រ​របស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​ប៉ះពាល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបបញ្ហាណាមួយក្នុងអំឡុងពេល​ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព សូមហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សផ្នែកសេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​សេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR ដើម្បី​ទទួលបាន​ជំនួយ។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಿದ ನವೀಕರಣವು AI ಎರೇಸರ್ ಮತ್ತು ಮುಖಾಮುಖಿ ಅನುವಾದ ಸೇರಿದಂತೆ ಹೊಸ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳನ್ನು ತರುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ನವೀಕರಿಸಲು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಗ್ಯಾಲರಿ">
<feature>ಹೊಸ AI ಎರೇಸರ್ ನಿಮಗೆ ಒಂದೇ ಟ್ಯಾಪ್‌ನ ಮೂಲಕ ಚಿತ್ರಗಳಲ್ಲಿರುವ ದಾರಿಹೋಕರು ಮತ್ತು ಇತರ ಅನಗತ್ಯ ಅಂಶಗಳನ್ನು ಬುದ್ಧಿವಂತಿಕೆಯಿಂದ ತೆಗೆದುಹಾಕಲು ಸಹಾಯ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಿ: ಗ್ಯಾಲರಿ > ಫೋಟೋ ಆಯ್ಕೆಮಾಡಿ > ಎಡಿಟ್ ಮಾಡಿ > AI ಎರೇಸರ್.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಮುಖಾಮುಖಿ ಅನುವಾದ">
<feature>ಸರದಿ ಕ್ರಮದ ಪರಿಸ್ಥಿತಿಯಲ್ಲಿ, ಇದು ಚೈನೀಸ್, ಇಂಗ್ಲೀಷ್, ಫ್ರೆಂಚ್, ಜರ್ಮನ್, ಸ್ಪ್ಯಾನಿಷ್, ಇಟಾಲಿಯನ್, ರಷ್ಯನ್, ಟರ್ಕಿಶ್, ಮಲಯ ಮತ್ತು ಅರೇಬಿಕ್ ನಡುವೆ ಪರಸ್ಪರ ಅನುವಾದವನ್ನು ಒದಗಿಸಬಹುದು. ಇದು ಧ್ವನಿ ಮತ್ತು ಪಠ್ಯ ಇನ್‌ಪುಟ್‌ನ ಜೊತೆಗೆ ಅನುವಾದ ಪ್ರಸಾರವನ್ನು ಸಹ ಬೆಂಬಲಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನೀವು ಇದನ್ನು ಪ್ರಯತ್ನಿಸಬಹುದು: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಸಹಾಯಕ > ಮುಖಾಮುಖಿ ಅನುವಾದ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಭದ್ರತೆ">
<feature>ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ಸೆಪ್ಟೆಂಬರ್ 2024) ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. HONOR ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್‌ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಈಗಲೂ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ಅಥವಾ ಬೆಂಬಲಕ್ಕಾಗಿ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಹೋಗಿ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 권장 업데이트에서는 AI 지우개와 대면식 번역을 비롯한 새로운 기능이 추가되었으며 보안 패치가 통합되었습니다. 업데이트하는 것이 좋습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="갤러리">
<feature>새로운 AI 지우개는 한 번의 탭으로 이미지에서 지나가는 사람이나 기타 원치 않는 요소를 지능적으로 제거할 수 있도록 도와줍니다. 갤러리 > 사진 선택 > 편집 > AI 지우개로 이동해서 사용해 보세요.</feature>
</features>
<features module="대면식 번역">
<feature>차례를 기다리는 상황에서 중국어, 영어, 프랑스어, 독일어, 스페인어, 이탈리아어, 러시아어, 터키어, 말레이어, 아랍어 간의 상호 번역을 제공할 수 있습니다. 또한 음성 및 텍스트 입력은 물론 번역 방송도 지원합니다. 설정 > 어시스턴트 > 대면식 번역으로 이동하면 사용해 볼 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="보안">
<feature>시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2024년 9월)가 통합되었습니다. HONOR 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 다음에 있는 당사 웹사이트를 방문하세요. https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터에는 영향을 미치지 않지만 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다.
2. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터로 가서 지원을 받으십시오.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ທີ່​ແນະ​ນຳນີ້​ນຳ​ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ໃໝ່​ມາ​ໃຫ້, ເຊິ່ງ​ລວມ​ມີ ຢາງລຶບ AI ແລະ ການ​ແປ​​ພາ​ສາແບບ​ເຊິ່ງ​ໜ້າ ແລະ ລວມເອົາໂປຣແກຣມແກ້ໄຂຄວາມປອດໄພ. ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ອັບ​ເດດ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ແກ​ເລີ​ຣີ">
<feature>​ຢາງລຶບ AI ໃໝ່​ສາ​ມາດ​ຊ່ວຍ​ທ່ານ​ເອົາຄົນ​ຍ່າງ​ຜ່ານ​ ແລະ ອົງ​ປະ​ກອບ​ທີ່​ບໍ່​ຕ້ອງ​ການ​ອື່ນໆອອກ​ຈາກ​ຮູບ​ພາບ​ໄດ້​ຢ່າງ​ອັດ​ສະ​ລິ​ຍະ​ດ້ວຍ​ການ​ແຕະ​ຄັ້ງ​ດຽວ. ​ລອງ​ໃຊ້​ມັນ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ແກ​ເລີ​ຣີ > ​ເ​ລືອກ​ຮູບ​ຖ່າຍ > ​ແກ້​ໄຂ > ​ຢາງລຶບ AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ການ​ແປ​​ພາ​ສາແບບ​ເຊິ່ງ​ໜ້າ">
<feature>ໃນ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ການ​ຜັດ​ປ່ຽນ​ກັນ​ເວົ້າ, ມັນ​ສາ​ມາດ​ປັບ​​ປຸງ​ການ​ແປ​ພາ​ສາຮ່ວມ​ກັນ​ລະ​ຫວ່າງ​ພາ​ສາ​ຈີນ, ພາ​ສາ​ອັງ​ກິດ, ​ພາ​ສາ​ຝ​ຣັ່ງ, ພາ​ສາ​ເຢຍ​ລະ​ມັນ, ພາ​ສາ​ສະ​ເປນ, ພາ​ສາ​ອີ​ຕາ​ລີ, ຣັດເຊຍ, ພາ​ສາ​ຕູ​ລະ​ກີ, ພາ​ສາ​ມາ​ເລ​ ແລະ ພາ​ສາ​ອາ​ຣັບ. ນອກນັ້ນ ມັນ​ຍັງ​ຮອງ​ຮັບ​ກາ​ນ​ປ້ອ​ນ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ດ້ວຍ​ສຽງ ແລະ ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ, ພ້ອມ​ທັງການ​ອອກ​ອາ​ກາດ​ການ​ແປ​ພາ​ສາ. ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ລອງ​ໃຊ້​ມັນ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ > ຜູ້ຊ່ວຍ > ການແປພາສາແບບເຊິ່ງໜ້າ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
<feature>ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ກັນ​ຍາ 2024) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ HONOR, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ກະລຸນາໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR ເພື່ອຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šiuo rekomenduojamu naujiniu įdiegiama naujų funkcijų, įskaitant DI trintuką ir nuosekliojo vertimo funkciją, taip pat įtraukiama saugumo pataisa. Rekomenduojama atnaujinti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Naujasis DI trintukas gali padėti vienu lietimu išmaniai pašalinti praeivius ir kitus nepageidaujamus elementus iš vaizdų. Išbandykite jį nuėję į Galeriją: ten pasirinkite nuotrauką ir tada „Redaguoti > DI trintukas“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nuoseklusis vertimas">
<feature>Kalbant po vieną, ji gali atlikti abipusį vertimą iš (į) kinų, anglų, prancūzų, vokiečių, ispanų, italų, rusų, turkų, malajų ir arabų kalbų (-as). Taip pat ji dera su balso ir teksto įvestimi bei vertimo transliavimo funkcija. Ją galite išbandyti nuėję į „Nuostatos > Pagelbiklis > Nuoseklusis vertimas“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Saugumas">
<feature>Siekiant užtikrinti sistemos saugumą, įtraukta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2024 m. rugsėjo mėn.). Jei reikia daugiau informacijos apie HONOR saugumo naujinius, apsilankykite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį naujinį, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys paveikti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama prieš naujinant padaryti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Jei naujinimo metu kyla problemų, skambinkite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba kreipkitės pagalbos į HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centrą.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo ieteicamo atjauninājumu tiek ieviestas jaunas funkcijas, tostarp AI dzēšgumija un Klātienes tulkošana, un iekļauts drošības ielāps. Ieteicams atjaunināt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Jaunā AI dzēšgumija var palīdzēt jums ar vienu pieskārienu viedi noņemt garāmgājējus un citus nevēlamus elementus no attēliem. Izmēģiniet to, atverot: Galerija > Atlasīt fotoattēlu > Rediģēt > AI dzēšgumija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Klātienes tulkošana">
<feature>Situācijā, kad runā pēc kārtas, tā var nodrošināt savstarpēju tulkojumu starp ķīniešu, angļu, franču, vācu, spāņu, itāliešu, krievu, turku, malajiešu un arābu valodu. Tā atbalsta arī balss un teksta ievadi, kā arī tulkošanas apraidi. Varat to izmēģināt, atverot: Iestatījumi > Palīgs > Klātienes tulkošana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Drošība">
<feature>Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2024. gada septembris). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par HONOR drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, lūdzu, zvaniet HONOR uzziņu dienestam vai dodieties uz HONOR klientu servisa centru, lai saņemtu atbalstu.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अनुशंसित अपडेट AI इरेजर आ आमने-सामने अनुवाद समेत नव विशेषता सभ अनैत अछि आओर सुरक्षा पैच समाविष्ट करैत अछि। अपडेट करबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गैलरी">
<feature>नव AI इरेजर अहाँ केँ एकहि टैप सँ इमेज सभ सँ राहगीर आ अन्य अवांछित तत्व सभ केँ बुद्धिमानी सँ हटाबए मे मदति कए सकैत अछि। एहि मे जा कए एकरा आजमाउ: गैलरी > फोटो चयन करू > संपादित करू > AI इरेजर।</feature>
</features>
<features module="आमने-सामने अनुवाद">
<feature>बेरा-बेरी सँ बजबाक स्थिति मे, ई चीनी, अंग्रेजी, फ्रेंच, जर्मन, स्पैनिश, इतालवी, रूसी, तुर्की, मलय आ अरबी केर बीच पारस्परिक अनुवाद प्रदान कए सकैत अछि। ई वॉयस आ टेक्स्ट इनपुट केर संगहि अनुवाद प्रसारण केर सेहो सपोर्ट करैत अछि। अहाँ एकरा सेटिंग्स > सहायक > आमने-सामने अनुवाद पर जा कए आजमा सकैत छी।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (सितंबर 2024) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अपन डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' सहायताक लेल कृपाकए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करू वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाउ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E te kaiwhakamahi, ka kawea mai e tēnei whakahōutanga tūtohutia ngā āhuahira hōu, tae atu ki te Ūkui AI me te Whakamāoritanga kanohi ki te kanohi, ā, ka komokomo i tētahi āpure haumarutanga. E tūtohutia ana kia whakahōu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Taiwhanga">
<feature>Ka taea e te Ūkui AI hōu te āwhina i a koe ki te tango mōhio i ngā kaihipa me tētahi atu huānga tē hiahiatia mai i ngā atahanga mā tētahi pato kotahi. Whakamātauria mā te haere ki: Taiwhanga > Tīpakohia tētahi whakaahua > Whakatika > Ūkui AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Whakamāoritanga kanohi ki te kanohi">
<feature>I roto i tētahi āhuatanga huri noa, ka taea e ia te whakarato i te whakamāoritanga tahi i waenganui i te Hainamana, Ingarihi, Wīwī, Tiamana, Pāniora, Ītariana, Rūhiana, Reo Tākei, Mareia, me te Arapi. E tautoko ana hoki i te tāuru reo me te kuputuhi, tae atu ki te pāohotanga whakawhitinga. Ka taea e koe te whakamātau mā te haere: Ngā tautuhinga > Kaiāwhina > Whakamāoritanga kanohi ki te kanohi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Haumarutanga">
<feature>Kua whakaurua te Āpure Haumarutanga Android (Mahuru 2024) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga HONOR, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore e pā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōu ki ō ngā raraunga whaiaro, engari me tārua tonu ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōu.
2. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōu, waea atu koa ki te raina waewera ratonga HONOR, haere rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki HONOR hei tautoko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова препорачано ажурирање носи нови карактеристики, вклучително и Гума за бришење со вештачка интелигенција и Преведување лице в лице и вградува безбедносна крпеница. Се препорачува да ажурирате.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерија">
<feature>Новата Гума за бришење со вештачка интелигенција може да ви помогне интелигентно да ги отстраните случајните минувачи и другите непосакувани елементи од сликите со еден допир. Пробајте ја преку одење во: Галерија > Изберете фотографија > Уреди > Гума за бришење со вештачка интелигенција.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Преведување лице в лице">
<feature>Во ситуација на разговор кога едното лице зборува, а другото лице слуша, и обратно, може да обезбеди взаемно преведување помеѓу кинески, англиски, француски, германски, шпански, италијански, руски, турски, малезиски и арапски. Исто така поддржува и говорно и текстуално внесување, како и емитување на преводот. Може да ја пробате преку одење во: Нагодување > Помошник > Преведување лице в лице.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безбедност">
<feature>Вградена е безбедносна крпеница за Android (септември 2024) за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за ажурирања на безбедноста од HONOR, посетете ја нашата веб-локација https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате.
2. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, јавете се на телефонскиот број на службата на HONOR или посетете сервисен центар за корисници на HONOR за да добиете поддршка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്ന അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് AI ഇറേസർ, മുഖാമുഖ വിവർത്തനം എന്നിവ ഉൾപ്പെടെയുള്ള പുതിയ സവിശേഷതകൾ അവതരിപ്പിക്കുകയും ഒരു സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ഗാലറി">
<feature>ഇമേജുകളിൽ നിന്ന് വഴിപ്പോക്കരെയും മറ്റ് അനാവശ്യ ഘടകങ്ങളെയും ഒരൊറ്റ ടാപ്പിൽ സമർത്ഥമായി നീക്കംചെയ്യാൻ പുതിയ AI ഇറേസറിന് നിങ്ങളെ സഹായിക്കാൻ കഴിയും. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കുക: ഗാലറി > ഒരു ഫോട്ടോ തിരഞ്ഞെടുക്കുക > എഡിറ്റ് ചെയ്യുക > AI ഇറേസർ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="മുഖാമുഖ വിവർത്തനം">
<feature>മറ്റുള്ളവരോട് സംസാരിക്കേണ്ടി വരുന്ന സാഹചര്യത്തിൽ, ഇതിന് ചൈനീസ്, ഇംഗ്ലീഷ്, ഫ്രഞ്ച്, ജർമ്മൻ, സ്‌പാനിഷ്, ഇറ്റാലിയൻ, റഷ്യൻ, ടർക്കിഷ്, മലായ്, അറബിക്ക് എന്നീ ഭാഷകളുടെ പരസ്‌പര വിവർത്തനം നൽകാൻ കഴിയും. കൂടാതെ, ഇത് ശബ്‌ദ, ടെക്‌സ്‌റ്റ് ഇൻപുട്ടിനെയും വിവർത്തനം ബ്രോഡ്‌കാസ്റ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിനെയും പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കുന്നു. നിങ്ങൾക്ക് ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് പരീക്ഷിച്ച് നോക്കാവുന്നതാണ്: ക്രമീകരണം > അസിസ്റ്റന്റ് > മുഖാമുഖ വിവർത്തനം.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സുരക്ഷ">
<feature>സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (സെപ്‌റ്റംബർ 2024) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. HONOR സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ ഔദ്യോഗിക വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് ആയ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9 സന്ദർശിക്കുക</feature>
</features>
<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കായി HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү санал болгож буй шинэчлэлтээр AI баллуур, Нүүр тулсан орчуулга зэрэг шинэ онцлогуудыг танилцуулж, хамгаалалтын нөхөөс багтаав. Шинэчлэхийг зөвлөж байна.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерей">
<feature>Шинэ AI Баллуур нь зургаас нэг товшилтоор өнгөрч буй хүмүүс болон бусад хүсээгүй элементийг ухаалгаар арилгахад тусална. Үүнийг Галерей > Зураг сонгох > Засах > AI Баллуур луу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Нүүр тулсан орчуулга">
<feature>Ээлжилсэн харилцан ярианд энэ нь хятад, англи, франц, герман, испани, итали, орос, турк, малай, араб хэлний хооронд харилцан орчуулга хийх боломжтой. Энэ нь дуу хоолой, бичвэрийн оролт, орчуулгын нэвтрүүлгийг дэмждэг. Та үүнийг Тохиргоо > Туслах > Нүүр тулсан орчуулга хэсэг рүү очиж туршиж үзэх боломжтой.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хамгаалалт">
<feature>Системийн хамгаалалтад зориулж Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2024 оны есдүгээр сар) багтаав. HONOR-н хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэл авах бол манай дараах вебсайтад зочилно уу: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгах нь таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч, шинэчлэхийн өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцөлсөн нь дээр.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад ямар нэг асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төв рүү очиж дэмжлэг авна уу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे शिफारस केलेले अद्यतन AI इरेजर आणि समोरासमोर भाषांतरासह नवीन वैशिष्ट्ये आणते आणि सुरक्षितता पॅच समाविष्ट करते. अद्यतनित करण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="गॅलरी">
<feature>नवीन AI इरेजर आपल्याला एका टॅपने इमेजमधून जाणारे आणि अन्य अवांछित घटक हुशारीने काढून टाकण्यास मदत करू शकते. येथे जाऊन वापरून पहा: गॅलरी > एक फोटो निवडा > संपादित करा > AI इरेजर.</feature>
</features>
<features module="समोरासमोर भाषांतर">
<feature>बदलत्या परिस्थितीत, ते चीनी, इंग्रजी, फ्रेंच, जर्मन, स्पॅनिश, इटालियन, रशियन, तुर्की, मलय आणि अरबीमध्ये परस्पर भाषांतर प्रदान करू शकते. हे व्हॉइस आणि मजकूर इनपुट तसेच भाषांतर प्रसारणास देखील समर्थन देते. आपण येथे जाऊन ते वापरून पाहू शकता: सेटिंग्ज > सहाय्यक > समोरासमोर भाषांतर.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षितता">
<feature>सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षितता पॅच (सप्टेंबर 2024) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. HONOR सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9 वर जा</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करा किंवा समर्थनासाठी HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जा.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini yang disyorkan ini memperkenalkan ciri baharu, termasuk Pemadam AI dan Penterjemahan bersemuka serta memasukkan tampalan keselamatan. Anda disyorkan agar mengemas kini.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Pemadam AI baharu boleh membantu anda mengeluarkan orang yang lalu-lalang dan elemen lain yang tidak diingini daripada imej dengan satu ketikan. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Galeri > Pilih foto > Edit > Pemadam AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Penterjemahan bersemuka">
<feature>Secara bergiliran, ia boleh menyediakan penterjemahan menyaling antara Bahasa Cina, Inggeris, Perancis, Jerman, Sepanyol, Itali, Rusia, Turki, Melayu dengan Arab. Ia juga menyokong input suara dan teks serta siaran penterjemahan. Anda boleh mencuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Pembantu > Penterjemahan bersemuka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keselamatan">
<feature>Tampalan Keselamatan Android (Sep 2024) telah dimasukkan untuk keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan HONOR, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tindakan memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan untuk membuat sandaran data sebelum mengemas kini.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, sila hubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau pergi ke pusat khidmat pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan sokongan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ အကြံပြုထားသော ဤအပ်ဒိတ်တွင် AI Eraser နှင့် မျက်နှာချင်းဆိုင် ဘာသာပြန်အပါအဝင် လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်အသစ်များ ပါဝင်ပြီး လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပုံပြခန်း">
<feature>AI Eraser အသစ်သည် တစ်ချက်နှိပ်ရုံဖြင့် ရုပ်ပုံများမှ ဖြတ်သန်းသွားလာသူများနှင့် အခြား မလိုလားသော အရာများကို ပါးပါးနပ်နပ် ဖယ်ရှားနိုင်စေသည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ ၎င်းကို စမ်းကြည့်ပါ- ပုံပြခန်း > ဓာတ်ပုံရွေးချယ်မည် > တည်းဖြတ်မည် > AI Eraser။</feature>
</features>
<features module="မျက်နှာချင်းဆိုင် ဘာသာပြန်">
<feature>အပြန်အလှန် စကားပြောကြသည့်အခါ ၎င်းသည် တရုတ်၊ အင်္ဂလိပ်၊ ပြင်သစ်၊ ဂျာမန်၊ စပိန်၊ အီတလီ၊ ရုရှား၊ တူရကီ၊ မလေးနှင့် အာရဗီတို့အကြား အပြန်အလှန် ဘာသာပြန်ခြင်းကို ပံ့ပိုးပေးနိုင်သည်။ ၎င်းသည် အသံဖြင့် စာရိုက်သွင်းမှုအပြင် ဘာသာပြန် ထုတ်လွှင့်မှုကိုလည်း ပံ့ပိုးပေးသည်။ သင်သည် ဖော်ပြပါသို့သွား၍ ၎င်းကိုစမ်းကြည့်နိုင်သည်- ဆက်တင် > အကူ > မျက်နှာချင်းဆိုင် ဘာသာပြန်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံခြုံရေး">
<feature>စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (စက်တင်ဘာ 2024) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ HONOR လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို သိရှိရန် ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ်သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းသည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာအပေါ် ထိခိုက်မည် မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်အတောအတွင်း ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခု ကြုံတွေ့ပါက အကူအညီအတွက် HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆိုပါ သို့မဟုတ် HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ အႀကံျပဳထားေသာ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္တြင္ AI Eraser ႏွင့္ မ်က္ႏွာခ်င္းဆိုင္ ဘာသာျပန္အပါအဝင္ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္အသစ္မ်ား ပါဝင္ၿပီး လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပုံျပခန္း">
<feature>AI Eraser အသစ္သည္ တစ္ခ်က္ႏွိပ္႐ုံျဖင့္ ႐ုပ္ပုံမ်ားမွ ျဖတ္သန္းသြားလာသူမ်ားႏွင့္ အျခား မလိုလားေသာ အရာမ်ားကို ပါးပါးနပ္နပ္ ဖယ္ရွားႏိုင္ေစသည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ ၎ကို စမ္းၾကည့္ပါ- ပုံျပခန္း > ဓာတ္ပုံေ႐ြးခ်ယ္မည္ > ျပင္ဆင္မည္ > AI Eraser။</feature>
</features>
<features module="မ်က္ႏွာခ်င္းဆိုင္ ဘာသာျပန္">
<feature>အျပန္အလွန္ စကားေျပာၾကသည့္အခါ ၎သည္ တရုတ္၊ အဂၤလိပ္၊ ျပင္သစ္၊ ဂ်ာမန္၊ စပိန္၊ အီတလီ၊ ႐ုရွား၊ တူရကီ၊ မေလးႏွင့္ အာရဗီတို႔အၾကား အျပန္အလွန္ ဘာသာျပန္ျခင္းကို ပံ့ပိုးေပးႏိုင္သည္။ ၎သည္ အသံျဖင့္ စာ႐ိုက္သြင္းမႈအျပင္ ဘာသာျပန္ ထုတ္လႊင့္မႈကိုလည္း ပံ့ပိုးေပးသည္။ သင္သည္ ေဖာ္ျပပါသို႔သြား၍ ၎ကိုစမ္းၾကည့္ႏိုင္သည္- ဆက္တင္ > အကူ > မ်က္ႏွာခ်င္းဆိုင္ ဘာသာျပန္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံျခံဳေရး">
<feature>စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (စက္တင္ဘာ 2024) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ HONOR လုံၿခဳံေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို သိရွိရန္ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းသည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာအေပၚ ထိခိုက္မည္ မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္အေတာအတြင္း ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခု ႀကဳံေတြ႕ပါက အကူအညီအတြက္ HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆိုပါ သို႔မဟုတ္ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, denne anbefalte oppdateringen bringer nye funksjoner, inkludert AI-viskelær og Ansikt-til-ansikt-oversettelse, samt integrerer en sikkerhetsoppdatering. Det anbefales å oppdatere.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleri">
<feature>Den nye KI-viskelær kan hjelpe deg med å fjerne forbipasserende og andre elementer fra bilder på intelligent vis med ett trykk. Prøv den ut ved å gå til: Galleri > Velg et bilde > Rediger > KI-viskelær.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ansikt-til-ansikt-oversettelse">
<feature>I en turtakingssituasjon kan den gi gjensidig oversettelse mellom kinesisk, engelsk, fransk, tysk, spansk, italiensk, russisk, tyrkisk, malaysisk og arabisk. Den støtter også tale- og tekstinndata, samt oversettelsessendinger. Du kan prøve det ved å gå til: Innstillinger > Assistent > Ansikt-til-ansikt-oversettelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhet">
<feature>Android-sikkerhetsoppdatering (sept. 2024) er innlemmet for systemsikkerhet. For mer informasjon om sikkerhetsoppdateringer fra HONOR, se nettstedet vårt: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke påvirke personopplysningene dine, men vi anbefaler likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer dataene dine før du oppdaterer.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, ring HONOR-kundeservice eller gå til HONOR-kundeservicesenteret for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, सिफारिस गरिएको यो अपडेटले AI इरेजर र फेस टु फेस अनुवाद गर्ने सुविधालगायतका नयाँ सुविधाहरू ल्याएको छ र यसमा सुरक्षा प्याच समावेश गरिएको छ । अपडेट गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ग्यालरी">
<feature>तपाईं नयाँ AI इरेजरका सहायताले फोटोमा भएका अनावश्यक व्यक्ति र अन्य अनावश्यक वस्तुहरू स्मार्ट तरिकाले हटाउन सक्नुहुन्छ । यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्नुहोस्: ग्यालरी > फोटो चयन गर्नुहोस् > सम्पादन गर्नुहोस् > AI इरेजर ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="फेस टु फेस अनुवाद">
<feature>यसले तपाईंलाई आवश्यक परेको अवस्थामा चिनियाँ, अङ्ग्रेजी, फ्रेन्च, जर्मन, स्पेनिस, इटालियन, रसियन, टर्किस, मलाय र अरबी भाषाका बिचमा अनुवाद गर्ने सुविधा प्रदान गर्न सक्छ । यसमा भ्वाइस र टेक्स्ट इन्पुट पनि दिन मिल्छ र अनुवाद पढेर सुनाउने सुविधा उपलब्ध छ । तपाईं यहाँ गएर यसलाई प्रयोग गरी हेर्न सक्नुहुन्छ: सेटिङहरू > सहायक > फेस टु फेस अनुवाद ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (सेप्टेम्बर 2024) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेटबारे थप जानकारीका लागि, कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस् https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. अपडेटको समयमा तपाईंले कुनै पनि समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने, कृपया HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गर्नुहोस् वा सहायताका लागि HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा जानुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruiker, deze aanbevolen update brengt nieuwe functies met zich mee, inclusief AI-gum en Face-to-face vertaling, en bevat een beveiligingspatch. Het wordt aanbevolen om bij te werken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Foto's">
<feature>De nieuwe AI-gum kan u helpen om met één tik op een intelligente manier de voorbijgangers en andere ongewenste elementen uit afbeeldingen te verwijderen. Probeer het uit via: Foto's > Selecteer een foto > Bewerken > AI-gum.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Face-to-face vertaling">
<feature>In een om-de-beurt-situatie kan het wederzijdse vertaling bieden tussen Chinees, Engels, Frans, Duits, Spaans, Italiaans, Russisch, Turks, Maleis en Arabisch. Het ondersteunt ook spraak- en tekstinvoer, evenals uitzending van vertalingen. U kunt het uitproberen via: Instellingen > Assistent > Face-to-face vertaling.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Beveiliging">
<feature>Android-beveiligingspatch (september 2024) is opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over HONOR-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Als u deze update installeert, worden uw persoonlijke gegevens niet beïnvloed, maar een back-up van uw gegevens maken voordat u bijwerkt wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, bel dan de HONOR-servicehotline of ga naar een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum voor ondersteuning.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଥିବା ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ରେ AI ଇରେଜର୍ ଏବଂ ଫେସ୍‌-ଟୁ-ଫେସ୍ ଅନୁବାଦ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରି ନୂତନ ବିଶେଷତାଗୁଡ଼ିକ ରହିଛି, ତଥା ଏକ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଗ୍ୟାଲେରୀ">
<feature>ନୂତନ AI ଇରେଜର୍ ଗୋଟିଏ ଟ୍ୟାପ୍‌ରେ ପଥଚାରୀ ଏବଂ ଅନ୍ୟାନ୍ୟ ଅବାଞ୍ଛିତ ଉପାଦାନଗୁଡ଼ିକୁ ପ୍ରତିଛବିରୁ ଚତୁରତାର ସହ ଅପସାରଣ କରିପାରେ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଆପଣ ଏହାକୁ ପରଖି ନିଅନ୍ତୁ: ଗ୍ୟାଲେରୀ > ଏକ ଫଟୋ ଚୟନ କରନ୍ତୁ > ସମ୍ପାଦନ କରନ୍ତୁ > AI ଇରେଜର୍।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଫେସ୍‌ ଟୁ ଫେସ୍ ଅନୁବାଦ">
<feature>ଚର୍ଚ୍ଚ କରିବା ପରିସ୍ଥିତିରେ, ଏହା ଚାଇନିଜ୍, ଇଂରାଜୀ, ଫ୍ରେଞ୍ଚ, ଜର୍ମାନ, ସ୍ପାନୀୟ, ଇଟାଲୀୟ, ଋଷିୟ, ତୁର୍କିସ, ମଳୟ ଏବଂ ଆରବୀୟ ଭାଷାଗୁଡ଼ିକ ମଧ୍ୟରେ ମ୍ୟୁଚ୍ୟୁଆଲ ଅନୁବାଦ ପ୍ରଦାନ କରିପାରିବ। ଏହା ଭଏସ୍ ଏବଂ ଟେକ୍ସଟ୍ ଇନପୁଟ୍, ତଥା ଅନୁବାଦ ବ୍ରୋଡକାଷ୍ଟ ମଧ୍ୟ ସମର୍ଥନ କରେ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଆପଣ ଏହାକୁ ପରଖି ପାରିବେ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ସହାୟକ > ଫେସ୍‌ ଟୁ ଫେସ୍ ଅନୁବାଦ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା">
<feature>Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ସେପ୍ଟେମ୍ବର 2024) ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। HONOR ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଦୟାକରି HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ସହାୟତା ପାଇଁ ଏକ HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੇ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਨਵੀਆਂ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ ਪੇਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀਆਂ ਗਈਆਂ ਹਨ, ਜਿਸ ਵਿੱਚ AI ਇਰੇਜ਼ਰ ਅਤੇ ਆਹਮੋ-ਸਾਹਮਣੇ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਹਨ, ਅਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਹੈ। ਇਹ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਗੈਲਰੀ">
<feature>ਨਵਾਂ AI ਇਰੇਜ਼ਰ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਇੱਕ ਟੈਪ ਨਾਲ ਤਸਵੀਰਾਂ ਤੋਂ ਰਾਹਗੀਰਾਂ ਅਤੇ ਹੋਰ ਅਣਚਾਹੇ ਐਲੀਮੈਂਟਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਸਮਝਦਾਰੀ ਨਾਲ ਹਟਾਉਣ ਵਿੱਚ ਮਦਦ ਕਰ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਅਜ਼ਮਾਓ: ਗੈਲਰੀ > ਇੱਕ ਫ਼ੋਟੋ ਚੁਣੋ > AI ਇਰੇਜ਼ਰ > ਸੋਧੋ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਆਹਮੋ-ਸਾਹਮਣੇ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ">
<feature>ਇੱਕ ਮੋੜ ਲੈਣ ਵਾਲੀ ਸਥਿਤੀ ਵਿੱਚ, ਇਹ ਚੀਨੀ, ਅੰਗ੍ਰੇਜ਼ੀ, ਫਰਾਂਸੀਸੀ, ਜਰਮਨ, ਸਪੈਨਿਸ਼, ਇਤਾਲਵੀ, ਰੂਸੀ, ਤੁਰਕੀ, ਮਲਯ, ਅਤੇ ਅਰਬੀ ਵਿਚਕਾਰ ਆਪਸੀ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ ਪ੍ਰਦਾਨ ਕਰ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ. ਇਹ ਆਵਾਜ਼ ਅਤੇ ਟੈਕਸਟ ਇਨਪੁੱਟ ਦੇ ਨਾਲ-ਨਾਲ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ ਬ੍ਰੌਡਕਾਸਟ ਦਾ ਵੀ ਸਮਰਥਨ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ। ਤੁਸੀਂ ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਸਹਾਇਕ > ਆਹਮੋ-ਸਾਹਮਣੇ ਅਨੁਵਾਦ 'ਤੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਅਜ਼ਮਾ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ">
<feature>ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਸਤੰਬਰ 2024) ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। HONOR ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਲਈ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵਿਤ ਨਹੀਂ ਹੋਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਸਹਾਇਤਾ ਲਈ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>W tej zalecanej aktualizacji wprowadzono nowe funkcje, takie jak Gumka AI oraz Tłumaczenia bezpośrednie. Zawiera też poprawkę zabezpieczeń. Zaleca się zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>Nowa funkcja Gumka AI może pomóc w inteligentnym usuwaniu przechodniów i niechcianych elementów ze zdjęć jednym dotknięciem. Wypróbuj ją, przechodząc do: Galeria > Wybierz zdjęcie > Edytuj > Gumka AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tłumaczenie twarzą w twarz">
<feature>Kiedy rozmówcy mówią po kolei, może zapewnić wzajemne tłumaczenie między językami chińskim, angielskim, francuskim, niemieckim, hiszpańskim, włoskim, rosyjskim, tureckim, malajskim i arabskim. Obsługuje również wprowadzanie głosu i tekstu, a także transmisje tłumaczeń. Funkcję tę możesz wypróbować, przechodząc do: Ustawienia > Asystent > Tłumaczenie twarzą w twarz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpieczenia">
<feature>Aktualizacja zawiera Poprawkę zabezpieczeń systemu Android (wrzesień 2024 r.). Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń urządzeń HONOR można znaleźć w naszej witrynie internetowej: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie wpływa na dane użytkownika, jednak zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej przed aktualizacją.
2. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, zadzwoń na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR, gdzie uzyskasz pomoc.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Prezado usuário, esta atualização recomendada traz novos recursos, incluindo o Apagador de IA e a Tradução face a face, além de incorporar um patch de segurança. É recomendado atualizar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>O novo Apagador de IA pode ajudar você a remover os transeuntes e outros elementos indesejados das imagens de forma inteligente com um único toque. Experimente acessando: Galeria > Selecionar uma foto > Editar > Apagador de IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tradução face a face">
<feature>Em uma situação de revezamento, ele pode fornecer tradução mútua entre chinês, inglês, francês, alemão, espanhol, italiano, russo, turco, malaio e árabe. Ele também suporta entrada de voz e texto, bem como transmissão de tradução. Você pode experimentar acessando: Configurações > Assistente > Tradução face a face.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Patch de segurança do Android (setembro de 2024) incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite nosso site: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, ligue para a linha de atendimento de serviço da HONOR ou vá à Central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização recomendada traz novas funcionalidades, incluindo o Apagador por IA e a Tradução frente a frente e incorpora uma correção de segurança. A atualização é recomendada.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>O novo Apagador por IA pode ajudar a remover, de forma inteligente, os transeuntes e outros elementos indesejados das imagens com um único toque. Experimente acedendo a: Galeria > Selecionar uma fotografia > Editar > Apagador por IA.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tradução frente a frente">
<feature>Numa situação inesperada, pode fornecer a tradução mútua entre chinês, inglês, francês, alemão, espanhol, italiano, russo, turco, malaio e árabe. Também suporta a entrada de voz e texto, bem como a transmissão da tradução. Pode experimentar acedendo a: Definições > Assistente > Tradução frente a frente.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Foi incorporada uma correção de segurança Android (setembro de 2024) para a segurança do sistema. Para mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não irá afetar os seus dados pessoais, mas continua a recomendar-se a realização prévia de uma cópia de segurança.
2. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, ligue para a linha direta de assistência da HONOR ou dirija-se ao centro de apoio ao cliente HONOR para suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare recomandată aduce funcții noi, inclusiv Radieră AI și Traducere la întâlnirile față în față, și încorporează o corecție de securitate. Se recomandă actualizarea.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Noua Radieră AI vă poate ajuta să eliminați în mod inteligent trecătorii și alte elemente nedorite din imagini cu o singură atingere. Încercați-o accesând la: Galerie > Selectați o fotografie > Editare > Radieră AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Traducere față în față">
<feature>Într-o situație în care se discută pe rând, poate oferi traducere reciprocă între chineză, engleză, franceză, germană, spaniolă, italiană, rusă, turcă, malaeză și arabă. De asemenea, acceptă introducerea de voce și text, precum și difuzarea traducerii. O puteți încerca accesând: Setări > Asistent > Traducere față în față.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Securitate">
<feature>Corecția de securitate Android (septembrie 2024) a fost inclusă pentru securitatea sistemului. Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de securitate HONOR, vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea actualizării nu va cauza ștergerea datelor dvs. personale, dar vă recomandăm totuși să realizați în prealabil o copie de rezervă.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, apelați linia de asistență HONOR sau vizitați un centru de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь, это рекомендованное обновление добавляет несколько новых функций, включая «AI-ластик» и «Непосредственный перевод», а также внедряет исправление безопасности. Мы рекомендуем выполнить обновление.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерея">
<feature>Новая функция «Удаление с помощью ИИ» поможет вам одним нажатием автоматически удалить прохожих и нежелательные элементы с изображений. Чтобы попробовать, перейдите в раздел «Галерея > Выбор фото > Изменить > Удаление с помощью ИИ».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Перевод диалога">
<feature>Эта функция может обеспечить последовательный перевод между китайским, английским, французским, немецким, испанским, итальянским, русским, турецким, малайским и арабским языками. Кроме того, она поддерживает голосовой и текстовый ввод, а также перевод трансляций. Чтобы попробовать, перейдите в раздел «Настройки > Ассистент > Перевод диалога».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безопасность">
<feature>В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (сентябрь 2024 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности HONOR, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/ru/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не затронет ваши персональные данные, но мы рекомендует сделать резервную копию данных перед обновлением.
2. При возникновении каких-либо проблем при обновлении обратитесь на горячую линию обслуживания HONOR или в службу поддержки клиента HONOR за помощью.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම නිර්දේශිත යාවත්කාලය AI මකනය සහ මුහුණට මුහුණලා පරිවර්තනය ඇතුළු නව විශේෂාංග ලබා දෙන අතර ආරක්ෂක පිළියමක් ඇතුළත් කරයි. යාවත්කාල කරන්නට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ගැලරිය">
<feature>නව AI මකනයට එහා මෙහා යන අය සහ අනෙකුත් අනවශ්‍ය දේවල් එක තට්ටු කිරීමකින් රූපවලින් බුද්ධිමත්ව ඉවත් කිරීමට ඔබට උපකාර කළ හැකි ය. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කරන්න: ගැලරිය > ඡායාරූපයක් තෝරා ගන්න > සංස්කරණය කරන්න > AI මකනය.</feature>
</features>
<features module="මුහුණට මුහුණලා පරිවර්තනය">
<feature>වාරය ගැනීමේ තත්වයක් තුළ දී, එයට චීන, ඉංග්‍රීසි, ප්‍රංශ, ජර්මානු, ස්පාඤ්ඤ, ඉතාලි, රුසියානු, තුර්කි, මැලේ සහ අරාබි අතර අන්‍යෝන්‍ය පරිවර්තනයක් සැපයීමට හැකිය. එය කටහඬ සහ පෙළ ආදානයට මෙන්ම පරිවර්තන විකාශනය කරන්නට ද සහය දක්වයි. ඔබට මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය උත්සාහ කළ හැකිය: සැකසුම් > සහායක > මුහුණට මුහුණලා පරිවර්තනය.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ආරක්ෂාව">
<feature>පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2024 සැප්) යොදාගෙන ඇත. HONOR ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9 වෙත යන්න</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේ දී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, කරුණාකර HONOR සේවා හොට්ලයින් අමතන්න නැතහොත් සහය සඳහා HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට යන්න.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený používateľ, táto odporúčaná aktualizácia prináša nové funkcie vrátane AI gumy a Osobného prekladu a obsahuje bezpečnostnú opravu. Aktualizácia sa odporúča.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galéria">
<feature>Nová funkcia AI guma vám pomôže jedným ťuknutím inteligentne odstrániť okoloidúcich a iné nežiaduce prvky z obrázkov. Vyskúšajte to v ponuke Galéria > Vybrať fotografiu > Upraviť > AI guma.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Osobný preklad">
<feature>Pri konverzácii dokáže zabezpečiť vzájomný preklad medzi čínštinou, angličtinou, francúzštinou, nemčinou, španielčinou, taliančinou, ruštinou, turečtinou, malajčinou a arabčinou. Podporuje aj hlasový a textový vstup, ako aj vysielanie prekladu. Môžete to vyskúšať v ponuke Nastavenia > Asistent > Osobný preklad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpečenie">
<feature>Súčasťou zabezpečenia systému je bezpečnostná oprava systému Android (zo septembra 2024). Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti HONOR, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať.
2. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytnú problémy, podporu môžete získať zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo návštevou Centra služieb zákazníkom HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta priporočena posodobitev prinaša nove funkcije, vključno s funkcijama Brisanje z UI in Prevajanje v živo, vključen pa je tudi varnostni popravek. Priporočamo posodobitev.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>S funkcijo Brisanje z UI lahko z enim samim dotikom pametno odstranite mimoidoče in druge neželene elemente s slik. Preizkusite jo tako, da odprete razdelek Galerija > Izberi fotografijo > Uredi > Brisanje z UI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prevajanje v živo">
<feature>V primeru dialoga lahko zagotovi vzajemno prevajanje med kitajščino, angleščino, francoščino, nemščino, španščino, italijanščino, ruščino, turščino, malajščino in arabščino. Podpira tudi glasovni in besedilni vnos ter oddajanje prevodov. Funkcijo lahko preizkusite v razdelku Nastavitve > Pomočnik > Prevajanje v živo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varnost">
<feature>Varnostni popravki za Android (september 2024) so vključeni za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah HONOR obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne bo vplivala na vaše osebne podatke, vendar vseeno priporočamo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodobitvijo naletite na težave, za podporo pokličite odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom izdelkov HONOR ali obiščite središče za storitve družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, den här rekommenderade uppdateringen innehåller nya funktioner, som AI-radergummi och Översättning ansikte mot ansikte, och implementerar en säkerhetskorrigering. Du rekommenderas att uppdatera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleri">
<feature>Nya AI-radergummi kan hjälpa dig att på ett smart sätt ta bort förbipasserande och andra oönskade element från bilder med ett enda tryck. Prova genom att gå till: Galleri > Välj ett foto > Redigera > AI-radergummi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Översättning ansikte mot ansikte">
<feature>I situationer med turtagning kan den tillhandahålla översättning för flera mellan kinesiska, engelska, franska, tyska, spanska, italienska, ryska, turkiska, malajiska och arabiska. Den stöder också röst- och textinmatning samt översättningssändning. Du kan prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Assistent > Översättning ansikte mot ansikte.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Säkerhet">
<feature>Android-säkerhetskorrigeringen (september 2024) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för HONOR går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar.
2. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs servicecenter och få support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili linalopendekezwa linaleta vipengele vipya, vikijumuisha Kifutio cha AI na tafsiri ya Ana kwa ana na linajumuisha rekebisho la usalama. Inapendekezwa usasishe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Matunzio">
<feature>Kifutio kipya cha AI kinaweza kukusaidia kuondoa kwa umaizi wapita njia na vipengele vingine visivyotakikana kutoka kwenye picha kwa kugusa tu. Kijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Matunzio > Chagua picha > Hariri > Kifutio cha AI.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tafsiri ya ana kwa ana">
<feature>Katika hali ya kuchukua zamu, kinaweza kukupa tafsiri ya kusaidiana kati ya Kichina, Kiingereza, Kifaransa, Kijerumani, Kihispania, Kiitaliano, Kirusi, Kituruki, Kimalei na Kiarabu. Pia kinaruhusu ingizo la usemi na maandishi, pamoja na utangazaji wa tafsiri. Unaweza kukijaribu kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Kisaidizi > Tafsiri ya ana kwa ana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Usalama">
<feature>Rekebisho la Usalama wa Android (Sep 2024) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa HONOR, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado unapendekezwa kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, tafadhali piga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au nenda kwenye kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha HONOR ili upate usaidizi.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படும் புதுப்பிப்பு AI அழிப்பான் மற்றும் நேருக்கு நேர் மொழிபெயர்ப்பு உள்ளிட்ட புதிய அம்சங்களைக் கொண்டு வருகிறது மற்றும் பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பைக் கொண்டுள்ளது. இதைப் புதுப்பிக்குமாறு பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="கேலரி">
<feature>புதிய AI அழிப்பான் ஒரே தட்டலில் வழிப்போக்கர்கள் மற்றும் பிற தேவையற்ற கூறுகளைப் படங்களிலிருந்து அறிவார்ந்த முறையில் அகற்ற உதவும். இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கவும்: கேலரி > புகைப்படத்தைத் தேர்ந்தெடு > திருத்து > AI அழிப்பான்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="நேருக்கு நேர் மொழிபெயர்ப்பு">
<feature>ஊடாடும் சூழ்நிலையில், சீனம், ஆங்கிலம், பிரெஞ்சு, ஜெர்மன், ஸ்பானிஷ், இத்தாலியன், ரஷ்யன், துருக்கி, மலாய் மற்றும் அரபு மொழிகளுக்கு இடையில் பரஸ்பர மொழிபெயர்ப்பை வழங்குகிறது. இது குரல் மற்றும் உரை உள்ளீட்டுடன், மொழிபெயர்ப்பை ஒளிபரப்பையும் ஆதரிக்கிறது. இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதை முயன்று பார்க்கலாம்: அமைப்புகள் > உதவியாளர் > நேருக்கு நேர் மொழிபெயர்ப்பு.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பாதுகாப்பு">
<feature>சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (செப் 2024) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. HONOR பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், உதவிக்காக HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைக்கவும் அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்லவும்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ సిఫార్సు చేయబడిన అప్‌డేట్ AI ఎరేజర్ మరియు ముఖాముఖి అనువాదంతో సహా కొత్త ఫీచర్‌లను అందిస్తుంది మరియు భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ చేర్చబడింది. అప్‌డేట్ చేయాలని సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="గ్యాలరీ">
<feature>కొత్త AI ఎరేజర్ ఒక ట్యాప్‌తో చిత్రాల నుండి పరిసరాల్లో వ్యక్తులు మరియు ఇతర అవాంఛిత అంశాలను తెలివిగా తీసివేయడానికి మీకు సహాయపడుతుంది. ఇక్కడికి వెళ్లి దీనిని ప్రయత్నించండి: గ్యాలరీ > ఫోటోను ఎంచుకోండి > సవరించు > AI ఎరేజర్.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ముఖాముఖి అనువాదం">
<feature>మలుపు తీసుకునే పరిస్థితిలో, ఇది చైనీస్, ఇంగ్లీష్, ఫ్రెంచ్, జర్మన్, స్పానిష్, ఇటాలియన్, రష్యన్, టర్కీష్, మలయ్ మరియు అరబిక్ భాషల మధ్య ఉమ్మడి అనువాదాన్ని అందిస్తుంది. ఇది వాయిస్ మరియు టెక్స్ట్ ఇన్‌పుట్ అలాగే అనువాదం ప్రసారానికి మద్దతు ఇస్తుంది. మీరు ఇక్కడికి వెళ్లి దీనిని ప్రయత్నించవచ్చు: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > సహాయకం > ముఖాముఖి అనువాదం.</feature>
</features>
<features module="భద్రత">
<feature>సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం Android భద్రత ప్యాచ్ (సెప్టెంబర్ 2024) పొందుపరచబడింది. HONOR భద్రత నవీకరణల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్ సందర్శించండి https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వల్ల మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటాపై ప్రభావం ఉండదు, అయితే అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇప్పటికీ సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీకు ఏవైనా సమస్యలు ఎదురైతే, దయచేసి HONOR సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయండి లేదా మద్దతు కోసం HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి వెళ్ళండి.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตที่แนะนำนี้มอบฟีเจอร์ใหม่ ๆ ซึ่งรวมถึงยางลบ AI และการแปลแบบตัวต่อตัว และรวมแพตช์ความปลอดภัย เราจึงแนะนำให้คุณอัปเดต</feature>
</features>
<features module="แกลเลอรี">
<feature>ยางลบ AI ใหม่ช่วยให้คุณลบผู้ที่ผ่านไปมาและส่วนประกอบที่ไม่ต้องการอื่น ๆ ออกจากรูปภาพได้อย่างง่ายดายด้วยการแตะครั้งเดียว ลองใช้โดยไปที่: แกลเลอรี > เลือกภาพถ่าย > แก้ไข > ยางลบ AI</feature>
</features>
<features module="การแปลแบบตัวต่อตัว">
<feature>ในสถานการณ์ที่สลับกันพูด บริการนี้จะมอบการแปลภาษาร่วมกันระหว่างภาษาจีน ภาษาอังกฤษ ภาษาฝรั่งเศส ภาษาเยอรมัน ภาษาสเปน ภาษาอิตาลี ภาษารัสเซีย ภาษาตุรกี ภาษามาเลย์ และภาษาอาหรับ และยังรองรับการป้อนข้อมูลด้วยเสียงและข้อความ รวมถึงการออกอากาศการแปลภาษาอีกด้วย คุณสามารถลองใช้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > ผู้ช่วย > การแปลแบบตัวต่อตัว</feature>
</features>
<features module="ความปลอดภัย">
<feature>มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัยของ Android (ก.ย. 2024) เพื่อการรักษาความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตการรักษาความปลอดภัยของ HONOR ได้ในเว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="โปรดทราบ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่กระทบต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เรายังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลของคุณก่อนที่จะอัปเดต
2. หากคุณพบปัญหาใด ๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต โปรดโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการของ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ HONOR เพื่อขอการสนับสนุน</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, naghahatid ng mga bagong feature ang inirerekomendang update na ito, kabilang ang AI na Pambura at Harapang pagsasalin, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch. Inirerekomendang mag-update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Makakatulong sa iyo ang bagong AI na Pambura na matalinong alisin ang mga dumadaan at iba pang hindi gustong elemento mula sa mga larawan sa isang tap. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Gallery > Pumili ng larawan > I-edit > AI na Pambura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Harapang pagsasalin">
<feature>Sa isang turn-taking na sitwasyon, puwede itong magbigay ng parehong pagsasalin sa pagitan ng Chinese, English, French, German, Spanish, Italian, Russian, Turkish, Malay, at Arabic. Sinusuportahan din nito ang pag-input gamit ang boses at text, pati na rin ang pag-broadcast ng pagsasalin. Puwede mo itong subukan sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Assistant > Harapang pagsasalin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Set 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, naghahatid ng mga bagong feature ang inirerekomendang update na ito, kabilang ang AI na Pambura at Harapang pagsasalin, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch. Inirerekomendang mag-update.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Makakatulong sa iyo ang bagong AI na Pambura na matalinong alisin ang mga dumadaan at iba pang hindi gustong elemento mula sa mga larawan sa isang tap. Subukan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Gallery > Pumili ng larawan > I-edit > AI na Pambura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Harapang pagsasalin">
<feature>Sa isang turn-taking na sitwasyon, puwede itong magbigay ng parehong pagsasalin sa pagitan ng Chinese, English, French, German, Spanish, Italian, Russian, Turkish, Malay, at Arabic. Sinusuportahan din nito ang pag-input gamit ang boses at text, pati na rin ang pag-broadcast ng pagsasalin. Puwede mo itong subukan sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Assistant > Harapang pagsasalin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Set 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Değerli kullanıcımız, önerilen bu güncelleme ile AI Silgi ve Yüz yüze çeviri gibi yeni özellikler ve bir güvenlik yaması eklendi. Güncellemeniz tavsiye edilir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Yeni AI Silgi tek dokunuşla görsellerde arka planda yer alan kişileri ve diğer istenmeyen unsurları akıllı şekilde kaldırmanıza yardımcı olabilir. Galeri > Bir fotoğraf seç > Düzenle > AI Silgi bölümüne giderek deneyebilirsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Yüz yüze çeviri">
<feature>Sırayla olmak üzere Çince, İngilizce, Fransızca, Almanca, İspanyolca, İtalyanca, Rusça, Türkçe, Malayca ve Arapça arasında çeviri gerçekleştirir. Ayrıca ses ve metin girişini destekler, bununla birlikte çeviriyi yayınlayabilir. Ayarlar > Asistan > Yüz yüze çeviri bölümüne giderek deneyebilirsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güvenlik">
<feature>Sistem güvenliği için Android Güvenlik Yamasını (Eylül 2024) içermektedir. HONOR Güvenlik güncellemeleri ile ilgili daha fazla bilgi için lütfen web sitemizi ziyaret edin: https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir, fakat yine de güncelleme yapmadan önce yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşmanız durumunda destek için lütfen HONOR servisi yardım hattını arayın veya HONOR müşteri servisi merkezlerinden birine gidin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>‏ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا AI يوقىتىش ۋە يۈزتۇرانە تەرجىمە ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«ئامبار»">
<feature>‏AI يوقىتىش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، رەسىمدىكى يولدا مېڭىۋاتقان ئادەم، باشقا نەرسە قاتارلىقلارنى ئاڭلىق يوقىتىپ، بىر كۇنۇپكا بىلەن رەسىمنى قۇتقۇزۇپ قالالايسىز، سىناش يولى: ئامبار > رەسىم > تەھرىرلەش > AI يوقىتىش.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«يۈزتۇرانە تەرجىمە قىلىش»">
<feature>‏نۆۋەتلىشىپ سۆزلىشىش كۆرۈنۈشىدە، خەنزۇچە، ئىنگلىزچە، فىرانسۇزچە، گېرمانچە، ئىسپانچە، ئىتالىيانچە، رۇسچە، تۈركچە، مالايچە ۋە ئەرەبچە ئارىسىدا ئۆزئارا تەرجىمە قىلىشنى قوللايدۇ. ئاۋازلىق ۋە خەتلىك كىرگۈزۈش، تەرجىمە نەتىجىسىنى ئاڭلىتىشنى قوللايدۇ، سىناش يولى: تەڭشەك > ئاڭلىق ياردەمچى > يۈزتۇرانە تەرجىمە.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«بىخەتەرلىك»">
<feature>ئاندرويدنىڭ 2024-يىل 9-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتىنى زىيارەت قىلىڭ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановний користувачу! Це рекомендоване оновлення вводить нові функції, зокрема "ШІ-гумка" й "Переклад тет-а-тет", і включає виправлення системи безпеки. Рекомендовано встановити це оновлення.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерея">
<feature>За допомогою нової функції "ШІ-гумка" можна інтелектуально видаляти перехожих та інші небажані елементи із зображень одним дотиком. Щоб спробувати, перейдіть до меню "Галерея" > "Вибрати фото" > "Змінити" > "ШІ-гумка".</feature>
</features>
<features module="Переклад тет-а-тет">
<feature>Використовуйте цю функцію по черзі зі співрозмовником, щоб перекладати такими мовами: китайська, англійська, французька, німецька, іспанська, італійська, російська, турецька, малайська й арабська. Ця функція також підтримує голосове й текстове введення, а також трансляцію перекладу. Щоб спробувати, перейдіть до меню "Налаштування" > "Помічник" > "Переклад тет-а-тет".</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безпека">
<feature>Виправлення для системи безпеки Android від вересня 2024 року впроваджено для посилення безпеки системи. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки HONOR див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примітки." type="end">
<feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, але перед оновленням радимо створити їхню резервну копію.
2. Якщо під час оновлення виникнуть якісь проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію служби підтримки HONOR або зверніться по допомогу в сервісний центр для клієнтів HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>محترم صارف، یہ تجویز کردہ اپ ڈیٹ نئی خصوصیات، بشمول AI مٹانے والی شے اور آمنے سامنے ترجمہ لاتی ہے، اور ایک سکیورٹی پیچ شامل کرتی ہے۔ اپ ڈیٹ کرنے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="گیلری">
<feature>نئی AI مٹانے والی شے آپ کو ایک ہی ٹیپ سے تصاویر سے غیر ضروری اور دیگر ناپسندیدہ عناصر کو ذہانت سے ہٹانے میں مدد کر سکتی ہے۔ یہاں جا کر آزمائیں: گیلری > تصویر منتخب کریں > ترمیم کریں > AI مٹانے والی شے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="آمنے سامنے ترجمہ">
<feature>اپنی باری آنے والی صورت حال میں، یہ چینی، انگریزی، فرانسیسی، جرمن، ہسپانوی، اطالوی، روسی، ترکی، مالے اور عربی کے درمیان باہمی ترجمہ فراہم کر سکتی ہے۔ یہ آواز اور متنی ان پٹ نیز ترجمہ براڈ کاسٹ کرنے میں بھی تعاون کرتی ہے۔ آپ اسے یہاں جا کر آزما سکتے ہیں: ترتیبات > اسِسٹنٹ > آمنے سامنے ترجمہ۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سیکورٹی">
<feature>‏‏Android سکیورٹی پیچ (ستمبر 2024) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ HONOR سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ ملاحظہ کریں: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں متاثر ہو گا، لیکن پھر بھی اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے سے اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2۔ اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو تعاون کے لیے براہ کرم HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کریں یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جائیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu tavsiya etiladigan yangilanishda yangi funksiyalar, jumladan, AI tozalagich hamda Yuzma-yuz tarjima funksiyalari taqdim etildi. Uni yangilash tavsiya etiladi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galereya">
<feature>Yangi AI tozalagich funksiyasi sizga rasmlardan begonalar va boshqa keraksiz narsalarni osonlik bilan intellektual olib tashlash imkonini beradi. Uni bu yerda sinang: Galereya > Surat tanlash > Tahrirlash > AI tozalagich.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Yuzma-yuz tarjima">
<feature>Oʻz navbatida, u xitoy, ingliz, fransuz, nemis, ispan, italyan, rus, turk, malay va arab tillari orasida oʻzaro tarjima qilish imkonini beradi. U ovozli va matnli maʼlumotlarni, shuningdek, ovozli tarjimani ham dastaklaydi. Uni bu yerda sinashingiz mumkin: Sozlamalar > Assistent > Yuzma-yuz tarjima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Xavfsizlik">
<feature>Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2024-yil, sentabr) kiritildi. HONOR Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, yordam uchun HONOR xizmat markazi tezkor raqamiga murojaat qiling yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyuring.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật đề xuất này có các tính năng mới, bao gồm AI Eraser và Dịch trực tiếp, đồng thời tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật. Bạn nên cập nhật.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bộ sưu tập">
<feature>Tính năng AI Eraser mới có thể giúp bạn xóa người qua đường và các thành phần không mong muốn khác một cách thông minh khỏi hình ảnh chỉ với một thao tác chạm. Hãy dùng thử tính năng này bằng cách vào: Bộ sưu tập > Chọn ảnh > Sửa > AI Eraser.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Dịch trực tiếp">
<feature>Trong tình huống thay phiên nhau, tính năng này có thể cung cấp bản dịch lẫn nhau giữa tiếng Trung, tiếng Anh, tiếng Pháp, tiếng Đức, tiếng Tây Ban Nha, tiếng Ý, tiếng Nga, tiếng Thổ Nhĩ Kỳ, tiếng Malay và tiếng Ả Rập. Tính năng này cũng hỗ trợ nhập giọng nói và văn bản, cũng như phát bản dịch. Bạn có thể dùng thử tính năng này bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Trợ lý > Dịch trực tiếp.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bảo mật">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này tích hợp Bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 9 năm 2024) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của HONOR, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ghi chú:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị ảnh hưởng. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新新增 AI 消除和面對面翻譯功能，整合安全性修補程式，建議你更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【圖片庫】">
<feature>新增 AI 消除功能，智能消除相片中的路人、雜物等，一鍵拯救廢片，體驗路徑：圖片庫 > 圖片 > 編輯 > AI 消除。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【面對面翻譯】">
<feature>支援在輪流對話場景下，中文、英文、法文、德文、西班牙文、意大利文、俄文、土耳其文、馬來西亞文、阿拉伯文之間的互譯。支援語音和文本輸入，以及翻譯結果廣播。體驗路徑：設定 > 智能助手 > 面對面翻譯。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>整合 Android 2024 年 9 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線，或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新新增 AI 消除和面對面翻譯功能，並整合安全性修補程式，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【圖片庫】">
<feature>新增 AI 消除功能，智慧消除相片中的路人、雜物等，一鍵拯救廢片，體驗路徑：圖片庫 > 圖片 > 編輯 > AI 消除。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【面對面翻譯】">
<feature>在支援在輪流對話場景下，中文、英文、法文、德文、西班牙文、義大利文、俄文、土耳其文、馬來西亞文、阿拉伯文之間的互譯。支援語音和文字輸入，以及翻譯結果播報，體驗路徑：設定 > 智慧助手 > 面對面翻譯。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>整合 Android 2024 年 9月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/9</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
