<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次升级为您推出全新MagicOS 8.0|Android 14系统，新系统更流畅、更安全、更好用、更省电，桌面更好玩，交互更高效便捷，推荐您更新体验。更多功能解锁敬请期待后续版本更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="玩转桌面">
<feature>【桌面图标】支持桌面图标大小调节，满足用户对图标大小的不同显示需求，体验路径：“设置->桌面和个性化->桌面设置->图标大小”。</feature>
<feature>【分屏】新增一步手势分屏功能，应用全屏下拖动底部至左上角，点击其他支持分屏应用，即可实现应用分屏。</feature>
<feature>【悬浮窗】迷你窗支持移动和悬停到手机桌面任意位置。</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1、本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2、请务必确保手机有10GB以上的内部存储空间，否则会有升级失败的风险（查看存储空间方法：设置 -> 存储）。
3、因部分第三方应用与MagicOS 8.0不兼容，更新后可能会出现第三方应用无法正常使用的情况（如闪退、卡顿、耗电等）。建议您在应用市场尝试将该应用更新至最新版本，若仍无法解决问题，请您耐心等待应用更新信息，并及时更新。
4、升级后，系统进行自优化适配，可能会出现发热、耗电快、卡顿或充电慢的问题，正常使用2~3天后会恢复正常。建议升级完成后将手机灭屏充电1~2小时以上再重启手机，以保证手机应用快速适配完。
5、 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear users, this update has launched brand-new MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 for you. The new system is smoother, safer, easier to use, more power-saving, and the home screen is more fun. We recommend you to update. Please stay tuned for upcoming version updates to unlock more features.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Explore the home screen">
<feature>【Home screen icons】The size of Home screen icons can be adjusted to meet the users' different needs. You can experience it by going to: Settings -> Home screen and style -> Home screen settings -> Icon size.</feature>
<feature>【App Extender】 You can now enable App Extender with a single gesture. Drag the bottom to the upper left corner, and then tap the other app supporting App Extender to display apps in dual windows.</feature>
<feature>【Floating window】 Mini window can be moved and hovered to any position on the home screen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. This update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. Make sure your phone has more than 10 GB of free storage space. Otherwise, the update may fail (Go to Settings -> Storage to check it).
3. Some third-party apps may not be compatible with MagicOS 8.0 and may malfunction after the update (such as crash, lag, abnormal power consumption). Please update your apps to the latest version in AppGallery. If the problems persist, please wait for upcoming app updates.
4. After updating, the system will adjust its settings to apply the optimizations. In the process, the phone may become hot, consume power fast, lag, or charge slowly. But it will return to normal in 2-3 days of use. After the update is done and before restarting the phone, we recommend charging it with the screen off for 1~2 hours to ensure the optimizations are applied.
5. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling HONOR service hotline or visiting HONOR Customer Service Center.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚዎች፣ ይህ ማሻሻያ አዲስ MagicOS 8.0|አንድሮይድ 14ን ለእርስዎ ጭኗል። አዲሱ ስርዓት ለስላሳ፣ ደህንነቱ የተጠበቀ፣ ለመጠቀም ቀላል፣ የበለጠ ኃይል ቆጣቢ ነው እና የመነሻ ገጹ የበለጠ አስደሳች ነው። እንዲያዘምኑ እንመክርዎታለን። ተጨማሪ ባህሪያትን ለመክፈት እባክዎ ቀጣይ የሚመጡትን የዝመና ስሪቶችን ይከታተሉ።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የመነሻ ገጹን ያስሱ">
<feature>【የመነሻ ገጽ አዶዎች】የተጠቃሚዎችን የተለያዩ ፍላጎቶች ለማሟላት የመነሻ ገጽ አዶዎች መጠን ሊስተካከል ይችላል። ወደ ቅንብሮች -> መነሻ ገጽ እና ቅጥ -> የመነሻ ማያ ቅንብሮች -> የአዶ መጠን በመሄድ ሊሞክቱት ይችላሉ።</feature>
<feature>【መተግበሪያ ማራዘሚያ】 አሁን መተግበሪያ ማራዘሚያን በአንድ የእጅ ምልክት ስራ ማስጀመር ይችላሉ። ታቹን ወደ የላይኛው ግራ ጥግ ይጎትቱት እና በመቀጠል መተግበሪያ ማራዘሚያን የሚደግፈውን ሌላውን መተግበሪያ በሁለት መስኮቶች ለማሳየት ይንኩ።</feature>
<feature>【ተንሳፋፊ መስኮት】 ትንሽ መስኮት በመነሻ ገጽ ላይ ወደ ማንኛውም ቦታ ማንቀሳቀስ እና ማንዣበብ ይችላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህ ዝማኔ የእርስዎን ግላዊ ውሂብ አይሰርዝም፣ ነገር ግን ቀደም ብለው መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ አሁንም ይመከራል።
2. ስልክዎ ከ10 ጂቢ በላይ ነፃ የማከማቻ ቦታ እንዳለው ያረጋግጡ። አለበለዚያ ዝማኔው ላይሳካ ይችላል (ወደ ቅንብሮች > ማከማቻ በመሄድ ያረጋግጡ)።
3. አንዳንድ የሦስተኛ-ወገን መተግበሪያዎች ከMagicOS 8.0 ጋር የሚጣጣሙ ላይሆኑ ይችላሉ እና ከዝመናው በኋላ ሊበላሹ (እንደ መሰናከል፣ መዘግየት፣ ያልተለመደ የኃይል ፍጆታ) ይችላሉ። እባክዎ መተግበሪያዎችዎን በAppGallery ውስጥ ወዳለው የቅርብ ጊዜ ስሪት ያዘምኑ። ችግሮቹ ከቀጠሉ፣ እባክዎን በቅርብ ለሚደረጉ የመተግበሪያ ዝማኔዎች ይጠብቁ።
4. ከዝማኔው በኋላ ስርዓቱ ማስተካከያውን ለመተግበር ቅንብሮቹን ያስተካክላል። በዚህ ሂደት ስልኩ ሊሞቅ፣ ሃይልን በፍጥነት ሊፈጅ፣ ሊዘገይ ወይም ቀስ ብሎ ባትሪ ሊሞላ ይችላል። ነገር ግን ከ2-3 ቀናት ጥቅም ላይ ከዋለ በኋላ ወደ መደበኛው ይመለሳል። ዝማኔው ከተጠናቀቀ በኋላ እና ስልኩን ዳግም ከማስነሳትዎ በፊት፣ ማስተካከያዎቹ መተግበራቸውን ለማረጋገጥ ስክሪኑ ጠፍቶ ከ1~2 ሰአታት ባትሪ እንዲሞሉ እንመክራለን።
5. በዝማኔው ወቅት ምንም አይነት ችግር ካጋጠምዎ ለHONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር በመደወል ወይም HONOR የደንበኞች የአገልግሎት ማዕከልን በመጎብኘት የእኛን እርዳታ ማግኘት ይችላሉ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزي المستخدم، أطلق هذا التحديث نظام التشغيل MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 الجديد تمامًا من أجلك. يتميز النظام الجديد بالمزيد من السلاسة والأمان وسهولة الاستخدام والقدرة على توفير الطاقة، كما أن استخدام الشاشة الرئيسية يضفي المزيد من المتعة. لذا ننصحك بالتحديث. يرجى ترقّب تحديثات الإصدار القادمة لاستكشاف المزيد من الميزات.</feature>
</features>
<features module="استكشاف الشاشة الرئيسية">
<feature>【أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية】يمكن تعديل حجم أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية لتلبية احتياجات المستخدمين المختلفة. يمكنك تجربة ذلك بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات -> الشاشة الرئيسية والنمط -> إعدادات الشاشة الرئيسية -> حجم الأيقونة.</feature>
<feature>【مُوسِع التطبيقات】 يمكنك الآن تمكين مُوسِع التطبيقات بواسطة إيماءة واحدة. اسحب الجزء السفلي إلى الزاوية العلوية اليمنى، ثم اضغط على التطبيق الآخر الذي يدعم مُوسِع التطبيقات لعرض التطبيقات في نوافذ مزدوجة.</feature>
<feature>【نافذة عائمة】 يمكن تحريك النافذة الصغيرة ووضعها في أي موضع على الشاشة الرئيسية.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. لن يؤدّي هذا التحديث إلى مسح بياناتك الشخصية، ومع ذلك نوصي بإجراء نسخ احتياطي مسبقًا.
‏2. تأكد من توفر مساحة تخزين فارغة تزيد عن 10 جيجابايت في هاتفك. وإلا، فقد يفشل التحديث (انتقل إلى الإعدادات > وحدة التخزين للتحقق من الأمر).
‏3. قد لا تكون بعض تطبيقات الطرف الثالث متوافقة مع الإصدار 7.1 من نظام MagicOS، وقد تحدث فيها حالات خلل بعد التحديث (كالتعطّل، أو التأخر، أو استهلاك الشحن بصورة غير طبيعية). يُرجى تحديث تطبيقاتك إلى أحدث إصدار في متجر التطبيقات. إذا استمرّت المشكلة، فنرجو منك ترقّب تحديثات التطبيقات القادمة.
‏4. بعد التحديث، سيضبط النظام إعداداته لتطبيق التحسينات. في أثناء العملية، قد ترتفع حرارة الجهاز، أو يستهلك الشحن بسرعة أكبر، أو يتأخر، أو يشحن ببطء. لكنه سيعود إلى حالته الطبيعية خلال يومين إلى 3 أيام من الاستخدام. بعد الانتهاء من التحديث وقبل إعادة تشغيل الهاتف، نوصي بشحنه مع مراعاة انطفاء الشاشة لمدة ساعة إلى ساعتين تقريبًا؛ لضمان تطبيق التحسينات.
‏5. إذا واجهت أي مشكلات في أثناء التحديث، فيُمكنك الحصول على المساعدة من خلالنا عن طريق الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة عملاء HONOR أو زيارة مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীসকল, এই আপডেটটোৱে আপোনাৰ বাবে একেবাৰে নতুন MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 লঞ্চ কৰিছে। নতুন ছিষ্টেমটো বাধাহীন, নিৰাপদ, ব্যৱহাৰ কৰিবলৈ সহজ, অধিক পাৱাৰ সংৰক্ষণ কৰে আৰু হোম স্ক্ৰীণ অধিক মনোৰঞ্জনমূলক। আমি আপোনাক আপডেট কৰিবলৈ অনুমোদন জনাওঁ। অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি অধিক ফিচাৰ আনলক কৰিবলৈ অনাগত সংস্কৰণৰ আপডেটসমূহৰ বাবে জড়িত হৈ থাকক।</feature>
</features>
<features module="হোম স্ক্ৰীণ অন্বেষণ কৰক">
<feature>【হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্ন】ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ বেলেগ বেলেগ প্ৰয়োজনবোৰ পূৰণ কৰিবলৈ হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্নৰ আকাৰ মিলাব পাৰি। আপুনি ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াৰ অভিজ্ঞতা ল'ব পাৰে: ছেটিংছ -> হোম স্ক্ৰীণ আৰু শৈলী -> হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ ছেটিংছ -> চিহ্নৰ আকাৰ।</feature>
<feature>【এপ্প্‌ এক্সটেণ্ডাৰ】 আপুনি এতিয়া এটা ভঙ্গিমাৰে এপ্প্‌ এক্সটেণ্ডাৰ সক্ষম কৰিব পাৰে। দুখন উইণ্ড'ত এপ্প্‌সমূহ প্ৰদৰ্শন কৰিবলৈ ওপৰৰ বাওঁ কোণত তলটো টানক আৰু তাৰপিছত এপ্প্‌ এক্সটেণ্ডাৰ সমৰ্থন কৰা অন্য এপ্প্‌টো টিপক।</feature>
<feature>【ফ্ল'টিং উইণ্ড'】 হোম স্ক্ৰীণখনত যিকোনো ঠাইলৈ মিনি উইণ্ড' লৈ যাব আৰু হোভাৰ কৰিব পাৰি।</feature>
</features>
<features module="টোকাসমূহ:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটোৱে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটা মোহাৰি নেপেলাব, কিন্তু তাৰ পূৰ্বে বেকআপ লোৱাটো এতিয়াও অনুমোদিত।
2. আপোনাৰ ফোনত 10 GB-তকৈ বেছি খালী সংগ্ৰহ স্থান থকাটো নিশ্চিত কৰক। অন্যথা, আপডেটটো বিফল হ'ব পাৰে (ইয়াক চাবলৈ ছেটিংছ > সংগ্ৰহণলৈ যাওক)।
3. MagicOS 8.0-ৰ সৈতে কিছুমান তৃতীয়-পক্ষৰ এপ্প্‌ সুসঙ্গত নহ'ব পাৰে আৰু আপডেটৰ পাছত বিজুতি ঘটিব পাৰে (যেনে, ক্ৰেছ হোৱা, লেহেমীয়া হোৱা, অস্বাভাৱিক পাৱাৰ খৰচ)। অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি AppGallery-ত থকা শেহতীয়া সংস্কৰণলৈ আপোনাৰ এপ্প্‌সমূহ আপডেট কৰক। যদি সমস্যাটো দেখা দি থাকে, তেন্তে অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি অনাগত এপ্প্‌ৰ আপডেটসমূহৰ বাবে অপেক্ষা কৰক।
4. আপডেট কৰাৰ পাছত ছিষ্টেমটোৱে অনুকূলিতকৰণ প্ৰয়োগ কৰিবলৈ ইয়াৰ ছেটিংচ মিলাব। প্ৰক্ৰিয়াটোত ফোনটো গৰম, পাৱাৰ দ্ৰুত গতিত খৰচ, লেহেমীয়া বা লেহেমীয়াকৈ চাৰ্জ হ'ব পাৰে। কিন্তু এইটো 2-3 দিন ব্যৱহাৰ কৰাৰ পাছত সাধাৰণলৈ ঘূৰি আহিব। অনুকূলিতকৰণ প্ৰয়োগ হোৱাটো নিশ্চিত কৰিবলৈ আপডেট সম্পন্ন হোৱাৰ পাছত আৰু ফোনটো পুনৰাৰম্ভ কৰাৰ আগত আমি ইয়াক স্ক্ৰীণ অফ ৰাখি 1~ 2 ঘণ্টা চাৰ্জ কৰিবলৈ অনুমোদন জনাও।
5. আপুনি আপডেটটোৰ সময়ত কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হ'লে, আপুনি HONOR সেৱাৰ হটলাইনত কল কৰি বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰ দৰ্শন কৰি আমাৰ সহায় লাভ কৰিব পাৰে।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçilər, bu yeniləmə sizin üçün tamamilə yeni MagicOS 8.0|Android 14-ü təqdim etdi. Yeni sistem daha fasiləsiz, təhlükəsiz, istifadəsi asandır, enerjiyə daha çox qənaət edir və əsas ekran daha maraqlıdır. Yeniləməyinizi tövsiyə edirik. Daha çox xüsusiyyətin kilidini açmaq üçün gələcək versiya yeniləmələri ilə bağlı bizi izləyin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Əsas ekranı araşdırın">
<feature>【Əsas ekran nişanları】Əsas ekran nişanlarının ölçüsü istifadəçilərin müxtəlif ehtiyaclarını ödəmək üçün tənzimlənə bilər. Bunu aşağıdakı bölmələrə keçməklə təcrübədən keçirə bilərsiniz: Parametrlər -> Əsas ekran və üslub -> Əsas ekran parametrləri -> Nişan ölçüsü.</feature>
<feature>【Proqram Genişləndiricisi】 Artıq bir jestlə Proqram Genişləndiricisini aktivləşdirə bilərsiniz. Aşağı tərəfi yuxarı sol küncə sürükləyin və sonra proqramları ikili pəncərələrdə göstərmək üçün Proqram Genişləndiricisini dəstəkləyən digər proqrama toxunun.</feature>
<feature>【Sürüşdürülən pəncərə】 Mini pəncərə köçürülə və əsas ekranda istənilən mövqeyə gətirilə bilər.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmə ilə şəxsi məlumatlarınız silinməyəcək, lakin qabaqcadan ehtiyat nüsxənin çıxarılması məsləhət görülür.
2. Telefonda ən azı 10 GB boş yaddaş yerinin olduğundan əmin olun. Əks halda, yeniləmə alınmaya bilər (Yoxlamaq üçün Parametrlər > Yaddaş bölməsinə keçin).
3. Bəzi üçüncü tərəf proqramları MagicOS 8.0 ilə uyğun olmaya və yeniləmədən sonra müvafiq qaydada işləməyə bilər (məsələn, xəta, ləngimə, qeyri-normal enerji sərfiyyatı). AppGallery-də proqramlarınızı ən son versiyaya yeniləyin. Problemlər davam edərsə, növbəti proqram yeniləmələrini gözləyin.
4. Yeniləmədən sonra sistem optimallaşdırmaları tətbiq etmək üçün öz parametrlərini tənzimləyəcək. Proses zamanı telefon qıza, enerjini sürətlə tükədə, ləngiyə, yaxud asta doldurula bilər. Lakin 2-3 günlük istifadədən sonra normal vəziyyətə qayıdacaq. Yeniləmə yerinə yetirildikdən sonra və telefonu yenidən başlatmamışdan əvvəl optimallaşdırmaların tətbiq edilməsini təmin etmək üçün onu ekran sönülü vəziyyətdə 1~2 saat doldurmağınızı tövsiyə edirik.
5. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlərlə üzləşsəniz, HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edərək və ya HONOR Müştəri Xidməti Mərkəzinə gedərək bizdən kömək əldə edə bilərsiniz.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran iki ngluncurake MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 anyar kanggo sampeyan. Sistem anyar iki luwih lancar, luwih aman, luwih gampang digunakake, luwih irit daya, lan layar ngarep luwih nyenengake. Disaranake supaya sampeyan nganyarake. Awasi terus panganyaran versi sing baka teka kanggo mbukak fitur liyane.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Njelajahi layar ngarep">
<feature>【Ikon Layar ngarep】Ukuran ikon Layar ngarep bisa diatur kanggo nyukupi kabutuhan pangguna sing beda-beda. Sampeyan bisa nggunakake fitur iki kanthi mbukak: Setelan -> Layar ngarep lan gaya -> Setelan layar ngarep -> Ukuran ikon.</feature>
<feature>【Pangulur Apl】 Sampeyan saiki bisa ngaktifake Pangulur Apl kanthi sak obahan. Seret saka ngisor menyang pojok kiwa ndhuwur, banjur tutul apl liyane sing ndhukung Pangulur Apl kanggo nampilake apl ing rong jendhela.</feature>
<feature>【Jendhela nglayang】 Jendhela mini bisa dipindhahake lan diarahake menyang sembarang posisi ing layar ngarep.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Panganyaran iki ora bakal mbusak data pribadi sampeyan, nanging sampeyan tetep disaranake nggawe serep sadurunge.
2. Pesthekake ponsel sampeyan nduwe enggon simpenan sing kosong luwih saka 10 GB. Yen ora, panganyaran bisa gagal (Bukak Setelan > Simpenan kanggo mriksa).
3. Sawetara apl pihak katelu ora cocog karo MagicOS 8.0 lan bisa gagal fungsi sawise panganyaran (kayata macet, rindhik, daya entek ora normal). Anyarake apl sampeyan dadi versi paling anyar ing AppGallery. Yen masalah ora rampung, enteni panganyaran apl sing mbesuk.
4. Sawise nganyarake, sistem bakal ngatur setelane kanggo ngecakake optimisasi. Sajrone proses kuwi, ponsel bisa dadi panas, cepet entek dayane, rindhik, suwe anggone ngisi daya. Nanging, ponsel bakal mbalik normal sawise digunakake 2-3 dina. Sawise panganyaran rampung lan sadurunge ponsel diwiwiti maneh, kita nyaranake sampeyan supaya mateni layar ponsel nalika ngisi daya 1~2 jam suwene kanggo mesthekake optimasi dicakake.
5. Yen sampeyan nemu masalah sajrone panganyaran, sampeyan bisa njaluk tulung kanthi nelpon hotline layanan HONOR utawa marani Pusat Layanan Pelanggan HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisnici, ovim ažuriranjem uveden je potpuno novi MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Novi sistem radi tečnije, bezbedniji je i lakši za korišćenje, više štedi energiju i poseduje zabavniji početni ekran. Preporučujemo vam da ažurirate. Pratite nas da biste dobijali obaveštenja o narednim verzijama ažuriranja kako biste otključali više funkcija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Istražite početni ekran">
<feature>【Ikone početnog ekrana】Veličina ikona početnog ekrana može da se podesi kako bi se zadovoljile potrebe korisnika. Možete to da uradite tako što ćete otići na: Podešavanja -> Početni ekran i stil -> Podešavanja početnog ekrana -> Veličina ikone.</feature>
<feature>【Proširivač aplikacije】 Sada Proširivač aplikacije možete omogućiti jednim pokretom. Prevucite dno do gornjeg levog ugla, a zatim dodirnite drugu aplikaciju koja podržava Proširivač aplikacije da biste aplikacije prikazali u dvostrukim prozorima.</feature>
<feature>【Plutajući prozor】 Mini-prozor može da se pomeri i da pluta na bilo kom mestu na početnom ekranu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ovo ažuriranje neće obrisati vaše lične podatke, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Uverite se da na telefonu ima više od 10 GB slobodnog prostora za skladištenje. U suprotnom, ažuriranje možda neće uspeti (Izaberite Podešavanja > Memorija da biste izvršili proveru).
3. Neke aplikacije trećih strana možda nisu kompatibilne sa verzijom MagicOS 8.0 i mogu postati neispravne nakon ažuriranja (na primer, otkazivanje, kašnjenje, neuobičajena potrošnja energije). Ažurirajte svoje aplikacije na najnoviju verziju u aplikaciji AppGallery. Ako se problemi i dalje javljaju, sačekajte predstojeća ažuriranja aplikacija.
4. Nakon ažuriranja, sistem će prilagoditi svoja podešavanja radi primene optimizacija. U tom procesu telefon može da se zagreva, da brzo troši energiju, da kasni ili da se sporo puni. Ali će se vratiti u uobičajeno stanje nakon 2–3 dana korišćenja. Nakon što se ažuriranje završi, a pre ponovnog pokretanja telefona, preporučujemo da punite telefon sa isključenim ekranom 1~2 sata da biste osigurali da optimizacije budu primenjene.
5. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, možete da dobijete našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetiti korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisnici, ovim ažuriranjem uveden je potpuno novi MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Novi sistem radi tečnije, bezbedniji je i lakši za korišćenje, više štedi energiju i poseduje zabavniji početni ekran. Preporučujemo vam da ažurirate. Pratite nas da biste dobijali obaveštenja o narednim verzijama ažuriranja kako biste otključali više funkcija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Istražite početni ekran">
<feature>【Ikone početnog ekrana】Veličina ikona početnog ekrana može da se podesi kako bi se zadovoljile potrebe korisnika. Možete to da uradite tako što ćete otići na: Podešavanja -> Početni ekran i stil -> Podešavanja početnog ekrana -> Veličina ikone.</feature>
<feature>【Proširivač aplikacije】 Sada Proširivač aplikacije možete omogućiti jednim pokretom. Prevucite dno do gornjeg levog ugla, a zatim dodirnite drugu aplikaciju koja podržava Proširivač aplikacije da biste aplikacije prikazali u dvostrukim prozorima.</feature>
<feature>【Plutajući prozor】 Mini-prozor može da se pomeri i da pluta na bilo kom mestu na početnom ekranu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ovo ažuriranje neće obrisati vaše lične podatke, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Uverite se da na telefonu ima više od 10 GB slobodnog prostora za skladištenje. U suprotnom, ažuriranje možda neće uspeti (Izaberite Podešavanja > Memorija da biste izvršili proveru).
3. Neke aplikacije trećih strana možda nisu kompatibilne sa verzijom MagicOS 8.0 i mogu postati neispravne nakon ažuriranja (na primer, otkazivanje, kašnjenje, neuobičajena potrošnja energije). Ažurirajte svoje aplikacije na najnoviju verziju u aplikaciji AppGallery. Ako se problemi i dalje javljaju, sačekajte predstojeća ažuriranja aplikacija.
4. Nakon ažuriranja, sistem će prilagoditi svoja podešavanja radi primene optimizacija. U tom procesu telefon može da se zagreva, da brzo troši energiju, da kasni ili da se sporo puni. Ali će se vratiti u uobičajeno stanje nakon 2–3 dana korišćenja. Nakon što se ažuriranje završi, a pre ponovnog pokretanja telefona, preporučujemo da punite telefon sa isključenim ekranom 1~2 sata da biste osigurali da optimizacije budu primenjene.
5. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, možete da dobijete našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetiti korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisnici, ovim ažuriranjem uveden je potpuno novi MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Novi sistem radi tečnije, bezbedniji je i lakši za korišćenje, više štedi energiju i poseduje zabavniji početni ekran. Preporučujemo vam da ažurirate. Pratite nas da biste dobijali obaveštenja o narednim verzijama ažuriranja kako biste otključali više funkcija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Istražite početni ekran">
<feature>【Ikone početnog ekrana】Veličina ikona početnog ekrana može da se podesi kako bi se zadovoljile potrebe korisnika. Možete to da uradite tako što ćete otići na: Podešavanja -> Početni ekran i stil -> Podešavanja početnog ekrana -> Veličina ikone.</feature>
<feature>【Proširivač aplikacije】 Sada Proširivač aplikacije možete omogućiti jednim pokretom. Prevucite dno do gornjeg levog ugla, a zatim dodirnite drugu aplikaciju koja podržava Proširivač aplikacije da biste aplikacije prikazali u dvostrukim prozorima.</feature>
<feature>【Plutajući prozor】 Mini-prozor može da se pomeri i da pluta na bilo kom mestu na početnom ekranu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ovo ažuriranje neće obrisati vaše lične podatke, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Uverite se da na telefonu ima više od 10 GB slobodnog prostora za skladištenje. U suprotnom, ažuriranje možda neće uspeti (Izaberite Podešavanja > Memorija da biste izvršili proveru).
3. Neke aplikacije trećih strana možda nisu kompatibilne sa verzijom MagicOS 8.0 i mogu postati neispravne nakon ažuriranja (na primer, otkazivanje, kašnjenje, neuobičajena potrošnja energije). Ažurirajte svoje aplikacije na najnoviju verziju u aplikaciji AppGallery. Ako se problemi i dalje javljaju, sačekajte predstojeća ažuriranja aplikacija.
4. Nakon ažuriranja, sistem će prilagoditi svoja podešavanja radi primene optimizacija. U tom procesu telefon može da se zagreva, da brzo troši energiju, da kasni ili da se sporo puni. Ali će se vratiti u uobičajeno stanje nakon 2–3 dana korišćenja. Nakon što se ažuriranje završi, a pre ponovnog pokretanja telefona, preporučujemo da punite telefon sa isključenim ekranom 1~2 sata da biste osigurali da optimizacije budu primenjene.
5. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, možete da dobijete našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetiti korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаныя карыстальнікі, гэта абнаўленне прапануе вам цалкам новую MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Новая сістэма працуе больш плаўна і бяспечна, зберагае энергію, яе стала прасцей выкарыстоўваць, а галоўны экран стаў больш цікавым. Мы рэкамендуем вам устанавіць гэта абнаўленне. Сачыце за будучымі абнаўленнямі версій, каб разблакіраваць дадатковыя функцыі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Даследуйце галоўны экран">
<feature>【Значкі на галоўным экране】Памер значкоў на галоўным экране можна рэгуляваць у адпаведнасці з рознымі патрэбамі карыстальнікаў. Каб паспрабаваць гэту функцыю, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады -> Галоўны экран і стыль -> Налады галоўнага экрана -> Памер значка».</feature>
<feature>【Пашыральнік праграм】 Цяпер вы можаце ўключыць Пашыральнік праграм адным жэстам. Пацягніце ад нізу да левага верхняга вугла, пасля чаго краніце іншую праграму, якая падтрымлівае адлюстраванне праграм у двух вокнах з дапамогай Пашыральніка праграм.</feature>
<feature>【Плаваючае акно】 Міні-акно можна перамясціць і зафіксаваць у любым месцы галоўнага экрана.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Гэта абнаўленне не сатрэ вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы рэкамендуем загадзя зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію.
2. Упэўніцеся, што ў сховішчы тэлефона больш за 10 ГБ свабоднага месца, інакш абнаўленне можа не быць устаноўлена (каб праверыць месца ў сховішчы, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Сховішча»).
3. Некаторыя праграмы трэціх бакоў могуць быць несумяшчальнымі з MagicOS 8.0 і могуць працаваць няправільна пасля абнаўлення (даваць збой, затрымкі, ненармальнае спажыванне зараду). Абнавіце праграмы да апошніх версій у AppGallery. Калі праблема не знікне, пачакайце будучых абнаўленняў праграм.
4. Пасля абнаўлення сістэма адрэгулюе налады, каб прымяніць аптымізацыю. У працэсе тэлефон можа награвацца, хутка спажываць зарад, працаваць з затрымкамі або марудна зараджацца. Але праз 2–3 дні нармальная праца будзе адноўлена. Пасля завяршэння абнаўлення і перад перазапускам тэлефона рэкамендуем 1–2 гадзіны зараджаць яго з выключаным экранам, каб гарантаваць, што аптымізацыя будзе прыменена.
5. Калі падчас выкарыстання вы сутыкняцеся з праблемамі, можаце атрымаць нашу дапамогу, патэлефанаваўшы на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або наведаўшы Сэрвісны цэнтр для кліентаў HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, с тази актуализация стартира чисто нов MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 за вас. Новата система е по-плавна, по-безопасна, по-лесна за използване, по-енергоспестяваща, а началният екран е по-забавен. Препоръчваме ви да актуализирате. Моля, останете на линия за предстоящите актуализации на версията, за да отключите още функции.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Разглеждане на началния екран">
<feature>【Икони на началния екран】Размерът на иконите на началния екран може да бъде зададен така, че да отговаря на различните нужди на потребителите. Можете да го изпробвате, като отидете на: „Настройки -> Начален екран и стил -> Настройки на началния екран -> Размер на икона“.</feature>
<feature>【Разширител на приложения】 Вече можете да активирате „Разширител на приложения“ с един жест. Плъзнете долната част до горния ляв ъгъл, след което докоснете другото приложение, поддържащо „Разширител на приложения“, за да показвате приложения в два прозореца.</feature>
<feature>【Плаващ прозорец】 Мини прозорецът може да бъде преместен и поставен с мишката на всяко място на началния екран.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Тази актуализация няма да изтрие личните ви данни, но все пак се препоръчва да направите архивиране преди това.
2. Уверете се, че в телефона ви има повече от 10 GB свободно място за съхранение. В противен случай актуализирането може да бъде неуспешно (Отидете на „Настройки > Съхранение“, за да проверите).
3. Някои приложения на трети лица може да не са съвместими с MagicOS 8.0 и да не функционират правилно след актуализацията (например срив, забавяне, необичайна консумация на енергия). Актуализирайте приложенията си до най-новата версия в AppGallery. Ако проблемите продължават, изчакайте предстоящите актуализации на приложенията.
4. След актуализиране системата ще коригира настройките си, за да приложи оптимизациите. В този процес телефонът може да стане топъл, да консумира бързо енергия, да се забави или да се зарежда бавно. Но той ще се нормализира след 2-3 дни употреба. След като актуализацията приключи и преди да рестартирате телефона, препоръчваме да го зареждате с изключен екран в продължение на 1 ~ 2 часа, за да сте сигурни, че оптимизациите са приложени.
5. Ако срещнете някакви проблеми по време на актуализацията, можете да получите нашата помощ, като се обадите на горещата линия за обслужване на HONOR или посетите Сервизен център за клиенти на HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারীগণ, এই আপডেটে আপনার একেবারে নতুন MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 লঞ্চ করা হয়েছে। নতুন সিস্টেমটি আরও নির্বিঘ্ন, নিরাপদ, ব্যবহার করা সহজ, আরও পাওয়ার-সেভিং এবং হোম স্ক্রিনটি আরও মজাদার৷ আমাদের আপনাকে এই আপডেটটি করে নেওয়ার সুপারিশ করি। আরও বৈশিষ্ট্য আনলক করতে অনুগ্রহ করে আসন্ন সংস্করণ আপডেটগুলির জন্য অপেক্ষা করুন।</feature>
</features>
<features module="হোম স্ক্রিন এক্সপ্লোর করুন">
<feature>【হোম স্ক্রিন আইকন】ব্যবহারকারীদের বিভিন্ন প্রয়োজন মেটাতে হোম স্ক্রিন আইকনগুলির আকার সামঞ্জস্যপূর্ণ করা যেতে পারে। আপনি এখানে গিয়ে এটির অভিজ্ঞতা পেতে পারেন: সেটিংস -> হোম স্ক্রিন এবং স্টাইল -> হোম স্ক্রিন সেটিংস -> আইকনের আকার।</feature>
<feature>【অ্যাপ এক্সটেন্ডার】 আপনি এখন একটিমাত্র জেশ্চার দিয়ে অ্যাপ এক্সটেন্ডার সক্রিয় করতে পারেন। নীচের দিককে উপরের বাঁদিকের কোণায় টেনে আনুন, এবং তারপরে ডুয়াল উইন্ডোতে অ্যাপগুলি প্রদর্শন করতে অ্যাপ এক্সটেন্ডারকে সমর্থনকারী অন্য অ্যাপটি ট্যাপ করুন।</feature>
<feature>【ভাসমান উইন্ডো】 মিনি উইন্ডোটি হোম স্ক্রিনের যেকোনো অবস্থানে সরানো এবং হোভার করা যেতে পারে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটা মুছে ফেলবে না, কিন্তু আগে থেকেই ব্যাকআপ নেওয়ার সুপারিশ করা হচ্ছে৷
2. নিশ্চিত করুন যে আপনার ফোনে 10GB এর বেশি সঞ্চয়স্থান খালি আছে৷ অন্যথায়, আপডেট ব্যর্থ হতে পারে (এটি দেখতে সেটিংস > স্টোরেজ-এ যান)।
3. কিছু তৃতীয় পক্ষের অ্যাপ MagicOS 8.0 এর সাথে সামঞ্জস্যপূর্ণ নাও হতে পারে এবং আপডেটের পরে ত্রুটিপূর্ণ হতে পারে (যেমন- ক্র্যাশ, ল্যাগ, অস্বাভাবিক শক্তি খরচ)। অনুগ্রহ করে AppGallery থেকে আপনার অ্যাপগুলিকে সর্বশেষ সংস্করণে আপডেট করুন। সমস্যাগুলি অব্যাহত থাকলে অনুগ্রহ করে আসন্ন অ্যাপের আপডেটের জন্য অপেক্ষা করুন।
4. আপডেট করার পরে অপটিমাইজেশনগুলি প্রয়োগ করতে সিস্টেমটি তার সেটিংস সমন্বয় করবে৷ এই প্রক্রিয়ায় ফোন গরম হয়ে যেতে পারে, দ্রুত শক্তি খরচ করতে পারে, ল্যাগ হতে পারে বা ধীরে ধীরে চার্জ হতে পারে। কিন্তু ব্যবহারের 2-3 দিনের মধ্যে এটি স্বাভাবিক অবস্থায় ফিরে আসবে। আপডেট হয়ে যাওয়ার পরে এবং ফোন রিস্টার্ট করার আগে অপটিমাইজেশনগুলি প্রয়োগ করা হয়েছে তা নিশ্চিত করতে আমরা 1~2 ঘণ্টা স্ক্রিন বন্ধ রেখে চার্জ করার পরামর্শ দিয়ে থাকি।
5. আপডেটের সময় আপনি যদি কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হন, তাহলে আপনি HONOR সেবার হটলাইনে কল করে বা HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে গিয়ে আমাদের সহায়তা পাবেন।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ལ་ MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་གསར་བ་བཏོན་ཡོད། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་གསར་བ་དེ་བས་ཐོགས་ཐུག་མེད་པ་དང་མེད་དེ་བས་བདེ་འཇགས། དེ་བས་སྤྱོད་བདེ། དེ་བས་གློག་བསྲི། ཅོག་ངོས་དེ་བས་སྤྲོ་ལྡན་ཡིན། མཉམ་འགུལ་དེ་བས་ནུས་ཕྱོད་མཐོ་ཞིང་སྟབས་བདེ་ཡིན། ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ནས་ཉམས་ལེན་བྱ་རྒྱུར་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད། དེ་ལས་མང་བའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་ཟྭ་འབྱེད་པར་རྗེས་ཀྱི་པར་གཞི་གསར་སྒྱུར་ལ་རེ་སྒུག་གནང་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="ཅོག་ངོས་གང་འདོད་དུ་རྩེད།">
<feature>【ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས།】 ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཆེ་ཆུང་སྙོམ་སྒྲིག་བྱེད་པར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད། སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་རིས་རྟགས་ཆེ་ཆུང་གི་མངོན་སྟོན་མི་འདྲ་བའི་རེ་འདུན་ཡིད་སྐོང་། ཉམས་ལེན་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་ལམ་ནི། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་ཅོག་ངོས་དང་སྒེར་གཤིས་ཅན། དེ་ནས་ཅོག་ངོས་སྒྲིག་འགོད། དེ་ནས་རིས་རྟགས་ཆེ་ཆུང་།</feature>
<feature>【ཡོལ་བགོ】 གོམ་གཅིག་གི་ལག་བརྡས་ཡོལ་བགོ་བའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཧྲིལ་ཡོལ་འོག་ཏུ་འོག་ཁུལ་གཡོན་གོང་ཟུར་དུ་འགུལ་འདྲུད་བྱས་ནས། ཡོལ་བགོ་ལ་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད་པའི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་གཞན་པར་བརྡབས་ན་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཡོལ་བགོ་མངོན་འགྱུར་བྱ་ཆོག</feature>
<feature>【གཡེང་སྒྲོམ།】སྒྲོམ་ཆུང་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་གྱི་ཅོག་ངོས་ཀྱི་གནས་ཡུལ་གང་རུང་དུ་སྤོ་འགུལ་དང་སྡོད་པར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་ལ་དོ་སྣང་བྱ་དགོས་པའི་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། ཡིན་ནའང་ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་གསར་སྒྱུར་མ་བྱས་གོང་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ཡག་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. ངེས་པར་དུ་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་ལ་ 10GB ཡན་གྱི་ནང་ཁུལ་ཉར་ཚགས་བར་སྟོང་ཡོད་པར་ཁག་ཐེག་བྱ་དགོས། དེ་ལྟར་མ་བྱས་ཚེ་རིམ་སྤོར་བྱེད་མི་ཐུབ་པའི་ཉེན་ཁ་ཡོད་སྲིད། (ཉར་ཚགས་བར་སྟོང་ལ་ལྟ་ཞིབ་བྱེད་ཐབས། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་གསོག་འཇོག)
3. ཕྱོགས་གསུམ་པའི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་དང་ MagicOS 8.0 མཐུན་འགྲིག་མིན་པའི་རྐྱེན་གྱིས་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱས་རྗེས་ཕྱོགས་གསུམ་པའི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་རྒྱུན་ལྡན་ལྟར་བཀོལ་ཐབས་བྲལ་བའི་གནས་ཚུལ་འབྱུང་སྲིད། (དཔེར་ན་མྱུར་ལོག་དང་ཐོགས་པ། གློག་ཟད་པ་སོགས།) ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཁྲོམ་ར་ནས་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་དེ་པར་གཞི་གསར་ཤོས་སུ་རིམ་སྤོར་བྱ་རྒྱུ་ཚོད་ལྟ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས། གལ་ཏེ་སྔར་བཞིན་གནད་དོན་ཐག་གཅོད་ཐབས་བྲལ་ཚེ། ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ་སྒུག་པ་མ་ཟད། དུས་ཐོག་ཏུ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་རོགས།
4. རིམ་སྤོར་བྱས་རྗེས། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་རང་ཉིད་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་མཐུན་སྒྲིག་བྱེད་ཅིང་། དྲོད་ཚད་འཕར་བ་དང་གློག་ཟད་ཚད་མགྱོགས་པ། ཐོགས་པའམ་གློག་གསོག་རྒྱུ་དལ་བ་བཅས་ཀྱི་གནད་དོན་འབྱུང་སྲིད། རྒྱུན་ལྡན་ལྟར་ཉིན་ 2~3 ལ་བཀོལ་སྤྱོད་བྱས་རྗེས་རྒྱུན་ལྡན་ལ་སླར་གསོ་བྱ་སྲིད། རིམ་སྤོར་བྱས་ཚར་རྗེས་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་བརྙན་ཡོལ་ཞི་བར་བྱས་ནས་ཆུ་ཚོད་ 1~2 ཡན་ལ་གློག་བསགས་ཏེ་སླར་ཡང་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་བསྐྱར་སློང་བྱས་ནས། ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་གྱི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་མགྱོགས་པོར་མཐུན་སྒྲིག་བྱས་ཚར་བར་ཁག་ཐེག་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
5. གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་ལ་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ་ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་སྐུ་མགྲོན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་སོང་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་རེ་ཞུ་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisnici, ovo ažuriranje je pokrenulo potpuno novi MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Novi sistem je brži, sigurniji, lakši za korištenje, štedi više energije i ima zabavniji početni ekran. Preporučujemo da izvršite ažuriranje. Pratite novosti za predstojeća ažuriranja verzije da otključate više funkcija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Istražite početni ekran">
<feature>【Ikone na početnom ekranu】Veličina ikona na početnom ekranu se može prilagoditi u skladu s različitim potrebama korisnika. Funkciju možete isprobati odlaskom u Postavke -> Početni ekran i stil -> Postavke početnog ekrana -> Veličina ikona.</feature>
<feature>【Proširivač aplikacija】 Sada možete omogućiti Proširivač aplikacija samo jednom gestom. Povucite sa dna u gornji lijevi ugao, a zatim dodirnite drugu aplikaciju koja podržava Proširivač aplikacija da bi se aplikacije prikazivale u dva prozora.</feature>
<feature>【Plutajući prozor】 Mini prozor se može premještati i postaviti da pluta na bilo koji položaj na početnom ekranu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ovim ažuriranjem se neće izbrisati vaši lični podaci, ali ipak se preporučuje da prethodno napravite sigurnosnu kopiju podataka.
2. Vodite računa da telefon ima više od 10 GB slobodnog prostora za pohranu. U suprotnom ažuriranje možda neće uspjeti. (Idite u Postavke > Pohrana da to provjerite.)
3. Neke aplikacije treće strane možda neće biti kompatibilne s MagicOS-om 7.1 i možda neće pravilno raditi nakon ažuriranja (mogu padati, kasniti, prekomjerno trošiti napajanje). Ažurirajte aplikacije na najnoviju verziju u aplikaciji AppGallery. Ako se problem ne otkloni, pričekajte naredna ažuriranja aplikacija.
4. Sistem će nakon ažuriranja prilagoditi svoje postavke kako bi se optimizacije primijenile. Za to vrijeme se telefon može zagrijati, brzo trošiti bateriju, kasniti ili se sporije puniti. Vratit će se u normalno stanje nakon 2–3 dana upotrebe. Kada se ažuriranje završi, a prije ponovnog pokretanja telefona, preporučujemo da ga punite s ugašenim ekranom 1-2 sata kako bi se optimizacije primijenile.
5. Ako tokom ažuriranja dođe do bilo kakvog problema, možete dobiti pomoć ako pozovete HONOR liniju korisničke podrške ili odete u HONOR servisni centar za korisnike.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolguts usuaris, aquesta actualització us presenta el nou MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. El nou sistema és més fluid, més segur, més fàcil d'utilitzar, amb més estalvi d'energia i la pantalla inicial més divertida. Us recomanem que feu l'actualització. Estigueu atents a les properes actualitzacions de versions per desbloquejar més funcions.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Exploració de la pantalla inicial">
<feature>【Icones de la pantalla inicial】La mida de les icones de la pantalla inicial pot ajustar-se per satisfer les diferents necessitats dels usuaris. Per provar-ho, aneu a: Configuració -> Pantalla inicial i estil -> Configuració de la pantalla inicial -> Mida de la icona.</feature>
<feature>【Extensor d'aplicacions】 Ara podeu habilitar l'Extensor d'aplicacions amb un sol gest. Arrossegueu la part inferior cap a l'extrem superior esquerre i, a continuació, toqueu l'altra aplicació que admet l'Extensor d'aplicacions per mostrar les aplicacions en finestres dobles.</feature>
<feature>【Finestra flotant】 La minifinestra es pot moure i traslladar a qualsevol posició de la pantalla inicial.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Aquesta actualització no esborrarà les dades personals però, tot i això, és recomanable que abans feu una còpia de seguretat de les dades.
2. El telèfon ha de tenir més de 10 GB d'emmagatzematge lliure. Si no, l'actualització podria fallar (podeu comprovar-ho a Configuració > Emmagatzematge).
3. Pot ser que algunes aplicacions de tercers no siguin compatibles amb MagicOS 7.1 i deixin de funcionar correctament després de l'actualització (es poden penjar, patir retard o tenir un consum d'energia anòmal). Actualitzeu les aplicacions a l'AppGallery. Si els problemes continuen, espereu-vos a futures actualitzacions de les aplicacions.
4. Quan s'hagi actualitzat, el sistema ajustarà la configuració per aplicar les optimitzacions. Durant el procés, pot ser que s'escalfi, consumeixi energia amb rapidesa, mostri retards o es carregui lentament, però tornarà a l'estat normal després de 2-3 dies d'ús. Quan s'hagi completat l'actualització i abans de reiniciar el telèfon, es recomana carregar-lo amb la pantalla apagada durant 1~2 hores per garantir que les optimitzacions s'apliquin.
5. Si us trobeu amb cap problema durant l'ús, podeu demanar-nos ajuda trucant a la línia directa d'atenció d'HONOR o anant al lloc web del Centre de serveis d'atenció al client d'HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážení uživatelé, tato aktualizace přináší zcela nový MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Nový systém je plynulejší, bezpečnější, snadněji se používá, šetří energii a domovská obrazovka je zábavnější. Doporučujeme provést aktualizaci. Očekávejte nadcházející aktualizace verze, abyste odemkli další funkce.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nová domovská obrazovka">
<feature>【Ikony na domovské obrazovce】Velikost ikon na domovské obrazovce lze upravit tak, aby vyhovovaly různým potřebám uživatelů. Můžete si to vyzkoušet tak, že přejdete na: Nastavení -> Domovská obrazovka a styl -> Nastavení domovské obrazovky -> Velikost ikony.</feature>
<feature>【Rozšíření aplikace】 Nyní můžete Rozšíření aplikace zapnout jediným gestem. Přetáhněte spodní část do levého horního rohu a potom klepněte na jinou aplikaci podporující Rozšíření aplikace, aby se aplikace zobrazily ve dvou oknech.</feature>
<feature>【Plovoucí okno】 Mini okno lze přesunout a umístit na libovolnou pozici na domovské obrazovce.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tato aktualizace nevymaže vaše osobní údaje, ale přesto se doporučuje je předem zálohovat.
2. Ujistěte se, že v telefonu máte více než 10 GB volného místa v úložišti. V opačném případě může aktualizace selhat (přejděte do Nastavení > Úložiště a zkontrolujte velikost).
3. Některé aplikace třetích stran nemusejí být kompatibilní se systémem MagicOS 8.0 a po aktualizaci mohou fungovat nesprávně (například selhání, prodlevy, neobvyklá spotřeba energie). Aktualizujte své aplikace na nejnovější verzi v AppGallery. Pokud problémy přetrvávají, počkejte na nadcházející aktualizace aplikace.
4. Po aktualizaci systém upraví svá nastavení tak, aby byly použity optimalizace. Telefon se přitom může zahřívat, rychle vybíjet baterii, zpomalit se nebo se pomalu nabíjet. Za 2 až 3 dny používání se však vše vrátí do normálu. Po dokončení aktualizace a před restartováním telefonu doporučujeme nabíjet telefon s vypnutou obrazovkou po dobu 1–2 hodin, aby se zajistilo použití optimalizací.
5. Pokud během aktualizace narazíte na nějaké problémy, zavolejte na zákaznickou linku HONOR nebo navštivte Centrum služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære brugere, denne opdatering har lanceret den helt nye MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 til dig. Det nye system er mere jævnt, sikrere, nemmere at bruge, mere strømbesparende, og hjemskærmen er sjovere. Vi anbefaler, at du opdaterer. Hold øje med kommende versionsopdateringer for at låse op for flere funktioner.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gå på opdagelse på hjemskærmen">
<feature>【Startskærmens ikoner】Størrelsen på Startskærmens ikoner kan justeres, så de imødekommer brugernes forskellige behov. Du kan opleve det ved at gå til: Indstillinger -> Startskærm og stil -> Indstillinger for startskærm -> Ikonstørrelse.</feature>
<feature>【App Extender】 Du kan nu aktivere App Extender med en enkelt gestus. Træk den nederste kant til øverste venstre hjørne, og tryk på den anden app, som understøtter App Extender, for at vise apps i dobbeltvindue.</feature>
<feature>【Flydende vindue】 Minivinduet kan flyttes og svæve over enhver position på startskærmen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bemærkninger:" type="end">
<feature>1. Denne opdatering sletter ikke dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadig at tage en sikkerhedskopi på forhånd.
2. Sørg for, at din telefon har mere end 10 GB ledig lagerplads. Ellers kan opdateringen mislykkes (gå til Indstillinger > Lager for at kontrollere det).
3. Nogle tredjeparts-apps er muligvis ikke kompatible med MagicOS 8.0 og kan fungere dårligt efter opdateringen (for eksempel nedbrud, forsinkelse, unormalt strømforbrug). Opdater dine apps til den nyeste version i AppGallery. Hvis problemet fortsætter, skal du vente på kommende appopdateringer.
4. Efter opdateringen vil systemet justere sine indstillingerne for at aktivere optimeringerne. Telefonen vil i processen blive varm, forbruge strøm hurtigt, lagge eller oplades langsomt. Men den vender tilbage til normal tilstand efter 2-3 dages brug. Når opdateringen er udført, og inden du genstarter telefonen, anbefaler vi at oplade den med skærmen slukket i 1-2 timer for at sikre, at optimeringerne aktiveres.
5. Hvis du oplever eventuelle problemer under opdateringen, kan du få vores hjælp ved at ringe til HONOR's servicehotline eller besøge HONOR's kundeservicecenter.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, in dieser Aktualisierung wird für Sie das brandneue MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 eingeführt. Das neue System funktioniert reibungsloser, ist sicherer, benutzerfreundlicher, stromsparender und der Startbildschirm ist unterhaltsamer gestaltet. Wir empfehlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen. Informieren Sie sich regelmäßig über zukünftige Versionsaktualisierungen, um in den Genuss von noch mehr Funktionen zu kommen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Startbildschirm erkunden">
<feature>【Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm】Die Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm kann an die unterschiedlichen Bedürfnisse der Nutzer angepasst werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Einstellungen -> Startbildschirm und Stil -> Startbildschirmeinstellungen -> Symbolgröße.</feature>
<feature>【App-Extender】 Sie können App-Extender jetzt mit einer Geste aktivieren. Ziehen Sie den unteren Rand in die obere linke Ecke und tippen Sie dann auf die andere App, die App-Extender unterstützt, um Apps in zwei Fenstern anzuzeigen.</feature>
<feature>【Unverankertes Fenster】 Das Minifenster kann verschoben und an einer beliebige Position auf dem Startbildschirm platziert werden.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bei dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch empfohlen, die Daten vorher zu sichern.
2. Stellen Sie sicher, dass Ihr Telefon über mehr als 10 GB an freiem Speicherplatz verfügt. Andernfalls kann die Aktualisierung fehlschlagen (Sie können dies unter Einstellungen > Speicher überprüfen).
3. Einige Drittanbieter-Apps sind möglicherweise nicht mit MagicOS 7.1 kompatibel und funktionieren u. U. nach der Aktualisierung nicht (sie stürzen beispielsweise ab, reagieren mit Verzögerung oder verbrauchen ungewöhnlich viel Strom). Aktualisieren Sie Ihre Apps in AppGallery auf die neuste Version. Wenn das Problem weiter besteht, warten Sie auf bevorstehende App-Aktualisierungen.
4. Nach der Aktualisierung passt das System seine Einstellungen an, um die Optimierungen anzuwenden. Bei diesem Vorgang kann sich das Telefon erwärmen, schnell Strom verbrauchen, verzögert reagieren oder langsam aufgeladen werden. Nach 2–3 Tagen Nutzung funktioniert es jedoch wieder normal. Nach der Aktualisierung und vor dem Neustart des Telefons wird empfohlen, dieses mit ausgeschaltetem Bildschirm 1–2 Stunden aufzuladen, um sicherzustellen, dass die Optimierungen angewendet werden.
5. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Kundenhotline von HONOR an oder besuchen Sie das Kundenservice-Center von HONOR, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, in dieser Aktualisierung wird für Sie das brandneue MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 eingeführt. Das neue System funktioniert reibungsloser, ist sicherer, benutzerfreundlicher, stromsparender und der Startbildschirm ist unterhaltsamer gestaltet. Wir empfehlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen. Informieren Sie sich regelmäßig über zukünftige Versionsaktualisierungen, um in den Genuss von noch mehr Funktionen zu kommen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Startbildschirm erkunden">
<feature>【Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm】Die Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm kann an die unterschiedlichen Bedürfnisse der Nutzer angepasst werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Einstellungen -> Startbildschirm und Stil -> Startbildschirmeinstellungen -> Symbolgröße.</feature>
<feature>【App-Extender】 Sie können App-Extender jetzt mit einer Geste aktivieren. Ziehen Sie den unteren Rand in die obere linke Ecke und tippen Sie dann auf die andere App, die App-Extender unterstützt, um Apps in zwei Fenstern anzuzeigen.</feature>
<feature>【Unverankertes Fenster】 Das Minifenster kann verschoben und an einer beliebige Position auf dem Startbildschirm platziert werden.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bei dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch empfohlen, die Daten vorher zu sichern.
2. Stellen Sie sicher, dass Ihr Telefon über mehr als 10 GB an freiem Speicherplatz verfügt. Andernfalls kann die Aktualisierung fehlschlagen (Sie können dies unter Einstellungen > Speicher überprüfen).
3. Einige Drittanbieter-Apps sind möglicherweise nicht mit MagicOS 7.1 kompatibel und funktionieren u. U. nach der Aktualisierung nicht (sie stürzen beispielsweise ab, reagieren mit Verzögerung oder verbrauchen ungewöhnlich viel Strom). Aktualisieren Sie Ihre Apps in AppGallery auf die neuste Version. Wenn das Problem weiter besteht, warten Sie auf bevorstehende App-Aktualisierungen.
4. Nach der Aktualisierung passt das System seine Einstellungen an, um die Optimierungen anzuwenden. Bei diesem Vorgang kann sich das Telefon erwärmen, schnell Strom verbrauchen, verzögert reagieren oder langsam aufgeladen werden. Nach 2–3 Tagen Nutzung funktioniert es jedoch wieder normal. Nach der Aktualisierung und vor dem Neustart des Telefons wird empfohlen, dieses mit ausgeschaltetem Bildschirm 1–2 Stunden aufzuladen, um sicherzustellen, dass die Optimierungen angewendet werden.
5. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Kundenhotline von HONOR an oder besuchen Sie das Kundenservice-Center von HONOR, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, in dieser Aktualisierung wird für Sie das brandneue MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 eingeführt. Das neue System funktioniert reibungsloser, ist sicherer, benutzerfreundlicher, stromsparender und der Startbildschirm ist unterhaltsamer gestaltet. Wir empfehlen, die Aktualisierung durchzuführen. Informieren Sie sich regelmäßig über zukünftige Versionsaktualisierungen, um in den Genuss von noch mehr Funktionen zu kommen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Startbildschirm erkunden">
<feature>【Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm】Die Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm kann an die unterschiedlichen Bedürfnisse der Nutzer angepasst werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Einstellungen -> Startbildschirm und Stil -> Startbildschirmeinstellungen -> Symbolgröße.</feature>
<feature>【App-Extender】 Sie können App-Extender jetzt mit einer Geste aktivieren. Ziehen Sie den unteren Rand in die obere linke Ecke und tippen Sie dann auf die andere App, die App-Extender unterstützt, um Apps in zwei Fenstern anzuzeigen.</feature>
<feature>【Unverankertes Fenster】 Das Minifenster kann verschoben und an einer beliebige Position auf dem Startbildschirm platziert werden.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bei dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch empfohlen, die Daten vorher zu sichern.
2. Stellen Sie sicher, dass Ihr Telefon über mehr als 10 GB an freiem Speicherplatz verfügt. Andernfalls kann die Aktualisierung fehlschlagen (Sie können dies unter Einstellungen > Speicher überprüfen).
3. Einige Drittanbieter-Apps sind möglicherweise nicht mit MagicOS 7.1 kompatibel und funktionieren u. U. nach der Aktualisierung nicht (sie stürzen beispielsweise ab, reagieren mit Verzögerung oder verbrauchen ungewöhnlich viel Strom). Aktualisieren Sie Ihre Apps in AppGallery auf die neuste Version. Wenn das Problem weiter besteht, warten Sie auf bevorstehende App-Aktualisierungen.
4. Nach der Aktualisierung passt das System seine Einstellungen an, um die Optimierungen anzuwenden. Bei diesem Vorgang kann sich das Telefon erwärmen, schnell Strom verbrauchen, verzögert reagieren oder langsam aufgeladen werden. Nach 2–3 Tagen Nutzung funktioniert es jedoch wieder normal. Nach der Aktualisierung und vor dem Neustart des Telefons wird empfohlen, dieses mit ausgeschaltetem Bildschirm 1–2 Stunden aufzuladen, um sicherzustellen, dass die Optimierungen angewendet werden.
5. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die Kundenhotline von HONOR an oder besuchen Sie das Kundenservice-Center von HONOR, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητοί χρήστες, αυτή η ενημέρωση κυκλοφόρησε για εσάς το ολοκαίνουργιο MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Το νέο σύστημα είναι πιο ομαλό, πιο ασφαλές, ευκολότερο στη χρήση, εξοικονομεί περισσότερη ενέργεια και η αρχική οθόνη είναι πιο διασκεδαστική. Σας συνιστούμε να ενημερώσετε. Μείνετε συντονισμένοι για τις επερχόμενες ενημερώσεις έκδοσης για να ξεκλειδώσετε περισσότερες δυνατότητες.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Εξερευνήστε την αρχική οθόνη">
<feature>【Εικονίδια αρχικής οθόνης】Το μέγεθος των εικονιδίων της αρχικής οθόνης μπορεί να προσαρμοστεί για να ανταποκρίνεται στις διαφορετικές ανάγκες των χρηστών. Μπορείτε να δοκιμάσετε αυτή τη λειτουργία μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις -> Αρχική οθόνη και στυλ -> Ρυθμίσεις αρχικής οθόνης -> Μέγεθος εικονιδίου.</feature>
<feature>【Επέκταση εφαρμογών】 Τώρα μπορείτε να ενεργοποιήσετε την Επέκταση εφαρμογών με μία μόνο κίνηση. Σύρετε το κάτω μέρος στην επάνω αριστερή γωνία και, στη συνέχεια, πατήστε την άλλη εφαρμογή που υποστηρίζει την Επέκταση εφαρμογών για να εμφανίσετε εφαρμογές σε δύο παράθυρα.</feature>
<feature>【Αιωρούμενο παράθυρο】 Το μικρό παράθυρο μπορεί να μετακινηθεί και να τοποθετηθεί σε οποιαδήποτε θέση στην αρχική οθόνη.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Αυτή η ενημέρωση δεν θα διαγράψει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, ωστόσο συνιστάται να δημιουργήσετε προηγουμένως ένα αντίγραφο ασφαλείας.
2. Βεβαιωθείτε ότι το τηλέφωνό σας έχει περισσότερα από 10 GB ελεύθερου χώρου αποθήκευσης. Διαφορετικά, η ενημέρωση ενδέχεται να αποτύχει (Μεταβείτε στις Ρυθμίσεις > Αποθηκευτικός χώρος για να την ελέγξετε).
3. Ορισμένες εφαρμογές τρίτων ενδέχεται να μην είναι συμβατές με το MagicOS 8.0 και ενδέχεται να παρουσιάσουν δυσλειτουργία μετά την ενημέρωση (όπως κατάρρευση, καθυστέρηση, μη φυσιολογική κατανάλωση ενέργειας). Ενημερώστε τις εφαρμογές σας στην πιο πρόσφατη έκδοση στο AppGallery. Εάν τα προβλήματα παραμένουν, περιμένετε τις επερχόμενες ενημερώσεις εφαρμογών.
4. Μετά την ενημέρωση, το σύστημα θα προσαρμόσει τις ρυθμίσεις του για να εφαρμόσει τις βελτιστοποιήσεις. Κατά την εκτέλεση της διαδικασίας, το τηλέφωνο μπορεί να ζεσταίνεται, να καταναλώνει ισχύ γρήγορα, να καθυστερεί ή να φορτίζει αργά. Ωστόσο, θα επανέλθει στη φυσιολογική λειτουργία του μέσα σε 2-3 ημέρες χρήσης. Μετά την ολοκλήρωση της ενημέρωσης και πριν από την επανεκκίνηση του τηλεφώνου, συνιστούμε να το φορτίσετε με απενεργοποιημένη την οθόνη για 1~2 ώρες, για να βεβαιωθείτε ότι εφαρμόστηκαν οι βελτιστοποιήσεις.
5. Αν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, μπορείτε να λάβετε τη βοήθειά μας καλώντας την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή εξυπηρέτησης της HONOR ή με επίσκεψη σε ένα κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear users, this update has launched brand-new MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 for you. The new system is smoother, safer, easier to use, more power-saving, and the home screen is more fun. We recommend you to update. Please stay tuned for upcoming version updates to unlock more features.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Explore the home screen">
<feature>【Home screen icons】The size of Home screen icons can be adjusted to meet the users' different needs. You can experience it by going to: Settings -> Home screen and style -> Home screen settings -> Icon size.</feature>
<feature>【App Extender】 You can now enable App Extender with a single gesture. Drag the bottom to the upper left corner, and then tap the other app supporting App Extender to display apps in dual windows.</feature>
<feature>【Floating window】 Mini window can be moved and hovered to any position on the home screen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. This update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. Make sure your phone has more than 10 GB of free storage space. Otherwise, the update may fail (Go to Settings > Storage to check it).
3. Some third-party apps may not be compatible with MagicOS 8.0 and may malfunction after the update (such as crash, lag, abnormal power consumption). Please update your apps to the latest version in AppGallery. If the problems persist, please wait for upcoming app updates.
4. After updating, the system will adjust its settings to apply the optimizations. In the process, the phone may become hot, consume power fast, lag, or charge slowly. But it will return to normal in 2-3 days of use. After the update is done and before restarting the phone, we recommend charging it with the screen off for 1~2 hours to ensure the optimizations are applied.
5. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling HONOR service hotline or visiting HONOR Customer Service Center.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimados usuarios: esta actualización ha lanzado el nuevo MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 para ustedes. El nuevo sistema es más fluido, seguro, fácil de usar, ahorra más energía y la pantalla principal es más divertida. Le recomendamos que actualice. Esté atento a las próximas actualizaciones de la versión para descubrir más funciones.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Explorar la pantalla principal">
<feature>【Iconos de la pantalla principal】El tamaño de los iconos de la pantalla principal se puede ajustar para satisfacer las diferentes necesidades de los usuarios. Puede experimentarlo si va a: Ajustes -> Pantalla principal y estilo -> Ajustes pantalla principal -> Tamaño de icono.</feature>
<feature>【Extensor de aplicaciones】 Ahora puede habilitar el Extensor de aplicaciones con un solo gesto. Arrastre la parte inferior hacia la esquina superior izquierda y luego toque la otra aplicación que admita Extensor de aplicaciones para mostrar aplicaciones en ventanas duales.</feature>
<feature>【Ventana flotante】 La miniventana se puede mover y colocar sobre cualquier posición en la pantalla principal.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Esta actualización no eliminará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad antes.
2. Asegúrese de que su teléfono tenga más de 10 GB de espacio de almacenamiento gratuito. De lo contrario, la actualización puede fallar (Vaya a Ajustes > Almacenamiento para comprobarlo).
3. Algunas aplicaciones de terceros pueden no ser compatibles con MagicOS 8.0 y pueden funcionar mal después de la actualización (como generación de errores, retrasos, consumo de energía anormal). Actualice sus aplicaciones a la última versión en AppGallery. Si los problemas persisten, espere las próximas actualizaciones de la aplicación.
4. Después de la actualización, el sistema modificará los ajustes para aplicar las optimizaciones. En el proceso, el teléfono puede calentarse, consumir energía rápidamente, retrasarse o cargarse lentamente. Pero volverá a la normalidad en 2-3 días de uso. Una vez finalizada la actualización y antes de reiniciar el teléfono, recomendamos cargarlo con la pantalla apagada durante 1 o 2 horas para garantizar que se apliquen las optimizaciones.
5. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, puede obtener nuestra ayuda llamando a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visitando el Centro de servicios de atención al cliente de HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimados usuarios: esta actualización ha lanzado el nuevo MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 para ustedes. El nuevo sistema es más fluido, seguro, fácil de usar, ahorra más energía y la pantalla principal es más divertida. Le recomendamos que actualice. Esté atento a las próximas actualizaciones de la versión para descubrir más funcionalidades.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Explorar la pantalla principal">
<feature>【Íconos de la pantalla principal】 El tamaño de los íconos de la pantalla principal se puede ajustar para satisfacer las diferentes necesidades de los usuarios. Para realizar este cambio, vaya a Ajustes -> Pantalla principal y estilo -> Ajustes de pantalla principal -> Tamaño de ícono.</feature>
<feature>【Extensor de aplicaciones】 Ahora puede habilitar el Extensor de aplicaciones con un solo gesto. Arrastre la parte inferior hacia la esquina superior izquierda y luego presione la otra aplicación que admita el Extensor de aplicaciones para mostrar aplicaciones en ventanas duales.</feature>
<feature>【Ventana flotante】 La miniventana se puede mover y colocar sobre cualquier posición en la pantalla principal.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Esta actualización no eliminará sus datos personales; sin embargo, le recomendamos hacer una copia de respaldo de los datos antes de actualizar.
2. Asegúrese de que su teléfono tenga más de 10 GB de espacio de almacenamiento gratuito. De lo contrario, la actualización puede fallar (vaya a Ajustes > Almacenamiento para comprobarlo).
3. Algunas aplicaciones de terceros pueden no ser compatibles con MagicOS 8.0 y es posible que funcionen mal después de la actualización (como fallas, lentitud, consumo de energía anormal). Actualice las aplicaciones a la versión más reciente en AppGallery. Si los problemas persisten, espere las próximas actualizaciones de la aplicación.
4. Después de la actualización, el sistema ajustará su configuración para aplicar las optimizaciones. Durante el proceso, el teléfono puede calentarse, consumir energía de forma rápida, funcionar lento o cargarse lentamente. Sin embargo, volverá a la normalidad en 2 o 3 días de uso. Una vez finalizada la actualización y antes de reiniciar el teléfono, se recomienda cargarlo con la pantalla apagada durante 1 o 2 horas para garantizar que se apliquen las optimizaciones.
5. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, puede llamar a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visitar el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Head kasutajad! See värskendus toob turule uhiuue operatsioonisüsteemi MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Uus süsteem on sujuvam, turvalisem, hõlpsamini kasutatav, energiasäästlikum ja mugavama avakuvaga. Soovitame teil värskendada. Olge kursis tulevaste versioonivärskendustega, et saada juurdepääs rohkematele funktsioone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Avakuvaga tutvumine">
<feature>【Avakuva ikoonid】Avakuva ikoonide suurust saab kohandada vastavalt kasutajate vajadustele. Selle funktsiooni kasutamiseks avage Sätted -> Avakuva ja stiil -> Avakuva sätted -> Ikooni suurus.</feature>
<feature>【Rakendusekordisti】 Nüüd saate rakendusekordisti lubada ühe liigutusega. Lohistage alumine osa vasakusse ülanurka ja seejärel puudutage teist rakendust, mis toetab rakendusekordistit, et kuvada rakendused kahes aknas.</feature>
<feature>【Ujuv aken】 Miniakent saab liigutada ja hõljutada mis tahes kohta avaekraanil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. See värskendus ei kustuta teie isikuandmeid, kuid soovitatav on siiski eelnevalt varundada.
2. Veenduge, et teie telefonil oleks rohkem kui 10 GB vaba mälu. Vastasel korral võib värskendamine nurjuda (selle kontrollimiseks avage Sätted > Mälu).
3. Mõned muude tootjate rakendused ei pruugi MagicOS 8.0-ga ühilduda ja võivad pärast värskendamist tõrkuda (nt kokkujooksmine, viivitus, ebatavaline energiatarve). Värskendage oma rakendused AppGallerys uusimale versioonile. Kui probleemid püsivad, oodake tulevasi rakenduste värskendusi.
4. Pärast värskendamist kohandab süsteem optimeerimiseks oma sätteid. Selle käigus võib telefon kuumeneda, kiiresti energiat tarbida, viivitada või aeglaselt laadida. Kuid see normaliseerub 2-3 päeva jooksul pärast kasutamist. Pärast värskendamise lõpetamist ja enne telefoni taaskäivitamist soovitame seda väljalülitatud ekraaniga 1–2 tundi laadida, et tagada optimeerimine.
5. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, saate meie abi, helistades HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või külastades HONORi teeninduskeskust.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile horiek, eguneratze honetan MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 berria kaleratu da zuretzat. Sistema berri hau arinagoa, seguruagoa eta erabilerrazagoa da, bateria gehiago aurrezten du eta hasierako pantaila dibertigarriagoa dauka. Eguneratzea gomendatzen dizugu. Eginbide gehiago ezagutzeko, egon adi datozen bertsio-eguneratzeei.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Arakatu hasierako pantaila">
<feature>【Hasierako pantailako ikonoak】Erabiltzaileen beharrak betetze aldera, hasierako pantailako ikonoen tamaina egokitu daiteke. Egokitzeko, joan Ezarpenak -> Hasierako pantaila eta estiloa -> Hasierako pantailako ezarpenak -> Ikonoen tamaina atalera.</feature>
<feature>【Aplikazio-hedatzailea】 Orain Aplikazio-hedatzailea keinu bakar batekin gai dezakezu. Arrastatu behealdetik goi-ezkerreko izkinara eta, ondoren, sakatu Aplikazio-hedatzailea onartzen duen beste aplikazio bat, aplikazioak leiho dualetan bistaratzeko.</feature>
<feature>【Leiho flotatzailea】 Leiho txikia hasierako pantailako edozein posiziotara mugitu eta haren gainetik pasa daiteke.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze honek ez ditu ezabatuko zure datu pertsonalak, baina babeskopia bat aurretik egitea gomendatzen da hala ere.
2. Ziurtatu telefonoak 10 GB baino gehiago dituela libre biltegian. Bestela, baliteke eguneratzeak huts egitea (joan Ezarpenak > Biltegia atalera, aukera hau egiaztatzeko).
3. Baliteke hirugarrenen aplikazio batzuk MagicOS 8.0-ekin bateragarriak ez izatea eta ez funtzionatzea eguneratzearen ondoren (adibidez, huts egitea, atzerapenak izatea edo ohi baino gehiagoko bateria kontsumitzea). Eguneratu aplikazioak azken bertsiora AppGallery-n. Arazoak badirau, itxaron hurrengo aplikazio-eguneratzeak kaleratu argitaratu arte.
4. Eguneratu ostean, sistemak optimizazioak aplikatzeko doituko ditu ezarpenak. Prozesuan, baliteke telefonoa berotzea, bateria bizkor kontsumitzea, atzerapenak izatea, edo motel kargatzea. Baina 2-3 egunez erabili ondoren normalduko da funtzionamendua. Eguneratu ostean eta telefonoa berrabiarazi aurretik, gomendagarria da 1~2 orduz kargatzea pantaila itzalita dagoela, optimizazioak aplikatu direla ziurtatzeko.
5. Eguneratu bitartean arazoren bat topatzen baduzu, HONOR-en zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara deituta edo HONOR-en bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora joanda eska diezagukezu laguntza.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>کاربران گرامی، در این به‌روزرسانی نسخه جدید MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 راه‌اندازی شده است. سیستم جدید روان‌تر، ایمن‌تر، با استفاده آسان‌تر، صرفه‌جویی بیشتر در مصرف انرژی و دارای صفحۀ اصلی جذاب‌تر است. توصیه می‌کنیم به‌روزرسانی کنید. لطفاً منتظر به‌روزرسانی نسخه‌های آتی برای ارائه قابلیت‌های بیشتر باشید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="کاوش در صفحۀ اصلی">
<feature>‏【آیکون‌های «صفحۀ اصلی»】اندازه آیکون‌های «صفحۀ اصلی» را می‌توان برای برآوردن نیازهای مختلف کاربران تنظیم کرد. می‌توانید آن را با رفتن به این قسمت تجربه کنید: تنظیمات -> صفحۀ اصلی و سبک -> تنظیمات صفحۀ اصلی -> اندازۀ آیکون.</feature>
<feature>‏【برنامه‌‌گستر】 اکنون می‌توانید «برنامه‌گستر» را با یک فرمان حرکتی فعال کنید. انگشتتان را از قسمت پایین به گوشه بالا سمت چپ بکشید و سپس روی برنامه دیگری که از «برنامه‌گستر» پشتیبانی می‌کند ضربه بزنید تا برنامه‌ها در دو پنجره نمایش داده شوند.</feature>
<feature>‏【پنجرۀ شناور】 پنجرۀ کوچک را می‌توان به هر موقعیتی در صفحۀ اصلی منتقل کرد و نگه داشت.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏نکات:" type="end">
<feature>‏۱. این به‌روزرسانی داده‌های شخصی شما را پاک نخواهد کرد، اما کماکان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام این کار از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.‎
‏‏۲. مطمئن شوید که تلفن شما بیش از ۱۰ گیگابایت فضای آزاد دارد. درغیراین‌صورت، ممکن است به‌روزرسانی انجام نشود. (برای بررسی آن، به «تنظیمات > محل ذخیره» بروید.)‎
‏‏۳. برخی از برنامه‌های شخص ثالث ممکن است با MagicOS 8.0 سازگار نباشند و ممکن است پس از به‌روزرسانی درست کار نکنند (اختلال‌هایی از قبیل از کار افتادن، تأخیر، مصرف نیروی غیرعادی). لطفاً برنامه‌های خود را در AppGallery به جدیدترین نسخه به‌روزرسانی کنید. اگر مشکلات برطرف نشد، لطفاً منتظر به‌روزرسانی‌های بعدی برنامه باشید.‎
‏‏۴. پس از به‌روزرسانی، سیستم به‌منظور اعمال بهینه‌سازی‌ها تنظیمات خود را تغییر می‌دهد. در این فرایند، ممکن است تلفن داغ شود، مصرف نیروی آن افزایش یابد، تأخیر داشته باشد یا سرعت شارژ شدن آن کاهش یابد. اما بعد از ۳-۲ روز استفاده به وضعیت عادی بازمی‌گردد. برای اطمینان از اعمال بهینه‌سازی‌ها، توصیه می‌کنیم پس از انجام به‌روزرسانی و قبل از راه‌اندازی مجدد تلفن، آن را با صفحۀ نمایش خاموش به‌مدت ۱ تا ۲ ساعت شارژ کنید.‎
‏‏۵. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، می‌توانید با تماس با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR یا مراجعه به «مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR» از ما کمک بگیرید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä päivitys on ottanut sinulle käyttöön täysin uuden MagicOS 8.0:n|Android 14:n. Uusi järjestelmä on tasaisempi, turvallisempi, helppokäyttöisempi ja virtaa säästävämpi, ja sen aloitusnäyttö on hauskempi. Suosittelemme päivitystä. Seuraa tulevia versiopäivityksiä, jotta saat käyttöösi lisää ominaisuuksia.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tutustu aloitusnäyttöön">
<feature>【Aloitusnäytön kuvakkeet】Aloitusnäytön kuvakkeiden kokoa voi säätää käyttäjän tarpeen mukaan. Voit ottaa sen käyttöön kohdasta: Asetukset -> Aloitusnäyttö ja tyyli -> Aloitusnäytön asetukset -> Kuvakkeen koko.</feature>
<feature>【Sovelluksen laajennin】 Nyt voit ottaa Sovelluksen laajentimen käyttöön yhdellä eleellä. Vedä alaosa vasempaan yläkulmaan ja napauta sitten toista Sovelluksen laajenninta tukevaa sovellusta, niin sovellukset näytetään kaksoisikkunoissa.</feature>
<feature>【Kelluva ikkuna】 Mini-ikkuna voidaan siirtää ja kohdistaa mihin tahansa kohtaan aloitusnäytöllä.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämä päivitys ei poista henkilökohtaisia tietojasi, mutta ne on suositeltavaa varmuuskopioida etukäteen.
2. Varmista, että puhelimessa on yli 10 Gt vapaata tallennustilaa. Muutoin päivitys voi epäonnistua (tarkista tämä kohdasta Asetukset > Tallennustila).
3. Jotkut kolmannen osapuolen sovellukset eivät ehkä ole yhteensopivia MagicOS 8.0:n kanssa, ja niissä voi ilmetä päivityksen jälkeen toimintahäiriö (kuten kaatuminen, viive tai epänormaali virrankulutus). Päivitä sovelluksesi uusimpaan versioon AppGalleryssä. Jos ongelma ei poistu, odota tulevia sovelluspäivityksiä.
4. Päivityksen jälkeen järjestelmä säätää asetuksiaan optimointien käyttöönottoa varten. Tässä prosessissa puhelin voi kuumeta, kuluttaa virtaa nopeasti, toimia viiveellä tai ladata hitaasti. Mutta tämä palautuu normaaliksi 2–3 käyttöpäivän jälkeen. Kun päivitys on tehty, puhelinta on suositeltavaa ladata ennen sen uudelleenkäynnistystä näyttö sammutettuna 1–2 tunnin ajan, jotta optimoinnit otetaan varmasti käyttöön.
5. Jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia, voit pyytää apua soittamalla HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käymällä HONOR-huoltoliikkeessä.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Chers utilisateurs, cette mise à jour a lancé pour vous le tout nouveau MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Le nouveau système est plus fluide, plus sûr, plus facile à utiliser, plus économe en énergie et l'écran d'accueil est plus amusant. Nous vous recommandons d'effectuer la mise à jour. Suivez-nous pour rester informés des prochaines mises à jour de version pour débloquer plus de fonctionnalités.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Découvrez l'écran d'accueil">
<feature>【Icônes de l'écran d'accueil】La taille des icônes de l'écran d'accueil peut être ajustée pour répondre aux différents besoins de l'utilisateur. Vous pouvez en faire l'expérience en allant dans : Paramètres -> Écran d'accueil et style -> Paramètres de l'écran d'accueil -> Taille de l'icône.</feature>
<feature>【Extension d'application】 Vous pouvez désormais activer l'Extension d'application d'un seul geste. Faites glisser le bas vers le coin supérieur gauche, puis appuyez sur l'autre application prenant en charge l'Extension d'application pour afficher les applications dans deux fenêtres.</feature>
<feature>【Fenêtre flottante】 La mini-fenêtre peut être déplacée et survolée vers n'importe quelle position sur l'écran d'accueil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'effacera pas vos données personnelles, mais une sauvegarde préalable est toujours recommandée.
2. Assurez-vous que votre téléphone dispose de plus de 10 Go d'espace de stockage disponible. Sinon, la mise à jour peut échouer (Accédez à Paramètres > Stockage pour le vérifier).
3. Certaines applications tierces peuvent ne pas être compatibles avec MagicOS 7.1 et peuvent mal fonctionner après la mise à jour (par exemple, plantage, décalage, consommation d'énergie anormale). Veuillez mettre à jour vos applications vers la dernière version dans AppGallery. Si les problèmes persistent, veuillez attendre les prochaines mises à jour de l'application.
4. Après la mise à jour, le système ajustera ses paramètres pour appliquer les optimisations. Au cours du processus, le téléphone peut devenir chaud, consommer de l'énergie rapidement, ralentir ou se charger lentement. Il reviendra à la normale après 2 à 3 jours d'utilisation. Une fois la mise à jour terminée et avant de redémarrer le téléphone, nous vous recommandons de le charger avec l'écran éteint pendant 1 à 2 heures pour vous assurer que les optimisations sont appliquées.
5. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la hotline de service HONOR ou vous rendre dans un Centre de services client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Chers utilisateurs, cette mise à jour a lancé pour vous le tout nouveau MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Le nouveau système est plus fluide, plus sûr, plus facile à utiliser, plus économe en énergie et l'écran d'accueil est plus amusant. Nous vous recommandons d'effectuer la mise à jour. Suivez-nous pour rester informés des prochaines mises à jour de version pour débloquer plus de fonctionnalités.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Découvrez l'écran d'accueil">
<feature>【Icônes de l'écran d'accueil】La taille des icônes de l'écran d'accueil peut être ajustée pour répondre aux différents besoins de l'utilisateur. Vous pouvez en faire l'expérience en allant dans : Paramètres -> Écran d'accueil et style -> Paramètres de l'écran d'accueil -> Taille de l'icône.</feature>
<feature>【Extension d'application】 Vous pouvez désormais activer l'Extension d'application d'un seul geste. Faites glisser le bas vers le coin supérieur gauche, puis appuyez sur l'autre application prenant en charge l'Extension d'application pour afficher les applications dans deux fenêtres.</feature>
<feature>【Fenêtre flottante】 La mini-fenêtre peut être déplacée et survolée vers n'importe quelle position sur l'écran d'accueil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'effacera pas vos données personnelles, mais une sauvegarde préalable est toujours recommandée.
2. Assurez-vous que votre téléphone dispose de plus de 10 Go d'espace de stockage disponible. Sinon, la mise à jour peut échouer (Accédez à Paramètres > Stockage pour le vérifier).
3. Certaines applications tierces peuvent ne pas être compatibles avec MagicOS 7.1 et peuvent mal fonctionner après la mise à jour (par exemple, plantage, décalage, consommation d'énergie anormale). Veuillez mettre à jour vos applications vers la dernière version dans AppGallery. Si les problèmes persistent, veuillez attendre les prochaines mises à jour de l'application.
4. Après la mise à jour, le système ajustera ses paramètres pour appliquer les optimisations. Au cours du processus, le téléphone peut devenir chaud, consommer de l'énergie rapidement, ralentir ou se charger lentement. Il reviendra à la normale après 2 à 3 jours d'utilisation. Une fois la mise à jour terminée et avant de redémarrer le téléphone, nous vous recommandons de le charger avec l'écran éteint pendant 1 à 2 heures pour vous assurer que les optimisations sont appliquées.
5. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la hotline de service HONOR ou vous rendre dans un Centre de services client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimados usuarios, esta actualización preséntalles o novo MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. O novo sistema fornece máis fluidez, é máis seguro e fácil de usar, aforra máis enerxía e conta cunha pantalla de inicio máis divertida. Recomendámoslles que realicen a actualización. Estean ao tanto das novas actualizacións da versión para desbloquear máis funcionalidades.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Explorar a pantalla de inicio">
<feature>【Iconas da pantalla de inicio】O tamaño das iconas da pantalla de inicio pódese axustar para adaptalo ás diferentes necesidades dos usuarios. Pode probar a facelo indo a Configuración -> Pantalla de inicio e estilo -> Configuración da pantalla de inicio -> Tamaño de iconas.</feature>
<feature>【Ampliador de aplicacións】 Agora pode activar Ampliador de aplicacións cun só xesto. Arrastre a parte inferior á esquina superior esquerda e toque a outra aplicación compatible con Ampliador de aplicacións para mostrar as aplicacións en ventás dobres.</feature>
<feature>【Ventá flotante】 A miniventá pode moverse e desprazarse a calquera posición da pantalla de inicio.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Esta actualización non eliminará os seus datos persoais, pero é recomendable que antes faga unha copia de seguranza destes datos.
2. Asegúrese de que o teléfono ten máis de 10 GB de espazo de almacenamento libres. Se non os ten, pode producirse un erro na actualización. (Para comprobar o espazo de almacenamento, vaia a Configuración > Almacenamento.)
3. É posible que algunhas aplicacións de terceiros non sexan compatibles con MagicOS 7.1 e que non funcionen correctamente despois da actualización (pode producirse un bloqueo, un retardo ou un consumo anormal de enerxía). Actualice as aplicacións á versión máis recente en AppGallery. Se os problemas continúan, espere a que haxa novas actualizacións das aplicacións.
4. Despois da actualización, o sistema axustará a configuración para aplicar as optimizacións. Durante este proceso é posible que o teléfono se quente, que consuma enerxía con rapidez, que experimente retardo ou que se cargue con lentitude. Non obstante, aos 2 ou 3 días de uso volverá funcionar con normalidade. Unha vez que se produza a actualización e antes de que se reinicie o teléfono, recomendámoslle que o cargue coa pantalla apagada durante 1 ou 2 horas, para garantir que se aplican as optimizacións.
5. Se atopa algún problema durante a actualización, pode pedirnos axuda chamando á liña directa de atención ao cliente de HONOR ou visitando o Centro de servizos do cliente de HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તાઓ, આ અપડેટે તમારા માટે એકદમ નવું MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 લૉન્ચ કર્યું છે. નવી સિસ્ટમ વધુ સરળ, સુરક્ષિત, ઉપયોગમાં સરળ, વધુ પાવર-બચત કરનારી અને હોમ સ્ક્રીન વધુ મનોરંજક છે. અમે તમને અપડેટ કરવાની ભલામણ કરીએ છીએ. કૃપા કરીને વધુ સુવિધાઓને અનલૉક કરવા માટે આગામી સંસ્કરણ અપડેટ્સ માટે ટ્યુન રહો.</feature>
</features>
<features module="હોમ સ્ક્રીનનું અન્વેષણ કરો">
<feature>【હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્ન】હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્નનું કદ વપરાશકર્તાઓની વિવિધ જરૂરિયાતોને પૂરી કરવા માટે સમાયોજિત કરી શકાય છે. તમે અહીં જઈને તેનો અનુભવ કરી શકો છો: સેટિંગ્સ -> હોમ સ્ક્રીન અને શૈલી -> હોમ સ્ક્રીન સેટિંગ્સ -> ચિહ્નનું કદ.</feature>
<feature>【એપ્લિકેશન એક્સ્ટેન્ડર】 તમે હવે એક જ હાવભાવ સાથે એપ્લિકેશન એક્સ્ટેન્ડરને સક્ષમ કરી શકો છો. નીચેથી ઉપરના ડાબા ખૂણે ખેંચો અને પછી ડ્યુઅલ વિન્ડોમાં એપ્લિકેશન પ્રદર્શિત કરવા માટે એપ્લિકેશન એક્સ્ટેન્ડરને સમર્થન કરતી અન્ય એપ્લિકેશનને ટૅપ કરો.</feature>
<feature>【ફ્લોટિંગ વિન્ડો】 મીની વિન્ડોને હોમ સ્ક્રીન પર કોઈપણ સ્થાન પર ખસેડી અને હોવર કરી શકાય છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને ભૂંસી નાખશે નહીં, પરંતુ હજી પણ અગાઉથી બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. સુનિશ્ચિત કરો કે તમારા ફોનમાં 10 GB કરતાં વધુ ખાલી સંગ્રહ સ્થાન છે. નહિંતર, અપડેટ નિષ્ફળ થઈ શકે છે (તેને તપાસવા માટે સેટિંગ્સ > સંગ્રહ પર જાઓ).
3. કેટલીક તૃતીય-પક્ષ એપ્લિકેશન્સ MagicOS 8.0 સાથે સુસંગત ન હોઈ શકે અને અપડેટ પછી ખામીયુક્ત કાર્ય શકે છે (જેમ કે ક્રેશ, લેગ, અસામાન્ય પાવર વપરાશ). કૃપા કરીને તમારી એપ્લિકેશન્સને AppGallery માં નવીનતમ સંસ્કરણ પર અપડેટ કરો. જો સમસ્યાઓ ચાલુ રહે, તો કૃપા કરીને આગામી એપ્લિકેશન અપડેટ્સની રાહ જુઓ.
4. અપડેટ કર્યા પછી, ઑપ્ટિમાઇઝેશન લાગુ કરવા માટે સિસ્ટમ તેના સેટિંગ્સને સમાયોજિત કરશે. પ્રક્રિયામાં, ફોન ગરમ થઈ શકે છે, પાવરનો ઝડપી ઉપયોગ કરી શકે છે, લેગ થઈ શકે છે અથવા ધીમે ધીમે ચાર્જ થઈ શકે છે. પરંતુ ઉપયોગના 2-3 દિવસમાં તે સામાન્ય થઈ જશે. અપડેટ થઈ ગયા પછી અને ફોનને ફરી શરૂ કરતા પહેલા, ઑપ્ટિમાઇઝેશન લાગુ થાય તેની ખાતરી કરવા માટે અમે તેને 1~2 કલાક માટે સ્ક્રીન બંધ રાખીને ચાર્જ કરવાની ભલામણ કરીએ છીએ.
5. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો તમે HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરીને અથવા HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્રની મુલાકાત લઈને અમારી મદદ મેળવી શકો છો.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ताओं, इस अद्यतन में आपके लिए बिल्कुल नया MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 लॉन्च किया गया है। नया सिस्टम अधिक सुचारू, अधिक सुरक्षित, उपयोग में अधिक आसान और पावर की अधिक बचत करने वाला है और इसमें होम स्क्रीन को अधिक मज़ेदार बनाया गया है। हम आपसे अद्यतन करने की अनुशंसा करते हैं। अधिक सुविधाएँ अनलॉक करने हेतु आगामी संस्करण के अद्यतन के लिए, कृपया हमारे साथ बने रहें।</feature>
</features>
<features module="होम स्क्रीन का अन्वेषण करना">
<feature>【होम स्क्रीन के आइकन】होम स्क्रीन के आइकन का आकार उपयोगकर्ताओं की अलग-अलग आवश्यकताओं को पूरा करने के लिए समायोजित किया जा सकता है। आप यहाँ जाकर इसका अनुभव कर सकते हैं: सेटिंग्स -> होम स्क्रीन और शैली -> होम स्क्रीन सेटिंग्स -> आइकन का आकार।</feature>
<feature>【ऐप एक्सटेंडर】 अब आप एक ही जेश्चर से ऐप एक्सटेंडर को सक्षम कर सकते हैं। नीचे से ऊपरी बाएँ कोने तक खींचें और उसके बाद डुअल विंडो में ऐप्स दिखाने के लिए ऐप एक्सटेंडर का समर्थन करने वाले अन्य ऐप पर टैप करें।</feature>
<feature>【फ़्लोटिंग विंडो】 मिनी विंडो को होम स्क्रीन पर किसी भी स्थिति में ले जाया और घुमाया जा सकता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने का सुझाव दिया जाता है।
2. सुनिश्चित करें कि आपके फ़ोन में 10 GB से अधिक खाली संग्रहण स्थान है। नहीं तो, अद्यतन विफल हो सकता है (इसे जाँचने के लिए सेटिंग्स > संग्रहण पर जाएँ)।
3. कुछ तृतीय-पक्ष ऐप्स MagicOS 8.0 के साथ संगत नहीं हो सकते हैं और अद्यतन के बाद खराब हो सकते हैं (जैसे कि क्रैश, देरी, असामान्य पॉवर उपभोग)। AppGallery में जाकर अपने ऐप्स का अद्यतन नवीनतम संस्करण में करें। अगर समस्या ठीक नहीं होती है, तो आगामी ऐप अद्यतनों की प्रतीक्षा करें।
4. अद्यतन करने के बाद, सिस्टम में अनुकूलन लागू करने के लिए इसकी सेटिंग्स समायोजित हो जाएगी। प्रक्रिया में, फ़ोन गर्म हो सकता है, तेज़ी से पॉवर का उपभोग हो सकता है, देरी हो सकती है या धीरे-धीरे चार्ज हो सकता है। लेकिन, 2-3 दिनों तक उपयोग के बाद यह सामान्य हो जाएगा। अद्यतन पूरा होने के बाद और फ़ोन पुनरारंभ होने से पहले, हम यह सुनिश्चित करने के लिए 1~2 घंटे तक स्क्रीन बंद करके चार्ज करने का सुझाव देते हैं कि अनुकूलन लागू हो गए हैं।
5. अगर आपको अद्यतन के दौरान कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो आप HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करके या HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाकर हमारी सहायता पा सकते हैं।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisnici, ovim ažuriranjem dobili ste na korištenje potpuno novi sustav MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Novi sustav radi ujednačenije, sigurnije, lakši je za korištenje, više štedi energiju, a početni je zaslon zabavniji. Preporučujemo vam da instalirate ažuriranje. Pratite nadolazeća ažuriranja verzije za otključavanje više značajki.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Istraživanje početnog zaslona">
<feature>【Ikone na početnom zaslonu】Veličina ikona na početnom zaslonu može se prilagoditi različitim potrebama korisnika. Možete isprobati odlaskom na: Postavke -> Početni zaslon i stil -> Postavke početnog zaslona -> Veličina ikone.</feature>
<feature>【Ekstender aplikacija】 Sada možete omogućiti Ekstender aplikacija jednim pokretom. Povucite donji dio u gornji lijevi kut, a zatim dodirnite drugu aplikaciju koja podržava Ekstender aplikacija za prikaz aplikacija u dvostrukim prozorima.</feature>
<feature>【Plutajući prozor】 Mini prozor može se pomicati i lebdjeti na bilo kojem položaju na početnom zaslonu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bilješke:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ovo ažuriranja neće izbrisati vaše osobne podatke, ali se ipak preporučuje prethodno sigurnosno kopiranje.
2. Provjerite ima li vaš telefon više od 10 GB slobodnog prostora za pohranu. U suprotnom, ažuriranje možda neće uspjeti (Idi na Postavke > Pohranjivanje za provjeru).
3. Neke aplikacije trećih strana možda nisu kompatibilne s aplikacijom MagicOS 8.0 i mogu nepravilno raditi nakon ažuriranja (kao što je rušenje, kašnjenje, neuobičajena potrošnja energije). Ažurirajte svoje aplikacije na najnoviju verziju na platformi AppGallery. Ako se problemi nastave, pričekajte nadolazeća ažuriranja aplikacije.
4. Nakon ažuriranja, sustav će prilagoditi svoje postavke za primjenu optimizacija. Tijekom tog postupka telefon se može zagrijati, brzo trošiti energiju, kasniti ili se sporo puniti. Ali vratit će se u redovito stanje za 2 do 3 dana uporabe. Nakon završetka ažuriranja i prije ponovnog pokretanja telefona, preporučujemo da ga punite 1 do 2 sata kada je zaslon isključen kako biste osigurali primjenu optimizacija.
5. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tijekom ažuriranja, našu pomoć možete dobiti tako da nazovete HONOR servisnu otvorenu liniju ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez a frissítés bevezeti a vadonatúj MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 rendszert. Az új rendszer zökkenőmentesebben és biztonságosabban működik, könnyebben használható, energiatakarékosabb, a főképernyő pedig még szórakoztatóbb. Javasoljuk, hogy telepítse a frissítést. Figyelje a közelgő verziófrissítéseket, amelyekkel további funkciókhoz juthat hozzá.</feature>
</features>
<features module="A főképernyő felfedezése">
<feature>【Ikonok a Főképernyőn】A Főképernyő ikonjainak mérete a különböző felhasználói igényeknek megfelelően módosítható. Ehhez használja a következő menüpontot: Beállítások -> Főképernyő és stílus -> Főképernyő beállításai -> Ikon mérete.</feature>
<feature>【Alkalmazáskiterjesztő】 Mostantól egyetlen mozdulattal engedélyezheti az Alkalmazáskiterjesztőt. Húzza el az alját a bal felső sarokba, majd a két alkalmazás dupla ablakban való megjelenítéséhez koppintson az Alkalmazáskiterjesztőt támogató másik alkalmazásra.</feature>
<feature>【Lebegő ablak】 A miniablakot tetszőleges pozícióba húzhatja a főképernyőn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ha telepíti e frissítést, azzal nem törli a személyes adatokat, de javasoljuk, hogy készítsen előtte biztonsági mentést.
2. Telefonján több mint 10 GB szabad tárhelyre lesz szükség. Ha ez nincs meg, előfordulhat, hogy a frissítés sikertelen lesz (a tárhely ellenőrzéshez lépjen a Beállítások > Tárhely menüpontba).
3. Nem minden harmadik féltől származó alkalmazás kompatibilis a MagicOS 8.0 verzióval, és ezek a frissítés után hibásan működhetnek (például összeomlás, késés és rendellenes energiafogyasztás fordulhat elő). Frissítse az alkalmazásokat a legújabb verzióra az AppGallery segítségével. Ha a problémák nem szűnnek meg, várja meg a jövőbeni alkalmazásfrissítéseket.
4. A frissítést követően a rendszer az optimalizáció érdekében módosítja a beállításait. E folyamat során a telefon felforrósodhat, jelentős mennyiségű áramot fogyaszthat, lelassulhat vagy lassan töltődhet. De 2-3 nap használat után helyreáll a szokásos működés. Javasoljuk, hogy a frissítés telepítése után, de még a telefon újraindítása előtt 1-2 órán át kikapcsolt képernyő mellett töltse a készüléket, hogy a rendszernek legyen elegendő ideje az optimalizálások alkalmazására.
5. Ha bármilyen problémába ütközik a frissítés során, kérjen tőlünk segítséget: hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini telah meluncurkan MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 baru untuk Anda. Sistem baru ini lebih lancar, lebih aman, lebih mudah digunakan, lebih hemat daya, dan dengan layar beranda yang lebih menyenangkan. Kami rekomendasikan Anda untuk memperbarui. Nantikan pembaruan versi mendatang untuk membuka lebih banyak fitur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Jelajahi layar beranda">
<feature>【Ikon Layar beranda】Ukuran ikon Layar beranda dapat disesuaikan untuk memenuhi kebutuhan pengguna yang berbeda-beda. Anda dapat mencobanya dengan membuka: Pengaturan -> Gaya dan layar beranda -> Pengaturan layar beranda -> Ukuran ikon.</feature>
<feature>【Penambah Aplikasi】 Kini, Anda dapat mengaktifkan Penambah Aplikasi dengan satu gerakan. Seret bagian bawah ke sudut kiri atas, lalu ketuk aplikasi yang mendukung Penambah Aplikasi untuk menampilkan aplikasi di jendela ganda.</feature>
<feature>【Jendela melayang】 Jendela mini dapat dipindah dan melayang di segala posisi di layar beranda.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Pembaruan ini tidak akan menghapus data pribadi Anda, tetapi pencadangan sebelumnya tetap direkomendasikan.
2. Pastikan ponsel memiliki lebih dari 10 GB ruang penyimpanan kosong. Jika tidak, pembaruan dapat gagal. (Buka Pengaturan > Penyimpanan untuk memeriksanya).
3. Beberapa aplikasi pihak ketiga mungkin tidak kompatibel dengan MagicOS 8.0 dan dapat mengalami malfungsi setelah pembaruan (seperti macet, lag, konsumsi daya abnormal). Perbarui aplikasi Anda ke versi terbaru di AppGallery. Jika masalah berlanjut, tunggulah pembaruan aplikasi yang akan datang.
4. Setelah memperbarui, sistem akan menyesuaikan pengaturan untuk menerapkan optimalisasi. Selama prosesnya, ponsel dapat menjadi panas, mengonsumsi daya lebih cepat, lag, atau lambat mengisi daya. Namun, hal itu akan kembali normal dalam 2-3 hari penggunaan. Setelah pembaruan selesai dan sebelum memulai ulang ponsel, sebaiknya Anda mengisi daya dengan layar mati selama 1~2 jam untuk memastikan pengoptimalan diterapkan.
5. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau mengunjungi Pusat Layanan Pelanggan HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan ini telah meluncurkan MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 baru untuk Anda. Sistem baru ini lebih lancar, lebih aman, lebih mudah digunakan, lebih hemat daya, dan dengan layar beranda yang lebih menyenangkan. Kami rekomendasikan Anda untuk memperbarui. Nantikan pembaruan versi mendatang untuk membuka lebih banyak fitur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Jelajahi layar beranda">
<feature>【Ikon Layar beranda】Ukuran ikon Layar beranda dapat disesuaikan untuk memenuhi kebutuhan pengguna yang berbeda-beda. Anda dapat mencobanya dengan membuka: Pengaturan -> Gaya dan layar beranda -> Pengaturan layar beranda -> Ukuran ikon.</feature>
<feature>【Penambah Aplikasi】 Kini, Anda dapat mengaktifkan Penambah Aplikasi dengan satu gerakan. Seret bagian bawah ke sudut kiri atas, lalu ketuk aplikasi yang mendukung Penambah Aplikasi untuk menampilkan aplikasi di jendela ganda.</feature>
<feature>【Jendela melayang】 Jendela mini dapat dipindah dan melayang di segala posisi di layar beranda.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Pembaruan ini tidak akan menghapus data pribadi Anda, tetapi pencadangan sebelumnya tetap direkomendasikan.
2. Pastikan ponsel memiliki lebih dari 10 GB ruang penyimpanan kosong. Jika tidak, pembaruan dapat gagal. (Buka Pengaturan > Penyimpanan untuk memeriksanya).
3. Beberapa aplikasi pihak ketiga mungkin tidak kompatibel dengan MagicOS 8.0 dan dapat mengalami malfungsi setelah pembaruan (seperti macet, lag, konsumsi daya abnormal). Perbarui aplikasi Anda ke versi terbaru di AppGallery. Jika masalah berlanjut, tunggulah pembaruan aplikasi yang akan datang.
4. Setelah memperbarui, sistem akan menyesuaikan pengaturan untuk menerapkan optimalisasi. Selama prosesnya, ponsel dapat menjadi panas, mengonsumsi daya lebih cepat, lag, atau lambat mengisi daya. Namun, hal itu akan kembali normal dalam 2-3 hari penggunaan. Setelah pembaruan selesai dan sebelum memulai ulang ponsel, sebaiknya Anda mengisi daya dengan layar mati selama 1~2 jam untuk memastikan pengoptimalan diterapkan.
5. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau mengunjungi Pusat Layanan Pelanggan HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentili utenti, questo aggiornamento include il lancio del nuovissimo MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Il nuovo sistema è più fluido, sicuro e facile da utilizzare, consente un maggiore risparmio energetico ed è dotato di una schermata Home più divertente. Vi consigliamo di eseguire l'aggiornamento. Non perdetevi i prossimi aggiornamenti della versione per sbloccare ulteriori funzioni.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Esplorazione della schermata Home">
<feature>【Icone della schermata Home】Le dimensioni delle icone della schermata Home possono essere modificate in base alle proprie esigenze. Per provare questa funzione, vai su Impostazioni -> Schermata Home e stile -> Impostazioni schermata Home -> Dimensioni delle icone.</feature>
<feature>【App Extender】 Ora puoi abilitare App Extender con un solo gesto. Trascina la parte inferiore nell'angolo in alto a sinistra, quindi tocca l'altra app che supporta App Extender per visualizzare le app in finestre doppie.</feature>
<feature>【Finestra mobile】 La mini finestra può essere spostata e posizionata in qualsiasi posizione della schermata Home.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Questo aggiornamento non eliminerà le tue informazioni personali. Si consiglia comunque di eseguire un backup prima di installarlo.
2. Assicurati che il telefono abbia almeno 10 GB si spazio di archiviazione libero. Altrimenti, l'aggiornamento potrebbe non riuscire (per verificare, vai in Impostazioni > Memoria).
3. Alcune app di terze parti potrebbero non essere compatibili con MagicOS 8.0 e potrebbero non funzionare correttamente dopo l'aggiornamento (si potrebbero verificare arresti, ritardi o un consumo anomalo di batteria). Aggiorna le app alla versione più recente in AppGallery. Se i problemi persistono, aspetta gli aggiornamenti futuri delle app.
4. Dopo l'aggiornamento, il sistema regolerà le relative impostazioni per applicare le ottimizzazioni. Durante il processo, il telefono potrebbe surriscaldarsi, consumare la batteria rapidamente, essere più lento o caricarsi più lentamente. Tornerà comunque alla normalità dopo 2-3 giorni di utilizzo. Una volta eseguito l'aggiornamento e prima di riavviare il telefono, ti consigliamo di caricarlo con lo schermo spento per 1-2 ore per assicurare che le ottimizzazioni vengano applicate.
5. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center HONOR o visitando un Centro servizio clienti HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentili utenti, questo aggiornamento include il lancio del nuovissimo MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Il nuovo sistema è più fluido, sicuro e facile da utilizzare, consente un maggiore risparmio energetico ed è dotato di una schermata Home più divertente. Vi consigliamo di eseguire l'aggiornamento. Non perdetevi i prossimi aggiornamenti della versione per sbloccare ulteriori funzioni.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Esplorazione della schermata Home">
<feature>【Icone della schermata Home】Le dimensioni delle icone della schermata Home possono essere modificate in base alle proprie esigenze. Per provare questa funzione, vai su Impostazioni -> Schermata Home e stile -> Impostazioni schermata Home -> Dimensioni delle icone.</feature>
<feature>【App Extender】 Ora puoi abilitare App Extender con un solo gesto. Trascina la parte inferiore nell'angolo in alto a sinistra, quindi tocca l'altra app che supporta App Extender per visualizzare le app in finestre doppie.</feature>
<feature>【Finestra mobile】 La mini finestra può essere spostata e posizionata in qualsiasi posizione della schermata Home.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Questo aggiornamento non eliminerà le tue informazioni personali. Si consiglia comunque di eseguire un backup prima di installarlo.
2. Assicurati che il telefono abbia almeno 10 GB si spazio di archiviazione libero. Altrimenti, l'aggiornamento potrebbe non riuscire (per verificare, vai in Impostazioni > Memoria).
3. Alcune app di terze parti potrebbero non essere compatibili con MagicOS 8.0 e potrebbero non funzionare correttamente dopo l'aggiornamento (si potrebbero verificare arresti, ritardi o un consumo anomalo di batteria). Aggiorna le app alla versione più recente in AppGallery. Se i problemi persistono, aspetta gli aggiornamenti futuri delle app.
4. Dopo l'aggiornamento, il sistema regolerà le relative impostazioni per applicare le ottimizzazioni. Durante il processo, il telefono potrebbe surriscaldarsi, consumare la batteria rapidamente, essere più lento o caricarsi più lentamente. Tornerà comunque alla normalità dopo 2-3 giorni di utilizzo. Una volta eseguito l'aggiornamento e prima di riavviare il telefono, ti consigliamo di caricarlo con lo schermo spento per 1-2 ore per assicurare che le ottimizzazioni vengano applicate.
5. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center HONOR o visitando un Centro servizio clienti HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמשים יקרים, עדכון זה השיק עבורכם את מערכת MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 החדשה לגמרי. המערכת החדשה חלקה יותר, בטוחה יותר, קלה יותר לשימוש, חסכונית יותר בחשמל, ומסך הבית מהנה יותר. אנו ממליצים לעדכן. אתם מוזמנים לעקוב אחר עדכוני גרסה קרובים שייתנו לכם גישה לתכונות נוספות.</feature>
</features>
<features module="גלו את מסך הבית">
<feature>‏【סמלי מסך הבית】ניתן להתאים את גודל הסמלים של מסך הבית כדי לענות על הצרכים השונים של המשתמשים. ניתן להתנסות בכך על-ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' -> 'מסך הבית וסגנון' -> 'הגדרות מסך הבית' -> 'גודל סמל'.</feature>
<feature>‏【מרחיב היישומים】 כעת תוכל להפעיל את 'מרחיב היישומים' במחווה אחת. גרור את החלק התחתון לפינה השמאלית העליונה, ולאחר מכן הקש על היישום האחר התומך ב'מרחיב היישומים' כדי להציג יישומים בשני חלונות.</feature>
<feature>‏【חלון צף】 מיני-חלון ניתן להזזה ולריחוף לכל מיקום במסך הבית.</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. עדכון זה לא ימחק את הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות אותם לפני העדכון.
‏2. ודא שלטלפון שלך יש יותר מ-GB ‏10 של שטח אחסון פנוי. אחרת, העדכון עשוי להיכשל (עבור אל 'הגדרות' > 'אחסון' כדי לבדוק את המקום הפנוי).
‏3. מספר יישומים של צד שלישי עשויים שלא להיות תואמים ל-MagicOS 8.0 ועשויים לתפקד באופן לקוי לאחר העדכון (כגון להתרסק, לפעול לאט, לצרוך חשמל באופן חריג). עדכן את היישומים שלך לגרסה האחרונה ב-AppGallery. אם הבעיות נמשכות, אנא המתן לעדכוני היישומים הקרובים.
‏4. לאחר העדכון, המערכת תתאים את הגדרותיה כדי להחיל את המיטובים. תוך כדי תהליך זה, הטלפון עלול להתחמם, לצרוך חשמל במהירות, לפעול באיטיות או להיטען לאט. אך פעילותו תחזור להיות תקינה תוך 3-2 ימי שימוש. לאחר סיום העדכון ולפני הפעלה מחדש של הטלפון, אנו ממליצים להטעין אותו עם המסך כבוי למשך כשעה עד שעתיים כדי להבטיח שהמיטובים הוחלו.
‏5. אם אתה נתקל בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, תוכל לקבל עזרה מאיתנו באמצעות התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמשים יקרים, עדכון זה השיק עבורכם את מערכת MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 החדשה לגמרי. המערכת החדשה חלקה יותר, בטוחה יותר, קלה יותר לשימוש, חסכונית יותר בחשמל, ומסך הבית מהנה יותר. אנו ממליצים לעדכן. אתם מוזמנים לעקוב אחר עדכוני גרסה קרובים שייתנו לכם גישה לתכונות נוספות.</feature>
</features>
<features module="גלו את מסך הבית">
<feature>‏【סמלי מסך הבית】ניתן להתאים את גודל הסמלים של מסך הבית כדי לענות על הצרכים השונים של המשתמשים. ניתן להתנסות בכך על-ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' -> 'מסך הבית וסגנון' -> 'הגדרות מסך הבית' -> 'גודל סמל'.</feature>
<feature>‏【מרחיב היישומים】 כעת תוכל להפעיל את 'מרחיב היישומים' במחווה אחת. גרור את החלק התחתון לפינה השמאלית העליונה, ולאחר מכן הקש על היישום האחר התומך ב'מרחיב היישומים' כדי להציג יישומים בשני חלונות.</feature>
<feature>‏【חלון צף】 מיני-חלון ניתן להזזה ולריחוף לכל מיקום במסך הבית.</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. עדכון זה לא ימחק את הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות אותם לפני העדכון.
‏2. ודא שלטלפון שלך יש יותר מ-GB ‏10 של שטח אחסון פנוי. אחרת, העדכון עשוי להיכשל (עבור אל 'הגדרות' > 'אחסון' כדי לבדוק את המקום הפנוי).
‏3. מספר יישומים של צד שלישי עשויים שלא להיות תואמים ל-MagicOS 8.0 ועשויים לתפקד באופן לקוי לאחר העדכון (כגון להתרסק, לפעול לאט, לצרוך חשמל באופן חריג). עדכן את היישומים שלך לגרסה האחרונה ב-AppGallery. אם הבעיות נמשכות, אנא המתן לעדכוני היישומים הקרובים.
‏4. לאחר העדכון, המערכת תתאים את הגדרותיה כדי להחיל את המיטובים. תוך כדי תהליך זה, הטלפון עלול להתחמם, לצרוך חשמל במהירות, לפעול באיטיות או להיטען לאט. אך פעילותו תחזור להיות תקינה תוך 3-2 ימי שימוש. לאחר סיום העדכון ולפני הפעלה מחדש של הטלפון, אנו ממליצים להטעין אותו עם המסך כבוי למשך כשעה עד שעתיים כדי להבטיח שהמיטובים הוחלו.
‏5. אם אתה נתקל בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, תוכל לקבל עזרה מאיתנו באמצעות התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様、今回の更新で新しいMagicOS 8.0|Android 14が登場しました。新しいシステムはさらにスムーズで安全、かつ使いやすく省電力で、ホーム画面がさらに面白くなりました。更新することをおすすめします。今後のバージョン更新でのさらなる機能の追加にご期待ください。</feature>
</features>
<features module="ホーム画面の進化">
<feature>【ホーム画面のアイコン】ホーム画面のアイコンのサイズを調整してユーザーの様々なニーズに対応できます。この機能は[設定] -> [ホーム画面とスタイル] -> [ホーム画面設定] -> [アイコンのサイズ]に移動して利用できます。</feature>
<feature>【App Extender】App Extenderを1回のジェスチャーで有効にできるようになりました。下部を左上隅にドラッグして、App Extenderをサポートする別のアプリをタップすると、アプリがデュアルウィンドウで表示されます。</feature>
<feature>【フローティングウィンドウ】ミニウィンドウをホーム画面で移動して、任意の位置でホバリングさせることができます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. 今回の更新で、個人情報は消去されませんが、事前にデータのバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2.お使いの携帯電話に10 GB以上の空き容量があることを確認してください。そうでない場合、更新に失敗する可能性があります（[設定] > [ストレージ]に移動して確認します）。
3.一部のサードパーティ製アプリは、MagicOS 8.0と互換性がない場合があり、更新後に不具合が生じる可能性があります（クラッシュ、遅延、異常な電力消費など）。AppGalleryでアプリを最新バージョンに更新してください。問題が解決しない場合は、今後のアプリの更新をお待ちください。
4.更新後、システムは設定を調整して最適化を適用します。その過程で、携帯電話が熱くなる、電力消費が早くなる、遅延が生じる、充電速度が遅くなることがありますが、使用後2～3日で正常に戻ります。更新を完了後、携帯電話を再起動する前に、最適化が適用されるように、画面をオフにして1～2時間充電することをおすすめします。
5.更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインに電話するか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターにアクセスしてサポートを受けることができます。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებლებო, ამ განახლებამ გამოუშვა სრულიად ახალი MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. ახალი სისტემა უფრო შეუფერხებელი, უსაფრთხო, მარტივად გამოსაყენებელი და ენერგოეფექტურია, საწყისი ეკრანი კი უფრო სახალისოა. გირჩევთ, განაახლოთ. მეტი ფუნქციის გასახსნელად დაელოდეთ ვერსიის მომავალ განახლებებს.</feature>
</features>
<features module="საწყისი ეკრანის დათვალიერება">
<feature>【საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამები】საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამების ზომა შეიძლება დარეგულირდეს მომხმარებლის საჭიროებების შესაბამისად. ამის გაკეთება შეგიძლიათ მენიუში: პარამეტრები -> საწყისი ეკრანი და სტილი -> საწყისი ეკრანის პარამეტრები -> პიქტოგრამის ზომა.</feature>
<feature>【აპის გამაფართოებელი】 ახლა შეგიძლიათ ერთი ჟესტით ჩართოთ აპის გამაფართოებელი. გადაიტანეთ ეკრანის ქვედა ნაწილი მარცხენა ზედა კუთხეში და შემდეგ შეეხეთ აპის გამაფართოებლის მხარდაჭერის მქონე სხვა აპს აპების ორმაგ ფანჯარაში საჩვენებლად.</feature>
<feature>【მცურავი ფანჯარა】 მინიფანჯრის გადატანა და დაკიდება შესაძლებელია საწყის ეკრანზე ნებისმიერ პოზიციაზე.</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ეს განახლება არ გამოიწვევს თქვენი პერსონალური მონაცემების წაშლას, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. უზრუნველყავით, რომ ტელეფონის საცავში თავისუფალი იყოს 10 გბ-ზე მეტი სივრცე. წინააღმდეგ შემთხვევაში, განახლება შეიძლება ვერ მოხერხდეს (შესამოწმებლად გახსენით პარამეტრები > საცავი).
3. ზოგიერთი მესამე მხარის პროგრამა, შესაძლოა, არ იყოს თავსებადი MagicOS 8.0-თან და განახლების შემდეგ ჯეროვნად ვერ იმუშაოს (მაგ., აღენიშნებოდეს ავარიული გათიშვა, შეფერხება, ენერგიის ანომალიური მოხმარება). განაახლეთ აპები უახლესი ვერსიით AppGallery-ში. თუ პრობლემები შენარჩუნდა, დაელოდეთ აპის მომავალ განახლებებს.
4. განახლების შემდეგ, სისტემა დაარეგულირებს თავის პარამეტრებს ოპტიმიზაციების გამოსაყენებლად. ამ პროცესში ტელეფონი შეიძლება გაცხელდეს, სწრაფად მოიხმაროს ენერგია, შეფერხდეს ან ნელა დაიმუხტოს. თუმცა, 2-3 დღის გამოყენების შემდეგ ნორმას დაუბრუნდება. განახლების დასრულების შემდეგ და ტელეფონის გადატვირთვამდე გირჩევთ, დატენოთ ის გამორთული ეკრანით 1~2 საათის განმავლობაში, რათა უზრუნველყოთ ოპტიმიზაციების გამოყენება.
5. თუ განახლების დროს რაიმე პრობლემა შეგექმნათ, ჩვენგან დახმარების მისაღებად შეგიძლიათ დარეკოთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან ეწვიოთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушылар, бұл жаңарту сіз үшін жап-жаңа MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 нұсқасын іске қосты. Жаңа жүйе көбірек бірқалыпты, қауіпсіз, пайдалану оңай, қуатты үнемдейді және негізгі экран қызықтырақ. Жаңартуды ұсынамыз. Қосымша мүмкіндіктердің құлпын ашу үшін алдағы нұсқа жаңартуларын бақылап отырыңыз.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Негізгі экранды зерттеу">
<feature>【Негізгі экран белгішелері】Негізгі экран белгішелерінің өлшемін пайдаланушылардың әртүрлі қажеттіліктеріне сай реттеуге болады. Келесіге өту арқылы оны қолданып көруге болады: «Параметрлер» -> «Негізгі экран және стиль» -> «Негізгі экран параметрлері» -> «Белгіше өлшемі».</feature>
<feature>【Қолданбаны кеңейткіш】 Енді «Қолданбаны кеңейткіш» мүмкіндігін бір қимылмен қосуға болады. Төменгі жағын жоғарғы сол жақ бұрышқа сүйреп, қолданбаларды қос терезеде көрсету үшін «Қолданбаны кеңейткіш» мүмкіндігін қолдайтын басқа қолданбаны түртіңіз.</feature>
<feature>【Қалқымалы терезе】 Шағын терезені жылжытуға және негізгі экрандағы кез келген орынға апаруға болады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңарту жеке деректерді өшірмейді, бірақ бұрынғы сақтық көшірме әлі де ұсынылады.
2. Телефоныңызда 10 ГБ-тан астам бос сақтау орны бар екеніне көз жеткізіңіз. Әйтпесе жаңарту сәтсіз болуы мүмкін (оны тексеру үшін «Параметрлер» > «Қойма» тармағына өтіңіз).
3. Кейбір үшінші тарап қолданбалары MagicOS 8.0 жүйесімен үйлесімді болмауы мүмкін және жаңартудан кейін дұрыс жұмыс істемеуі мүмкін (мысалы, жаңылыс, кідіріс, қалыпсыз қуат тұтыну). AppGallery ішінде қолданбаларды соңғы нұсқасына жаңартыңыз. Мәселелер шешілмесе, қолданбаның алдағы жаңартуларын күтіңіз.
4. Жаңартқаннан кейін жүйе оңтайландыруларды қолдану үшін өз параметрлерін реттейді. Процесс барысында телефон қызып, қуатты жылдам тұтынуы, қатып қалуы немесе баяу зарядталуы мүмкін. Бірақ ол 2-3 күн пайдаланғаннан кейін қалпына келеді. Жаңартылғаннан кейін және телефонды қайта іске қоспас бұрын оңтайландырулар қолданылғанына көз жеткізу үшін оны экран өшірулі күйінде 1~2 сағат бойы зарядтау ұсынылады.
5. Жаңарту кезінде қандай да бір мәселе орын алса, HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне қоңырау шалу не HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына бару арқылы көмегімізді ала аласыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះបានបើកដំណើរការ MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 ដ៏ថ្មីសន្លាងសម្រាប់អ្នក។ ប្រព័ន្ធថ្មីនេះកាន់តែរលូន មានសុវត្ថិភាព និងងាយស្រួលប្រើ សន្សំសំចៃថាមពលកាន់តែច្រើន ហើយអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើមកាន់តែសប្បាយ។ យើងសូមណែនាំឱ្យអ្នកធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព។ សូមបន្តតាមដានបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពកំណែនាពេលខាងមុខ ដើម្បីដោះសោមុខងារច្រើនទៀត។</feature>
</features>
<features module="រុករកអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម">
<feature>【រូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម】ទំហំរូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើមអាចត្រូវបានលៃតម្រូវ ដើម្បីបំពេញតាមតម្រូវការខុសៗគ្នារបស់អ្នកប្រើ។ អ្នកអាចទទួលបទពិសោធប្រើប្រាស់វាបានដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ -> អេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម និងរចនាប័ទ្ម -> ការកំណត់អេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម -> ទំហំរូបតំណាង។</feature>
<feature>【មុខងារពង្រីកបន្ថែមកម្មវិធី】 ឥឡូវ អ្នកអាចបើកមុខងារពង្រីកបន្ថែមកម្មវិធីដោយប្រើកាយវិការតែមួយ។ ចុចអូសផ្នែកខាងក្រោមទៅជ្រុងខាងលើខាងឆ្វេង រួចប៉ះកម្មវិធីម្ខាងទៀតដែលអាចប្រើមុខងារពង្រីកបន្ថែមកម្មវិធី ដើម្បីបង្ហាញកម្មវិធីនៅក្នុងវិនដូពីរ។</feature>
<feature>【វិនដូអណ្ដែត】 វិនដូខ្នាតតូចអាចត្រូវបានផ្លាស់ទី និងដាក់ព្រួញពីលើទៅទីតាំងណាមួយនៅលើអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​លុបទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ចេញទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ត្រូវប្រាកដថាទូរស័ព្ទរបស់អ្នកមានទំហំឧបករណ៍ផ្ទុកទិន្នន័យទំនេរលើសពី 10 GB។ បើមិនដូច្នោះទេ ការធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពអាចមិនបានសម្រេច (ចូលទៅកាន់ការកំណត់ > ឧបករណ៍ផ្ទុក ដើម្បីពិនិត្យមើលវា)។
3. កម្មវិធីរបស់ភាគីទីបីមួយចំនួនអាចមិនត្រូវគ្នាជាមួយ MagicOS 8.0 និងអាច​ដំណើរការ​ខុសប្រក្រតី​បន្ទាប់ពីការធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព (ដូចជា គាំង ដើរយឺត ការប្រើប្រាស់​ថាមពល​ខុសធម្មតា)។ សូមធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពកម្មវិធីរបស់អ្នកទៅកំណែចុងក្រោយបំផុតនៅក្នុង AppGallery។ ប្រសិនបើនៅតែមានបញ្ហា សូមរង់ចាំបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពកម្មវិធីនាពេលខាងមុខ។
4. បន្ទាប់ពីធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព ប្រព័ន្ធនឹងលៃតម្រូវការកំណត់របស់វា ដើម្បីអនុវត្ត​ការធ្វើឱ្យប្រសើរឡើង។ នៅក្នុងដំណើរការនេះ ទូរស័ព្ទអាចនឹងក្តៅ ប្រើប្រាស់ថាមពលលឿន ដើរយឺត ឬសាកថ្មយឺត​។ ​ប៉ុន្តែវានឹងត្រលប់មកធម្មតាវិញបន្ទាប់ពីប្រើបាន 2-3 ថ្ងៃ។ បន្ទាប់​ពី​ការធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពត្រូវ​បានបញ្ចប់ និង​មុន​ពេល​ចាប់​ផ្ដើម​ទូរស័ព្ទ​ឡើង​វិញ យើង​សូម​ណែនាំ​ឱ្យ​សាក​ថ្មវា​ដោយ​បិទ​អេក្រង់​រយៈពេល 1~2 ម៉ោង ដើម្បី​ធានា​ថា​ការ​ធ្វើឱ្យប្រសើរឡើង​ត្រូវ​បាន​អនុវត្ត។
5. ប្រសិនបើ​អ្នក​ជួបប្រទះបញ្ហា​ណាមួយ​ក្នុងអំឡុង​ការធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ អ្នកអាច​ទទួល​ជំនួយ​របស់យើង​បាន​ដោយ​ហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័ស​សេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬ​ទៅកាន់​មជ្ឈមណ្ឌលសេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ನಿಮಗಾಗಿ ಹೊಚ್ಚಹೊಸ MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 ಅನ್ನು ಬಿಡುಗಡೆ ಮಾಡಿದೆ. ಹೊಸ ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಸುಗಮವಾಗಿದೆ, ಸುರಕ್ಷಿತವಾಗಿದೆ, ಬಳಸಲು ಸುಲಭವಾಗಿದೆ, ಹೆಚ್ಚು ವಿದ್ಯುತ್ ಉಳಿತಾಯ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಹೆಚ್ಚು ವಿನೋದದಿಂದ ಕೂಡಿದೆ. ನೀವು ನವೀಕರಿಸಬೇಕೆಂದು ನಾವು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡುತ್ತೇವೆ. ಇನ್ನೂ ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳನ್ನು ಅನ್‌ಲಾಕ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಮುಂಬರುವ ಆವೃತ್ತಿಯ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳಿಗಾಗಿ ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಿರೀಕ್ಷಿಸಿ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಅನ್ವೇಷಿಸಿ">
<feature>【ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳು】ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ವಿವಿಧ ಅಗತ್ಯಗಳನ್ನು ಪೂರೈಸಲು ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳ ಗಾತ್ರವನ್ನು ಸರಿಹೊಂದಿಸಬಹುದು. ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು -> ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮತ್ತು ಶೈಲಿ -> ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು -> ಐಕಾನ್ ಗಾತ್ರ ಎಂಬಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನೀವು ಇದರ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು.</feature>
<feature>【ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಎಕ್ಸ್‌ಟೆಂಡರ್】 ಈಗ ನೀವು ಒಂದೇ ಗೆಶ್ಚರ್‌ನ ಮೂಲಕ ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಎಕ್ಸ್‌ಟೆಂಡರ್ ಅನ್ನು ಸಕ್ರಿಯಗೊಳಿಸಬಹುದು. ಡ್ಯುಯಲ್ ವಿಂಡೋಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಆ್ಯಪ್‍ಗಳನ್ನು ಪ್ರದರ್ಶಿಸಲು, ಕೆಳಭಾಗವನ್ನು ಮೇಲಿನ ಎಡ ಮೂಲೆಗೆ ಎಳೆಯಿರಿ ಮತ್ತು ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಎಕ್ಸ್‌ಟೆಂಡರ್ ಅನ್ನು ಬೆಂಬಲಿಸುವ ಇತರ ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಅನ್ನು ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ.</feature>
<feature>【ಫ್ಲೋಟಿಂಗ್ ವಿಂಡೋ】ಮಿನಿ ವಿಂಡೋವನ್ನು ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಯಾವುದೇ ಸ್ಥಾನಕ್ಕೆ ಸರಿಸಬಹುದು ಮತ್ತು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸ್ಥಾನದಲ್ಲಿ ಸುಳಿದಾಡುವಂತೆ ಮಾಡಬಹುದು.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಅಳಿಸುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ಮುಂಚಿತವಾಗಿ ಬ್ಯಾಕ್‌ಅಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ ಇಡಲು ಈಗಲೂ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನಿಮ್ಮ ಫೋನ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ 10 GB ಗಿಂತ ಹೆಚ್ಚು ಉಚಿತ ಸಂಗ್ರಹಣೆ ಸ್ಥಳವಿದೆ ಎಂದು ಖಚಿತಪಡಿಸಿಕೊಳ್ಳಿ. ಇಲ್ಲದಿದ್ದರೆ, ನವೀಕರಣ ವಿಫಲವಾಗಬಹುದು (ಇದನ್ನು ಪರಿಶೀಲಿಸಲು ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಸಂಗ್ರಹಣೆಗೆ ಹೋಗಿ).
3. ಕೆಲವು ತರ್ಡ್-ಪಾರ್ಟಿ ಆ್ಯಪ್‌ಗಳು MagicOS 8.0 ನೊಂದಿಗೆ ಹೊಂದಾಣಿಕೆಯಾಗದೇ ಇರಬಹುದು ಮತ್ತು ನವೀಕರಣದ ನಂತರ ಅಸಮರ್ಪಕವಾಗಿ ಕಾರ್ಯನಿರ್ವಹಿಸಬಹುದು (ಉದಾಹರಣೆಗೆ ಕ್ರ್ಯಾಶ್, ಲ್ಯಾಗ್, ಅಸಹಜ ವಿದ್ಯುತ್ ಬಳಕೆ). ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಆ್ಯಪ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು AppGallery ಯಲ್ಲಿ ಇತ್ತೀಚಿನ ಆವೃತ್ತಿಗೆ ನವೀಕರಿಸಿ. ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳು ಮುಂದುವರಿದರೆ, ಮುಂಬರುವ ಆ್ಯಪ್ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳಿಗಾಗಿ ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಿರೀಕ್ಷಿಸಿ.
4. ನವೀಕರಿಸಿದ ನಂತರ, ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸೇಶನ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಅನ್ವಯಿಸಲು ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ತನ್ನ ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಸರಿಹೊಂದಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಈ ಪ್ರಕ್ರಿಯೆಯಲ್ಲಿ, ಫೋನ್ ಬಿಸಿಯಾಗಬಹುದು, ವೇಗವಾಗಿ ವಿದ್ಯುತ್ ಬಳಸಬಹುದು, ಲ್ಯಾಗ್ ಆಗಬಹುದು ಅಥವಾ ನಿಧಾನವಾಗಿ ಚಾರ್ಜ್ ಆಗಬಹುದು. ಆದರೆ 2-3 ದಿನಗಳ ಬಳಕೆಯಲ್ಲಿ ಇದು ಸಾಮಾನ್ಯ ಸ್ಥಿತಿಗೆ ಮರಳುತ್ತದೆ. ನವೀಕರಣ ಮಾಡಿದ ನಂತರ ಮತ್ತು ಫೋನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಮರುಪ್ರಾರಂಭಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು, ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸೇಶನ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಅನ್ವಯಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ ಎಂದು ಖಚಿತಪಡಿಸಿಕೊಳ್ಳಲು 1~2 ಗಂಟೆಗಳ ಕಾಲ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಆಫ್ ಇಟ್ಟು ಅದನ್ನು ಚಾರ್ಜ್ ಮಾಡಲು ನಾವು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡುತ್ತೇವೆ.
5. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ನೀವು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಅಥವಾ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನಮ್ಮ ಸಹಾಯವನ್ನು ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자님, 이번 업데이트로 완전히 새로운 MagicOS 8.0|Android 14가 출시되었습니다. 새로운 시스템은 보다 원활하고, 안전하고, 사용하기 쉽고, 절전 성능이 우수하며, 홈 화면도 더 재미있어졌습니다. 업데이트하시기를 권장합니다. 더 많은 기능이 공개될 향후의 버전 업데이트에도 계속해서 관심 부탁드립니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="홈 화면 탐색">
<feature>【홈 화면 아이콘】홈 화면 아이콘의 크기는 사용자의 다양한 요구에 맞게 조정할 수 있습니다. 설정 -> 홈 화면 및 스타일 -> 홈 화면 설정 -> 아이콘 크기로 이동하여 체험해 볼 수 있습니다.</feature>
<feature>【앱 확장 프로그램】 이제 한 번의 제스처로 앱 확장 프로그램을 실행할 수 있습니다. 하단을 왼쪽 상단으로 드래그한 다음 앱 확장 프로그램을 지원하는 다른 앱을 탭하여 앱을 이중 창에 표시합니다.</feature>
<feature>【플로팅 윈도우】 미니 윈도우는 홈 화면의 원하는 위치로 이동하고 마우스를 가져갈 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트로 개인 데이터가 지워지지는 않지만 그래도 미리 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다.
2. 휴대폰에 10GB가 넘는 여유 저장 공간이 있는지 확인하십시오. 그렇지 않으면 업데이트에 실패할 수 있습니다(설정 > 저장 공간으로 이동하여 확인).
3. 일부 타사 앱은 MagicOS 8.0과 호환되지 않을 수 있으며 업데이트 후 오작동(충돌, 지연, 비정상적인 소비 전력 등)이 발생할 수 있습니다. AppGallery에서 앱을 최신 버전으로 업데이트하십시오. 문제가 계속되면 예정된 앱 업데이트를 기다리시기 바랍니다.
4. 업데이트 이후 시스템은 설정을 조정하여 최적화를 적용합니다. 이 과정에서 휴대폰 온도 상승, 빠른 전력 소모, 지연, 느린 충전이 발생할 수 있습니다. 하지만 2~3일의 사용 후에는 정상으로 복구됩니다. 업데이트가 완료된 후에는 휴대폰을 다시 시작하기 전에 최적화가 적용될 수 있도록 1~2시간 동안 화면을 끈 상태에서 충전하는 것을 바람직합니다.
5. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화를 걸거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터를 방문하여 지원을 요청할 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ຮຽນ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ໄດ້​ເປີດ​ໃຊ້ MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 ແບບ​ໃໝ່​ໃຫ້​ກັບ​ທ່ານ. ລະ​ບົບ​ໃໝ່​ຄ່ອງ​ຕົວ​ຂຶ້ນ, ປອດ​ໄພ​​ຂຶ້ນ, ໃຊ້​ງານ​ງ່າຍ​ຂຶ້ນ, ການ​ປະ​ຢັດ​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານຫຼາຍ​ຂຶ້ນ ແລະ ໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ​ມ່ວນ​ຍິ່ງ​ຂຶ້ນ. ພວກ​ເຮົາ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ທ່ານ​ອັບ​ເດດ. ກະ​ລຸ​ນາ​ເຝົ້າ​​ຕິດ​ຕາມການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ເວີ​ຊັນ​​ທີ່​ກຳ​ລັງ​ຈະ​ມາ​ເຖິງ ເພື່ອ​ປົດ​ລັອກ​ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ເພີ່ມ​ເຕີມ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ສຳຫຼວດ​ເບິ່ງໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ຫຼັກ">
<feature>​【ໄອ​ຄອນໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ】ສາ​ມາດ​ປັບຂະ​ໜາດ​ຂອງໄອ​ຄອນໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ​ເພື່ອ​ໃຫ້​ຕອບ​ສະ​ໜອງໄດ້​ຕ​າມ​ຄວາມ​ຕ້ອງ​ການ​ທີ່​ແຕກ​ຕ່າງ​ກັນ​ຂອງ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້. ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ສຳ​ຜັດ​ປະ​ສົບ​ການມັນ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ -> ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ ແລະ ຮູບ​ແບບ -> ການຕັ້ງຄ່າໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ -> ຂະ​ໜາດ​ໄອ​ຄອນ.</feature>
<feature>【ຕົວ​ຂະ​ຫຍາຍ​ແອັບ】 ຕອນ​ນີ້ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ເປີດ​ໃຊ້​ງານຕົວ​ຂະ​ຫຍາຍ​ແອັບ​ດ້ວຍ​ທ່າ​ທາງ​ດຽວ​ໄດ້​ແລ້ວ.ລາກດ້ານລຸ່ມສຸດໄປຫາມຸມຊ້າຍສຸດດ້ານເທິງ ແລະ ຈາກນັ້ນ ແຕະແອັບອື່ນທີ່ຮອງຮັບຕົວຂະຫຍາຍແອັບ ເພື່ອສະແດງແອັບໃນໜ້າຈໍຄູ່.</feature>
<feature>【ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ລອຍ】 ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ນ້ອຍສາ​ມາດ​ຍ້າຍ ແລະ ລອຍ​ຕົວ​ໄປ​ຫາ​ຕຳ​ແໜ່ງ​ໃດ​ໜຶ່ງ​ໃນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ​ໄດ້.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການອັບເດດນີ້ຈະບໍ່ລຶບຂໍ້ມູນສ່ວນຕົວຂອງທ່ານ, ແຕ່ພວກເຮົາກໍຍັງຂໍແນະນຳໃຫ້ທ່ານສຳຮອງຂໍ້ມູນໄວ້ລ່ວງໜ້າ.
2. ກວດ​ໃຫ້​ແນ່​ໃຈ​ວ່າ​ໂທ​ລະ​ສັບ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ມີພື້ນທີ່ຈັດເກັບຂໍ້ມູນຫວ່າງຫຼາຍກວ່າ 10 GB. ຖ້າ​ບໍ່​ດັ່ງ​ນັ້ນ, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ອາດ​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສຳ​ເລັດ (ໄປ​ທີ່ ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ > ບ່ອນ​ຈັດ​ເກັບ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ ເພື່ອກວດ​ເບິ່ງ​ມັນ).
3. ບາງ​ແອັບ​ພາກ​ສ່ວນ​ທີ​ສາມ​ອາດ​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ເຂົ້າ​ກັນ​ໄດ້​ກັບ MagicOS 8.0 ແລະ ອ​າດ​ຈະເກີດ​ຂັດ​ຂ້ອງ​ຫຼັງ​ຈາກ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ (ເຊັ່ນ: ບໍ່ເດີນ, ​ຊ້າ, ການ​ໃຊ້​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານ​ຜິດ​ປົກ​ກະ​ຕິ). ​ກະ​ລຸ​ນາ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ແອັບຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ເປັນ​ເວີ​ຊັນ​ໃໝ່ຫຼ້າ​ສຸດຢູ່​ໃນ AppGallery. ຖ້າ​ຍັງ​ມີ​ບັນ​ຫາ​ຢູ່, ກະລຸນາລໍຖ້າການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ແອັບທີ່​ກຳ​ລັງ​ຈະ​ມາ​ເຖິງ.
4. ຫຼັງ​ຈາກ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ, ລະ​ບົບ​ຈະ​ປັບ​ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ​ຂອງ​ມັນ​ເພື່ອ​ນຳ​ໃຊ້​ການ​ປັບ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ. ໃນ​ຂະ​ບວນ​ການ, ໂທ​ລະ​ສັບ​ອາດ​ຈະ​ຮ້ອນ, ໃຊ້​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານ​ໄວ, ຊ້າ ຫຼື ສາກ​ໄດ້​ຊ້າ. ແຕ່​ມັນ​ຈະ​ກັບ​ຄືນ​ເປັນ​ປົກ​ກະ​ຕິ​ໃນ 2-3 ມື້ ຂອງ​ການ​ໃຊ້​ງານ. ຫຼັງ​ຈາກ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ສຳ​ເລັດ ແລະ ກ່ອນ​ປິດ​ເ​ປີດ​ໂທ​ລະ​ສັບ​ຄືນ​ໃໝ່, ພວກ​ເຮົາ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສາກ​ມັນ​​ດ້ວຍ​ໜ້າ​​ຈໍປິດ​ເປັນ​ເວ​ລາ 1~2 ຊົ່ວ​ໂມງ ເພື່ອ​ຮັບ​ປະ​ກັນ​ວ່າ​ໄດ້​ນຳ​ໃຊ້​ການ​ປັບ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ.
5. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ທ່ານສາມາດຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອຈາກພວກເຮົາໄດ້ ໂດຍການໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamieji naudotojai, šiuo naujiniu pristatoma visiškai nauja sistema „MagicOS 8.0“|„Android 14“. Naujoji sistema yra sklandesnė, saugesnė, paprastesnė naudoti, taupiau eikvoja energiją, o pradžios ekranas – dar smagesnis. Rekomenduojame atnaujinti. Laukite būsimų versijos naujinių, kad galėtumėte atrakinti daugiau funkcijų.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pradžios ekrano naršymas">
<feature>【Pradžios ekrano piktogramos】Pradžios ekrano piktogramų dydį galima reguliuoti pagal skirtingus naudotojų poreikius. Tai galite išbandyti nuėję į „Nuostatos -> Pradžios ekranas ir stilius -> Pradžios ekrano nuostatos -> Piktogramos dydis“.</feature>
<feature>【Programėlių plėstuvas】 Nuo šiol programėlių plėstuvą galite įjungti vienu gestu. Nuvilkite apačią į viršutinį kairįjį kampą, tada palieskite kitą programėlę, derančią su programėlių plėstuvo funkcija, kad programėlės būtų rodomos dviejuose languose.</feature>
<feature>【Slankusis langas】 Minilangą galima perkelti ir užvesti į bet kurią pradžios ekrano vietą.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Šis naujinys neištrins jūsų asmeninių duomenų, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama iš anksto padaryti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Užtikrinkite, kad telefono atmintinėje būtų daugiau nei 10 GB laisvos vietos. Priešingu atveju gali nepavykti atnaujinti (norėdami tai patikrinti, eikite į „Nuostatos > Atmintinė“).
3. Kai kurios trečiųjų šalių programėlės gali būti nesuderinamos su „MagicOS 7.1“ ir po atnaujinimo gali sutrikti jų veikimas (pvz., jos gali strigti, vėluoti, naudoti daug energijos). Platformoje „AppGallery“ atnaujinkite programėles į naujausią versiją. Jei problemos išlieka, palaukite būsimų programėlės naujinių.
4. Po atnaujinimo sistema pakoreguos savo nuostatas ir pritaikys optimizavimo priemonių. Šio proceso metu telefonas gali įkaisti, greitai naudoti energiją, delsti arba lėtai įsikrauti. Vis dėlto po 2–3 dienų naudojimo jis vėl veiks normaliai. Atnaujinus ir prieš paleidžiant telefoną iš naujo, rekomenduojame jį 1–2 valandas įkrauti išjungtu ekranu, kad būtų pritaikytos optimizavimo priemonės.
5. Jei naujinimo metu kiltų bet kokių problemų, galite kreiptis į mus pagalbos paskambindami HONOR priežiūros karštąja linija arba apsilankydami HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centre.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāji! Šis atjauninājums jums ir ieviesis pilnīgi jaunu MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Jaunā sistēma ir vienmērīgāka, drošāka, vieglāk lietojama, vairāk taupa enerģiju, un sākuma ekrāns ir jautrāks. Mēs iesakām atjaunināt. Sekojiet līdzi gaidāmajiem versiju atjauninājumiem, lai atbloķētu citas funkcijas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Izpētīt sākuma ekrānu">
<feature>【Sākuma ekrāna ikonas】 Sākuma ekrāna ikonu izmēru var pielāgot, lai atbilstu lietotāju dažādajām vajadzībām. Varat to izbaudīt, atverot: Iestatījumi -> Sākuma ekrāns un stils -> Sākuma ekrāna iestatījumi -> Ikonas izmērs.</feature>
<feature>【Lietotņu paplašinātājs】 Tagad varat iespējot lietotņu paplašinātāju ar vienu žestu. Velciet apakšējo daļu uz augšējo kreiso stūri un pēc tam pieskarieties otrai lietotnei, kas atbalsta lietotņu paplašinātāju, lai parādītu lietotnes divos logos.</feature>
<feature>【Peldošais logs】 Mini logu var pārvietot un novietot uz jebkuru pozīciju sākuma ekrānā.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Ar šo atjauninājumu jūsu personas dati netiks dzēsti, taču joprojām ir ieteicams iepriekš izveidot dublējumu.
2. Pārliecinieties, vai tālrunī ir vairāk nekā 10 GB brīvas vietas. Pretējā gadījumā atjaunināšana var neizdoties (lai to pārbaudītu, dodieties uz Iestatījumi > Krātuve).
3. Dažas trešo pušu lietotnes var nebūt saderīgas ar MagicOS 8.0 un pēc atjaunināšanas var darboties nepareizi (piemēram, avārija, aizkave, neparasts enerģijas patēriņš). Atjauniniet savas lietotnes uz jaunāko versiju pakalpojumā AppGallery. Ja problēmas joprojām pastāv, uzgaidiet turpmākos lietotņu atjauninājumus.
4. Pēc atjaunināšanas sistēma pielāgos savus iestatījumus, lai piemērotu optimizācijas. Šajā procesā tālrunis var sakarst, ātri patērēt enerģiju, aizkavēties vai uzlādēties lēni. Bet tā normāls stāvoklis atgriezīsies 2–3 lietošanas dienu laikā. Pēc atjaunināšanas un pirms tālruņa restartēšanas iesakām 1–2 stundas uzlādēt to ar izslēgtu ekrānu, lai nodrošinātu optimizācijas.
5. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, varat saņemt mūsu palīdzību, zvanot uz HONOR klientu apkalpošanas dienesta tālruni vai apmeklējot HONOR klientu pakalpojumu centru.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता सभ, ई अपडेट अहाँक लेल एकदम नव MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 लॉन्च कयलक अछि। नव सिस्टम बेसी सहज, सुरक्षित आ उपयोग मे आसान, बेसी पावर बचत करए वला अछि आओर होम स्क्रीन बेसी मजेदार अछि। हमसभ अहाँ केँ अपडेट करबाक अनुशंसा करैत छी। कृपाकए आओर विशेषता सभ अनलॉक करबाक हेतु आबएवला वर्जन अपडेट सभक लेल बनल रहू।</feature>
</features>
<features module="होम स्क्रीन एक्सप्लोर करू">
<feature>【होम स्क्रीनक आइकन】उपयोगकर्ता सभक विभिन्न आवश्यकता सभ केँ पूरा करबाक लेल होम स्क्रीन आइकन केर आकार केँ समायोजित कयल जा सकैत अछि। अहाँ एहि मे जा कए एकरा अनुभव कए सकैत छी: सेटिंग्स -> होम स्क्रीन आ शैली -> होम स्क्रीनक सेटिंग्स -> आइकनक आकार।</feature>
<feature>【एप एक्सटेंडर】 आब अहाँ एप एक्सटेंडर केँ एकल हाव-भाव सँ सक्षम कए सकैत छी। बॉटम सँ उपरका बामा कोन मे खींचू आ तकर बाद ड्यूअल विंडोज मे प्रदर्शित करबाक लेल एप एक्सटेंडर केँ सपोर्ट करए वला अन्य एप केँ टैप करू।</feature>
<feature>【फ्लोटिंग विंडो】 मिनी विंडो केँ होम स्क्रीन पर कोनो स्थिति मे मूव आ हॉवर कयल जा सकैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणी:" type="end">
<feature>1. ई अपडेट अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा केँ नहि मेटायत, मुदा तैयो एकटा डेटा बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. सुनिश्चित करू जे अहाँक फोन मे 10 GB सँ बेसी भंडारण स्थान खाली अछि। नहि त'अपडेट विफल भए सकैत अछि (एकर जाँच करबाक लेल सेटिंग्स > भंडारण मे जाउ।)
3. किछु तेसर-पक्षक एप MagicOS 8.0 केर संग अनुकूल नहियो भए सकैत अछि आ अपडेटक बाद किछु खराबी आबि सकैत अछि (जेना कि क्रैश, लैग, असामान्य पावर खपत)। कृपाकए अपन एप सभ केँ AppGallery मे नवीनतम वर्जन मे अपडेट करू। यदि समस्या बनल रहैत अछि त' कृपाकए आबय वला एप अपडेट सभक प्रतीक्षा करू।
4. अपडेट कयलाक बाद, अनुकूलन सभ लागू करबाक लेल सिस्टम एकर सेटिंग्स समायोजित करत। एहि प्रोसेस मे फोन गरम भए सकैत अछि, तेजी सँ पावर केर खपत भए सकैत अछि, लैग उत्पन्न भए सकैत अछि वा चार्ज धीमा भए सकैत अछि। मुदा 2-3 दिनक उपयोग मे ई वापिस सामान्य भए जायत। अपडेट पूरा भए गेलाक बाद आ फोन केँ पुनर्प्रारंभ कयला सँ पहिने, ई सुनिश्चित करबाक लेल जे अनुकूलन सभ लागू भए गेल अछि, हमसभ अनुशंसा करैत छी जे बंद स्क्रीन केर संग 1~2 घंटा धरि चार्ज करू।
5. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन केँ कॉल कए वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र जा कए हमरासभक सहायता लए सकैत छी।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E ngā kaiwhakamahi, kua whakarewaina e tēnei whakahōutanga te MagicOS hōu 8.0|Android 14 māu. He māeneene ake te pūnaha hōu, he haumaru ake, he ngāwari ake te whakamahi, te tiaki hiko ake, ā, he ngahau ētahi anō te mata kāinga. E tūtohu ana mātou kia whakahōu koe. Kia tūtira koa mō ngā whakahōutanga putanga e tū mai nei hei wetemaukati i ētahi anō ngā āhuahira.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tūhura i te mata kāinga">
<feature>【 Ngā tohu mata kāinga】 Ka taea te huri i te rahi o ngā ata mata Kāinga kia tutuki ai ngā hiahia rerekē o ngā kaiwhakamahi. Ka taea e koe te wheako mā te haere: Ngā Tautuhinga - > Mata Kāinga me te kāhua - > Ngā tautuhinga mata kāinga - > Rahi ata.</feature>
<feature>【Pūwhakawhānui Taupānga】 Ināianei ka taea e koe te whakahohe i te Pūwhakawhānui Taupānga mā tētahi tohu ā-pū kotahi. Tōia te raro ki te kokonga mauī o runga, kātahi ka pato i tētahi atu taupānga e tautoko ana i te Pūwhakawhānui Taupānga hei whakaatu taupānga ki ngā matapihi takirua.</feature>
<feature>【matapihi māu】 Ka taea te nuku i te matapihi iti me te whakaparo ki tētahi tūnga i te mata kāinga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore e mukua e tēnei whakahōu ō raraunga whaiaro, engari e tūtohua tonutia ana he pūrua.
2. Me mātua whakarite he neke atu i te 10 GB te mokowā rokiroki wātea o tō waea. Ki te kore, ka rahua pea te whakahōu (Haere ki Ngā tautuhinga > Rokiroki hei tirotiro).
3. Kāore pea ētahi taupānga rōpū kē i te hototahi ki a MagicOS 8.0, ā, ka hapa pea i muri i te whakahōu (pērā i te hinga, whetō, whakapetonga hiko rerekē). Me whakahōu ō taupānga ki te putanga hōu rawa i AppGallery. Mēnā ka raruraru tonu, me tatari mō ngā whakahōu taupānga e heke iho.
4. I muri i te whakahōu, ka whakatika te pūnaha i ngā tautuhinga hei hoatu i ngā arotautanga. I roto i te tukanga, ka wera pea te waea, ka tere te whakapeto hiko, whetō, he pōturi te whakahiko rānei. Engari hoki ki te āhua tika i roto i te 2-3 rā o te whakamahinga. I muri i te otinga o te whakahōu, ā, i mua i te tīmata anō i te waea, e tūtohu ana mātou kia whakahiko ana me te weto o te mata mō te 1~2 hei whakarite kua hoatuna ngā arotautanga.
5. Mēnā ka pā mai he raruraru i te whakahōutanga, ka taea e koe te tiki āwhina mā te waea atu ki te waeawera ratonga a HONOR, te haere rānei ki tētahi Pokapū Ratonga Kiritaki HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитувани корисници, ова ажурирање за вас го воведува сосем новиот MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Новиот систем е погладок, побезбеден, полесен за користење, штеди повеќе енергија и почетниот екран е позабавен. Ви препорачуваме да ажурирате. Бидете во тек за претстојните ажурирања на верзијата за да отклучите повеќе карактеристики.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Истражете го почетниот екран">
<feature>【Икони на почетниот екран】Големината на иконите на почетниот екран може да се прилагоди за да се задоволат различните потреби на корисниците. Може да го искусите тоа со одење во: Нагодување -> Почетен екран и стил -> Поставки за почетниот екран -> Големина на икони.</feature>
<feature>【Проширувач на апликации】 Сега можете да овозможите Проширувач на апликации со еден гест. Повлечете го дното кон горниот лев агол, па допрете ја другата апликација што поддржува Проширувач на апликации за да прикажувате апликации во двоен прозорец.</feature>
<feature>【Лебдечки прозорец】 Мини прозорецот може да се премести и да лебди во која било позиција на почетниот екран.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ова ажурирање нема да ги избрише вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува претходно правење резервна копија.
2. Уверете се дека телефонот има повеќе од 10 GB слободен простор во меморијата. Во спротивно, ажурирањето може да не успее (одете во Нагодување > Меморија за да го проверите).
3. Некои апликации од друг производител може да не се компатибилни со MagicOS 8.0 и може да не работат исправно по ажурирањето (како што се паѓање, заостанување, невообичаена потрошувачка на енергија). Ажурирајте ги вашите апликации со најновата верзија во AppGallery. Ако проблемите продолжуваат, почекајте ги претстојните ажурирања на апликациите.
4. По ажурирањето, системот ќе го прилагоди своето нагодување за да се применат оптимизациите. Во тој процес, телефонот може да се вжешти, брзо да ја троши енергијата, да заостанува или бавно да се полни. Но, ќе се врати во нормала по 2-3 дена употреба. Откако ќе заврши ажурирањето и пред да го престартувате телефонот, препорачуваме да го полните со исклучен екран 1~2 часа за да се осигурате дека се применети оптимизациите.
5. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, може да ја добиете нашата помош со повикување на телефонскиот број на службата на HONOR или посета на Центарот за услуги за корисници на HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താക്കളേ, ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് നിങ്ങൾക്കായി പുതുപുത്തൻ MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 സമാരംഭിച്ചിട്ടുണ്ട്. പുതിയ സിസ്റ്റം സുഗമമായതും സുരക്ഷിതവും ഉപയോഗിക്കാൻ എളുപ്പമുള്ളതും കൂടുതൽ പവർ ലാഭിക്കുന്നതുമാണെന്ന് മാത്രമല്ല, ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ കൂടുതൽ രസകരമായതുമാണ്. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യാൻ ഞങ്ങൾ നിങ്ങളോട് ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു. കൂടുതൽ സവിശേഷതകൾ അൺലോക്ക് ചെയ്യാൻ വരാനിരിക്കുന്ന പതിപ്പ് അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾക്കായി കാത്തിരിക്കുക.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ അടുത്തറിയുക">
<feature>【ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീന്‍ ഐക്കണുകൾ】ഉപയോക്താക്കളുടെ വ്യത്യസ്‌ത ആവശ്യകതകൾ നിറവേറ്റാനായി ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കണുകളുടെ വലുപ്പം ക്രമീകരിക്കാൻ കഴിയും. നിങ്ങൾക്ക് ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് അനുഭവിച്ചറിയാം: ക്രമീകരണം -> ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനും ശൈലിയും -> ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ക്രമീകരണം -> ഐക്കൺ വലുപ്പം.</feature>
<feature>【ആപ്പ് എക്സ്റ്റെൻഡർ】 നിങ്ങൾക്ക് ഇപ്പോൾ ഒരൊറ്റ ഗെസ്‌ചറിൽ ആപ്പ് എക്സ്റ്റെൻഡർ പ്രവർത്തനസജ്ജമാക്കാം. ഇരട്ട വിൻഡോകളിൽ ആപ്പുകൾ പ്രദർശിപ്പിക്കാൻ, ചുവടുഭാഗം മുകളിൽ ഇടതുകോണിലേക്ക് ഡ്രാഗ് ചെയ്‌ത ശേഷം ആപ്പ് എക്സ്റ്റെൻഡറിനെ പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കുന്ന മറ്റൊരു ആപ്പിൽ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
<feature>【ഫ്ലോട്ടിംഗ് വിൻഡോ】 ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനിൽ ഏതൊരു സ്ഥാനത്തേക്കും മിനി വിൻഡോ നീക്കാനും ഹോവർ ചെയ്യാനും കഴിയും.</feature>
</features>
<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്ഡേറ്റ് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ മായ്‌ക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും മുൻകൂട്ടി ഒരു ബാക്കപ്പ് എടുത്തുവയ്‌ക്കാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. നിങ്ങളുടെ ഫോണിൽ 10 GB-യിൽ കൂടുതൽ സംഭരണ സ്ഥലം ഒഴിഞ്ഞ് കിടക്കുന്നുണ്ടെന്ന് ഉറപ്പാക്കുക. അല്ലാത്തപക്ഷം, അപ്ഡേറ്റ് പരാജയപ്പെട്ടേക്കാം. (അത് പരിശോധിക്കാൻ, ക്രമീകരണം > സംഭരണം എന്നതിലേക്ക് പോകുക).
3. ചില മൂന്നാം കക്ഷി ആപ്പുകൾ MagicOS 8.0-ന് അനുയോജ്യമായിരിക്കണമെന്നില്ല, ഇവ അപ്ഡേറ്റിന് ശേഷം തെറ്റായി പ്രവർത്തിച്ചേക്കാം (ക്രാഷാകൽ, മന്ദഗതിയിലാകൽ, അസ്വാഭാവിക പവർ ഉപഭോഗം എന്നിവ പോലുള്ളവ). നിങ്ങളുടെ ആപ്പുകൾ AppGallery-യിലെ ഏറ്റവും പുതിയ പതിപ്പിലേക്ക് അപ്ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുക. പ്രശ്നങ്ങൾ തുടരുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, വരാനിരിക്കുന്ന ആപ്പ് അപ്ഡേറ്റുകൾക്കായി കാത്തിരിക്കുക.
4. അപ്ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്ത ശേഷം, ഒപ്റ്റിമൈസേഷനുകൾ പ്രയോഗിക്കുന്നതിനായി സിസ്റ്റം അതിന്റെ ക്രമീകരണം ക്രമപ്പെടുത്തും. ഈ പ്രക്രിയയ്‌ക്കിടെ, ഫോൺ ചൂടാകുകയോ പവർ വേഗത്തിൽ ഉപഭോഗം ചെയ്യുകയോ മന്ദഗതിയിലാകുകയോ ചാർജ് ചെയ്യുന്നത് സാവധാനമാകുകയോ ചെയ്‌തേക്കാം. എന്നാൽ 2-3 ദിവസത്തെ ഉപയോഗത്തിന് ശേഷം ഇത് സാധാരണ നിലയിലേക്ക് മടങ്ങും. അപ്ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്തതിന് ശേഷവും ഫോൺ പുനരാരംഭിക്കുന്നതിന് മുമ്പും, ഒപ്റ്റിമൈസേഷനുകൾ പ്രയോഗിച്ചിട്ടുണ്ടെന്ന് ഉറപ്പാക്കാനായി സ്ക്രീൻ ഓഫ് ചെയ്ത് ഇത് 1~2 മണിക്കൂർ ചാർജ് ചെയ്യാൻ ഞങ്ങൾ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
5. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്‌ത് ഞങ്ങളുടെ സഹായം കരസ്ഥമാക്കാവുന്നതാണ്.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр танд зориулсан цоо шинэ MagicOS 8.0|Андройд 14 нээлтээ хийлээ. Шинэ систем илүү жигд, илүү найдвартай, хэрэглэхэд хялбар, эрчим хүч илүү хэмнэдэг, үндсэн дэлгэц хэрэглэхэд илүү хөгжилтэй боллоо. Танд шинэчлэхийг зөвлөж байна. Илүү олон онцлог нээхийн тулд удахгүй гарах хувилбарын шинэчлэлтийг хүлээж байгаарай.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Үндсэн дэлгэцийг судлаарай">
<feature>【Үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зураг】Үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зургийн хэмжээг хэрэглэгчдийн янз бүрийн хэрэгцээнд нийцүүлэн тохируулах боломжтой. Та Тохиргоо -> Үндсэн дэлгэц ба хэв маяг -> Үндсэн дэлгэцийн тохиргоо -> Шигтгээ зургийн хэмжээ рүү очиж үүнийг туршиж болно.</feature>
<feature>【Апликэйшн өргөтгөгч】 Та одоо нэг дохио зангаагаар Апликэйшн өргөтгөгчийг идэвхжүүлэх боломжтой боллоо. Доод талыг зүүн дээд булан руу чирээд дараа нь Апликэйшн өргөтгөгчийг дэмждэг өөр апликэйшн дээр товшиж апликэйшнийг давхар цонхонд харуулна уу.</feature>
<feature>【Хөвдөг цонх】 Мини цонхыг үндсэн дэлгэцийн аль ч байрлалд шилжүүлж, зөөх боломжтой.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч урьдчилан нөөцлөхийг зөвлөж байна.
2. Таны утасны хадгалах санд 10 ГБ-с их зай байгаа эсэхийг шалгана уу. Эс бөгөөс шинэчлэх боломжгүй байж болзошгүй. (Тохиргоо > Хадгалах сан руу очиж шалгана уу.)
3. Зарим гуравдагч этгээдийн апликэйшн MagicOS 8.0-той нийцэхгүй байж болох бөгөөд шинэчилсний дараа хэвийн бус ажиллаж болзошгүй (эвдрэх, хоцрох, эрчим хүч хэвийн бус зарцуулах гэх мэт). Апликэйшнээ AppGallery дотроос хамгийн сүүлийн хувилбар луу шинэчилнэ үү. Хэрэв асуудал гарсан хэвээр байвал апликэйшн шинэчлэгдэхийг хүлээнэ үү. 
4. Систем шинэчлэгдсэний дараа оновчлолыг хэрэгжүүлэхийн тулд тохиргоогоо тааруулна. Энэ явцад утас халж, цэнэг хурдан зарцуулж, хоцорч, эсвэл удаан цэнэглэж болзошгүй. Гэвч 2-3 хоног хэрэглэсний дараа хэвийн байдалд шилжинэ. Оновчлол хэрэгжсэн эсэхийг магадлахын тулд шинэчлэгдэж дуусаад, утсаа унтрааж асаахын өмнө дэлгэц унтраалттай үед 1~2 цаг цэнэглэхийг зөвлөж байна.
5 Танд шинэчлэх явцад асуудал тулгарвал HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утсаар залгах буюу HONOR Хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төвд зочилж тусламж авах боломжтой.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्त्यांनो, या अद्यतनाने आपल्यासाठी अगदी नवीन MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 लॉन्‍च केले आहे. नवीन सिस्टम अधिक सोपे, सुरक्षित, वापरण्यास सोपी, अधिक पॉवर वाचवणारी आणि मुख्य स्क्रीन अधिक मजेदार आहे. आम्ही आपल्याला अद्यतनित करण्याची शिफारस करतो. कृपया अधिक वैशिष्ट्ये अनलॉक करण्यासाठी आगामी आवृत्ती अद्यतनांसाठी संपर्कात रहा.</feature>
</features>
<features module="मुख्य स्क्रीन एक्सप्लोर करा">
<feature>【मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्हे】वापरकर्त्यांच्या विविध गरजा पूर्ण करण्यासाठी मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्हांचा आकार समायोजित केला जाऊ शकतो. येथे जाऊन आपण याचा अनुभव घेऊ शकता: सेटिंग्ज -> मुख्य स्क्रीन आणि शैली -> मुख्य स्क्रीन सेटिंग्ज -> चिन्हाचा आकार.</feature>
<feature>【ॲप एक्सटेंडर】 आपण आता एका जेश्चरसह ॲप एक्सटेंडर सक्षम करू शकता. तळाशी वरच्या डाव्या कोपऱ्यात ओढा आणि नंतर दुहेरी विंडोमध्ये ॲप्स प्रदर्शित करण्यासाठी ॲप एक्स्टेंडरला सपोर्ट करणारे अन्य ॲप टॅप करा.</feature>
<feature>【फ्लोटिंग विंडो】 मिनी विंडो मुख्य स्क्रीनवर कोणत्याही स्थितीत हलवली आणि फिरवली जाऊ शकते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन आपला वैयक्तिक डेटा मिटवणार नाही, परंतु आधीच बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. आपल्या फोनमध्ये 10 GB पेक्षा जास्त विनामूल्य संचयन जागा असल्याची खात्री करा. अन्यथा, अद्यतन अयशस्वी होऊ शकते (ते तपासण्यासाठी सेटिंग्ज > संचयन वर जा).
3. काही तृतीय-पक्ष अ‍ॅप्स MagicOS 8.0 शी सुसंगत नसू शकतात आणि अद्यतनानंतर खराब होऊ शकतात (जसे की क्रॅश, लॅग, असामान्य पॉवर वापर). कृपया आपले अ‍ॅप्स AppGallery मधील नवीनतम आवृत्तीवर अद्यतनित करा. समस्या कायम राहिल्यास, कृपया आगामी अ‍ॅप अद्यतनांची प्रतीक्षा करा.
4. अद्यतनित केल्यानंतर, ऑप्टिमायझेशन लागू करण्यासाठी सिस्टम त्याच्या सेटिंग्ज समायोजित करेल. प्रक्रियेत, फोन गरम होऊ शकतो, पॉवर जलद वापरतो, लॅग होऊ शकतो किंवा हळू चार्ज होऊ शकतो. परंतु ते वापरल्यानंतर 2-3 दिवसात सामान्य होईल. अद्यतन पूर्ण झाल्यानंतर आणि फोन पुन्हा प्रारंभ करण्यापूर्वी, ऑप्टिमायझेशन लागू झाले आहेत याची खात्री करण्यासाठी आम्ही 1~2 तास स्क्रीन बंद ठेवून चार्ज करण्याची शिफारस करतो.
5. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, आपण HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करून किंवा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्राला भेट देऊन आमची मदत मिळवू शकता.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini ini telah melancarkan MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 serba baharu untuk anda. Sistem baharu ini lebih lancar, lebih selamat, lebih mudah untuk digunakan, lebih menjimatkan kuasa dan skrin utama lebih menarik. Kami mengesyorkan agar anda membuat kemas kini. Sila nantikan kemas kini versi akan datang untuk membuka lebih banyak ciri.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Terokai skrin utama">
<feature>【Ikon Skrin utama】Saiz ikon Skrin utama boleh dilaraskan untuk memenuhi keperluan pengguna yang berbeza. Anda boleh mencuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan -> Skrin utama dan gaya -> Tetapan skrin utama -> Saiz ikon.</feature>
<feature>【Pelanjut Aplikasi】 Anda kini boleh mendayakan Pelanjut Aplikasi dengan satu gerak isyarat. Seret bahagian bawah ke penjuru kiri sebelah atas, kemudian ketik aplikasi lain yang menyokong Pelanjut Aplikasi untuk memaparkan aplikasi dalam dwi tetingkap.</feature>
<feature>【Tetingkap apungan】 Tetingkap mini boleh dialihkan dan hover ke mana-mana kedudukan pada skrin utama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kemas kini ini tidak akan memadamkan data peribadi anda tetapi anda masih disyorkan untuk membuat sandaran terlebih dahulu.
2. Pastikan telefon anda mempunyai lebih daripada 10 GB ruang storan bebas. Jika tidak, kemas kini mungkin gagal (Pergi ke Tetapan > Storan untuk menyemak).
3. Sesetengah aplikasi pihak ketiga mungkin tidak serasi dengan MagicOS 8.0 dan mungkin tidak berfungsi selepas kemas kini (seperti runtuh, ketinggalan, penggunaan kuasa yang tidak normal). Sila kemas kini aplikasi anda kepada versi terkini dalam AppGallery. Jika masalah berterusan, sila tunggu kemas kini aplikasi akan datang.
4. Selepas mengemas kini, sistem akan melaraskan tetapannya untuk menggunakan pengoptimuman. Dalam proses itu, telefon mungkin menjadi panas, menggunakan kuasa dengan cepat, ketinggalan atau mengecas dengan perlahan. Tetapi ia akan kembali normal dalam masa 2-3 hari penggunaan. Selepas kemas kini selesai dan sebelum memulakan semula telefon, kami mengesyorkan mengecas telefon dengan skrin dimatikan selama 1~2 jam untuk memastikan pengoptimuman digunakan.
5. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa melakukan kemas kini ini, anda boleh mendapatkan bantuan daripada kami dengan menghubungi talian penting perkhidmatan HONOR atau melawati Pusat Khidmat Pelanggan HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူများ၊ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်တွင် သင့်အတွက် အသစ်စက်စက် MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 ပါဝင်သည်။ စနစ်သစ်သည် ပိုချောမွေ့ပြီး ပို၍အန္တရာယ်ကင်းကာ သုံးရပိုလွယ်ကူ၍ ပါဝါကို ပိုမိုချွေတာပေးသည့်အပြင် ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်သည် ပို၍နှစ်သက်စဖွယ်ဖြစ်သည်။ အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ရန် သင့်အား အကြံပြုပါသည်။ နောက်ထပ်လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များကို လော့ခ်ဖွင့်ရန် လာမည့်ဗားရှင်းအပ်ဒိတ်များကို နားစွင့်နေပါ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်ကို စူးစမ်းလေ့လာခြင်း">
<feature>【ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် အိုင်ကွန်များ】သုံးစွဲသူများ၏ လိုအပ်ချက်အမျိုးမျိုးနှင့် ကိုက်ညီစေရန် ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် အိုင်ကွန်များ၏ အရွယ်အစားကို ချိန်ညှိနိုင်သည်။ သင်သည် ဆက်တင် -> ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်နှင့် စတိုင် -> ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် ဆက်တင် -> အိုင်ကွန် အရွယ်အစားသို့ သွား၍ ၎င်းကို တွေ့ကြုံသုံးစွဲနိုင်သည်။</feature>
<feature>【အက်ပ်တိုးချဲ့】 ယခုအခါ လက်ဟန်တစ်ခုတည်းဖြင့် အက်ပ်တိုးချဲ့ကို ဖွင့်နိုင်ပါပြီ။ အောက်ခြေကို အပေါ်ဘယ်ဘက်ထောင့်သို့ ဆွဲရွှေ့ပြီးနောက် အက်ပ်များကို ဝင်းဒိုးနှစ်ခုဖြင့် ပြသရန် အက်ပ်တိုးချဲ့ သုံးနိုင်သော အခြားအက်ပ်ကို နှိပ်ပါ။</feature>
<feature>【Floating ဝင်းဒိုး】 မီနီဝင်းဒိုးကို ရွှေ့နိုင်ပြီး ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်ရှိ မည်သည့်နေရာသို့မဆို လေပေါ်ဝဲနိုင်သည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာကို ဖျက်ပစ်မည်မဟုတ်သော်လည်း ကြိုတင်၍ ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ထားရန်လည်း အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. သင့်ဖုန်းတွင် သိုလှောင်မှု နေရာလွတ် 10 GB အထက်ရှိကြောင်း သေချာအောင်လုပ်ပါ။ သို့မဟုတ်ပါက အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်နိုင်မည် မဟုတ်ပါ (၎င်းကိုစစ်ဆေးရန် ဆက်တင် > သိုလှောင်မှုသို့ သွားပါ)။
3. ပြင်ပ အဖွဲ့အစည်း အက်ပ်အချို့သည် MagicOS 8.0 နှင့် မကိုက်ညီနိုင်သဖြင့် အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ပြီးနောက် (ပျက်စီးခြင်း၊ ထစ်ခြင်း၊ ပါဝါသုံးစွဲမှု မူမမှန်ခြင်းကဲ့သို့) လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်မူမမှန်ခြင်း ဖြစ်ပေါ်နိုင်ပါသည်။ သင့်အက်ပ်များကို AppGallery တွင် နောက်ဆုံးထွက်ဗားရှင်းသို့ အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ပါ။ ပြဿနာ ဆက်ရှိနေသေးပါက လာမည့် အက်ပ် အပ်ဒိတ်များကို စောင့်ပေးပါ။
4. အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ပြီးနောက် စနစ်သည် အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိမှုများကို အသုံးပြုရန် ၎င်း၏ဆက်တင်များကို ချိန်ညှိပါမည်။ ဆောင်ရွက်နေစဉ်တွင် ဖုန်းပူလာခြင်း၊ ပါဝါသုံးစွဲမှု မြန်ခြင်း၊ ထစ်ခြင်း သို့မဟုတ် အားသွင်းမှု နှောင့်နှေးခြင်းတို့ ဖြစ်နိုင်ပါသည်။သို့သော် 2-3 ရက် အသုံးပြုပြီးချိန်တွင် ပုံမှန်ပြန်ဖြစ်ပါမည်။ အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်ပြီးနောက် ဖုန်းကို ပြန်လည်မစတင်မီ အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိမှုများကို အသုံးပြုကြောင်း သေချာစေရန် 1~2 နာရီကြာ မျက်နှာပြင်ပိတ်၍ အားသွင်းရန် ကျွန်ုပ်တို့ အကြံပြုပါသည်။
5. အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်စဉ်အတွင်း ပြဿနာတစ်စုံတစ်ရာနှင့် ကြုံရပါက HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှု ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆို၍ဖြစ်စေ၊ HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားရောက်၍ဖြစ်စေ ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ အကူအညီကို ရယူနိုင်ပါသည်။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူမ်ား၊ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္တြင္ သင့္အတြက္ အသစ္စက္စက္ MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 ပါဝင္သည္။ စနစ္သစ္သည္ ပိုေခ်ာေမြ႕ၿပီး ပို၍အႏၲရာယ္ကင္းကာ သုံးရပိုလြယ္ကူ၍ ပါဝါကို ပိုမိုေခြၽတာေပးသည့္အျပင္ ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္သည္ ပို၍ႏွစ္သက္စဖြယ္ျဖစ္သည္။ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ရန္ သင့္အား အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။ ေနာက္ထပ္လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ားကို ေလာ့ခ္ဖြင့္ရန္ လာမည့္ဗားရွင္းအပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားကို နားစြင့္ေနပါ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ကို စူးစမ္းေလ့လာျခင္း">
<feature>【ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ား】သုံးစြဲသူမ်ား၏ လိုအပ္ခ်က္အမ်ိဳးမ်ိဳးႏွင့္ ကိုက္ညီေစရန္ ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ား၏ အ႐ြယ္အစားကို ခ်ိန္ညႇိႏိုင္သည္။ သင္သည္ ဆက္တင္ -> ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ႏွင့္ စတိုင္ -> ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ ဆက္တင္ -> အိုင္ကြန္ အ႐ြယ္အစားသို႔ သြား၍ ၎ကို ေတြ႕ႀကဳံသုံးစြဲႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
<feature>【အက္ပ္တိုးခ်ဲ႕】 ယခုအခါ လက္ဟန္တစ္ခုတည္းျဖင့္ အက္ပ္တိုးခ်ဲ႕ကို ဖြင့္ႏိုင္ပါၿပီ။ ေအာက္ေျခကို အေပၚဘယ္ဘက္ေထာင့္သို႔ ဆြဲေ႐ႊ႕ၿပီးေနာက္ အက္ပ္မ်ားကို ဝင္းဒိုးႏွစ္ခုျဖင့္ ျပသရန္ အက္ပ္တိုးခ်ဲ႕ သုံးႏိုင္ေသာ အျခားအက္ပ္ကို ႏွိပ္ပါ။</feature>
<feature>【Floating ဝင္းဒိုး】 မီနီဝင္းဒိုးကို ေ႐ႊ႕ႏိုင္ၿပီး ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ရွိ မည္သည့္ေနရာသို႔မဆို ေလေပၚဝဲႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာကို ဖ်က္ပစ္မည္မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း ႀကိဳတင္၍ ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ထားရန္လည္း အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. သင့္ဖုန္းတြင္ သိုေလွာင္မႈ ေနရာလြတ္ 10 GB အထက္ရွိေၾကာင္း ေသခ်ာေအာင္လုပ္ပါ။ သို႔မဟုတ္ပါက အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ႏိုင္မည္ မဟုတ္ပါ (၎ကိုစစ္ေဆးရန္ ဆက္တင္ > သိုေလွာင္မႈသို႔ သြားပါ)။
3. ျပင္ပ အဖြဲ႕အစည္း အက္ပ္အခ်ိဳ႕သည္ MagicOS 8.0 ႏွင့္ မကိုက္ညီႏိုင္သျဖင့္ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ၿပီးေနာက္ (ပ်က္စီးျခင္း၊ ထစ္ျခင္း၊ ပါဝါသုံးစြဲမႈ မူမမွန္ျခင္းကဲ့သို႔) လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မူမမွန္ျခင္း ျဖစ္ေပၚႏိုင္ပါသည္။ သင့္အက္ပ္မ်ားကို AppGallery တြင္ ေနာက္ဆုံးထြက္ဗားရွင္းသို႔ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ပါ။ ျပႆနာ ဆက္ရွိေနေသးပါက လာမည့္ အက္ပ္ အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားကို ေစာင့္ေပးပါ။
4. အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ၿပီးေနာက္ စနစ္သည္ အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိမႈမ်ားကို အသုံးျပဳရန္ ၎၏ဆက္တင္မ်ားကို ခ်ိန္ညႇိပါမည္။ ေဆာင္႐ြက္ေနစဥ္တြင္ ဖုန္းပူလာျခင္း၊ ပါဝါသုံးစြဲမႈ ျမန္ျခင္း၊ ထစ္ျခင္း သို႔မဟုတ္ အားသြင္းမႈ ေႏွာင့္ေႏွးျခင္းတို႔ ျဖစ္ႏိုင္ပါသည္။သို႔ေသာ္ 2-3 ရက္ အသုံးျပဳၿပီးခ်ိန္တြင္ ပုံမွန္ျပန္ျဖစ္ပါမည္။ အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ၿပီးေနာက္ ဖုန္းကို ျပန္လည္မစတင္မီ အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိမႈမ်ားကို အသုံးျပဳေၾကာင္း ေသခ်ာေစရန္ 1~2 နာရီၾကာ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ပိတ္၍ အားသြင္းရန္ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
5. အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္စဥ္အတြင္း ျပႆနာတစ္စုံတစ္ရာႏွင့္ ႀကဳံရပါက HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈ ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆို၍ျဖစ္ေစ၊ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားေရာက္၍ျဖစ္ေစ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ အကူအညီကို ရယူႏိုင္ပါသည္။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, denne oppdateringen har lansert den helt nye MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 for deg. Det nye systemet kjører jevnere, er tryggere og enklere å bruke, sparer mer batteri og startskjermen er mer fornøyelig. Vi anbefaler at du oppdaterer. Følg med for kommende versjonsoppdateringer for å låse opp flere funksjoner.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Utforsk startskjermen">
<feature>[Startskjermikoner]Størrelsen på startskjermikonene kan justeres for å møte brukernes ulike behov. Du kan prøve selv ved å gå til: Innstillinger -> Startskjerm og stil -> Innstillinger for startskjerm -> Ikonstørrelse.</feature>
<feature>【App-utvidelse】 Du kan nå aktivere App-utvidelse med en enkelt bevegelse. Dra bunnen til øverste venstre hjørne og trykk deretter på den andre appen som støtter App-utvidelse for å vise appene i doble vinduer.</feature>
<feature>【Svevende vindu】 Minivindu kan flyttes og settes over enhver posisjon på startskjermen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Denne oppdateringen vil ikke slette personopplysningene dine, men det anbefales likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer på forhånd.
2. Sørg for at telefonen har mer enn 10 GB ledig lagringsplass. Hvis ikke kan oppdateringen mislyktes (Gå til Innstillinger > Lagring for å sjekke).
3. Det er mulig at enkelte tredjeparts-apper ikke er kompatible med MagicOS 8.0 og kan oppleve feil etter oppdateringen (som krasj, forsinkelse og unormal batteribruk). Oppdater appene dine til den nyeste versjonen i AppGallery. Vent på kommende appoppdateringer hvis problemet vedvarer.
4. Etter oppdatering vil systemet justere innstillingene for å anvende optimeringene. Telefonen kan bli varm, bruke batteri raskt, oppleve forsinkelser eller lade sakte under prosessen. Den vil gå tilbake til normalt innen 2 – 3 dager med bruk. Etter at oppdateringen er ferdig og før du starter telefonen på nytt, anbefaler vi at du lader med skjermen av i 1 ~ 2 timer for å sørge for at optimeringene anvendes.
5. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, kan du få hjelp av oss ved å ringe til HONOR-kundeservice eller besøke et HONOR-kundeservicesenter.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ताहरू, यो अपडेटमा तपाईंका लागि बिल्कुलै नयाँ MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 लन्च गरिएको छ । यो नयाँ प्रणाली अझ बढी सहज, सुरक्षित, प्रयोग गर्न अझ धेरै सजिलो र अझ धेरै पावर बचत गर्ने खालको छ र गृह स्क्रिन अझ रमाइलो बनाइएको छ । हामी तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्न सिफारिस गर्छौँ । कृपया थप सुविधाहरू अनलक गर्न आगामी संस्करणका अपडेटका बारेमा सुसूचित रहनुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गृह स्क्रिनको अन्वेषण गर्नुहोस्">
<feature>【गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरू】प्रयोगकर्ताका फरक फरक आवश्यकताहरू पूरा गर्नका लागि गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरूको आकार बदल्न मिल्छ । तपाईंले यहाँ गएर यसको अनुभव लिन सक्नुहुन्छ: सेटिङहरू -> गृह स्क्रिन र शैली -> गृह स्क्रिन सेटिङहरू -> आइकनको साइज ।</feature>
<feature>【एप एक्स्टेन्डर】 तपाईं अब एकल इशारा प्रयोग गरी एप एक्स्टेन्डर सक्षम गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ । पुछारको भागलाई तानेर सिरानको बायाँ कुनामा लैजानुहोस् अनि एपहरूलाई डुअल विन्डोमा देखाउन एप एक्स्टेन्डर प्रयोग गर्न मिल्ने अन्य एपहरूमा ट्याप गर्नुहोस् ।</feature>
<feature>【फ्लोटिङ विन्डो】 मिनी विन्डो सार्न सकिन्छ र गृह स्क्रिनमा कुनै पनि स्थानमा होभर गर्न सकिन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. यो अद्यावधिकले तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटा मेट्ने छैन तर पहिले नै डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न अझै पनि सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. तपाईंको फोनमा 10 GB भन्दा धेरै भण्डारण ठाउँ खाली छ भनी सुनिश्चित गर्नुहोस् । अन्यथा, अद्यावधिक असफल हुन सक्छ (यसलाई जाँच गर्न सेटिङहरू > भण्डारणमा जानुहोस्) ।
3. केही तेस्रो-पक्ष एपहरू MagicOS 8.0 सँग अनुकूल नहुन सक्छन् र अद्यावधिक भएपछि खराबी आउन सक्छ (जस्तै क्र्यास हुने, ल्याग हुने, असामान्य रूपमा पावर खपत हुने) । कृपया आफ्ना एपहरूलाई AppGallery को नवीनतम संस्करणमा अद्यावधिक गर्नुहोस् । समस्याहरू भइरहेमा, कृपया आगामी एप अद्यावधिकहरू प्रतीक्षा गर्नुहोस् ।
4. अद्यावधिक गरेपछि, प्रणालीले अप्टिमाइजेसनहरू लागू गर्नका लागि आफ्ना सेटिङहरू समायोजन गर्ने छ । उक्त प्रक्रियामा, फोन तातो हुन, पावर छिटो खपत गर्न, ल्याग हुन वा बिस्तारै चार्ज हुन सक्छ । तर 2-3 दिन प्रयोग गरेपछि यो सामान्य स्थितिमा फर्कने छ । अद्यावधिक पूरा भएपछि र फोन फेरि सुरु गर्नुअघि, हामी अप्टिमाइजेसनहरू लागू भएका छन् भनी सुनिश्चित गर्नका लागि फोनलाई स्क्रिन अफ राखेर 1~ 2 घण्टा चार्ज गर्न सिफारिस गर्छौँ ।
5. तपाईंले अद्यावधिको अवधिमा कुनै पनि समस्या सामना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईं HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गरेर वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा गएर हाम्रो मद्दत प्राप्त गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruikers, deze update heeft de gloednieuwe MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 voor u gelanceerd. Het nieuwe systeem is vloeiender, veiliger, gebruiksvriendelijker, energiezuiniger en het startscherm is leuker. We raden u aan om bij te werken. Blijf op de hoogte van aankomende versie-updates om meer functies te ontgrendelen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Het startscherm verkennen">
<feature>【Startschermpictogrammen】De grootte van Startschermpictogrammen kan worden aangepast aan de verschillende behoeften van de gebruikers. U kunt het ervaren via: Instellingen -> Startscherm en stijl -> Startscherminstellingen -> Pictogramgrootte.</feature>
<feature>【App-uitbreider】 U kunt nu App-uitbreider inschakelen met één enkel gebaar. Sleep de onderkant naar de linkerbovenhoek en tik vervolgens op de andere app die App-uitbreider ondersteunt om apps in dubbele vensters weer te geven.</feature>
<feature>【Zwevend venster】 Minivenster kan worden verplaatst en naar elke positie op het startscherm worden bewogen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Deze update zal uw persoonlijke gegevens niet wissen, maar een back-up vooraf wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Zorg ervoor dat uw telefoon meer dan 10 GB vrije opslagruimte heeft. Anders kan de update mislukken (ga naar Instellingen > Opslag om dit te controleren).
3. Sommige apps van derden zijn mogelijk niet compatibel met MagicOS 8.0 en kunnen na de update defect raken (zoals crash, vertraging, abnormaal energieverbruik). Werk uw apps bij naar de nieuwste versie in AppGallery. Als de problemen aanhouden, wacht dan op aankomende app-updates.
4. Na het updaten zal het systeem zijn instellingen aanpassen om de optimalisaties toe te passen. Tijdens het proces kan de telefoon warm worden, snel energie verbruiken, vertragen of langzaam opladen. Maar de telefoon zal terugkeren naar normaal binnen 2-3 dagen van gebruik. Nadat de update is voltooid en voordat de telefoon opnieuw wordt gestart, raden we aan deze 1 tot 2 uur op te laden met het scherm uit om ervoor te zorgen dat de optimalisaties worden toegepast.
5. Als u tijdens de update problemen ondervindt, kunt u onze hulp krijgen door te bellen met de HONOR-servicehotline of een bezoek te brengen aan een klantenservicecentrum van HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତାଗଣ, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ପାଇଁ ବ୍ରାଣ୍ଡ-ନୂଆ MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 ଲଞ୍ଚ କରିଛି। ନୂତନ ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସ୍ମୁଦର, ନିରାପଦ, ବ୍ୟବହାର କରିବାରେ ସହଜ, ଅଧିକ ପାୱାର ସଞ୍ଚୟ କରେ, ଏବଂ ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଆହୁରି ମଜାଦାର। ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବାକୁ ଆମେ ଆପଣଙ୍କୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରୁ। ଆହୁରି ଅଧିକ ବିଶେଷତା ଅନଲକ୍‌ କରିବାକୁ ଆଗନ୍ତ ସଂସ୍କରଣ ଅପଡେଟ୍ ଉପରେ ନଜର ରଖନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌‌ଟି ଏକ୍ସପ୍ଲୋର୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ">
<feature>【ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍‌】ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକର ଆକାର ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତାଙ୍କ ବିଭିନ୍ନ ଆବଶ୍ୟକତା ପୂରଣ କରିବାକୁ ଆଡଜଷ୍ଟ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଆପଣ ଏହାର ଅନୁଭୂତି ନେଇପାରିବେ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ -> ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଏବଂ ଷ୍ଟାଇଲ୍‌ -> ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ସେଟିଂସ୍ -> ଆଇକନ୍‌‌‌ର ଆକାର।</feature>
<feature>【ଆପ୍‌ ପରିବର୍ଦ୍ଧକ】 ଗୋଟିଏ ଜେଶ୍ଚର୍‌ରେ ଆପଣ ବର୍ତ୍ତମାନ ଆପ୍‌ ପରିବର୍ଦ୍ଧକ ସକ୍ଷମ କରିପାରିବେ। ନିମ୍ନକୁ ଉପର ବାମ କୋଣକୁ ଡ୍ରାଗ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ, ଏବଂ ତାପରେ ଡୁଆଲ୍‌ ୱିଣ୍ଡୋସ୍‌ରେ ଆପସ୍‌ ପ୍ରଦର୍ଶନ କରିବାକୁ ଆପ୍‌ ପରିବର୍ଦ୍ଧକ ସମର୍ଥନ କରୁଥିବା ଅନ୍ୟ ଆପ୍‌କୁ ଟ୍ୟାପ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
<feature>【ଭାସମାନ ୱିଣ୍ଡୋ】 ଛୋଟ ୱିଣ୍ଡୋ ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌‌ରେ ଯେକୌଣସି ସ୍ଥିତିକୁ ଘୁଞ୍ଚାଯାଇ ପାରିବ ଏବଂ ହୋଭର୍‌ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ବିଲୋପ କରିବ ନାହିଁ, କିନ୍ତୁ ଏକ ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ତଥାପି ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ନିଶ୍ଚିତ କରନ୍ତୁ ଯେ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଫୋନ୍‌ରେ 10 GBରୁ ଅଧିକ ମୁକ୍ତ ଷ୍ଟୋରେଜ୍‌ ସ୍ପେସ୍‌ ରହିଛି। ଅନ୍ୟଥା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ବିଫଳ ହୋଇପାରେ (ଏହା ଯାଞ୍ଚ କରିବାକୁ, ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ଷ୍ଟୋରେଜ୍‌କୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ)।
3. କିଛି ତୃତୀୟ ପକ୍ଷ ଆପସ୍ MagicOS 8.0 ସହ ସୁସଙ୍ଗତ ହୋଇନପାରେ ଏବଂ ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରାଯିବା ପରେ ମାଲଫଙ୍କସନ୍ ହୋଇପାରେ (ଯେପରିକି କ୍ରାସ୍ ହେବା, ମନ୍ଥର, ଅସାମାନ୍ୟ ପାୱାର୍ ଖର୍ଚ୍ଚ)। ଦୟାକରି AppGalleryରେ ନିଜ ଆପସ୍‌କୁ ସର୍ବନୂତନ ସଂସ୍କରଣକୁ ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ। ଯଦି ସମସ୍ୟାଟି ତଥାପି ରହେ, ଦୟାକରି ଆଗନ୍ତ ଆପ୍ ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ‌ ପାଇଁ ଅପେକ୍ଷା କରନ୍ତୁ।
4. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବା ପରେ, ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜେସନ୍‌ ଲାଗୁ ଲରିକରିବାକୁ ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ ଏହାର ସେଟିଂସ୍‌ ଆଡଜଷ୍ଟ କରିବ। ପ୍ରକ୍ରିୟାଟିରେ, ଫୋନ୍‌‌ଟି ଗରମ ହୋଇପାରେ, ଦ୍ରୁତ ଭାବେ ପାୱାର୍‌ ଖର୍ଚ୍ଚ କରିପାରେ, ମନ୍ଥର ହୋଇପାରେ, କିମ୍ବା ଧିରେ ଚାର୍ଜ ହୋଇପାରେ। କିନ୍ତୁ ଏହା ବ୍ୟବହାର କରାଯିବା 2-3ଦିନ ଭିତରେ ସାମାନ୍ୟ ଅବସ୍ଥାକୁ ଫେରିବ। ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜେସନ୍‌ ଲାଗୁ କରାଯାଇଥିବା ନିଶ୍ଚିତ କରିବାକୁ, ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରାଯିବା ପରେ ଏବଂ ଫୋନ୍‌ଟି ପୁନରାରମ୍ଭ କରାଯିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ, ଏହାର ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଅଫ୍‌ କରି 1~2 ଘଣ୍ଟା ପାଇଁ ଚାର୍ଜ କରିବାକୁ ଆମେ ସୁପାରିଶ କରୁ।
5. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବା ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଆପଣ HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌କୁ କଲ୍‌ କରି କିମ୍ବା HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଇ, ଆମ ସହାୟତା ପାଇପାରିବେ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਲਈ ਬਿਲਕੁਲ ਨਵੇਂ MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 ਨੂੰ ਲਾਂਚ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਨਵਾਂ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਵਧੇਰੇ ਨਿਰਵਿਘਨ, ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ, ਵਰਤੋਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਆਸਾਨ, ਵਧੇਰੇ ਪਾਵਰ-ਬੱਚਤ ਵਾਲਾ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਵਧੇਰੇ ਮਜ਼ੇਦਾਰ ਹੈ। ਅਸੀਂ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕਰਦੇ ਹਾਂ। ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਹੋਰ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਅਨਲੌਕ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਅਗਾਮੀ ਸੰਸਕਰਣ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਲਈ ਬਣੇ ਰਹੋ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਦੀ ਪੜਚੋਲ ਕਰੋ">
<feature>【ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨ】ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰਾਂ ਦੀਆਂ ਵਿਭਿੰਨ ਲੋੜਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਪੂਰਾ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨਾਂ ਦਾ ਆਕਾਰ ਵਿਵਸਥਿਤ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਤੁਸੀਂ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਦਾ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ -> ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਅਤੇ ਸ਼ੈਲੀ -> ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ -> ਆਈਕੋਨ ਦਾ ਆਕਾਰ।</feature>
<feature>【ਐਪ ਐਕਸਟੈਂਡਰ】 ਹੁਣ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਇੱਕ ਜੈਸਚਰ ਨਾਲ ਐਪ ਐਕਸਟੈਂਡਰ ਨੂੰ ਸਮਰੱਥ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ। ਹੇਠਲੇ ਪਾਸੇ ਨੂੰ ਖਿੱਚ ਕੇ ਉੱਪਰਲੇ ਖੱਬੇ ਕੋਨੇ 'ਤੇ ਲੈ ਜਾਓ, ਅਤੇ ਉਸਤੋਂ ਬਾਅਦ ਡੂਅਲ ਵਿੰਡੋਜ਼ ਵਿੱਚ ਐਪਾਂ ਡਿਸਪਲੇ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਐਪ ਐਕਸਟੈਂਡਰ ਦਾ ਸਮਰਥਨ ਕਰਨ ਵਾਲੀ ਦੂਜੀ ਐਪ 'ਤੇ ਟੈਪ ਕਰੋ।</feature>
<feature>【ਫਲੋਟਿੰਗ ਵਿੰਡੋ】 ਮਿੰਨੀ ਵਿੰਡੋ ਨੂੰ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਿਸੇ ਵੀ ਸਥਿਤੀ ਵਿੱਚ ਲਿਜਾਇਆ ਅਤੇ ਘੁੰਮਾਇਆ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਹ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡਾਟੇ ਨੂੰ ਨਹੀਂ ਮਿਟਾਏਗੀ, ਪਰ ਫਿਰ ਵੀ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਯਕੀਨੀ ਬਣਾਓ ਕਿ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਫ਼ੋਨ ਵਿੱਚ 10 GB ਤੋਂ ਵੱਧ ਸਟੋਰੇਜ਼ ਲਈ ਥਾਂ ਖ਼ਾਲੀ ਹੋਵੇ। ਨਹੀਂ ਤਾਂ, ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਅਸਫਲ ਹੋ ਸਕਦੀ ਹੈ (ਇਸ ਦੀ ਜਾਂਚ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਸਟੋਰੇਜ਼ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ)।
3. ਕੁਝ ਤੀਜੀ-ਧਿਰ ਦੀਆਂ ਐਪਾਂ MagicOS 8.0 ਲਈ ਢਕਵੀਆਂ ਨਹੀਂ ਹੋ ਸਕਦੀਆਂ ਅਤੇ ਹੋ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ ਕਿ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਤੋਂ ਬਾਅਦ ਖਰਾਬੀ ਕਰਨ (ਜਿਵੇਂ ਕਿ ਕ੍ਰੈਸ਼, ਦੇਰੀ, ਅਸਧਾਰਨ ਰੂਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਪਾਵਰ ਖਪਤ)। ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਆਪਣੀਆਂ ਐਪਾਂ ਨੂੰ AppGallery ਵਿੱਚ ਨਵੀਨਤਮ ਸੰਸਕਰਣ ਵਿੱਚ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰੋ। ਜੇ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਬਣੀ ਰਹਿੰਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਆਉਣ ਵਾਲੀ ਐਪ ਸੰਬੰਧੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੀ ਉਡੀਕ ਕਰੋ।
4. ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਬਾਅਦ, ਸਿਸਟਮ ਅਨੁਕੂਲਤਾਵਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਲਾਗੂ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਆਪਣੀਆਂ ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਵਿਵਸਥਿਤ ਕਰੇਗਾ। ਪ੍ਰਕਿਰਿਆ ਵਿੱਚ, ਫ਼ੋਨ ਗਰਮ ਹੋ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ, ਪਾਵਰ ਦੀ ਤੇਜ਼ੀ ਨਾਲ ਖਪਤ ਕਰ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ, ਦੇਰੀ ਕਰ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ, ਜਾਂ ਹੌਲੀ-ਹੌਲੀ ਚਾਰਜ ਹੋ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਪਰ ਵਰਤਣ ਨਾਲ 2-3 ਦਿਨਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਇਹ ਮੁੜ ਤੋਂ ਆਮ ਵਾਂਗ ਕੰਮ ਕਰੇਗਾ। ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਹੋ ਜਾਣ ਤੋਂ ਬਾਅਦ ਅਤੇ ਫ਼ੋਨ ਨੂੰ ਰੀਸਟਾਰਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ, ਅਸੀਂ ਇਸ ਨੂੰ 1~2 ਘੰਟਿਆਂ ਲਈ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਬੰਦ ਕਰਕੇ ਚਾਰਜ ਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਿਸ਼ ਕਰਦੇ ਹਾਂ ਤਾਂ ਜੋ ਇਹ ਯਕੀਨੀ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਜਾ ਸਕੇ ਕਿ ਅਨੁਕੂਲਤਾਵਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਲਾਗੂ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।
5. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰਕੇ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਮਦਦ ਲੈ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja wprowadza zupełnie nowy system MagicOS 8.0 | Android 14. Działa on płynniej, jest bezpieczniejszy i łatwiejszy w użyciu oraz zużywa mniej energii, a z ekranu głównego korzysta się jeszcze przyjemniej. Zaleca się zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji i oczekiwanie na kolejne, w których odblokowanych zostanie jeszcze więcej funkcji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznaj ekran główny">
<feature>[Ikony na ekranie głównym] Rozmiar ikon na Ekranie głównym można dostosować do różnych potrzeb użytkowników. W tym celu wybierz Ustawienia -> Ekran główny i styl -> Ustawienia ekranu głównego -> Rozmiar ikon.</feature>
<feature>[Rozszerzone wyświetlanie aplikacji] Rozszerzone wyświetlanie aplikacji można teraz włączać jednym gestem. Przeciągnij dół do lewego górnego rogu, a następnie dotknij innej aplikacji obsługującej Rozszerzone wyświetlanie aplikacji, aby wyświetlić aplikacje w dwóch oknach.</feature>
<feature>[Okno przestawne] Małe okno można przenosić i ustawiać w dowolnej pozycji na ekranie głównym.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ta aktualizacja nie powoduje wymazania danych użytkownika, jednak zalecamy uprzednie wykonanie kopii zapasowej.
2. Upewnij się, że telefon ma ponad 10 GB wolnej pamięci, ponieważ niewystarczająca ilość miejsca może spowodować niepowodzenie aktualizacji (przejdź do opcji Ustawienia > Pamięć, aby sprawdzić ilość dostępnego miejsca).
3. Niektóre aplikacje innych firm mogą nie być zgodne z MagicOS 8.0 i mogą nie działać prawidłowo po aktualizacji (mogą ulegać awarii, działać z opóźnieniem lub powodować nietypowe zużycie energii). Zaktualizuj aplikacje do najnowszej wersji w AppGallery. Jeśli problem będzie się utrzymywał, poczekaj na pojawienie się aktualizacji aplikacji.
4. Po aktualizacji system dostosuje ustawienia w celu przeprowadzenia optymalizacji. W trakcie tego procesu telefon może być gorący, działać z opóźnieniem, szybko zużywać energię lub ładować się powoli. W ciągu 2–3 dni powróci do stanu normalnej eksploatacji. Po przeprowadzeniu aktualizacji i przed ponownym uruchomieniem telefonu zalecamy ładowanie go przez 1~2 godziny z wyłączonym ekranem, aby mieć pewność, że optymalizacja została przeprowadzona.
5. Jeśli napotkasz jakiś problem podczas aktualizacji, zadzwoń na infolinię HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy HONOR, aby uzyskać pomoc.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caros usuários, esta atualização lançou o novo MagicOS 8.0 | Android 14 para vocês. O novo sistema é mais suave, mais seguro, mais fácil de usar, proporciona mais economia de energia e tem uma tela inicial mais divertida. Recomendamos que você faça a atualização. Preste atenção às próximas atualizações de versão para desbloquear mais recursos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Explore a tela inicial">
<feature>【Tamanho dos ícones da Tela inicial】O tamanho dos ícones da Tela inicial pode ser ajustado para atender às diferentes necessidades dos usuários. Você pode experimentar acessando: Configurações -> Tela inicial e estilo -> Configurações da Tela inicial -> Tamanho do ícone.</feature>
<feature>【Extensor de aplicativo】 Agora é possível ativar o Extensor de aplicativo com um único gesto. Arraste a parte inferior para a superior esquerda, depois toque no outro aplicativo compatível com o Extensor de aplicativo para exibir aplicativos em duas janelas.</feature>
<feature>【Janela flutuante】 A minijanela pode ser movida e posicionado em qualquer posição da Tela inicial.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Esta atualização não apagará seus dados pessoais, mas ainda é recomendado fazer um backup antes de atualizar.
2. Certifique-se de que seu celular tenha mais que 10 GB livres de espaço de armazenamento. Caso contrário, a atualização pode falhar (Acesse Configurações > Armazenamento para verificar).
3. Alguns aplicativos de terceiros podem não ser compatíveis com o MagicOS 8.0 e podem apresentar mau funcionamento após a atualização (como travamentos, lag, consumo anormal de bateria). Atualize seus aplicativos para as versões mais recentes na AppGallery. Se os problemas persistirem, espere as próximas atualizações de aplicativos. 
4. Após atualizar, o sistema ajustará suas configurações para aplicar as otimizações. No processo, o telefone pode ficar quente, consumir bateria rapidamente, apresentar lag ou carregar devagar. Entretanto, ele voltará ao normal após 2 ou 3 dias de uso. Depois que a atualização for concluída e antes de reiniciar o telefone, recomendamos carregá-lo com a tela desligada por 1 a 2 horas, a fim de confirmar que as otimizações foram aplicadas.
5. Caso encontre algum problema durante a atualização, você poderá receber nosso suporte ligando para a linha de atendimento da HONOR ou acessando a Central de serviços do cliente HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caros utilizadores, esta atualização lançou o novo MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 vós. O novo sistema é mais simples, mais seguro, mais fácil de utilizar, poupa mais energia e o ecrã inicial é mais divertido. Recomendamos-lhe que atualize. Fique atento às próximas atualizações da versão para desbloquear mais funcionalidades.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Explorar o ecrã inicial">
<feature>【Ícones do ecrã inicial】O tamanho dos ícones do ecrã inicial pode ser ajustado para satisfazer as diferentes necessidades dos utilizadores. Pode experimentá-lo, acedendo a: Definições > Ecrã inicial e estilo > Definições do ecrã inicial > Tamanho do ícone.</feature>
<feature>【Extensão de aplicações】 Pode agora ativar a Extensão de aplicações com um único gesto. Arraste a parte inferior para o canto superior esquerdo e, de seguida, toque na outra aplicação que suporta a Extensão de aplicações para apresentar aplicações em janelas duplas.</feature>
<feature>【Janela flutuante】 A mini janela pode ser movida e deslocada para qualquer posição no ecrã inicial.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Esta atualização não irá eliminar os seus dados pessoais, mas recomendamos que crie uma cópia de segurança previamente.
2. Certifique-se de que o seu telemóvel possui mais de 10 GB de espaço de armazenamento livre. Caso contrário, a atualização pode falhar (aceda a Definições > Armazenamento para verificar).
3. Algumas aplicações de terceiros podem não ser compatíveis com o MagicOS 8.0 e podem não funcionar corretamente após a atualização (podendo, por exemplo, bloquear, ficar lentas ou apresentar um consumo de energia anormal). Atualize as suas aplicações para as versões mais recentes através da AppGallery. Se o problema persistir, aguarde pelo lançamento de futuras atualizações para as aplicações.
4. Após a atualização, o sistema irá ajustar as respetivas definições de modo a aplicar as otimizações. Durante este processo, o telemóvel pode aquecer, consumir mais energia, ficar lento ou demorar mais tempo a carregar. No entanto, este voltará ao normal após 2-3 dias de utilização. Após a atualização estar concluída e antes de reiniciar o telemóvel, recomendamos que efetue o carregamento com o ecrã desligado durante 1~2 horas para garantir que as otimizações são aplicadas.
5. Se encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, pode obter ajuda telefonando para a linha direta do serviço de assistência da HONOR ou visitando o Centro de Serviços ao Cliente da HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimați utilizatori, această actualizare a lansat noul MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 pentru dvs. Noul sistem este mai fluid, mai sigur, mai ușor de utilizat, economisește mai bine bateria, iar ecranul de pornire este mai distractiv. Vă recomandăm să instalați actualizarea. Continuați să urmăriți actualizările viitoare ale versiunii pentru a debloca mai multe funcții.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Explorați ecranul de pornire">
<feature>【Pictograme ecran de pornire】Dimensiunea pictogramelor Ecranului de pornire poate fi ajustată pentru a răspunde nevoilor specifice utilizatorilor. Puteți să experimentați accesând: Setări -> Ecran de pornire și stil -> Setări ecran de pornire -> Dimensiunea pictogramei.</feature>
<feature>【Extindere aplicații】 Acum puteți activa funcția Extindere aplicații cu un singur gest. Trageți partea de jos către colțul din stânga sus, apoi atingeți cealaltă aplicație care acceptă funcția Extindere aplicații pentru a afișa aplicațiile în ferestre duale.</feature>
<feature>【Fereastră flotantă】 Mini-fereastra poate fi mutată și plasată în orice poziție pe ecranul de pornire.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Această actualizare nu vă va șterge datele personale, dar este totuși recomandat să faceți o copie de rezervă în prealabil.
2. Asigurați-vă că telefonul are cel puțin 10 GB spațiu de stocare liber. În caz contrar, actualizarea poate eșua (mergeți la Setări > Spațiu de Stocare pentru a verifica spațiul liber).
3. Este posibil ca unele aplicații terțe să nu fie compatibile cu MagicOS 8.0 și să funcționeze defectuos după actualizare (să se blocheze, să reacționeze greu sau să consume anormal de multă energie). Actualizați-vă aplicațiile la ultimele versiuni din AppGallery. Dacă problemele persistă, așteptați actualizările viitoare ale aplicațiilor.
4. După actualizare, sistemul își va ajusta setările pentru a aplica optimizările. Pe parcursul acestui proces, telefonul se poate încălzi puternic, poate consuma excesiv de multă energie, poate reacționa greu sau se poate încărca încet. Dar va reveni la normal în 2-3 zile de utilizare. După finalizarea actualizării, înainte de repornire, vă recomandăm să încărcați telefonul cu ecranul oprit timp de 1 ~ 2 ore pentru a vă asigura că optimizările sunt aplicate.
5. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, puteți obține ajutorul nostru sunând la linia de asistență telefonică HONOR sau vizitând Centrul de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы разработали это обновление, чтобы представить вам новую версию системы MagicOS 8.0 на базе Android 14. В этой версии работа с устройством станет более удобной, безопасной, простой в использовании и энергоэффективной, а рабочий экран — более привлекательным. Рекомендуем установить это обновление и следить за выходом новых, в которых мы представим дополнительные полезные функции.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Новые функции рабочего экрана">
<feature>[Значки рабочего экрана] Чтобы настроить размер значков рабочего экрана, перейдите в раздел Настройки -> Рабочий экран и стиль -> Настройки экрана -> Размер значков.</feature>
<feature>【App Extender】 Теперь вы можете включать App Extender одним жестом. Чтобы отобразить приложения в двух окнах, перетащите низ в левый верхний угол, а затем нажмите на другое приложение, поддерживающее App Extender.</feature>
<feature>【Плавающее окно】 Миниокно можно переместить в любое место на рабочем экране.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не приведет к удалению ваших персональных данных, однако мы рекомендуем заранее сделать резервную копию данных.
2. Убедитесь, что на телефоне свободно более 10 ГБ памяти. В противном случае может произойти сбой обновления. Чтобы проверить объем свободного места в памяти, перейдите в раздел Настройки > Память.
3. Некоторые сторонние приложения могут быть несовместимы с MagicOS 7.1, поэтому после обновления могут возникнуть неполадки (например, сбои, задержки или повышенный расход заряда батареи). Обновите приложения до последней версии в AppGallery. Если проблемы не удается устранить, дождитесь выхода обновлений этих приложения.
4. После завершения обновления настройки устройства будут автоматически изменены, чтобы оптимизировать работу системы. При этом телефон может нагреваться, быстро расходовать заряд, не отвечать на нажатия или медленно заряжаться. Эти явления исчезнут через 2–3 дня. После завершения обновления и перед перезагрузкой телефона рекомендуем подключить его к источнику питания и выключить экран на 1–2 часа, чтобы оптимизация прошла без сбоев.
5. При возникновении проблем во время обновления обратитесь за помощью, позвонив на горячую линию службы поддержки HONOR или посетив сервисный центр для клиентов HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලකයිනි, මෙම යාවත්කාලය ඔබ වෙනුවෙන් නවතම MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 දියත් කර ඇත. නව පද්ධතිය වඩා සුමට, ආරක්ෂිත, භාවිතයට පහසු, බලය වැඩිපුර ඉතිරි කරන අතර මුල් තිරය වඩා විනෝදජනක වේ. යාවත් කරන ලෙස අපි ඔබට නිර්දේශ කරමු. තවත් විශේෂාංග අගුළු හැරීමට කරුණාකර ඉදිරි අනුවාද යාවත්කාලීන සඳහා රැඳී සිටින්න.</feature>
</features>
<features module="මුල් තිරය ගවේශනය කරන්න">
<feature>【මුල් තිර අයිකන】මුල් තිර අයිකනවල ප්‍රමාණය පරිශීලකයින්ගේ විවිධ අවශ්‍යතා සපුරාලීමට සීරු මාරු කළ හැකිවනු ඇත. ඔබට මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය අත්විඳිය හැකිය: සැකසුම් -> මුල් තිරය සහ විලාසය -> මුල් තිර සැකසුම් -> අයිකනයේ ප්‍රමාණය.</feature>
<feature>【යෙදුම් විස්තාරකය】 ඔබට දැන් තනි අභිනයකින් යෙදුම් විස්තාරකය සක්‍රිය කළ හැකිය. පහළ කෙළවර ඉහළ වම් කෙළවරට ඇදගෙන ගොස්, ඉන්පසු ද්විත්ව කවුළු තුළ යෙදුම් සංදර්ශනය කිරීමට යෙදුම් විස්තාරකය සඳහා සහය දක්වන අනෙක් යෙදුම තට්ටු කරන්න.</feature>
<feature>【පාවෙන කවුළුව】 කුඩා කවුළුව මුල් තිරයේ ඕනෑම පිහිටීමකට ගෙන යාමට සහ මතින් ගෙන යාමට හැකිවනු ඇත.</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්ත නොමකනු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් ඊට පෙර උපස්ථ කිරීමක් නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. ඔබගේ දුරකථනයේ 10 GB ට වැඩි නිදහස් ගබඩා ඉඩක් ඇති බවට වග බලා ගන්න. එසේ නැතිනම්, යාවත්කාලය අසාර්ථකවීමට ඉඩ ඇත (එය පරීක්ෂා කිරීමට සැකසුම් > ගබඩාව වෙත යන්න).
3. සමහර තෙවන පාර්ශ්ව යෙදුම් MagicOS 8.0 සමග අනුකූල නොවීමට ඉඩ ඇති අතර යාවත්කාල කිරීමෙන් පසු ක්‍රමවත්ව ක්‍රියා නොකිරීමට (බිඳවැටීම, ප්‍රමාදය, අසාමාන්‍ය බල පරිභෝජනය වැනි) ඉඩ ඇත. කරුණාකර ඔබගේ යෙදුම් AppGallery හි නවතම අනුවාදයට යාවත්කාල කරන්න. ගැටළු දිගටම පවතින්නේ නම්, කරුණාකර ඉදිරියට එන යෙදුම් යාවත්කාල සඳහා රැඳී සිටින්න.
4. යාවත්කාල කිරීමෙන් පසුව, ප්‍රශස්තකරණ යොදා ගැනීම සඳහා පද්ධතිය එහි සැකසුම් සීරු මාරු කරනු ඇත. ක්‍රියාවලියේ දී, දුරකථනය උණුසුම් වීමට, බලය වේගයෙන් පරිභෝජනය කිරීමට, ප්‍රමාද වීමට හෝ සෙමින් ආරෝපණය වීමට ඉඩ ඇත. නමුත් එය භාවිතා කිරීමෙන් දින 2-3 කින් ආපසු සාමාන්‍ය තත්වයට පත් වනු ඇත. යාවත්කාලය සිදු කිරීමෙන් පසුව සහ දුරකථනය නැවත ඇරඹීමට පෙර, ප්‍රශස්තකරණයන් යොදාගෙන ඇති බව තහවුරු කිරීමට පැය 1~2 ක් තිරය අක්‍රියව තබාගෙන එය ආරෝපණය කරන ලෙස අපි නිර්දේශ කරමු.
5. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේදී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, ඔබට HONOR සේවා හොට්ලයින් ඇමතීමෙන් හෝ HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට පිවිසීමෙන් අපගේ උපකාර ලබා ගත හැකිය.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážení používatelia, táto aktualizácia pre vás zavádza úplne nový systém MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Nový systém je plynulejší, bezpečnejší, ľahšie sa používa, šetrí energiou a má zábavnejšiu domovskú obrazovku. Odporúčame vám vykonať aktualizáciu. Nadchádzajúce aktualizácie tejto verzie odomknú ďalšie funkcie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Preskúmanie domovskej obrazovky">
<feature>【Ikony na domovskej obrazovke】Veľkosť ikon na domovskej obrazovke možno upraviť tak, aby vyhovovala rôznym potrebám používateľov. Môžete to vyskúšať v časti: Nastavenia -> Domovská obrazovka a štýl -> Nastavenia domovskej obrazovky -> Veľkosť ikon.</feature>
<feature>【Extender aplikácií】 Extender aplikácií môžete zapnúť jediným gestom. Potiahnite spodnú časť do ľavého horného rohu a potom ťuknite na inú aplikáciu podporujúcu Extender aplikácií, aby sa aplikácie zobrazili v dvoch oknách.</feature>
<feature>【Plávajúce okno】 Miniokno možno presunúť a umiestniť na ľubovoľnú pozíciu na domovskej obrazovke.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Táto aktualizácia nevymaže vaše osobné údaje, no odporúčame pred ňou vykonať zálohu.
2. Uistite sa, že máte v telefóne viac ako 10 GB voľného ukladacieho priestoru. V opačnom prípade môže aktualizácia zlyhať (priestor môžete skontrolovať v položke Nastavenia > Ukladací priestor).
3. Niektoré externé aplikácie nemusia byť kompatibilné so systémom MagicOS 8.0 a po aktualizácii môžu fungovať nesprávne (napríklad padať, oneskorovať sa, mať nadmernú spotrebu energie). Aktualizujte svoje aplikácie na najnovšiu verziu v obchode AppGallery. Ak problémy pretrvávajú, počkajte na ďalšie aktualizácie aplikácií.
4. Po aktualizácii systém upraví svoje nastavenia tak, aby sa použili optimalizácie. Počas tohto procesu sa telefón môže zahrievať, rýchlo spotrebovávať energiu, oneskorovať sa alebo sa pomaly nabíjať. Do normálneho stavu sa však vráti po 2 – 3 dňoch používania. Po dokončení aktualizácie a pred reštartovaním telefónu ho odporúčame nabíjať s vypnutou obrazovkou 1 až 2 hodiny, aby sa zaistilo použitie optimalizácií.
5. Ak sa v priebehu aktualizácie vyskytne akýkoľvek problém, môžete získať pomoc zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo navštívte zákaznícke servisné stredisko spoločnosti HONOR.4. Po aktualizácii systém upraví svoje nastavenia tak, aby sa použili optimalizácie. Počas tohto procesu sa telefón môže zahrievať, rýchlo spotrebovávať energiu, oneskorovať sa alebo sa pomaly nabíjať. Do normálneho stavu sa však vráti po 2 – 3 dňoch používania. Po dokončení aktualizácie a pred reštartovaním telefónu ho odporúčame nabíjať s vypnutou obrazovkou 1 až 2 hodiny, aby sa zaistilo použitie optimalizácií.
5. Ak sa v priebehu aktualizácie vyskytne akýkoľvek problém, môžete získať pomoc zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo navštívte zákaznícke servisné stredisko spoločnosti HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabniki, s to posodobitvijo je bila dodana popolnoma nova različica sistema MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Novi sistem nima motenj, je varnejši, enostavnejši za uporabo in zagotavlja večje varčevanje z energijo, začetni zaslon pa je zabavnejši. Priporočamo posodobitev. Redno preverjajte prihodnje posodobitve različic, da odklenete več funkcij.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Raziščite začetni zaslon">
<feature>【Ikone na začetnem zaslonu】Velikost ikon na začetnem zaslonu je mogoče prilagoditi, da ustreza različnim potrebam vsakega uporabnika. To lahko preizkusite tako, da izberete: Nastavitve -> Začetni zaslon in slog -> Nastavitve začetnega zaslona -> Velikost ikone.</feature>
<feature>【Razširitev za aplikacije】 Zdaj lahko funkcijo Razširitev za aplikacije omogočite z eno potezo. Povlecite spodnji del v zgornji levi kot in se nato dotaknite druge aplikacije, ki podpira Razširitev za aplikacije, da aplikaciji prikažete v dveh oknih.</feature>
<feature>【Plavajoče okno】 Mini okno se lahko premakne in postavi tako, da lebdi, v poljuben položaj na začetnem zaslonu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ta posodobitev ne bo izbrisala vaših osebnih podatkov, a vseeno priporočamo, da prej naredite varnostno kopijo.
2. Poskrbite, da bo v telefonu več kot 10 GB prostora v shrambi. Posodobitev sicer morda ne bo uspela (odprite Nastavitve > Pomnilnik in preverite).
3. Nekatere aplikacija drugega ponudnika morda niso združljive s sistemom MagicOS 8.0 in po posodobitvi ne bodo pravilno delovale (pride lahko npr. do zrušitev, zakasnitev, neobičajne porabe energije). V trgovini AppGallery vse aplikacije posodobite na najnovejšo različico. Če se težava ponovi, počakajte na prihodnje posodobitve aplikacij.
4. Sistem bo po posodobitvi prilagodil nastavitve in uveljavil optimizacije. Telefon lahko pri tem postane vroč, poraba energije lahko hitro naraste, prihaja lahko do zakasnitev ali počasnega polnjenja. Čez 2–3 dni se povrne običajno delovanje. Ko je posodobitev končana in preden znova zaženete telefon, priporočamo, da ga z ugasnjenim zaslonom polnite 1–2 uri, s čimer zagotovite, da bodo optimizacije uveljavljene.
5. Če pri posodobitvi naletite na kakršne koli težave, se lahko za pomoč obrnete na nas tako, da za pomoč pokličete odprto linijo za storitve HONOR ali obiščete servisni center HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, i den här uppdateringen presenteras helt nya MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 för dig. Det nya systemet är smidigare, säkrare, enklare att använda, mer energibesparande och dessutom är startsidan roligare. Vi rekommenderar att du uppdaterar. Håll utkik efter kommande versionsuppdateringar som ger dig tillgång till fler funktioner.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Utforska startsidan">
<feature>【Ikoner på startsidan】Storleken på startsidans ikoner kan justeras för att passa användarnas olika behov. Du kan prova själv genom att gå till: Inställningar -> Startsida och stil -> Inställningar för startsidan -> Ikonstorlek.</feature>
<feature>【Apputökare】 Du kan nu aktivera Apputökare med en enda gest. Dra från nederkanten till det övre vänstra hörnet och tryck sedan på den andra appen som stöder Apputökare för att visa appar i dubbla fönster.</feature>
<feature>【Flytande fönster】 Minifönster kan flyttas och hovras till valfri position på startsidan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Den här uppdateringen raderar inga personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du gör en säkerhetskopia innan du installerar uppdateringen.
2. Se till att din telefon har mer än 10 GB ledigt lagringsutrymme. Om du inte gör det kan uppdateringen misslyckas (Gå till Inställningar > Lagring för att kontrollera det).
3. Vissa appar från tredje parter kanske inte är kompatibla med MagicOS 8.0 och fungerar eventuellt inte korrekt efter uppdateringen (till exempel krascher, lag, onormal energiförbrukning). Uppdatera apparna till den senaste versionen i AppGallery. Om problemen kvarstår ska du vänta på kommande appuppdateringar.
4. Efter uppdateringen justerar systemet inställningarna för att tillämpa optimeringarna. I processen kan telefonen bli varm, förbruka ström snabbt, lagga eller ladda långsamt. Men den återgår till det normala efter 2–3 dagars användning. Efter att uppdateringen är klar och innan du startar om telefonen rekommenderar vi att du laddar den med skärmen avstängd i 1–2 timmar för att säkerställa att optimeringarna tillämpas.
5. Om du stöter på problem under uppdateringen kan du få hjälp från oss genom att ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs kundtjänstcenter.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Watumiaji wapendwa, sasisho hili limezindua MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 mpya kwa ajili yako. Mfumo mpya ni laini zaidi, salama zaidi, na rahisi zaidi kutumia, unaokoa nishati zaidi na skrini ya mwanzo inaburudisha zaidi. Tunapendekeza usasishe. Tafadhali makinika kwa masasisho ya toleo yajayo ili kufungua vipengele zaidi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Vinjari skrini ya mwanzo">
<feature>【Aikoni za skrini ya mwanzo】Ukubwa wa aikoni za Skrini ya mwanzo unaweza kurekebishwa ili kufikia mahitaji tofauti ya watumiaji. Unaweza kuipata kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio -> Skrini ya mwanzo na mtindo -> Mipangilio ya Skrini ya mwanzo -> Ukubwa wa aikoni.</feature>
<feature>【Kienezi Programu】 Sasa unaweza kuwezesha Kienezi Programu kwa ishara moja tu. Kokota upande wa chini wa kona ya juu kushoto kisha uguse programu hiyo nyingine inayoruhusu Kienezi Programu ili kuonyesha programu kwenye madirisha mawili.</feature>
<feature>【Dirisha linaloelea】 Dirisha dogo linaweza kubamishwa na kuenezwa hadi eneo lolote kwenye skrini ya mwanzo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Sasisho hili halitafuta data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini chelezo kabla ya kusakinisha linapendekezwa.
2. Hakikisha kuwa simu yako ina zaidi ya GB 10 za nafasi tupu ya hifadhi. La sivyo, sasisho litafeli (Nenda kwenye Mipangilio > Hifadhi ili kuiangalia).
3. Huenda baadhi ya programu za mtu mwingine zisitangamane na MagicOS 8.0 na huenda zisifanye kazi vizuri baada ya sasisho (kama vile kuharibika, kujikokota, utumiaji nishati usio wa kawaida). Tafadhali sasisha programu zako hadi kwenye toleo la hivi karibuni kwenye AppGallery. Ikiwa matatizo yataendelea, tafadhali subiri masasisho yajayo ya programu.
4. Baada ya kusasisha, mfumo utarekebisha mipangilio yake ili kutekeleza uboreshaji. Katika mchakato huu, huenda simu ikawa na joto jingi, ikatumia nishati kwa haraka, ikajikokota au ikachaji polepole. Lakini itarejea hali ya kawaida baada ya siku 2-3 za matumizi. Baada ya sasisho kukamilika na kabla ya kuwasha upya simu, tunapendekeza kuichaji skrini ikiwa imezimwa kwa saa 1~2 ili kuhakikisha kuwa uboreshaji umetekelezwa.
5. Ikiwa utakumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, unaweza kupata usaidizi wetu kwa kupiga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au kutembelea Kituo cha Huduma kwa Wateja cha HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்பான பயனர்களே, இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு உங்களுக்காகப் புத்தம் புதிய MagicOS 8.0|Android 14-ஐ அறிமுகப்படுத்தியுள்ளது. புதிய சிஸ்டம் மென்மையானது, பாதுகாப்பானது, பயன்படுத்த எளிதானது, அதிக ஆற்றல் சேமிப்பு கொண்டது மற்றும் முகப்புத் திரை மிகவும் வேடிக்கையாக அமைந்துள்ளது. புதுப்பிக்குமாறு பரிந்துரைக்கிறோம். மேலும் அம்சங்களைத் திறக்க, வரவிருக்கும் பதிப்பு புதுப்பிப்புகளுக்காகக் காத்திருங்கள்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="முகப்புத் திரையை ஆராய்க">
<feature>【முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான்கள்】முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான்களின் அளவைப் பயனர்களின் வெவ்வேறு தேவைகளைப் பூர்த்தி செய்யும் வகையில் சரிசெய்யலாம். இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் நீங்கள் அதைப் பயன்படுத்தலாம்: அமைப்புகள் -> முகப்புத் திரை மற்றும் ஸ்டைல் -> முகப்புத் திரை அமைப்புகள் -> ஐகான் அளவு.</feature>
<feature>【செயலி நீட்டிப்பி】 இப்போது நீங்கள் ஒரு ஒற்றைச் சைகை மூலம் செயலி நீட்டிப்பியைச் செயல்படுத்தலாம். மேல் இடது மூலைக்குக் கீழே இருந்து இழுத்து, இரட்டைச் சாளரங்களில் செயலிகளைக் காட்ட, செயலி நீட்டிப்பியை ஆதரிக்கும் பிற செயலியைத் தட்டவும்.</feature>
<feature>【மிதவைச் சாளரம்】 முகப்புத் திரையில் எந்த நிலைக்கும் மினி சாளரத்தை நகர்த்தலாம் மற்றும் ஹோவர் செய்யலாம்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவை அழிக்காது, எனினும் தொடர்வதற்கு முன் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுக்குமாறு பரிந்துரைக்கிறோம்.
2. உங்கள் மொபைலில் 10 GB-க்கும் மேல் காலி இடம் இருப்பதை உறுதிசெய்து கொள்ளவும். இல்லையெனில் புதுப்பிப்பு தோல்வியடையக்கூடும் (அமைப்புகள் > சேமிப்பகம் என்பதற்குச் சென்று, அதைச் சரிபார்க்கவும்).
3. சில மூன்றாம் தரப்புச் செயலிகள் MagicOS 8.0 உடன் இணங்காமல் இருக்கலாம் மற்றும் புதுப்பித்தலுக்குப் பிறகு செயலிழந்து போகலாம் (செயலிழப்பு, தாமதம், அசாதாரண மின் நுகர்வு போன்றவை). AppGallery-இல் உங்கள் செயலிகளைச் சமீபத்திய பதிப்பிற்குப் புதுப்பிக்கவும். சிக்கல்கள் தொடர்ந்தால், வரவிருக்கும் செயலிப் புதுப்பிப்புகளுக்காகக் காத்திருக்கவும்.
4. புதுப்பித்த பிறகு, உகந்ததாக்கங்களைப் பயன்படுத்த சிஸ்டம் அதன் அமைப்புகளைச் சரிசெய்யும். செயல்பாட்டின்போது, மொபைல் சூடாகலாம், ஆற்றலை வேகமாக நுகரலாம், தாமதமாகலாம் அல்லது மெதுவாகச் சார்ஜ் செய்யலாம். எனினும் 2-3 நாட்கள் பயன்படுத்தினால் இயல்பு நிலைக்குத் திரும்பும். புதுப்பிப்பு முடிந்ததும், மொபைலை மறுதொடங்குவதற்கு முன், உகந்ததாக்கங்கள் பயன்படுத்தப்படுவதை உறுதிசெய்ய, 1~2 மணிநேரம் திரையை அணைத்த நிலையில் சார்ஜ் செய்யுமாறு பரிந்துரைக்கிறோம்.
5. புதுப்பிக்கும்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைப்பதன் மூலமோ அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்தைப் பார்வையிடுவதன் மூலமோ எங்கள் உதவியைப் பெறலாம்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారులకు, ఈ అప్‌డేట్ మీ కోసం సరికొత్త MagicOS 8.0|Android 14ను లాంచ్ చేసింది. కొత్త సిస్టమ్ ఉపయోగించడం సులభం, సురక్షితం, మరింత పవర్ ఆదా అవుతుంది మరియు హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చాలా ఆకర్షణీయంగా ఉంటుంది. మీరు అప్‌డేట్ చేయాలని మేము సిఫార్సు చేస్తున్నాము. దయచేసి మరిన్ని ఫీచర్‌లను అన్‌లాక్ చేయడానికి రాబోయే సంస్కరణ అప్‌డేట్‌లు కోసం చూస్తూ ఉండండి.</feature>
</features>
<features module="హోమ్ స్క్రీన్‌ను విశ్లేషించండి">
<feature>【హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాలు】వినియోగదారుల విభిన్న అవసరాలకు తగినట్లు హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాల పరిమాణాన్ని సర్దుబాటు చేయవచ్చు. మీరు ఇక్కడికి వెళ్లి దానిని ఆనందించవచ్చు: సెట్టింగ్‌లు -> హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ మరియు శైలి -> హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ సెట్టింగ్‌లు -> చిహ్నం పరిమాణం.</feature>
<feature>【అప్లికేషన్ ఎక్స్‌టెండర్】 మీరు ఒక సంజ్ఞతో ఇప్పుడు అప్లికేషన్ ఎక్స్‌టెండర్‌ను ప్రారంభించవచ్చు. దిగువ భాగాన్ని ఎగువ ఎడమ మూలకు లాగి, ఆపై డ్యూయల్ విండోల్లో అప్లికేషన్‌లను ప్రదర్శించడానికి అప్లికేషన్ ఎక్స్‌టెండర్‌కు మద్దతు ఇచ్చే ఇతర అప్లికేషన్‌ను ట్యాప్ చేయండి.</feature>
<feature>【తేలియాడే విండో】 మినీ విండోను తరలించవచ్చు మరియు హోమ్ స్క్రీన్‌పై ఏదైనా స్థానానికి హోవర్ చేయవచ్చు.</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్ మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటాను ఎరేజ్ చేయదు, కాని ముందుగానే బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇప్పటికీ సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది. 
2. మీ ఫోన్‌లో 10 GB కంటే ఎక్కువ ఖాళీ నిల్వ స్థలం ఉన్నట్లు నిర్ధారించుకోండి. లేకపోతే, అప్‌డేట్ విఫలం కావచ్చు (దానిని తనిఖీ చేయడానికి సెట్టింగ్‌లు > నిల్వకు వెళ్ళండి). 
3. కొన్ని మూడవ పక్ష అప్లికేషన్‌లు MagicOS 8.0తో అనుకూలంగా ఉండకపోవచ్చు మరియు అప్‌డేట్ తర్వాత తప్పుగా పని చేయవచ్చు (క్రాష్, ఆలస్యం, అసాధారణ పవర్ వినయోగం వంటివి). దయచేసి AppGalleryలో తాజా సంస్కరణకు మీ అప్లికేషన్‌లను అప్‌డేట్ చేయండి. సమస్యలు కొనసాగినట్లయితే, దయచేసి రాబోయే అప్లికేషన్ అప్‌డేట్‌ల కోసం వేచి ఉండండి. 
4. అప్‌డేట్ అయిన తర్వాత, ఆప్టిమైజేషన్‌లను వర్తింపజేయడానికి సిస్టమ్ దాని సెట్టింగ్‌లను సర్దుబాటు చేస్తుంది. ప్రాసెస్‌లో, ఫోన్ వేడెక్కవచ్చు, పవర్‌ను వేగంగా వినియోగిస్తుంది, ఆలస్యం కావచ్చు లేదా నెమ్మదిగా ఛార్జ్ కావచ్చు. కాని ఇది 2-3 రోజుల వినియోగంలో తిరిగి సాధారణ స్థితికి వస్తుంది. అప్‌డేట్ పూర్తయిన మరియు ఫోన్‌ను పునఃప్రారంభించిన తర్వాత, ఆప్టిమైజేషన్‌లు వర్తించబడ్డాయని నిర్ధారించడానికి స్క్రీన్‌ను ఆఫ్ చేసి 1~2 గంటలపాటు ఛార్జ్ చేయాలని మేము సిఫార్సు చేస్తున్నాము. 
5. మీరు అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో ఏదైనా సమస్యలను ఎదుర్కొన్నట్లయితే, మీరు HONOR సర్వీసు హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయడం లేదా HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రాన్ని సందర్శించడం ద్వారా మా సహాయాన్ని పొందవచ్చు.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตนี้จะเปิดตัว MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 ใหม่ล่าสุดสำหรับคุณ ระบบใหม่จะราบรื่นกว่า ใช้งานง่ายกว่า ประหยัดพลังงานมากกว่า และมีหน้าจอหลักที่สนุกขึ้น เราแนะนำให้คุณอัปเดต โปรดติดตามการอัปเดตเวอร์ชันที่กำลังจะมาถึงเพื่อปลดล็อกฟีเจอร์เพิ่มเติม</feature>
</features>
<features module="สำรวจหน้าจอหลัก">
<feature>【ไอคอนหน้าจอหลัก】 ปรับขนาดไอคอนหน้าจอหลักได้ เพื่อให้เป็นไปตามความต้องการที่แตกต่างกันของผู้ใช้ ลองใช้งานได้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า -> หน้าจอหลักและสไตล์ -> การตั้งค่าหน้าจอหลัก -> ขนาดไอคอน</feature>
<feature>【App Extender】 ตอนนี้คุณสามารถเปิดใช้งาน App Extender ด้วยการใช้ท่าทางเดียวได้แล้ว ให้ลากจากด้านล่างขึ้นมายังมุมซ้ายบน จากนั้นแตะแอปอื่นๆ ที่รองรับ App Extender เพื่อแสดงแอปในหน้าต่างคู่</feature>
<feature>【หน้าต่างแบบลอย】 คุณสามารถขยับและวางหน้าต่างขนาดเล็กที่ตำแหน่งใดก็ได้บนหน้าจอหลัก</feature>
</features>
<features module="หมายเหตุ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การอัปเดตนี้จะไม่ลบข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่ยังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลล่วงหน้า
2. ตรวจสอบให้แน่ใจว่าโทรศัพท์ของคุณมีพื้นที่เก็บข้อมูลว่างมากกว่า 10 กิกะไบต์ มิฉะนั้น อาจอัปเดตไม่สำเร็จ (ไปที่ การตั้งค่า > ที่เก็บข้อมูล เพื่อตรวจสอบ) 
3. แอปของบุคคลที่สามบางแอปอาจไม่สามารถใช้ร่วมกันได้กับ MagicOS 8.0และอาจทำงานผิดปกติหลังจากการอัปเดต (เช่น การขัดข้อง การล่าช้า การใช้พลังงานผิดปกติ) โปรดอัปเดตแอปของคุณให้เป็นเวอร์ชันล่าสุดใน AppGallery หากปัญหายังคงอยู่ โปรดรอการอัปเดตแอปที่กำลังจะมาถึง
4. หลังจากอัปเดตแล้ว ระบบจะปรับการตั้งค่าเพื่อปรับใช้ค่าที่เหมาะสมที่สุด ในระหว่างการดำเนินการนี้ โทรศัพท์อาจร้อนขึ้้น ใช้พลังงานหมดเร็ว ล่าช้า หรือชาร์จไฟช้า แต่จะกลับสู่สภาวะปกติเมื่อใช้ไป 2-3 วัน หลังจากการอัปเดตเสร็จสิ้นและก่อนรีสตาร์ทโทรศัพท์ เราแนะนำให้ชาร์จโทรศัพท์โดยปิดหน้าจอเป็นเวลา 1~2 ชั่วโมง เพื่อให้แน่ใจว่ามีการปรับใช้ค่าที่เหมาะสมที่สุดแล้ว
5. หากคุณพบปัญหาใด ๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต คุณสามารถขอรับความช่วยเหลือจากเราได้โดยโทรไปที่สายด่วนบริการ HONOR หรือแวะไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้า HONOR ของเรา</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na mga user, inilunsad ng update na ito ang bagong MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 para sa iyo. Ang bagong system ay mas smooth, mas ligtas, mas madaling gamitin, mas nakakatipid sa baterya, at mas masaya ang home screen. Inirerekomenda naming mag-update ka. Manatiling nakatutok sa mga paparating na update ng bersyon para i-unlock ang higit pang feature.</feature>
</features>
<features module="I-explore ang home screen">
<feature>【Mga icon ng Home screen】Puwedeng i-adjust ang laki ng mga icon ng Home screen para matugunan ang iba't ibang pangangailangan ng mga user. Puwede mo itong maranasan sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting -> Home screen at estilo -> Mga setting ng home screen -> Laki ng icon.</feature>
<feature>【App Extender】 Puwede mo nang i-enable ang App Extender gamit ang isang gesture. I-drag ang ibaba patungo sa kaliwang sulok sa itaas, at pagkatapos ay i-tap ang kabilang app na sumusuporta sa App Extender para ipakita ang mga app sa dalawang window.</feature>
<feature>【Lumulutang na window】 Puwedeng ilipat at i-hover ang mini window sa anumang posisyon sa home screen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi buburahin ng update na ito ang iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa rin ang isang pag-back up bago gawin ito.
2. Tiyaking may higit sa 10 GB na libreng espasyo ng storage ang iyong telepono. Kung hindi, puwedeng pumalya ang update (Pumunta sa Mga Setting > Storage para tingnan ito).
3. Puwedeng hindi tugma ang ilang third-party na app sa MagicOS 8.0 at puwedeng hindi gumana nang maayos pagkatapos ng update (gaya ng pag-crash, pag-lag, hindi normal na pagkonsumo ng baterya). Paki-update ang iyong mga app sa pinakabagong bersyon sa AppGallery. Kung magpatuloy ang problema, maghintay sa mga paparating na update ng app.
4. Pagkatapos mag-update, ia-adjust ng system ang mga setting nito para ilapat ang mga pag-optimize. Habang isinasagawa ang proseso, puwedeng uminit, mabilis na kumonsumo ng baterya, mag-lag, o mabagal na mag-charge ang telepono. Pero babalik ito sa normal sa loob ng 2-3 araw ng paggamit. Pagkatapos ng update at bago i-restart ang telepono, inirerekomenda naming i-charge ito nang naka-off ang screen sa loob ng 1~ 2 oras para matiyak na nailapat ang mga pag-optimize.
5. Kung nakakaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, puwede mong kunin ang aming tulong sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pagbisita sa Customer Service Center ng HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na mga user, inilunsad ng update na ito ang bagong MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 para sa iyo. Ang bagong system ay mas smooth, mas ligtas, mas madaling gamitin, mas nakakatipid sa baterya, at mas masaya ang home screen. Inirerekomenda naming mag-update ka. Manatiling nakatutok sa mga paparating na update ng bersyon para i-unlock ang higit pang feature.</feature>
</features>
<features module="I-explore ang home screen">
<feature>【Mga icon ng Home screen】Puwedeng i-adjust ang laki ng mga icon ng Home screen para matugunan ang iba't ibang pangangailangan ng mga user. Puwede mo itong maranasan sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting -> Home screen at estilo -> Mga setting ng home screen -> Laki ng icon.</feature>
<feature>【App Extender】 Puwede mo nang i-enable ang App Extender gamit ang isang gesture. I-drag ang ibaba patungo sa kaliwang sulok sa itaas, at pagkatapos ay i-tap ang kabilang app na sumusuporta sa App Extender para ipakita ang mga app sa dalawang window.</feature>
<feature>【Lumulutang na window】 Puwedeng ilipat at i-hover ang mini window sa anumang posisyon sa home screen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi buburahin ng update na ito ang iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa rin ang isang pag-back up bago gawin ito.
2. Tiyaking may higit sa 10 GB na libreng espasyo ng storage ang iyong telepono. Kung hindi, puwedeng pumalya ang update (Pumunta sa Mga Setting > Storage para tingnan ito).
3. Puwedeng hindi tugma ang ilang third-party na app sa MagicOS 8.0 at puwedeng hindi gumana nang maayos pagkatapos ng update (gaya ng pag-crash, pag-lag, hindi normal na pagkonsumo ng baterya). Paki-update ang iyong mga app sa pinakabagong bersyon sa AppGallery. Kung magpatuloy ang problema, maghintay sa mga paparating na update ng app.
4. Pagkatapos mag-update, ia-adjust ng system ang mga setting nito para ilapat ang mga pag-optimize. Habang isinasagawa ang proseso, puwedeng uminit, mabilis na kumonsumo ng baterya, mag-lag, o mabagal na mag-charge ang telepono. Pero babalik ito sa normal sa loob ng 2-3 araw ng paggamit. Pagkatapos ng update at bago i-restart ang telepono, inirerekomenda naming i-charge ito nang naka-off ang screen sa loob ng 1~ 2 oras para matiyak na nailapat ang mga pag-optimize.
5. Kung nakakaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, puwede mong kunin ang aming tulong sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pagbisita sa Customer Service Center ng HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Değerli kullanıcılar, bu güncelleme ile yepyeni MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 kullanımınıza sunuldu. Bu güncelleme, gelişmiş güç tasarrufu özellikleri ve daha keyifli bir başlangıç ekranıyla daha akıcı, daha güvenli ve daha kullanıcı dostu bir deneyim sunuyor. Güncelleme yapmanızı önemle tavsiye ederiz. Eklenecek özellikler için takipte kalın.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Başlangıç ekranını keşfedin">
<feature>【Başlangıç ekranı simgeleri】Başlangıç ekranı simgelerinin boyutları, farklı kullanıcı ihtiyaçlarını karşılamak için ayarlanabilir. Ayarlar -> Başlangıç ekranı ve stil -> Başlangıç ekranı ayarları -> Simge boyutu adımlarını takip ederek bunu deneyimleyebilirsiniz.</feature>
<feature>【Uygulama Genişletici】 Artık Uygulama Genişleticiyi tek bir hareketle etkinleştirebilirsiniz. Uygulamaları çift pencerede görüntülemek için alt kısmı sol üst köşeye sürükleyin ve ardından Uygulama Genişleticiyi destekleyen diğer uygulamaya dokunun.</feature>
<feature>【Kayan pencere】 Mini pencere, başlangıç ekranında herhangi bir konuma taşınabilir ve gezdirilebilir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncelleme kişisel verilerinizi silmeyecektir, fakat yine de öncesinde yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Telefonunuzda 10 GB üzeri boş alan olduğundan emin olun. Olmaması durumunda güncelleme yapılamayabilir (Kontrol etmek için Ayarlar > Depolama bölümüne gidin).
3. Bazı üçüncü taraf uygulamalar MagicOS 8.0 ile uyumlu olmayabilir ve güncellemeden sonra doğru çalışmayabilir (çökme, gecikme, anormal güç tüketimi gibi). Lütfen AppGallery üzerinden uygulamalarınızı en son sürüme güncelleyin. Sorun devam ederse lütfen gelen uygulama güncellemelerini bekleyin.
4. Güncelleme sonrasında sistem optimizasyonları uygulamak için ayarları yapacaktır. Bu esnada telefon ısınabilir, hızla güç tüketebilir, gecikebilir veya yavaş şarj olabilir. 2-3 günlük kullanım sonrasında normale dönecektir. Güncelleme tamamlanıp telefon yeniden başlatılmadan önce telefonun ekranı kapalı şekilde 1-2 saat şarj edilerek optimizasyonların uygulandığından emin olunması önerilir.
5. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorun yaşamanız durumunda HONOR servis yardım hattını arayarak veya HONOR Müşteri Servisi Merkezini ziyaret ederek yardım alabilirsiniz.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا ئەڭ يېڭى MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 سىستېمىسى تارقىتىلدى، يېڭى سىستېما تېخىمۇ راۋان، تېخىمۇ بىخەتەر، ئىشلىتىش تېخىمۇ ئاسان، تېخىمۇ توك تېجەشچان، ئۈستەليۈزى تېخىمۇ قىزىقارلىق، ئالاقە تېخىمۇ ئۈنۈملۈك ۋە قولاي، يېڭىلاپ تەسىراتلىنىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز. تېخىمۇ كۆپ ئىقتىدارلار كېيىنكى نەشرىدە ئېلان قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ئۈستەليۈزىنى ئويناش">
<feature>‏«ئۈستەليۈزى سىنبەلگىسى» ئۈستەليۈزىدىكى سىنبەلگە چوڭلۇقىنى تەڭشەشنى قوللاپ، ئىشلەتكۈچىلەرنىڭ سىنبەلگە چوڭلۇقىنى ئوخشىمىغان چوڭلۇقتا كۆرسىتىش ئېھتىياجىنى قاندۇرىدۇ، سىناش يولى: «تەڭشەك > ئۈستەليۈزى ۋە خاسلاشتۇرۇش > ئۈستەليۈزى تەڭشىكى > سىنبەلگە چوڭلۇقى».</feature>
<feature>«ئېكران بۆلۈش» ئىشارە ئارقىلىق ئېكران بۆلۈش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ئەپ پۈتۈن ئېكران ھالەتتە ئاستىنى ئوڭ تەرەپ ئۈستىگىچە سۆرەپ، ئېكران بۆلۈشنى قوللايدىغان باشقا ئەپنى چەكسىڭىزلا، ئەپ ئېكرانىنى بۆلۈشنى ئەمەلگە ئاشۇرغىلى بولىدۇ.</feature>
<feature>«لەيلىمە كۆزنەك» كىچىك كۆزنەك يانفون ئۈستەليۈزىنىڭ خالىغان ئورنىغا يۆتكەش ۋە شۇ ھالەتتە لەيلىتىشنى قوللايدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىشقا تېگىشلىك ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇمات زاپاسلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.
‏2. يانفونىڭىزدا 10GB دىن ئارتۇق ساقلاش بوشلۇقى بارلىقىنى جەزملەشتۈرۈڭ، بولمىسا يېڭىلانماسلىقى مۇمكىن (ساقلاش بوشلۇقىنى كۆرۈش ئۇسۇلى: تەڭشەك -> بوشلۇق).
‏3. بىر قىسىم ئۈچىنچى تەرەپ ئەپى بىلەن MagicOS 8.0 ماسلاشمىغانلىقى سەۋەبىدىن، يېڭىلانغاندىن كېيىن ئۈچىنچى تەرەپ ئەپىنى نورمال ئىشلەتكىلى بولمايدىغان ئەھۋال كېلىپ چىقىشى مۇمكىن (مەسىلەن، تۇيۇقسىز چېكىنىش، قېتىۋېلىش، توك خوراش قاتارلىقلار). ئەپ بازىرىدا ئەپنى ئەڭ يېڭى نەشرىگە يېڭىلاشنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز، ئەگەر مەسىلە ھەل بولمىسا، ئەپ يېڭىلاش ئۇچۇرىنى ساقلاپ ۋاقتىدا يېڭىلاڭ.
‏4. نەشرىنى ئۆستۈرگەندىن كېيىن، سىستېما ماسلىشىشنى ئەلالاشتۇرىدۇ، بۇ ۋاقىتتا قىزىش، توك خوراش، قېتىۋېلىش ياكى توكلاش ئاستا بولۇش مەسىلىلىرى كېلىپ چىقىشى مۇمكىن، 2-3 كۈن نورمال ئىشلەتكەندىن كېيىن ئەسلىگە كېلىدۇ. دەرىجىسىنى ئۆستۈرگەندىن كېيىن، يانفوننىڭ ئېكرانىنى ئېتىپ 1-2 سائەتتىن ئارتۇق توكلىغاندىن كېيىن يانفوننى قايتا قوزغىتىپ، يانفوندىكى ئەپنىڭ تېز ماسلىشىشىغا كاپالەتلىك قىلىڭ.
‏5. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановні користувачі! У межах цього оновлення на пристрої встановлюється нова ОС MagicOS 8.0|Android 14. Її особливості – плавніша робота, підвищена безпека, простіше використання, більша енергоефективність і функціональніший головний екран. Рекомендуємо встановити це оновлення. Для розблокування додаткових функцій чекайте на оновлення до наступних версій.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Робота на головному екрані">
<feature>【Піктограми головного екрана】Розмір піктограм на головному екрані можна настроювати відповідно до потреб користувача. Щоб зробити це, перейдіть у меню "Налаштування" -> "Головний екран і стиль" -> "Налаштування головного екрана" -> "Розмір піктограми".</feature>
<feature>【Розширення додатка】 Тепер ви можете ввімкнути Розширення додатка одним жестом. Перетягніть нижню частину у верхній лівий кут, а потім торкніться іншого додатка, що підтримує Розширення додатка, щоб відобразити додатки в подвійних вікнах.</feature>
<feature>【Переміщуване вікно】 Міні-вікно можна переміщувати та наводити в будь-яке положення на головному екрані.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Нотатки." type="end">
<feature>1. Це оновлення не стиратиме ваші особисті дані, проте ми все одно радимо заздалегідь виконати резервне копіювання.
2. Переконайтеся, що на телефоні є понад 10 ГБ вільного місця в пам’яті, інакше вам може не вдатися встановити оновлення. Щоб перевірити наявну пам’ять, перейдіть у розділ "Налаштування" -> "Пам’ять".
3. Деякі сторонні додатки можуть бути не сумісні з MagicOS 7.1 і можуть неналежно працювати після оновлення (наприклад, аварійно завершувати роботу, повільно працювати, аномально споживати енергію). Оновіть свої додатки до останньої версії в AppGallery. Якщо проблеми не зникнуть, дочекайтеся випуску оновлення додатка.
4. Після встановлення оновлення система відкоригує власні налаштування для застосування оптимізації. Під час цього процесу телефон може нагріватися, швидко витрачати заряд акумулятора, повільно працювати й заряджатися. Проте через 2–3 дні він знову нормально працюватиме. Після того як оновлення буде встановлення радимо не відразу перезавантажувати телефон, а спочатку зарядити акумулятор із вимкненим екраном протягом 1–2 годин, щоб усі оновлення оптимізації було застосовано.
5. Якщо під час оновлення сталася помилка, зателефонуйте на номер гарячої лінії HONOR або відвідайте Сервісний центр клієнтів HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>محترم صارفین، اس اپ ڈیٹ نے آپ کے لیے بالکل نیا MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 شروع کیا ہے۔ نیا سسٹم ہموار، محفوظ، استعمال میں آسان، بجلی کی زیادہ بچت، اور ہوم اسکرین زیادہ پرلطف ہے۔ ہم آپ کو اپ ڈیٹ کرنے کا مشورہ دیتے ہیں۔ مزید خصوصیات کو ان لاک کرنے کے لیے براہ کرم آنے والے ورژن کی اپ ڈیٹس کے لیے دیکھتے رہیں۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="ہوم اسکرین کو دریافت کریں">
<feature>‏【ہوم اسکرین آئیکنز】ہوم اسکرین آئیکنز کا سائز صارفین کی مختلف ضروریات کو پورا کرنے کے لیے ایڈجسٹ کیا جا سکتا ہے۔ آپ درج ذیل پر جا کر تجربہ کر سکتے ہیں: ترتیبات -> ہوم اسکرین اور اسٹائل -> ہوم اسکرین کی ترتیبات -> آئیکن کا سائز۔</feature>
<feature>‏【ایپ ایکسٹنڈر】 اب آپ ایک ہی اشارے سے ایپ ایکسٹنڈر کو فعال کر سکتے ہیں۔ نیچے سے بالائی بائیں کنارے پر گھسیٹیں، اور پھر ایپس کو دوہری ونڈو میں ڈسپلے کرنے کے لیے ایپ ایکسٹنڈر میں تعاون کرنے والی دیگر ایپ پر ٹیپ کریں۔</feature>
<feature>‏【معلق ونڈو】 چھوٹی ونڈو کو ہوم اسکرین پر کسی بھی پوزیشن پر منتقل اور شامل کیا جا سکتا ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏1۔ یہ اپ ڈیٹ آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں مٹائے گی، لیکن پہلے سے بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2۔ یقینی بنائیں کہ آپ کے فون میں 10 GB سے زائد اسٹوریج کی جگہ خالی ہے۔ بصورت دیگر، اپ ڈیٹ ناکام ہو سکتی ہے۔ (اسے چیک کرنے کے لیے ترتیبات > اسٹوریج پر جائیں)۔
‏3۔ ممکن ہے کہ کچھ فریق ثالث ایپس MagicOS 8.0 کے ساتھ مطابقت پذیر نہ ہوں اور اپ ڈیٹ کے بعد عمل پذیری میں ناکامی ہو سکتی ہیں (جیسا کہ کریش، وقفہ، غیر معمولی بجلی کی کھپت)۔ براہ کرم اپنی ایپس کو AppGallery میں تازہ ترین ورژن میں اپ ڈیٹ کریں۔ اگر مسائل برقرار رہتے ہیں، تو براہ کرم آئندہ کی ایپ اپ ڈیٹس کا انتظار کریں۔ 
‏4۔ اپ ڈیٹ کرنے کے بعد، سسٹم بہتریوں کو لاگو کرنے کے لیے اپنی ترتیبات کو ایڈجسٹ کرے گا۔ اس عمل میں، فون گرم ہو سکتا ہے، بجلی تیزی سے استعمال کر سکتا ہے، وقفہ ہو سکتا ہے، یا آہستہ چارج کر سکتا ہے۔ لیکن استعمال کے 3-2 دن میں یہ معمول پر آ جائے گا۔ اپ ڈیٹ ہو جانے کے بعد اور فون کو ری اسٹارٹ کرنے سے پہلے، ہم تجویز دیتے ہیں کہ اسے 2~ 1 گھنٹے تک اسکرین آف کر کے چارج کریں تاکہ یہ یقینی بنایا جا سکے کہ بہتریاں لاگو ہو گئی ہیں۔
‏5۔ اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو آپ HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کر کے، یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جا کر ہماری مدد حاصل کر سکتے ہیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchilar, ushbu yangilanishda siz uchun yangi MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 taqdim etildi. Yangi tizim yanada ravon, xavfsiz, foydalanish uchun oson va quvvatni tejaydi hamda bosh ekran yanada qiziqarli. Yangilashingizni tavsiya qilamiz. Yana boshqa funksiyalardan foydalanish uchun kelgusi versiya yangilanishlarini kuzatib boring.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bosh ekran bilan tanishish">
<feature>【Bosh ekrandagi belgilar】Bosh ekrandagi belgilarning hajmi foydalanuvchilarning turli ehtiyojlarini qondirish uchun sozlanishi mumkin. Uni bu yerda sinashingiz mumkin: Sozlamalar -> Bosh ekran va uslub -> Bosh ekran sozlamalari -> Belgilar hajmi.</feature>
<feature>【Ilovani kengaytirish】 Endi Ilovani kengaytirish funksiyasini bitta ishora bilan yoqishingiz mumkin. Ilovalarni juft oynalarda chiqarish uchun pastki qismidan ushlab yuqori chap burchakka torting va keyin Ilovani kengaytirish funksiyasini dastaklaydigan narigi ilovani bosing.</feature>
<feature>【Qalqib chiquvchi oyna】 Bosh ekranda mini oynani surish va istalgan joyga olib borish mumkin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizni oʻchirib tashlamaydi, lekin ularni oldindan zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Telefoningizda kamida 10 GB boʻsh xotira joyi borligini tekshiring. Aks holda, yangilash amalga oshmasligi mumkin (Sozlamalar > Xotira ruknida tekshiring).
3. Ayrim tashqi ilovalar MagicOS 8.0 tizimiga mos kelmasligi va yangilashdan keyin kutilganidek ishlamasligi mumkin (masalan, ishdan chiqish, kechikish, noodatiy quvvat sarfi). Ilovalaringizni AppGallery orqali eng oxirgi versiyalariga yangilang. Agar muammolar yuz berishda davom etsa, navbatdagi ilova yangilanishlarini kuting.
4. Yangilashdan keyin tizim optimizatsiyalarni tatbiq etish uchun oʻz sozlamalarini oʻzgartiradi. Bu jarayonda telefon qizishi, tez quvvat sarflashi, qotib ishlashi yoki sekin quvvatlanishi mumkin. Lekin, u 2-3 kun ishlatilganidan keyin normal holatiga qaytadi. Optimizatsiyalar tatbiq etilishi uchun yangilashdan keyin va telefonni qayta ishga tushirishdan oldin uni ekranni oʻchirgan holda 1~2 soat quvvatlashni tavsiya qilamiz.
5. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, bizdan HONOR mijozlarga xizmat tezkor raqamiga telefon qilish yoki HONOR Mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyurish orqali yordam olishingiz mumkin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật này giới thiệu MagicOS 8.0|Android 14 hoàn toàn mới dành cho bạn. Hệ thống mới mượt mà hơn, an toàn hơn, dễ sử dụng hơn, tiết kiệm điện hơn và màn hình chính thú vị hơn. Chúng tôi khuyến nghị bạn cập nhật. Hãy theo dõi các phiên bản cập nhật sắp tới để khám phá nhiều tính năng khác.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Khám phá màn hình chính">
<feature>[Biểu tượng Màn hình chính]Có thể điều chỉnh kích thước biểu tượng Màn hình chính để đáp ứng các nhu cầu khác nhau của người dùng. Bạn có thể trải nghiệm tính năng này bằng cách vào: Cài đặt -> Phong cách và màn hình chính -> Cài đặt màn hình chính -> Kích thước biểu tượng.</feature>
<feature>【Mở rộng ứng dụng】 Giờ đây, bạn có thể bật tính năng Mở rộng ứng dụng chỉ bằng một cử chỉ. Kéo phần cuối lên góc trên bên trái, rồi chạm vào ứng dụng kia có hỗ trợ Mở rộng ứng dụng để hiển thị các ứng dụng trong hai cửa sổ.</feature>
<feature>【Cửa sổ di động】 Cửa sổ nhỏ có thể được di chuyển và chuyển đến vị trí bất kỳ trên màn hình chính.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lưu ý:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bản cập nhật này sẽ không xóa dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước.
2. Đảm bảo điện thoại của bạn có hơn 10 GB dung lượng lưu trữ trống. Nếu không, quá trình cập nhật có thể không thành công (Vào mục Cài đặt > Bộ nhớ để kiểm tra).
3. Một số ứng dụng bên thứ ba có thể không tương thích với MagicOS 8.0 và có thể gặp trục trặc sau khi cập nhật (chẳng hạn như gặp lỗi, chậm, tiêu thụ pin bất thường). Vui lòng cập nhật ứng dụng lên phiên bản mới nhất trong AppGallery. Nếu sự cố vẫn tiếp diễn, vui lòng chờ các bản cập nhật ứng dụng sắp tới.
4. Sau khi cập nhật, hệ thống sẽ điều chỉnh cài đặt để áp dụng các mục tối ưu hóa. Trong quá trình này, điện thoại có thể bị nóng, hao pin nhanh, chậm hoặc sạc chậm nhưng sẽ trở lại bình thường sau 2 – 3 ngày sử dụng. Sau khi cập nhật xong và trước khi khởi động lại điện thoại, bạn nên sạc điện thoại khi màn hình tắt trong 1~2 giờ để đảm bảo áp dụng các mục tối ưu hóa.
5. Nếu gặp phải bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, bạn có thể yêu cầu trợ giúp bằng cách gọi đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ của HONOR hoặc truy cập Trung tâm Dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次升級為您推出全新 MagicOS 8.0 | Android 14 系統，新系統更流暢、更安全、更好用、更省電，主屏幕更好玩，互動更高效快捷，建議您更新體驗。如需了解更多功能解鎖內容，敬請期待日後版本更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="玩轉主屏幕">
<feature>【主屏幕圖標】支援主屏幕圖標大小調節，滿足用戶對圖標大小的不同顯示需求，體驗路徑：「設定->主屏幕和個人化->主屏幕設定->圖標大小」。</feature>
<feature>【分割屏幕】新增了一步手勢分割屏幕功能，應用程式全屏幕下拖動底部至左上方，輕觸其他支援分割屏幕應用程式，即可啟用應用程式分割屏幕。</feature>
<feature>【浮動視窗】迷你視窗支援移動和懸停到手機主屏幕任何位置。</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1、本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2、務請確保手機有 10 GB 以上的內部儲存空間，否則存在升級失敗的風險（檢視儲存空間的方法：設定 -> 儲存）。
3、由於部分第三方應用程式與 MagicOS 8.0 不相容，更新後，第三方應用程式可能無法正常使用（例如無預警關閉、畫面滯幀、高耗電現象等）。建議您嘗試前往應用程式市場，將該應用程式更新至最新版本，若仍無法解決問題，請耐心等待應用程式更新通知，並及時更新。
4、升級後，系統會自動優化適配，可能出現發熱、耗電過快、畫面滯幀或充電緩慢的問題，正常使用 2 至 3 天後將恢復正常。建議升級完成後，將手機熄屏充電 1 至 2 小時以上，然後再重新啟動手機，以確保手機應用程式快速適配完畢。
5、更新過程中，如遇任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次升級為您推出全新的 MagicOS 8.0 | Android 14 系統，新系統更流暢、更安全、更好用、更省電，桌面更好玩，互動更高效便捷，建議您更新體驗。若要解鎖更多功能，敬請期待後續版本更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="玩轉桌面">
<feature>【桌面圖示】支援桌面圖示大小調整，滿足使用者對圖示大小的不同顯示需求，體驗路徑：「設定->桌面和個人化->桌面設定->圖示大小」。</feature>
<feature>【螢幕分割】新增一步手勢螢幕分割功能，在應用程式全螢幕下，將底部拖曳至左上角，輕觸其他支援螢幕分割的應用程式，即可實現應用程式螢幕分割。</feature>
<feature>【懸浮視窗】迷你視窗支援移動和懸停至手機桌面的任意位置。</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1、本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2、請務必確保手機有 10GB 以上的內部儲存空間，否則會有升級失敗的風險（查看儲存空間方法：設定 -> 儲存空間）。
3、因部分第三方應用程式與 MagicOS 8.0 不相容，更新後可能會出現第三方應用程式無法正常使用的情況（如閃退、停滯、耗電等）。建議您在應用程式商店嘗試將該應用程式更新至最新版本，若仍無法解決問題，請耐心等待應用程式更新資訊，並及時更新。
4、升級後，系統進行自動最佳化調整，可能會出現發熱、耗電快、停滯或充電慢的問題，正常使用 2~3 天後會恢復正常。建議升級完成後將手機螢幕關閉充電 1~2 小時以上再將手機重新開機，以確認手機應用程式快速調整完成。
5、更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或至榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
