<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新优化部分场景相机拍照成像效果，修复部分场景异常耗电问题，提升系统性能、稳定性和热体验，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相机】">
<feature>优化部分场景下长焦拍摄的亮度、颜色效果。
优化部分场景下人像对焦成像效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【性能】">
<feature>修复部分应用启动概率卡死问题。
优化应用启动动效概率丢帧问题。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【功耗】">
<feature>修复部分场景异常耗电问题。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【热体验】">
<feature>提升部分场景热体验。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系统】">
<feature>提升系统稳定性，让您的手机运行更稳定。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>合入安卓2024年7月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update optimizes the imaging effect in some scenarios, fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenes, improves the system performance, stability and heating experience, and incorporates a security patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>This update optimizes the brightness and color effect of telephoto shooting in some scenarios.
This update optimizes the portrait focus imaging effect in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performance">
<feature>This update fixes the problem of random lagging when launching some apps.
This update optimizes the problem of random frame drops in app startup motion effect.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Power consumption">
<feature>This update fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenes.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Heating experience">
<feature>This update optimizes the heating experience in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>This update improves the system stability to make your device run more stably.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android Security Patch (July 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service center for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ የሚመከር ዝማኔ በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች የምስል ተጽእኖን ያተባል፣ በአንዳንድ ትዕይንቶች ላይ ያልተለመደ የኃይል ፍጆታ ችግርን ያስተካክላል፣ የስርዓቱን አፈጻጸም፣ መረጋጋት እና ማሞቂያ ተሞክሮ ያሻሽላል እና የደህንነት መጠገኛን ያካትታል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ካሜራ">
<feature>ይህ ዝማኔ በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች የቴሌፎቶ የማንሳት ብሩህነት እና የቀለም ተጽእኖን ያተባል።
ይህ ዝማኔ በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች ላይ የቁም ምስል ትኩረትን ይተባል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="አፈጻጸም">
<feature>ይህ ዝማኔ አንዳንድ መተግበሪያዎችን ሲያስጀምሩ የዘፈቀደ መዘግየትን ችግር ያስተካክላል።
ይህ ዝማኔ በመተግበሪያ መጀመር እንቅስቃሴ ተጽእኖ ላይ የዘፈቀደ ፍሬም ማጥት ችግሮችን ያተባል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የኃይል ፍጆታ">
<feature>ይህ ዝማኔ በአንዳንድ ትዕይንቶች ላይ ያለውን ያልተለመደ የኃይል ፍጆታ ችግር ያስተካክላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የማሞቂያ ተሞክሮ">
<feature>ይህ ማሻሻያ በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች የማሞቂያ ተሞክሮን ያተባል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ስርዓት">
<feature>ይህ ዝማኔ መሳሪያዎ ይበልጥ በተረጋጋ ሁኔታ እንዲያስኬድ ለማድረግ የስርዓት መረጋጋትን ያሻሽላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ደህንነት">
<feature>ለስርዓት ደህንነት የአንድሮይድ የደህንነት መጠገኛን (ጁላይ 2024) ተካቷል። ስለ HONOR ደህንነት ዝማኔዎች ተጨማሪ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎን የእኛን ድር ጣቢያ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7 ይጎብኙ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፡-" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ማሻሻያ መጫን የእርስዎን የግል መረጃዎን አይደመስስም፣ ነገር ግን አስቀድሞ መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ አሁንም ይመከራል።
2. በማሻሻያው ወቅት ማንኛውም አይነት ችግር ካጋጠመዎት እባክዎን ወደ HONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር ይደውሉ ወይም ድጋፍ ለማግኘት ወደ HONOR የደንበኞች የአገልግሎት ማዕከል ይሂዱ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزي المستخدم، يحسّن هذا التحديث الموصى تأثير التصوير في بعض السيناريوهات، ويصلح مشكلة استهلاك الطاقة غير الطبيعي في بعض الحالات، ويحسّن أداء النظام واستقراره ويعالج تجربة زيادة السخونة، ويضمّن تصحيح أمان.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الكاميرا">
<feature>يحسّن هذا التحديث السطوع وتأثير الألوان عند تصوير لقطات مقربة في بعض السيناريوهات.‬
يحسّن هذا التحديث تأثير التصوير عن طريق التركيز على صور البورتريه في بعض السيناريوهات.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأداء">
<feature>يصلح هذا التحديث مشكلة التأخير العشوائي الذي يحدث عند تشغيل بعض التطبيقات.
يحسّن هذا التحديث مشكلة انخفاض معدل الإطارات بطريقة عشوائية في تأثير حركة بدء تشغيل التطبيق.</feature>
</features>
<features module="استهلاك الطاقة">
<feature>يُصلح هذا التحديث مشكلة استهلاك الطاقة غير الطبيعي في بعض الحالات.</feature>
</features>
<features module="تجربة زيادة السخونة">
<feature>يحسّن هذا التحديث تجربة زيادة السخونة في بعض السيناريوهات.</feature>
</features>
<features module="النظام">
<feature>يحسّن هذا التحديث استقرار النظام لجعل جهازك يعمل بشكل أكثر استقرارًا.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأمان">
<feature>تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (يوليو 2024) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في HONOR، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>1. لن يؤدي تثبيت هذا التحديث إلى مسح بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية مسبقًا.
2. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة HONOR أو انتقل إلى مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR للحصول على الدعم.‬</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই অনুমোদিত আপডেটটোৱে কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত ইমেজিং প্ৰভাৱ অনুকূলন কৰে, কিছুমান দৃশ্যত অস্বাভাৱিক পাৱাৰ খৰচৰ সমস্যাটো সমাধান কৰে, ছিষ্টেমৰ কাৰ্যদক্ষতা, স্থিৰতা আৰু গৰম হোৱাৰ অভিজ্ঞতা উন্নত কৰে আৰু এটা নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="কেমেৰা">
<feature>এই আপডেটটোৱে কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত টেলিফটো শ্বুটিঙৰ উজ্জ্বলতা আৰু ৰঙৰ প্ৰভাৱ অনুকূলন কৰে।
এই আপডেটটোৱে কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত প'ৰ্ট্ৰেইট ফ'কাচ ইমেজিং প্ৰভাৱ অনুকূলন কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="কাৰ্যদক্ষতা">
<feature>এই আপডেটটোৱে কিছুমান এপ্প্‌ প্ৰাৰম্ভ কৰাৰ সময়ত যাদৃচ্ছিক লেগিঙৰ সমস্যাটো সমাধান কৰে।
এই আপডেটটোৱে এপ্প্‌ আৰম্ভণিৰ গতিৰ প্ৰভাৱত যাদৃচ্ছিক ফ্ৰেম কমাৰ সমস্যাটো অনুকূলন কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="পাৱাৰ খৰচ">
<feature>এই আপডেটটোৱে কিছুমান দৃশ্যত অস্বাভাৱিক পাৱাৰ খৰচৰ সমস্যাটো সমাধান কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গৰম হোৱাৰ অভিজ্ঞতা">
<feature>এই আপডেটটোৱে কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত গৰম হোৱাৰ অভিজ্ঞতা অনুকূলন কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ছিষ্টেম">
<feature>এই আপডেটটোৱে আপোনাৰ ডিভাইচ অধিক স্থিৰকৈ চলিব পৰা কৰিবলৈ ছিষ্টেমৰ স্থিৰতা উন্নত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিৰাপত্তা">
<feature>ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (জুলাই 2024) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। HONOR নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটা মোহৰা নহ'ব, কিন্তু তথাপিও তাৰ আগতে বেকআপ ল'বলৈ অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আপডেটৰ সময়ত আপুনি যদি কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হয়, তেন্তে সমৰ্থনৰ বাবে অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত ফোন কৰিব বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ যাব।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, tövsiyə olunan bu yeniləmə bəzi hallarda görüntü effektini optimallaşdırır, bəzi hallarda qeyri-normal enerji istehlakı problemini həll edir, sistemin performansını, sabitliyini və isitmə təcrübəsini yaxşılaşdırır və təhlükəsizlik paketi daxil edir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə bəzi hallarda telefoto çəkilişinin parlaqlığını və rəng effektini optimallaşdırır.
Bu yeniləmə bəzi hallarda portret fokusunun görüntü effektini optimallaşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performans">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə bəzi tətbiqləri işə salarkən təsadüfi gecikmə problemini həll edir.
Bu yeniləmə tətbiqin başlatma hərəkət effektində təsadüfi kadr düşmə problemini optimallaşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Enerji sərfiyyatı">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə bəzi hallarda qeyri-normal enerji sərfiyyatı problemini həll edir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="İsitmə təcrübəsi">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə bəzi hallarda isitmə təcrübəsini optimallaşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə cihazınızın daha stabil işləməsi üçün sistem stabilliyini təkmilləşdirir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Təhlükəsizlik">
<feature>Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android Təhlükəsizlik Paketi (Aprel 2024-cü il) daxil edilib. HONOR Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün veb-saytımıza daxil olun: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması ilə şəxsi məlumatlarınız silinməyəcək, lakin yenə də qabaqcadan ehtiyat nüsxənin çıxarılması tövsiyə edilir.
2. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlərlə qarşılaşsanız, dəstək üçün HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edin, yaxud HONOR müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə gedin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran sing disaranake iki ngoptimalake efek gambar ing sawetera skenario, ndandani masalah panggunaan daya sing ora normal ing sawetara adegan, ngapikake kinerja, stabilitas, lan pangalaman panas sistem, sarta nggabungake patch keamanan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Panganyaran iki ngoptimalake efek padhange lan warna panjupukan telefoto ing sawetara skenario.
Panganyaran iki ngoptimalake efek gambar fokus potret ing sawetara skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kinerja">
<feature>Panganyaran iki ndandani masalah nyendat random nalika ngluncurake sawetara apl.
Panganyaran iki ngoptimalake masalah frame acak mudhun ing efek obahan wiwitan apl.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panggunaan daya">
<feature>Panganyaran iki ndandani masalah panggunaan daya sing ora normal ing sawetara skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pangalaman panas">
<feature>Panganyaran iki ngoptimalake pangalaman panas ing sawetara skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Panganyaran iki ngapikake stabilitas sistem supaya piranti sampeyan mlaku kanthi luwih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Patch Keamanan Android (Juli 2024) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan HONOR bisa dideleng ing situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mbusak data pribadi sampeyan, nanging nggawe serep dhisik tetep disaranake.
2. Yen ana masalah sajrone proses panganyaran, telpona hotline layanan HONOR utawa bukak pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR kanggo njaluk dhukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem se optimizuje efekat slike u nekim scenarijima, rešava problem abnormalne potrošnje struje u nekim scenama, poboljšava se sistem učinka, stabilnosti i iskustva sa zagrevanjem i ono sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se optimizuje efekat osvetljaja i boje telefoto snimanja u nekim scenarijima.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizuje efekat slike fokusa na portretu u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Učinak">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se rešava problem nasumičnog kašnjenja kada se pokrenu neke aplikacije.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizuje problem nasumičnog pada rama kod efekta pokreta prilikom pokretanja aplikacije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se rešava problem nepravilne potrošnje energije u pojedinim situacijama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iskustvo sa zagrevanjem">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se optimizuje iskustvo zagrevanja u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem je poboljšana stabilnost sistema, zbog čega vaš uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (jul 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem se optimizuje efekat slike u nekim scenarijima, rešava problem abnormalne potrošnje struje u nekim scenama, poboljšava se sistem učinka, stabilnosti i iskustva sa zagrevanjem i ono sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se optimizuje efekat osvetljaja i boje telefoto snimanja u nekim scenarijima.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizuje efekat slike fokusa na portretu u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Učinak">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se rešava problem nasumičnog kašnjenja kada se pokrenu neke aplikacije.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizuje problem nasumičnog pada rama kod efekta pokreta prilikom pokretanja aplikacije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se rešava problem nepravilne potrošnje energije u pojedinim situacijama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iskustvo sa zagrevanjem">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se optimizuje iskustvo zagrevanja u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem je poboljšana stabilnost sistema, zbog čega vaš uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (jul 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem se optimizuje efekat slike u nekim scenarijima, rešava problem abnormalne potrošnje struje u nekim scenama, poboljšava se sistem učinka, stabilnosti i iskustva sa zagrevanjem i ono sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se optimizuje efekat osvetljaja i boje telefoto snimanja u nekim scenarijima.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizuje efekat slike fokusa na portretu u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Učinak">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se rešava problem nasumičnog kašnjenja kada se pokrenu neke aplikacije.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizuje problem nasumičnog pada rama kod efekta pokreta prilikom pokretanja aplikacije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se rešava problem nepravilne potrošnje energije u pojedinim situacijama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iskustvo sa zagrevanjem">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se optimizuje iskustvo zagrevanja u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem je poboljšana stabilnost sistema, zbog čega vaš uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (jul 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта рэкамендаванае абнаўленне аптымізуе эфект візуалізацыі ў некаторых сцэнарыях, выпраўляе праблему анамальнага энергаспажывання ў некаторых сцэнах, павышае прадукцыйнасць і ўстойлівасць сістэмы, памяншае праблему награвання і ўключае выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне аптымізуе яркасць і колеравы эфект здымкі тэлефотакамерай у некаторых сцэнарыях.
Гэта абнаўленне аптымізуе эфект партрэтнай факусіроўкі ў некаторых сцэнарыях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Прадукцыйнасць">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне ўстараняе праблему выпадковых затрымак пры запуску некаторых праграм.
Гэта абнаўленне выпраўляе праблему выпадковага пропуску кадраў у эфекце руху падчас запуску праграм.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Энергаспажыванне">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне ўстараняе праблему анамальнага энергаспажывання ў некаторых сцэнах.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Праблема награвання">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне памяншае награванне ў некаторых сцэнарыях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сістэма">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне павышае ўстойлівасць сістэмы, што робіць працу вашай прылады больш стабільнай.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бяспека">
<feature>Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (ліпень 2024 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі HONOR можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не сатрэ вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем загадзя зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, патэлефануйце на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або звярніцеся па дапамогу ў сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази препоръчителна актуализация оптимизира ефекта на заснемане на изображенията в някои ситуации, отстранява проблема с необичайното потребление на енергия в някои сцени, подобрява производителността на системата, стабилността и загряването и включва корекция за сигурност.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Тази актуализация оптимизира ефекта на яркост и цвят при заснемане на телефото в някои ситуации.
Тази актуализация оптимизира ефекта на портретното фокусиране при някои ситуации.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Производителност">
<feature>С тази актуализация се отстранява проблемът със случайното забавяне при стартиране на някои приложения.
Тази актуализация оптимизира проблема със случайното пропускане на кадри при ефекта на движение при стартиране на приложения.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Консумация на енергия">
<feature>С тази актуализация се отстранява проблемът с необичайното потребление на енергия при някои сцени.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Загряване">
<feature>В тази актуализация е оптимизирано загряването в някои ситуации.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>С тази актуализация се подобрява стабилността на системата, за да работи устройството ви по-стабилно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Защита">
<feature>Корекцията за сигурност на Android (юли 2024 г.) е включена за защита на системата. За още информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на HONOR посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да изтрие личните ви данни, но е препоръчително архивиране преди това.
2. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализирането, обадете се на обслужващата гореща линия на HONOR или посетете сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR за поддръжка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই সুপারিশকৃত আপডেটটি কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে ইমেজিং ইফেক্টকে অপটিমাইজ করে, কিছু দৃশ্যে অস্বাভাবিক শক্তি খরচের সমস্যা সমাধান করে, সিস্টেমের কর্মক্ষমতা, স্থিতিশীলতা এবং গরম হওয়ার অভিজ্ঞতা উন্নত করে এবং একটি নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ অন্তর্ভুক্ত করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ক্যামেরা">
<feature>এই আপডেটটি কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে টেলিফটো শুটিং-এর উজ্জ্বলতা এবং রঙের ইফেক্টকে অপটিমাইজ করে।
এই আপডেটটি কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে পোর্ট্রেট ফোকাস ইমেজিং ইফেক্টকে অপটিমাইজ করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="কর্মক্ষমতা">
<feature>এই আপডেটটি কিছু অ্যাপ চালু করার সময় এলোপাথাড়ি পিছিয়ে পড়ার সমস্যা সমাধান করে।
এই আপডেটটি অ্যাপ শুরু হওয়ার মোশন ইফেক্টে এলোপাথাড়ি ফ্রেম ড্রপের সমস্যাকে অপটিমাইজ করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="শক্তি খরচ">
<feature>এই আপডেটটি কিছু দৃশ্যে অস্বাভাবিক শক্তি খরচের সমস্যা সমাধান করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গরম হওয়ার অভিজ্ঞতা">
<feature>এই আপডেট কিছু ক্ষেত্রে গরম হওয়ার অভিজ্ঞতাকে অপটিমাইজ করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="সিস্টেম">
<feature>আপনার ডিভাইসকে আরও স্থিতিশীলভাবে চালানোর জন্য, এই আপডেটটি সিস্টেমের স্থিতিশীলতাকে আরও উন্নত করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিরাপত্তা">
<feature>সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (জুলাই 2024) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। HONOR-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, অনুগ্রহ করে আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="দ্রষ্টব্য:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটা মুছে যাবে না, তবে তা সত্ত্বেও আগে থেকে ব্যাকআপ নেওয়ার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. আপনি যদি আপডেটের সময় কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হন তাহলে অনুগ্রহ করে HONOR সার্ভিস হটলাইনে কল করুন বা সহায়তার জন্য HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে যান।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་པར་ཆས་ཀྱི་པར་ལེན་བརྙན་འགྲུབ་ཁྱད་ནུས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་གློག་ཟད་རྒྱུན་ལྡན་མིན་པའི་གནད་དོན་ཉམས་གསོ་བྱས་ཡོད། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་གཤིས་ནུས་དང་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན། ཚ་བའི་ཉམས་ལེན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད། བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདུས་གྲུབ་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【པར་ཆས།】">
<feature>བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་འོག་ཏུ་མདོ་རིང་གི་པར་ལེན་གསལ་ཚད་དང་ཁ་དོག་ཁྱད་ནུས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད།
བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་འོག་གི་མིའི་གཟུགས་མདོ་སྒྲིག་དང་བརྙན་འགྲུབ་ཁྱད་ནུས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【གཤིས་ནུས།】">
<feature>ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཁག་ཅིག་འགོ་སློང་སྐབས་སྲིད་ཕྱོད་ཅན་གྱི་ཐོགས་པའི་གནད་དོན་ཉམས་གསོ་བྱས་ཡོད།
ཉེར་སྤྱོད་འགོ་སློང་བའི་འགུལ་རྣམ་ཁྱད་ནུས་ཀྱི་སྲིད་ཕྱོད་ཅན་གྱི་བརྙན་པར་བོར་བའི་གནད་དོན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【ནུས་རྩོལ།】">
<feature>བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་གློག་ཟད་རྒྱུན་ལྡན་མིན་པའི་གནད་དོན་ཉམས་གསོ་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【ཚ་བའི་ཉམས་ལེན།】">
<feature>བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་ཚ་བའི་ཉམས་ལེན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བྱས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རྒྱུད་ཁོངས།】">
<feature>རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་འཁོར་སྐྱོད་བྱས་པ་སྔར་བས་བརྟན་འཇགས་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【བདེ་འཇགས།】">
<feature>ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2024 ལོའི་ཟླ་ 7 པའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་བསྡེབས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་ཇེ་བཟང་དུ་གཏོང་བ། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/7 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་གསར་སྒྱུར་མ་བྱས་གོང་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ཡག་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་ལ་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ་ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་སྐུ་མགྲོན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་སོང་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་རེ་ཞུ་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje optimizira efekat slika u određenim scenarijima, rješava problem neuobičajene potrošnje energije u određenim scenama, poboljšava performanse i stabilnost sistema te iskustvo sa zagrijavanjem i ugrađuje sigurnosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparat">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje optimizira efekat osvjetljenja i boje telefoto snimanja u određenim scenarijima.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizira efekat fokusiranja portretnih slika u određenim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performanse">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje rješava problem nasumičnog kašnjenja prilikom pokretanja određenih aplikacija.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizira problem nasumičnog gubljenja kadra u efektu kretanja prilikom pokretanja aplikacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje rješava problem neuobičajene potrošnje energije u određenim scenama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iskustvo sa zagrijavanjem">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje optimizira iskustvo sa zagrijavanjem u određenim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje poboljšava stabilnost sistema kako bi se omogućio stabilniji rad uređaja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (juli 2024) radi sigurnosti sistema. Više informacija o HONOR sigurnosnim ažuriranjima potražite na našoj web lokaciji https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja se neće izbrisati lični podaci, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització recomanada optimitza l'efecte d'imatge en determinades situacions, soluciona el problema del consum d'energia anormal en algunes situacions, millora el rendiment del sistema, l'estabilitat i la sensació d'escalfament i incorpora un pedaç de seguretat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Càmera">
<feature>Aquesta actualització optimitza la brillantor i l'efecte del color de la fotografia amb teleobjectiu en determinades situacions.
Aquesta actualització optimitza l'efecte d'imatge de l'enfocament del retrat en algunes situacions.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendiment">
<feature>Aquesta actualització soluciona el problema del retard aleatori en iniciar algunes aplicacions.
Aquesta actualització optimitza el problema de les caigudes de fotogrames aleatòries en l'efecte de moviment en iniciar una aplicació.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consum d'energia">
<feature>Aquesta actualització soluciona el problema del consum d'energia anormal en determinades situacions.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sensació d'escalfament">
<feature>Aquesta actualització optimitza la sensació d'escalfament en determinades situacions.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Aquesta actualització millora l'estabilitat del sistema, la qual cosa permet que el funcionament del dispositiu sigui més estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguretat">
<feature>S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (juliol del 2024) per a la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'HONOR, consulteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Si instal·leu aquesta actualització, les dades personals no s'esborraran, però us recomanem que en feu una còpia de seguretat.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o aneu al centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR per demanar assistència.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený uživateli, tato doporučená aktualizace optimalizuje obrazový efekt v některých situacích, opravuje problém neobvyklé spotřeby energie v některých případech, zlepšuje výkon systému, stabilitu a zahřívání a instaluje bezpečnostní opravu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparát">
<feature>Tato aktualizace optimalizuje jas a barevný efekt při fotografování teleobjektivem v některých scénách.
Tato aktualizace v některých scénách optimalizuje efekt zaostření na výšku.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Výkonnost">
<feature>Tato aktualizace opravuje problém náhodného zpoždění při spouštění některých aplikací.
Tato aktualizace optimalizuje problém náhodných vypuštěných snímků v pohybovém efektu při spuštění aplikace.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Spotřeba energie">
<feature>Tato aktualizace opravuje problém neobvyklé spotřeby energie v některých situacích.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zahřívání">
<feature>Tato aktualizace snižuje zahřívání zařízení v některých situacích.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Tato aktualizace vylepšuje stabilitu systému, aby zařízení pracovalo stabilněji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezpečnost">
<feature>Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (červenec 2024) pro systém Android zajišťující bezpečnost systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích HONOR najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalací této aktualizace nebudou vymazány vaše osobní údaje, ale přesto se doporučuje je předem zálohovat.
2. Pokud se během aktualizace setkáte s nějakými problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo si vyžádejte podporu v Centru služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger, denne anbefalede opdatering optimerer billedeffekten i nogle scenarier, løser problemet med unormalt strømforbrug i visse scener, forbedrer systemets ydeevne, stabilitet og varmeoplevelse samt inkorporerer en sikkerhedsrettelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Denne opdatering optimerer lysstyrken og farveeffekten på telefotooptagelser i nogle scenarier.
Denne opdatering optimerer billedeffekten med portrætfokus i nogle scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ydeevne">
<feature>Denne opdatering løser problemet med tilfældig lagging, når nogle apps startes.
Denne opdatering optimerer problemet med tilfældig lav FPS for bevægelseseffekten ved app-opstart.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Strømforbrug">
<feature>Denne opdatering løser problemet med unormalt strømforbrug i visse scener.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varmeoplevelse">
<feature>Denne opdatering optimerer varmeoplevelsen i nogle scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Denne opdatering forbedrer systemstabiliteten for at få din enhed til at køre mere stabilt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhed">
<feature>Android sikkerhedsrettelse (juli 2024) er blevet integreret for øget systemsikkerhed. For yderligere oplysninger om HONOR-sikkerhedsopdateringer kan du besøge vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering sletter ikke dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadigvæk at tage en sikkerhedskopi på forhånd.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du ringe til HONORs service-hotline eller gå til HONOR kundeservicecenter for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung optimiert den Bildeffekt in einigen Szenarien, behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenen, verbessert die Systemleistung und -stabilität sowie das Erwärmungserlebnis und umfasst einen Sicherheitspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung optimiert in einigen Szenarien die Helligkeit und Farbwirkung von Aufnahmen mit dem Teleobjektiv.
Diese Aktualisierung optimiert den Porträtfokus-Bildeffekt in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Leistung">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung behebt das Problem zufälliger Verzögerungen beim Starten einiger Apps.
Diese Aktualisierung optimiert das Problem zufälliger Framedrops im Bewegungseffekt beim App-Start.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stromverbrauch">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Erwärmungserlebnis">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung optimiert das Erwärmungserlebnis in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung verbessert die Systemstabilität, damit Ihr Gerät stabiler läuft.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Juli 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Durch die Installation dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch trotzdem empfohlen, im Vorfeld eine Datensicherung vorzunehmen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung optimiert den Bildeffekt in einigen Szenarien, behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenen, verbessert die Systemleistung und -stabilität sowie das Erwärmungserlebnis und umfasst einen Sicherheitspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung optimiert in einigen Szenarien die Helligkeit und Farbwirkung von Aufnahmen mit dem Teleobjektiv.
Diese Aktualisierung optimiert den Porträtfokus-Bildeffekt in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Leistung">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung behebt das Problem zufälliger Verzögerungen beim Starten einiger Apps.
Diese Aktualisierung optimiert das Problem zufälliger Framedrops im Bewegungseffekt beim App-Start.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stromverbrauch">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Erwärmungserlebnis">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung optimiert das Erwärmungserlebnis in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung verbessert die Systemstabilität, damit Ihr Gerät stabiler läuft.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Juli 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Durch die Installation dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch trotzdem empfohlen, im Vorfeld eine Datensicherung vorzunehmen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung optimiert den Bildeffekt in einigen Szenarien, behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenen, verbessert die Systemleistung und -stabilität sowie das Erwärmungserlebnis und umfasst einen Sicherheitspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung optimiert in einigen Szenarien die Helligkeit und Farbwirkung von Aufnahmen mit dem Teleobjektiv.
Diese Aktualisierung optimiert den Porträtfokus-Bildeffekt in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Leistung">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung behebt das Problem zufälliger Verzögerungen beim Starten einiger Apps.
Diese Aktualisierung optimiert das Problem zufälliger Framedrops im Bewegungseffekt beim App-Start.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stromverbrauch">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Erwärmungserlebnis">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung optimiert das Erwärmungserlebnis in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung verbessert die Systemstabilität, damit Ihr Gerät stabiler läuft.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Juli 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Durch die Installation dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch trotzdem empfohlen, im Vorfeld eine Datensicherung vorzunehmen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η προτεινόμενη ενημέρωση βελτιστοποιεί το αποτέλεσμα απεικόνισης σε ορισμένα σενάρια, διορθώνει το πρόβλημα της μη φυσιολογικής κατανάλωσης ενέργειας σε ορισμένες σκηνές, βελτιώνει την εμπειρία απόδοσης, σταθερότητας και θέρμανσης του συστήματος και ενσωματώνει μια ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Κάμερα">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιστοποιεί τη φωτεινότητα και την ποιότητα χρωμάτων της λήψης με τηλεφακό σε ορισμένα σενάρια.
Αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιστοποιεί το αποτέλεσμα απεικόνισης εστίασης σε κατακόρυφη προβολή σε ορισμένα σενάρια.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Επιδόσεις">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση διορθώνει το πρόβλημα της τυχαίας καθυστέρησης κατά την εκκίνηση ορισμένων εφαρμογών.
Αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιστοποιεί το πρόβλημα των τυχαίων μειώσεων καρέ στο εφέ κίνησης της εκκίνησης εφαρμογών.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Κατανάλωση ενέργειας">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση διορθώνει το πρόβλημα της μη φυσιολογικής κατανάλωσης ενέργειας σε ορισμένες σκηνές.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Εμπειρία θέρμανσης">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιστοποιεί την εμπειρία θέρμανσης σε ορισμένα σενάρια.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σύστημα">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιώνει τη σταθερότητα του συστήματος για να λειτουργεί η συσκευή σας πιο σταθερά.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ασφάλεια">
<feature>Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Ιούλιος 2024) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας HONOR, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα διαγράψει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, ωστόσο συνιστάται προηγουμένως η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας.
2. Εάν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, καλέστε την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή της HONOR ή μεταβείτε στο κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR για υποστήριξη.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update optimises the imaging effect in some scenarios, fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenes, improves the system performance, stability and heating experience, and incorporates a security patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>This update optimises the brightness and colour effect of telephoto shooting in some scenarios.
This update optimises the portrait focus imaging effect in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performance">
<feature>This update fixes the problem of random lagging when launching some apps.
This update optimises the problem of random frame drops in app startup motion effect.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Power consumption">
<feature>This update fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenes.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Heating experience">
<feature>This update optimises the heating experience in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>This update improves the system stability to make your device run more stably.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android Security Patch (July 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service centre for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, esta actualización recomendada optimiza el efecto de imagen en algunos escenarios, soluciona el problema del consumo anormal de energía en algunos casos, mejora el rendimiento del sistema, la estabilidad y la experiencia de calentamiento e incorpora un parche de seguridad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>Esta actualización optimiza el brillo y el efecto de color de las fotos con teleobjetivo en algunos escenarios.
Esta actualización optimiza el efecto de imagen de enfoque de retrato en algunos escenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendimiento">
<feature>Esta actualización soluciona el problema del retraso aleatorio al iniciar algunas aplicaciones.
Esta actualización optimiza el problema de las caídas aleatorias de fotogramas en el efecto de movimiento de inicio de la aplicación.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de energía">
<feature>Esta actualización soluciona el problema del consumo de energía anormal en algunas escenas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Experiencia de calentamiento">
<feature>Esta actualización optimiza la experiencia de calentamiento en algunos escenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Esta actualización mejora la estabilidad del sistema para que el dispositivo funcione de manera más estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (julio de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Aunque la instalación de esta actualización no eliminará sus datos personales, se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad antes.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para obtener ayuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario: esta actualización recomendada optimiza el efecto de imagen en algunos escenarios, soluciona el problema del consumo de energía anormal en algunas escenas, mejora el rendimiento del sistema, la estabilidad y la experiencia de calentamiento, y se incorpora un parche de seguridad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>Esta actualización optimiza el brillo y el efecto de color de la toma con teleobjetivo en algunos escenarios.
Esta actualización optimiza el efecto de imagen de enfoque vertical en algunos escenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendimiento">
<feature>Esta actualización soluciona el problema del retraso aleatorio al iniciar algunas aplicaciones.
Esta actualización optimiza el problema de las caídas aleatorias de fotogramas en el efecto de movimiento de inicio de la aplicación.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de energía">
<feature>Esta actualización soluciona el problema del consumo de energía anormal en algunas escenas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Experiencia de calentamiento">
<feature>Esta actualización optimiza la experiencia de calentamiento en algunos escenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Esta actualización mejora la estabilidad del sistema para hacer que el dispositivo funcione de manera más estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (julio de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Esta actualización no eliminará sus datos personales; sin embargo, le recomendamos hacer una copia de respaldo de los datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visite el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja! See soovitatav värskendus optimeerib mõnes olukorras pildiefekti, lahendab mõnes olukorras ebanormaalse energiatarbimise probleemi, parandab süsteemi tööd ja stabiilsust, vähendab kuumaks minemise esinemist ning sisaldab turvapaika.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kaamera">
<feature>See värskendus optimeerib mõnes olukorras telefoto jäädvustamisel heleduse ja värviefekti.
See värskendus optimeerib mõnes olukorras portreefookuse pildiefekti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Jõudlus">
<feature>See värskendus parandab mõne rakenduse käivitamisel esineva juhusliku pika reaktsiooniaja probleemi.
See värskendus optimeerib juhusliku kaadri kustutamise probleemi rakenduse käivitamisel liikumisefektis.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energiakulu">
<feature>See värskendus lahendab mõnes olukorras ebanormaalse energiatarbimise probleemi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kuumaks minemise esinemine">
<feature>See värskendus optimeerib mõnes olukorras kuumaks minemise esinemist.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Süsteem">
<feature>See värskendus parandab süsteemi stabiilsust ja muudab seadme töö stabiilsemaks.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvalisus">
<feature>Lisati süsteemi turvalisemaks muutev Androidi turvapaik (juuli 2024). Lisateavet HONORi turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei kustuta teie isikuandmeid, kuid eelnev varundamine on siiski soovitatav.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, helistage HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või minge toe saamiseks HONORi klienditeeninduskeskusesse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile agurgarria, gomendatutako eguneratze honetan, optimizatu egin da agertoki batzuetako irudi-efektua, egoera batzuetan bateriaren kontsumo anormalaren arazoa konpondu da, sistemaren errendimendua, egonkortasuna eta beroketa-esperientzia hobetu dira, eta segurtasun-adabaki bat gehitu da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Eguneratze honetan, agertoki batzuetan teleobjektibo bidezko tiroaren distira eta kolore efektua optimizatu dira.
Eguneratze honetan, zenbait agertokitan erretratuaren ikuspegi irudiaren efektua optimizatu da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Errendimendua">
<feature>Eguneratze honetan, aplikazio batzuk abiaraztean ausazko atzerapenaren arazoa konpondu da.
Eguneratze honetan, optimizatu egin da fotogramen ausazko erortzeen arazoa mugimendu-efektuan, aplikazio bat abiaraztean.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bateriaren kontsumoa">
<feature>Eguneratze honetan ezohiko bateriaren kontsumoaren arazoa konpondu da egoera batzuetan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Berokuntza-esperientzia">
<feature>Eguneratze honetan, berokuntza-esperientzia hobetu da zenbait agertokitan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Eguneratze honetan sistemaren egonkortasuna hobetu da, gailuak hobeto funtziona dezan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurtasuna">
<feature>Android-en segurtasun-adabakia (2024ko uzt.) gehitu da sistema seguru egoteko. HONOR Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago nahi izanez gero, joan gure webgunera: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzen baduzu ere, zure datu pertsonalak ez dira ezabatuko, baina, hala ere, instalatu aurretik haien babeskopia bat egitea gomendatzen da.
2. Eguneratze-prozesuan arazoren bat izanez gero, deitu HONOR zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara edo joan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora laguntza jasotzeko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی پیشنهادی، جلوۀ تصویربرداری را در برخی از سناریوها بهینه می‌کند، مشکل مصرف غیرعادی نیرو در برخی شرایط را برطرف می‌کند، عملکرد سیستم، پایداری و تجربه گرمایش را بهبود می‌بخشد و یک وصله امنیتی در آن گنجانده شده است.</feature>
</features>
<features module="دوربین">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی روشنایی و جلوه رنگ تصویربرداری تله‌فوتو را در برخی سناریوها بهینه می‌کند.
این به‌روزرسانی جلوه تصویربرداری فوکوس پرتره را در برخی سناریوها بهینه می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="عملکرد">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی مشکل تأخیر تصادفی هنگام راه‌اندازی برخی برنامه‌ها را برطرف می‌کند.
این به‌روزرسانی مشکل افت فریم تصادفی در جلوه حرکتی راه‌اندازی برنامه را بهینه می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="مصرف نیرو">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی مشکل مصرف غیرعادی نیرو در برخی شرایط را برطرف می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="تجربه گرمایش">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی، تجربه گرمایش در برخی شرایط را بهینه می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="سیستم">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی پایداری سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد تا دستگاه شما عملکرد پایدارتری داشته باشد.</feature>
</features>
<features module="امنیت">
<feature>برای حفظ امنیت سیستم، وصلۀ امنیتی Android (ژوئیه ۲۰۲۴) گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر دربارۀ به‌روزرسانی‌های امنیتی HONOR، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما به این نشانی مراجعه کنید: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="نکات:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏۱. با نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما پاک نخواهد شد، اما همچنان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام این به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.
‏‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، لطفاً جهت دریافت پشتیبانی با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä suositeltu päivitys optimoi kuvaustehosteen joissakin tilanteissa, korjaa epätavallisen virrankulutuksen ongelman joissakin tilanteissa, parantaa järjestelmän suorituskykyä, vakautta ja lämpökokemusta ja sisältää turvallisuuskorjauksen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Tämä päivitys optimoi teleobjektiivikuvauksen kirkkauden ja väritehosteen joissakin tilanteissa.
Tämä päivitys optimoi muotokuvan tarkennuksen kuvaustehosteen joissakin tilanteissa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Suorituskyky">
<feature>Tämä päivitys korjaa satunnaisen viiveongelman joidenkin sovellusten käynnistyksessä.
Tämä päivitys korjaa sovelluksen käynnistysanimaation satunnaisen kuvien putoamisen ongelman.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Virrankulutus">
<feature>Tämä päivitys korjaa epätavallisen virrankulutuksen ongelman joissakin tilanteissa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lämpökokemus">
<feature>Tämä päivitys optimoi lämpökokemuksen joissakin tilanteissa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Järjestelmä">
<feature>Tämä päivitys parantaa järjestelmän vakautta, jotta laite toimisi vakaammin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvallisuus">
<feature>Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (heinäkuu 2024) on sisällytetty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja HONORin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on verkkosivustollamme: https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei poista henkilökohtaisia tietojasi, mutta ne on silti suositeltavaa varmuuskopioida etukäteen.
2. Jos päivityksessä ilmenee ongelmia, soita HONORin palvelunumeroon tai mene valtuutettuun HONOR-asiakaspalvelukeskukseen tukea varten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée optimise l'effet d'imagerie dans certains scénarios, corrige le problème de consommation d'énergie anormale dans certaines scènes, améliore les performances, la stabilité et l'expérience d'échauffement du système et intègre un correctif de sécurité.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Appareil photo">
<feature>Cette mise à jour optimise la luminosité et l'effet de couleur des prises de vue au téléobjectif dans certains scénarios.
Cette mise à jour optimise l'effet d'imagerie de la mise au point en mode portrait dans certains scénarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performance">
<feature>Cette mise à jour corrige le problème de ralentissement aléatoire lors du lancement de certaines applications.
Cette mise à jour optimise le problème de pertes d'images aléatoires dans l'effet de mouvement au démarrage des applications.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consommation d'énergie">
<feature>Cette mise à jour corrige le problème de consommation d'énergie anormale dans certaines scènes.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Expérience d'échauffement">
<feature>Cette mise à jour optimise l'expérience d'échauffement dans certains scénarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>Cette mise à jour améliore la stabilité du système de votre appareil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Le correctif de sécurité Android (juillet 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'effacera pas vos données personnelles, mais une sauvegarde préalable est tout de même recommandée.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée optimise l'effet d'imagerie dans certains scénarios, corrige le problème de consommation d'énergie anormale dans certaines scènes, améliore les performances, la stabilité et l'expérience d'échauffement du système et intègre un correctif de sécurité.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Appareil photo">
<feature>Cette mise à jour optimise la luminosité et l'effet de couleur des prises de vue au téléobjectif dans certains scénarios.
Cette mise à jour optimise l'effet d'imagerie de la mise au point en mode portrait dans certains scénarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performance">
<feature>Cette mise à jour corrige le problème de ralentissement aléatoire lors du lancement de certaines applications.
Cette mise à jour optimise le problème de pertes d'images aléatoires dans l'effet de mouvement au démarrage des applications.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consommation d'énergie">
<feature>Cette mise à jour corrige le problème de consommation d'énergie anormale dans certaines scènes.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Expérience d'échauffement">
<feature>Cette mise à jour optimise l'expérience d'échauffement dans certains scénarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>Cette mise à jour améliore la stabilité du système de votre appareil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Le correctif de sécurité Android (juillet 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'effacera pas vos données personnelles, mais une sauvegarde préalable est tout de même recommandée.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario: esta actualización recomendada optimiza o efecto de creación de imaxes en certos escenarios, soluciona o problema co consumo de enerxía anormal e certas escenas, mellora o rendemento, a estabilidade e a temperatura do sistema, e incorpora un parche de seguranza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>Esta actualización optimiza a luminosidade e o efecto de cor do disparo con teleobxectivo en certos casos.
Esta actualización optimiza o efecto de enfoque de imaxes en modo retrato en certos casos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendemento">
<feature>Esta actualización soluciona o problema de retrasos ao iniciar certas aplicacións.
Esta actualización optimiza o problema de caídas de fotogramas aleatorias no efecto de movemento de inicio de aplicacións.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de enerxía">
<feature>Esta actualización soluciona o problema do consumo de enerxía anómalo nalgúns casos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Temperatura">
<feature>Esta actualización optimiza a experiencia de temperatura elevada en determinadas situacións.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Esta actualización mellora a estabilidade do sistema para que o dispositivo funcione dun xeito máis estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguranza">
<feature>Incorpórase o parche de seguranza de Android (xullo de 2024) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información acerca das actualizacións de seguranza de HONOR, visite o noso sitio web: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ao instalar esta actualización non se eliminarán os seus datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar antes unha copia de seguranza.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou visite un centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ ભલામણ કરેલ અપડેટ કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં ઇમેજિંગ પ્રભાવને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે, કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં અસામાન્ય પાવર વપરાશની સમસ્યાને ઠીક કરે છે, સિસ્ટમની કામગીરી, સ્થિરતા અને ગરમ થવાના અનુભવને સુધારે છે અને સુરક્ષા પેચનો સમાવેશ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="કૅમેરા">
<feature>આ અપડેટ કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં ટેલિફોટો શૂટિંગના ચળકાટ અને રંગના પ્રભાવને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે.
આ અપડેટ કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં પોર્ટ્રેટ ફોકસ ઇમેજિંગ પ્રભાવને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="કામગીરી">
<feature>આ અપડેટ કેટલિક એપ્લિકેશન્સ લૉન્ચ કરતી વખતે યાદૃચ્છિક વિલંબની સમસ્યાને ઠીક કરે છે.
આ અપડેટ એપ્લિકેશન સ્ટાર્ટઅપ મોશન પ્રભાવમાં યાદૃચ્છિક ફ્રેમ ડ્રોપની સમસ્યાને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="પાવર વપરાશ">
<feature>આ અપડેટ કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં અસાધારણ પાવર વપરાશની સમસ્યાને ઠીક કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ગરમ થવાનો અનુભવ">
<feature>આ અપડેટ કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓ માટે ગરમ થવાના અનુભવને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સિસ્ટમ">
<feature>તમારું ઉપકરણ વધુ સ્થિર રીતે ચલાવવા આ અપડેટ સિસ્ટમની સ્થિરતામાં સુધારો કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સુરક્ષા">
<feature>Android સુરક્ષા પેચ (જુલાઈ 2024) સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. HONOR સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7 ની મુલાકાત લો</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારો વ્યક્તિગત ડેટા ભૂંસાઈ જશે નહીં, પરંતુ અગાઉથી બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો કૃપા કરીને HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરો અથવા સમર્થન માટે HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્ર પર જાઓ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अनुशंसित अद्यतन से कुछ परिदृश्यों में इमेजिंग प्रभाव को अनुकूलित किया जाता है, कुछ दृश्यों में असामान्य पॉवर उपभोग की समस्या ठीक की जाती है, सिस्टम के प्रदर्शन, स्थिरता और हीटिंग अनुभव में सुधार किया जाता है और सुरक्षा पैच शामिल किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कैमरा">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से कुछ परिदृश्यों में टेलीफ़ोटो शूटिंग की चमक और रंग प्रभाव को अनुकूलित किया जाता है।
इस अद्यतन से कुछ परिदृश्यों में पोर्ट्रेट फ़ोकस इमेजिंग प्रभाव को अनुकूलित किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्रदर्शन">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से कुछ ऐप्स लॉन्च करते समय रैंडम लैगिंग की समस्या को ठीक किया जाता है।
इस अद्यतन से ऐप स्टार्टअप गति प्रभाव में रैंडम फ़्रेम ड्रॉप की समस्या को ठीक किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="पॉवर उपभोग">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से, कुछ दृश्यों में असामान्य पॉवर उपभोग की समस्या को ठीक किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="हीटिंग अनुभव">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से, कुछ परिदृश्यों में हीटिंग अनुभव को अनुकूलित किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से सिस्टम स्थिरता में सुधार किया जाता है, ताकि आपके डिवाइस को अधिक स्थिर रूप से चलाया जा सके।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>सिस्टम की सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (जुलाई, 2024) शामिल किया गया है। HONOR सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7 पर जाएँ</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो सहायता के लिए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करें या सहायता के लिए HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाएँ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se preporučenim ažuriranjem optimizira efekt slika u nekim scenarijima, rješava se problem neuobičajeno velike potrošnje energije u nekim scenama, poboljšavaju se performanse, stabilnost i zagrijavanje sustava, a implementirana je i sigurnosna zakrpa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparat">
<feature>Ovim se ažuriranjem optimizira svjetlina i efekt boja za telefotografsko snimanje u nekim scenarijima.
Ovim se ažuriranjem optimizira efekt fokusiranja na portret u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performanse">
<feature>Ovim se ažuriranjem rješava problem nasumičnog kašnjenja prilikom pokretanja nekih aplikacija.
Ovim se ažuriranjem optimizira problem nasumičnog preskakanja sličica tijekom pokretanja aplikacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Ovim se ažuriranjem rješava problem neuobičajeno velike potrošnje energije u nekim scenama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iskustvo zagrijavanja">
<feature>Ovim se ažuriranjem optimizira iskustvo zagrijavanja u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sustav">
<feature>Ovim se ažuriranjem poboljšava stabilnost sustava pa uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (srpanj 2024.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke HONOR Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalacijom ovog ažuriranja neće se izbrisati vaši osobni podaci, ali preporučujemo da ipak prije ažuriranja izradite sigurnosnu kopiju.
2. Ako tijekom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za pomoć nazovite telefonsku korisničku službu tvrtke HONOR ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku tvrtke HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez az ajánlott frissítés bizonyos helyzetekben optimalizálja a képalkotási hatást, kijavítja a bizonyos jeleneteknél előforduló rendellenes energiafogyasztás problémáját, javítja a rendszer teljesítményét, stabilitását és melegedését, valamint egy biztonsági javítást tartalmaz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Ez a frissítés bizonyos helyzetekben optimalizálja a telefotós fényképezés fényerejét és színhatását.
Ez a frissítés bizonyos helyzetekben optimalizálja a portréfókusz képi hatását.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Teljesítmény">
<feature>Ez a frissítés megszünteti az egyes alkalmazások elindításakor jelentkező véletlenszerű késést.
Ez a frissítés megszünteti az alkalmazások indításakor véletlenszerűen jelentkező képkockakieséseket.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energiafogyasztás">
<feature>Ez a frissítés bizonyos esetekben kijavítja a nem megfelelő energiafogyasztással kapcsolatos problémát.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Melegedés">
<feature>Ez a frissítés bizonyos helyzetekben optimalizálja a melegedést.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendszer">
<feature>Ez a frissítés javítja a rendszer stabilitását, így a készülék zökkenőmentesebben működik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biztonság">
<feature>Tartalmazza a rendszer biztonságát fokozó Android biztonsági javítást (2024. július). A HONOR biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. E frissítés telepítése nem törli a személyes adatokat, de javasoljuk, hogy készítsen előtte biztonsági mentést.
2. Ha problémába ütközik a frissítés során, hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini mengoptimalkan efek pencitraan di beberapa skenario, memperbaiki masalah konsumsi daya abnormal di beberapa skenario, meningkatkan kinerja sistem, stabilitas, dan pengalaman pemanasan, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Pembaruan ini mengoptimal kecerahan dan efek warna pengambilan gambar telefoto di beberapa skenario.
Pembaruan ini mengoptimalkan efek pencitraan fokus potret di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kinerja">
<feature>Pembaruan ini memperbaiki masalah lag acak saat meluncurkan beberapa aplikasi.
Pembaruan ini mengoptimalkan masalah penurunan bingkai yang acak saat efek gerakan memulai aplikasi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Konsumsi daya">
<feature>Pembaruan ini memperbaiki masalah konsumsi daya abnormal di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pengalaman pemanasan">
<feature>Pembaruan ini mengoptimalkan pengalaman pemanasan di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Pembaruan ini meningkatkan stabilitas sistem agar pengoperasian perangkat Anda lebih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Penambal Keamanan Android (Juli 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan menghapus data pribadi Anda, tetapi masih disarankan untuk melakukan pencadangan sebelumnya.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, silakan hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan dukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini mengoptimalkan efek pencitraan di beberapa skenario, memperbaiki masalah konsumsi daya abnormal di beberapa skenario, meningkatkan kinerja sistem, stabilitas, dan pengalaman pemanasan, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Pembaruan ini mengoptimal kecerahan dan efek warna pengambilan gambar telefoto di beberapa skenario.
Pembaruan ini mengoptimalkan efek pencitraan fokus potret di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kinerja">
<feature>Pembaruan ini memperbaiki masalah lag acak saat meluncurkan beberapa aplikasi.
Pembaruan ini mengoptimalkan masalah penurunan bingkai yang acak saat efek gerakan memulai aplikasi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Konsumsi daya">
<feature>Pembaruan ini memperbaiki masalah konsumsi daya abnormal di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pengalaman pemanasan">
<feature>Pembaruan ini mengoptimalkan pengalaman pemanasan di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Pembaruan ini meningkatkan stabilitas sistem agar pengoperasian perangkat Anda lebih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Penambal Keamanan Android (Juli 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan menghapus data pribadi Anda, tetapi masih disarankan untuk melakukan pencadangan sebelumnya.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, silakan hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan dukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento raccomandato ottimizza l'effetto delle immagini in determinati scenari, risolve il consumo anomalo di energia in certi scenari, migliora le prestazioni, la stabilità e la gestione termica del sistema e incorpora una patch di sicurezza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotocamera">
<feature>L'aggiornamento ottimizza la luminosità e gli effetti colore delle riprese con teleobiettivo in determinati scenari.
Questo aggiornamento ottimizza la messa a fuoco dell'immagine nei ritratti in determinati scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prestazioni">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento risolve il problema del ritardo casuale all'avvio di alcune app.
Questo aggiornamento ottimizza il problema della perdita casuale di fotogrammi nell'effetto movimento all'avvio dell'app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo di energia">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento risolve il problema del consumo di energia anomalo in alcuni scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gestione termica">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento ottimizza la gestione termica in alcuni scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento migliora la stabilità del sistema, per garantire un funzionamento più stabile del dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (luglio 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non comporta l'eliminazione delle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento raccomandato ottimizza l'effetto delle immagini in determinati scenari, risolve il consumo anomalo di energia in certi scenari, migliora le prestazioni, la stabilità e la gestione termica del sistema e incorpora una patch di sicurezza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotocamera">
<feature>L'aggiornamento ottimizza la luminosità e gli effetti colore delle riprese con teleobiettivo in determinati scenari.
Questo aggiornamento ottimizza la messa a fuoco dell'immagine nei ritratti in determinati scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prestazioni">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento risolve il problema del ritardo casuale all'avvio di alcune app.
Questo aggiornamento ottimizza il problema della perdita casuale di fotogrammi nell'effetto movimento all'avvio dell'app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo di energia">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento risolve il problema del consumo di energia anomalo in alcuni scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gestione termica">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento ottimizza la gestione termica in alcuni scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento migliora la stabilità del sistema, per garantire un funzionamento più stabile del dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (luglio 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non comporta l'eliminazione delle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה ממטב את אפקט ההדמיה בתרחישים מסוימים, פותר את הבעיה של צריכת חשמל חריגה בסצנות מסוימות, משפר את ביצועי המערכת, את יציבותה ואת חוויית החימום, ומשלב תיקון אבטחה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מצלמה">
<feature>עדכון זה ממטב את הבהירות ואת אפקט הצבע של צילום טלפוטו בתרחישים מסוימים.
עדכון זה ממטב את אפקט ההדמיה של מיקוד דיוקן בתרחישים מסוימים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ביצועים">
<feature>עדכון זה פותר את הבעיה של השתהות אקראית בעת הפעלת יישומים מסוימים.
עדכון זה ממטב את הבעיה של נפילת מסגרות אקראית באפקט התנועה בעת הפעלת היישום.</feature>
</features>
<features module="צריכת חשמל">
<feature>עדכון זה פותר את הבעיה של צריכת חשמל חריגה בסצנות מסוימות.</feature>
</features>
<features module="חוויית החימום">
<feature>עדכון זה ממטב את חוויית החימום בתרחישים מסוימים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מערכת">
<feature>עדכון זה משפר את יציבות המערכת כדי לגרום להתקן שלך לפעול בצורה יציבה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מיולי 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תמחק את הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לבצע גיבוי מראש.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה ממטב את אפקט ההדמיה בתרחישים מסוימים, פותר את הבעיה של צריכת חשמל חריגה בסצנות מסוימות, משפר את ביצועי המערכת, את יציבותה ואת חוויית החימום, ומשלב תיקון אבטחה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מצלמה">
<feature>עדכון זה ממטב את הבהירות ואת אפקט הצבע של צילום טלפוטו בתרחישים מסוימים.
עדכון זה ממטב את אפקט ההדמיה של מיקוד דיוקן בתרחישים מסוימים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ביצועים">
<feature>עדכון זה פותר את הבעיה של השתהות אקראית בעת הפעלת יישומים מסוימים.
עדכון זה ממטב את הבעיה של נפילת מסגרות אקראית באפקט התנועה בעת הפעלת היישום.</feature>
</features>
<features module="צריכת חשמל">
<feature>עדכון זה פותר את הבעיה של צריכת חשמל חריגה בסצנות מסוימות.</feature>
</features>
<features module="חוויית החימום">
<feature>עדכון זה ממטב את חוויית החימום בתרחישים מסוימים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מערכת">
<feature>עדכון זה משפר את יציבות המערכת כדי לגרום להתקן שלך לפעול בצורה יציבה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מיולי 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תמחק את הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לבצע גיבוי מראש.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様。この推奨更新では、一部の状況での画像処理効果が最適化され、一部の状況での異常な消費電力の問題が修正され、システムの性能、安定性、高温化体験が改善され、セキュリティパッチが組み込まれます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="カメラ">
<feature>この推奨更新では、一部の状況での望遠撮影の明るさと色彩効果が最適化されます。
この推奨更新では、一部の状況でのポートレートフォーカスの画像処理効果が最適化されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="性能">
<feature>この推奨更新では、一部のアプリの起動時に発生する不規則な遅延の問題が修正されます。
この推奨更新では、アプリ起動時のモーション効果で発生する不規則なコマ落ちの問題が最適化されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="消費電力">
<feature>今回の更新によって、一部の状況における異常な消費電力の問題が修正されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="高温体験">
<feature>今回の更新では、一部の状況における高温体験が最適化されました。</feature>
</features>
<features module="システム">
<feature>今回の更新では、システムの安定性が改善され、デバイスがより安定して動作するようになります。</feature>
</features>
<features module="セキュリティ">
<feature>システムセキュリティのためにAndroidセキュリティパッチ（2024年7月）が組み込まれました。HONORのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報が消去されることはありませんが、事前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターでサポートを受けてください。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ეს რეკომენდებული განახლება ახდენს გამოსახულების ეფექტის ოპტიმიზებას ზოგიერთ სცენარში, აგვარებს ენერგიის არანორმალური მოხმარების პრობლემას ზოგიერთ გარემოებაში, აუმჯობესებს სისტემის მუშაობას, სტაბილურობასა და გადახურებასთან დაკავშირებულ გამოცდილებას და ჩართავს უსაფრთხოების შესწორებას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="კამერა">
<feature>ეს განახლება ახდენს ტელეფოტო გადაღების სიკაშკაშისა და ფერის ეფექტის ოპტიმიზებას ზოგიერთ სცენარში.
ეს განახლება ახდენს პორტრეტის ფოკუსის გამოსახულების ეფექტის ოპტიმიზებას ზოგიერთ სცენარში.</feature>
</features>
<features module="მუშაობის ხარისხი">
<feature>ეს განახლება აგვარებს ზოგიერთი აპის გაშვებისას შემთხვევითი ჩამორჩენის პრობლემას.
ეს განახლება ახდენს აპის გაშვებისას მოძრაობის ეფექტში ჩარჩოს შემთხვევითი დაყოფის პრობლემას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ენერგიის მოხმარება">
<feature>ეს განახლება აღმოფხვრის ზოგიერთ სცენაში ენერგიის არანორმალურ მოხმარებასთან დაკავშირებულ პრობლემას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="გადახურებასთან დაკავშირებული გამოცდილება">
<feature>ეს განახლება ახდენს გადახურების ოპტიმიზებას ზოგიერთ სცენარში.</feature>
</features>
<features module="სისტემა">
<feature>ეს განახლება აუმჯობესებს სისტემის სტაბილურობას, რის შედეგადაც მოწყობილობა უფრო სტაბილურად მუშაობს.</feature>
</features>
<features module="უსაფრთხოება">
<feature>სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის ჩაირთო Android უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (2024 წლის ივლისი). HONOR-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ გამოიწვევს თქვენი პერსონალური მონაცემების წაშლას, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. განახლების დროს პრობლემების წარმოქმნის შემთხვევაში, მხარდაჭერისთვის დარეკეთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან მიმართეთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл ұсынылған жаңарту кейбір сценарийлерде кескіндеу әсерін оңтайландырады, кейбір көріністерде қалыпсыз қуат тұтыну мәселесін шешеді, жүйе өнімділігін, тұрақтылығын және жылыту тәжірибесін жақсартады және қауіпсіздік патчын біріктіреді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту кейбір сценарийлерде телефотосурет түсірудің жарықтығы мен түс әсерін оңтайландырады.
Бұл жаңарту кейбір сценарийлерде портрет фокусын кескіндеу әсерін оңтайландырады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Өнімділік">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту кейбір қолданбаларды іске қосқан кезде кездейсоқ кешігу мәселесін шешеді.
Бұл жаңарту қолданбаны іске қосу қозғалысы әсеріндегі кадрдың кездейсоқ түсу мәселесін оңтайландырады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қуат тұтыну">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту кейбір көріністерде қалыпсыз қуат тұтыну мәселесін шешеді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Жылыту тәжірибесі">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту кейбір сценарийлерде жылыту тәжірибесін оңтайландырады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Жүйе">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту жүйенің тұрақтылығын жақсартып, құрылғыңыздың тұрақтырақ жұмыс істеуіне мүмкіндік береді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қауіпсіздік">
<feature>Android қауіпсіздік патчы (шілде, 2024) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. HONOR қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнатсаңыз, жеке деректер өшпейді, бірақ бұрынғы сақтық көшірме әлі де ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту барысында мәселелер орын алса, қолдау алу үшін HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне хабарласыңыз немесе HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына барыңыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពដែលបានណែនាំនេះធ្វើឱ្យបែបផែនរូបភាពប្រសើរឡើងនៅក្នុងសេណារីយោមួយចំនួន ដោះស្រាយបញ្ហានៃការប្រើប្រាស់​ថាមពលខុសប្រក្រតីក្នុងទិដ្ឋភាពមួយចំនួន កែលម្អប្រតិបត្តិការប្រព័ន្ធ ស្ថិរភាព និងបទពិសោធកម្ដៅ និងរួមបញ្ចូលបំណះសន្តិសុខ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កាមេរ៉ា">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យកម្រិតពន្លឺ និងបែបផែនពណ៌នៃការថតរូបពីចម្ងាយប្រសើរឡើងក្នុងសេណារីយោមួយចំនួន។
បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យបែបផែនរូបភាពផ្ដោតនៃរូបភាពពាក់កណ្តាលខ្លួនប្រសើរឡើងក្នុងសេណារីយោមួយចំនួន។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ប្រតិបត្តិការ">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះដោះស្រាយបញ្ហានៃការដើរស្ទួកៗដោយចៃដន្យ នៅពេលបើកដំណើរការកម្មវិធីមួយចំនួន។
បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យបញ្ហានៃការធ្លាក់ហ្វ្រេមដោយចៃដន្យក្នុងបែបផែនចលនាចាប់ផ្ដើមកម្មវិធីប្រសើរឡើង។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ការប្រើប្រាស់​ថាមពល">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះដោះស្រាយបញ្ហានៃការប្រើប្រាស់​ថាមពលខុសប្រក្រតីនៅក្នុងឆាកមួយចំនួន។</feature>
</features>
<features module="បទពិសោធកម្ដៅ">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យ​បទពិសោធកម្ដៅ​ប្រសើរឡើង​ក្នុង​សេណារីយោ​មួយចំនួន។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ប្រព័ន្ធ">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះកែលម្អស្ថិរភាពប្រព័ន្ធ ដើម្បីធ្វើឱ្យឧបករណ៍របស់អ្នកដំណើរការបានកាន់តែមានស្ថិរភាព។</feature>
</features>
<features module="សន្តិសុខ">
<feature>បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (មិថុនា 2024) ត្រូវបាន​រួមបញ្ចូល​សម្រាប់​សន្តិសុខ​ប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់​ព័ត៌មាន​បន្ថែម​អំពី​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​សន្តិសុខ HONOR សូមចូលទៅ​គេហទំព័រ​របស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​លុបទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ចេញទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបបញ្ហាណាមួយក្នុងអំឡុងពេល​ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព សូមហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សផ្នែកសេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​សេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR ដើម្បី​ទទួលបាន​ជំនួយ។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಿದ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಇಮೇಜಿಂಗ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ, ಕೆಲವು ದೃಶ್ಯಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಅಸಹಜ ಪವರ್ ಬಳಕೆಯ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಯನ್ನು ಪರಿಹರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಕಾರ್ಯಕ್ಷಮತೆ, ಸ್ಥಿರತೆ ಮತ್ತು ಬಿಸಿಯಾಗುವಿಕೆಯ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾ">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಟೆಲಿಫೋಟೋ ಶೂಟಿಂಗ್‌ನ ಹೊಳಪು ಮತ್ತು ಬಣ್ಣದ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.
ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಭಾವಚಿತ್ರ ಫೋಕಸ್ ಇಮೇಜಿಂಗ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಕಾರ್ಯಕ್ಷಮತೆ">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು, ಕೆಲವು ಆ್ಯಪ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಪ್ರಾರಂಭಿಸುವಾಗ ಕಂಡುಬರುವ ಯಾದೃಚ್ಛಿಕ ಮಂದಗತಿಯ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಯನ್ನು ಪರಿಹರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.
ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಸ್ಟಾರ್ಟ್‌ಅಪ್ ಮೋಷನ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಯಾದೃಚ್ಛಿಕ ಫ್ರೇಮ್ ಡ್ರಾಪ್‌ಗಳ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಯನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಪವರ್ ಬಳಕೆ">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಕೆಲವು ದೃಶ್ಯಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಅಸಹಜ ವಿದ್ಯುತ್ ಬಳಕೆಯ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಯನ್ನು ಪರಿಹರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಬಿಸಿಯಾಗುವಿಕೆ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆ">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಉಂಟಾಗುವ ಬಿಸಿಯಾಗುವಿಕೆ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಸಾಧನವನ್ನು ಹೆಚ್ಚು ಸ್ಥಿರವಾಗಿ ರನ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಸ್ಥಿರತೆಯನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಭದ್ರತೆ">
<feature>ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ಜುಲೈ 2024) ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. HONOR ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್‌ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸಿದರೆ ಇದು ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಅಳಿಸುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ಮುಂಚಿತವಾಗಿ ಬ್ಯಾಕ್‍ಅಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ ಇಡಬೇಕೆಂದು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ಅಥವಾ ಬೆಂಬಲಕ್ಕಾಗಿ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಹೋಗಿ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이 권장 업데이트는 일부 시나리오에서 이미징 효과를 최적화하고 일부 장면에서 비정상적인 소비 전력 문제를 수정하며 시스템 성능, 안정성 및 발열 경험을 개선하고 보안 패치를 통합합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="카메라">
<feature>이 업데이트는 일부 시나리오에서 망원 촬영의 밝기 및 색상 효과를 최적화합니다.
이 업데이트는 일부 시나리오에서 세로 보기 초점 이미징 효과를 최적화합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="성능">
<feature>이 업데이트는 일부 앱을 실행할 때 무작위로 지연되는 문제를 해결합니다.
이 업데이트는 앱 시작 모션 효과의 무작위 프레임 드롭 문제를 최적화합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="소비 전력">
<feature>이 업데이트는 일부 장면에서 비정상적인 소비 전력 문제를 해결합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="발열 경험">
<feature>이번 업데이트로 일부 시나리오에서 발열 경험이 최적화됩니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="시스템">
<feature>이 업데이트에서는 장치가 더 안정적으로 실행될 수 있도록 시스템 안정성이 개선됩니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="보안">
<feature>시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2024년 7월)가 통합되었습니다. HONOR 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 다음에 있는 당사 웹사이트를 방문하세요. https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터는 삭제되지 않지만, 사전에 백업하시기를 권장합니다.
2. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터로 가서 지원을 받으십시오.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ຮຽນ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ທີ່​ແນະ​ນຳນີ້ປັບ​ເອັບ​ເຝັກຮູບ​ພາບ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ພາບ​ການ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ, ແກ້​ໄຂ​ບັນ​ຫາ​ຂອງ​ການ​ໃຊ້​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານ​ຜິ​ດ​ປົກ​ກະ​ຕິ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ການ, ປັບ​ປຸງ​ປະ​ສິດ​ທິ​ພາບ​, ​ຄວາມ​ສະ​ຖຽນ ແລະ ປະ​ສົບ​ການ​ການ​ເຮັດຄວາມ​ຮ້ອນຂອງລະ​ບົບ ແລະ ລວມເອົາ​ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ເຂົ້າ​ກັນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ກ້ອງຖ່າຍຮູບ">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ປັບ​ຄວາມແຈ້ງ ແລະ ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ສີ​ຂອງການ​ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບ​​ໄລ​ຍະ​ໄກ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ພາບ​ການ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ.
ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້ປັບເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ຮູບ​ພາບໂຟ​ກັ​ສ​ຮູບ​ເຄິ່ງ​​ຕົວໃນບາງສະພາບການ​ໃຫ້ເໝາະສົມ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ປະ​ສິດ​ທິ​ພາບ">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ບັນ​ຫາຄວາມ​​ຊັກ​ຊ້າ​ແບບ​ສຸ່ມ ເມື່ອ​ເປີດ​ໃ​ຊ້​ບາງ​ແອັບ.
ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ປັບບັນ​ຫາ​ຂອງ​ເຟ​ຣມ​ສຸ່ມ​ຕົກ​ໃນ​ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ການ​ເຄື່ອນ​ໄຫວ​ເມື່ອ​ເລີ່ມ​ຕົ້ນ​ແອັບ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="​ການ​ໃຊ້​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານ">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ບັນ​ຫາ​​ການ​ໃຊ້​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານ​​ຜິດ​ປົກ​ກະ​ຕິ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ການ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ປະ​ສົບ​ການ​ເຮັດ​ຄວາມ​ຮ້ອນ">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້ປັບປະ​ສົບການເຮັດ​ຄວາມ​ຮ້ອນໃນບາງສະພາບການໃຫ້ເໝາະສົມ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ລະບົບ">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້ປັບປຸງຄວາມສະຖຽນຂອງລະບົບ ເພື່ອເຮັດໃຫ້ອຸປະກອນຂອງທ່ານເຮັດວຽກໄດ້ສະຖຽນຍິ່ງຂຶ້ນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
<feature>ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ກໍ​ລະ​ກົດ 2024) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ HONOR, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການຕິດຕັ້ງການອັບເດດນີ້ຈະບໍ່ລຶບຂໍ້ມູນສ່ວນຕົວຂອງທ່ານ, ແຕ່ຂໍແນະນຳໃຫ້ທ່ານສຳຮອງຂໍ້ມູນໄວ້ລ່ວງໜ້າ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ກະລຸນາໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR ເພື່ອຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šiuo rekomenduojamu naujiniu kai kuriuose scenarijuose optimizuojamas vaizdavimo efektas, kai kuriose scenose išsprendžiama neįprastų energijos sąnaudų problema, pagerinamas sistemos našumas, stabilumas ir kaitimo patirtis, taip pat įtraukiama saugumo pataisa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Šiuo naujiniu kai kuriuose scenarijuose optimizuojamas šviesumas ir spalvų efektas fotografuojant teleobjektyvu.
Šiuo naujiniu kai kuriuose scenarijuose optimizuojamas portreto fokusavimo vaizdo efektas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Našumas">
<feature>Šiuo naujiniu išsprendžiama atsitiktinio vėlavimo paleidžiant kai kurias programėles problema.
Šiuo naujiniu optimizuojama atsitiktinių kadrų dingimo problema, susijusi su programėlės paleidimo judesio efektu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energijos sąnaudos">
<feature>Šiuo naujiniu kai kuriose scenose išsprendžiama neįprastų energijos sąnaudų problema.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kaitimo patirtis">
<feature>Šiuo naujiniu kai kuriuose scenarijuose optimizuojama kaitimo patirtis.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Šiuo naujiniu pagerinamas sistemos stabilumas, kad įrenginys veiktų stabiliau.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Saugumas">
<feature>Siekiant užtikrinti sistemos saugumą, įtraukta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2024 m. liepos mėn.). Jei reikia daugiau informacijos apie HONOR saugumo naujinius, apsilankykite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos:" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį atnaujinimą, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys ištrinti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama iš anksto padaryti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Jei atnaujinimo metu kyla problemų, skambinkite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba kreipkitės pagalbos į HONOR priežiūros centrą.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo ieteicamo atjauninājumu tiek optimizēts attēlveidošanas efektu dažos scenārijos, novērsts neparasts enerģijas patēriņš dažās ainās, uzlabota sistēmas veiktspēja, stabilitāte un sildīšanas pieredze, kā arī ietverts drošības ielāps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Ar šo atjauninājumu dažos gadījumos tiek optimizēts telefoto uzņemšanas spilgtums un krāsu efekts.
Ar šo atjauninājumu dažos gadījumos tiek optimizēts portreta fokusa attēlveidošanas efekts.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Veiktspēja">
<feature>Šis atjauninājums novērš nejaušas kavēšanās problēmu, palaižot dažas lietotnes.
Ar šo atjauninājumu tiek optimizēta nejaušu kadru kritumu problēma lietotnes startēšanas kustības efektā.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Enerģijas patēriņš">
<feature>Šis atjauninājums novērš neparastu enerģijas patēriņa problēmu dažos scenārijos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sildīšanas pieredze">
<feature>Ar šo atjauninājumu ir optimizēta sildīšanas pieredze dažiem scenārijiem.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistēma">
<feature>Ar šo atjauninājumu ir uzlabota sistēmas stabilitāte, padarot jūsu ierīci stabilāku.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Drošība">
<feature>Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2024. gada jūlijs). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par HONOR drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Instalējot šo atjauninājumu, jūsu personas dati netiks dzēsti, taču joprojām ir ieteicams iepriekš izveidot dublējumu.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, lūdzu, zvaniet HONOR uzziņu dienestam vai dodieties uz HONOR klientu servisa centru, lai saņemtu atbalstu.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अनुशंसित अपडेट किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे इमेजिंग प्रभाव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि, किछु दृश्य सभ मे असामान्य बिजलीक खपत केर समस्याक समाधान करैत अछि, सिस्टमक कार्य-क्षमता, स्थिरता आ गरम होयबाक अनुभव मे सुधार करैत अछि आओर सुरक्षा पैच समाविष्ट करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कैमरा">
<feature>ई अपडेट किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे टेलीफोटो शूटिंग केर चमक आ रंग प्रभाव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि।
ई अपडेट किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे पोर्ट्रेट फोकस इमेजिंग प्रभाव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कार्य-प्रदर्शन">
<feature>ई अपडेट किछु एप सभ आरंभ करैत काल रैंडम लैग केर समस्याक समाधान करैत अछि।
ई अपडेट एप शुरू करैत काल केर मोशन प्रभाव मे रैंडम फ्रेम ड्रॉप केर समस्या केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="बिजलीक खपत">
<feature>ई अपडेट किछु दृश्य सभ मे असामान्य बिजलीक खपत केर समस्याक समाधान करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गरम होयबाक अनुभव">
<feature>किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे ई अपडेट गरम होयबाक अनुभव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>ई अपडेट सिस्टमक स्थिरता मे सुधार कयलक अछि, जाहि सँ अहाँक डिवाइस बेसी स्थिर रूप सँ चलि सकए।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (जुलाई 2024) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहि मेटायत मुदा पहिने सँ एकटा बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' सहायताक लेल कृपाकए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन केँ कॉल करू वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाउ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E te kaiwhakamahi, mā tēnei whakahōutanga e manako ana e arotau te pānga atahanga i ētahi tauari, ka whakatika i te take o te whakapetonga hiko rerekē i ētahi tirohanga, ka whakapai ake i te mahinga pūnaha, te mauritanga me te wheako whakamātao, me te whakauru i tētahi āpure haumarutanga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kāmera">
<feature>Ka arotautia e tēnei whakahōu te tīahonga me te pānga tae o te tākaro arotahiroa i ētahi tauari.
Ka arotautia e tēnei whakahōu te rākeitanga atahanga pānga arotahi poutū i ētahi tauari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mahinga">
<feature>Ka whakatika tēnei whakahōu i te raruraru o te takamuri matapōkere ina whakarewatanga i ētahi taupānga.
Ka arotau e tēnei whakahōu te raruraru o te tāpare matapōkere e taka ana i roto i te rākeitanga pānga whakaoho taupānga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Whakapetonga hiko">
<feature>Mā tēnei whakahōu e whakatika te take o te whakapetonga hiko rerekē i ētahi tirohanga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Te whakawera wheako">
<feature>Ka arotau e tēnei whakahōu te wheako whakawera i ētahi tauari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pūnaha">
<feature>Mā tēnei whakahōu ka whakapai ake i te taimautanga pūnaha kia pai ake ai te haere o tō pūrere.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Haumarutanga">
<feature>Kua whakaurua te Āpure Haumarutanga Android (Hōngongoi 2024) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga HONOR, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore te tāuta i tēnei whakahōu e ūkui i ō raraunga whaiaro, engari e manakohia tonutia ana tētahi pūrua i mua.
2. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōutanga, waea atu koa ki te waewera ratonga HONOR, ka haere rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki HONOR hei tautoko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова препорачано ажурирање го оптимизира ефектот на сликање во некои сценарија, го исправа проблемот на абнормална потрошувачка на енергија во некои сцени, ги подобрува перформансите на системот, стабилноста и искуството со греењето и вградува безбедносна крпеница.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Ова ажурирање го оптимизира ефектот на осветленоста и боите при телефотографско сликање во некои сценарија.
Ова ажурирање го оптимизира ефектот на сликање со фокус за портрет во некои сценарија.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Перформанси">
<feature>Ова ажурирање го исправа проблемот на случајно одложување кога се вклучуваат некои апликации.
Ова ажурирање го оптимизира проблемот со случајни опаѓања во кадрите на ефектот на движење при стартување на апликациите.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Потрошувачка на енергија">
<feature>Ова ажурирање го поправа проблемот на абнормална потрошувачка на енергија во некои сцени.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Искуство со греењето">
<feature>Ова ажурирање го оптимизира искуството со греењето во некои сценарија.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>Ова ажурирање ја подобрува стабилноста на системот за уредот да работи постабилно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безбедност">
<feature>Вградена е безбедносна крпеница за Android (јули 2024) за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за ажурирања на безбедноста од HONOR, посетете ја нашата веб-локација https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да ги избрише вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува однапред да направите резервна копија.
2. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, повикајте го телефонскиот број на службата на HONOR или одете во центарот за услуги за корисници на HONOR за да добиете поддршка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്ന അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ ഇമേജിംഗ് ഇഫക്റ്റ് ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുകയും ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ അസ്വാഭാവിക വൈദ്യുതി ഉപഭോഗത്തിന്റെ പ്രശ്‌നം പരിഹരിക്കുകയും സിസ്റ്റം പ്രകടനവും സ്ഥിരതയും താപനില ഉയരൽ അനുഭവവും മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ഒരു സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ക്യാമറ">
<feature>ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ ടെലിഫോട്ടോ ഷൂട്ടിംഗിന്റെ പ്രകാശവും വർണ്ണ ഇഫക്റ്റും ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു.
ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ പോർട്രെയ്‌റ്റ് ഫോക്കസ് ഇമേജിംഗ് ഇഫക്റ്റ് ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="പ്രകടനം">
<feature>ചില ആപ്പുകൾ സമാരംഭിക്കുമ്പോഴുള്ള റാൻഡം ലാഗ് ചെയ്യലിന്റെ പ്രശ്‌നം ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പരിഹരിക്കുന്നു.
ആപ്പ് ആരംഭിക്കുമ്പോൾ ചലന ഇഫക്റ്റിൽ ഉണ്ടാകുന്ന റാൻഡം ഫ്രെയിം ഡ്രോപ്പുകളുടെ പ്രശ്‌നം ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പരിഹരിക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="വൈദ്യുതി ഉപഭോഗം">
<feature>ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ അസ്വാഭാവിക വൈദ്യുതി ഉപഭോഗത്തിന്റെ പ്രശ്‌നം ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പരിഹരിക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="താപനില ഉയരൽ അനുഭവം">
<feature>ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ താപനില ഉയരൽ അനുഭവം ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സിസ്റ്റം">
<feature>നിങ്ങളുടെ ഉപകരണം കൂടുതൽ സ്ഥിരതയോടെ പ്രവർത്തിക്കാൻ ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് സിസ്റ്റം സ്ഥിരത മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സുരക്ഷ">
<feature>സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (ജൂലൈ 2024) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. HONOR സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ ഔദ്യോഗിക വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് ആയ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7 സന്ദർശിക്കുക</feature>
</features>
<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ മായ്‌ക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും മുൻകൂട്ടി ഒരു ബാക്കപ്പ് എടുത്തുവയ്‌ക്കാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കായി HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү санал болгож буй шинэчлэлтээр зарим тохиолдол дахь дүрсний эффектийг оновчилж, зарим тохиолдол дахь хэвийн бус эрчим хүчний хэрэглээний асуудлыг засаж, системийн гүйцэтгэл, тогтвортой байдал, халдаг байдлыг сайжруулж, хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг багтаав.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камер">
<feature>Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр зарим тохиолдол дахь телефото зураг авалтын тодролт, өнгөний эффектийг оновчилсон.
Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр зарим тохиолдол дахь хөрөг зургийн фокустай дүрслэлийн эффектийг оновчилсон.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Гүйцэтгэл">
<feature>Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр зарим апликэйшнийг эхлүүлэх үед санамсаргүй хоцрох асуудлыг зассан.
Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр апликэйшн эхлүүлэх хөдөлгөөний нөлөөнд санамсаргүй фрэйм унах асуудлыг оновчилсон.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Эрчим хүчний хэрэглээ">
<feature>Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр зарим тохиолдол дахь хэвийн бус эрчим хүчний хэрэглээний асуудлыг зассан.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Халдаг байдал">
<feature>Энэ шинэчлэлтээр зарим тохиолдолд халдаг байдлыг оновчилсон.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр таны төхөөрөмжийг илүү тогтвортой ажиллуулахын тулд системийн тогтвортой байдлыг нэмэгдүүлэв.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хамгаалалт">
<feature>Системийн хамгаалалтад зориулж Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2024 оны долдугаар сар) багтаав. HONOR-н хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэл авах бол манай дараах вебсайтад зочилно уу: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгахад таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч урьдчилан нөөцлөхийг зөвлөж байна.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад аливаа асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төвд зочилж тусламж авна уу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे शिफारस केलेले अद्यतन काही परिस्थितींमध्ये प्रतिमांचा प्रभाव ऑप्टिमाइझ करते, काही दृश्यांमध्ये असामान्य पॉवर वापराच्या समस्येचे निराकरण करते, सिस्टम कार्यप्रदर्शन, स्थिरता आणि गरम होण्याचा अनुभव सुधारते आणि सुरक्षितता पॅच समाविष्ट करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="कॅमेरा">
<feature>हे अद्यतन काही परिस्थितींमध्ये टेलीफोटो शूटिंगचा ब्राइटनेस आणि कलर प्रभाव ऑप्टिमाइझ करते.
हे अद्यतन काही परिस्थितींमध्ये पोर्ट्रेट फोकस प्रतिमांचा प्रभाव ऑप्टिमाइझ करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="कार्यप्रदर्शन">
<feature>हे अद्यतन काही ॲप्स लाँच करताना रँडम लॅगिंगच्या समस्येचे निराकरण करते.
हे अद्यतन ॲप स्टार्टअप मोशन इफेक्टमध्ये यादृच्छिक फ्रेम ड्रॉपची समस्या ऑप्टिमाइझ करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="पॉवर वापर">
<feature>हे अद्यतन काही दृश्यांमध्ये असामान्य पॉवर वापराच्या समस्येचे निराकरण करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="गरम होण्याचा अनुभव">
<feature>हे अद्यतन काही परिस्थितींमध्ये गरम होण्याचा अनुभव ऑप्टिमाइझ करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>हे अद्यतन आपले उपकरण अधिक स्थिरपणे चालण्‍यासाठी सिस्‍टम स्‍थिरता सुधारते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षितता">
<feature>सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षितता पॅच (जुलै 2024) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. HONOR सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7 वर जा</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्थापित केल्याने आपला वैयक्तिक डेटा मिटणार नाही, परंतु आधीच बॅकअप घेण्याची अजूनही शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करा किंवा समर्थनासाठी HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जा.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini yang disyorkan ini mengoptimumkan kesan pengimejan dalam beberapa senario, membetulkan isu penggunaan kuasa yang tidak normal dalam beberapa latar, meningkatkan prestasi sistem, kestabilan dan pengalaman pemanasan serta memasukkan tampalan keselamatan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Kemas kini ini mengoptimumkan kecerahan dan kesan warna penangkapan telefoto dalam beberapa senario.
Kemas kini ini mengoptimumkan kesan pengimejan fokus potret dalam beberapa senario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prestasi">
<feature>Kemas kini ini membetulkan masalah bebatan rawak semasa melancarkan beberapa aplikasi.
Kemas kini ini mengoptimumkan masalah kejatuhan bingkai rawak dalam kesan gerakan permulaan aplikasi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Penggunaan kuasa">
<feature>Kemas kini ini membetulkan isu penggunaan kuasa yang tidak normal dalam beberapa latar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pengalaman pemanasan">
<feature>Kemas kini ini mengoptimumkan pengalaman pemanasan dalam beberapa senario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Kemas kini ini meningkatkan kestabilan sistem untuk membolehkan peranti anda berjalan dengan lebih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keselamatan">
<feature>Tampalan Keselamatan Android (Jul 2024) telah dimasukkan untuk keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan HONOR, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Pemasangan kemas kini ini tidak akan memadamkan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda disyorkan agar masih membuat sandaran terlebih dahulu.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, sila hubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau pergi ke pusat khidmat pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan sokongan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ အကြံပြုထားသော ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အချို့အခြေအနေများတွင် ရုပ်ပုံ အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်၊ အချို့ဖြစ်ရပ်များတွင် ပါဝါ သုံးစွဲမှု မူမမှန်သည့် ပြဿနာကို ဖြေရှင်းပေးပြီး စနစ် စွမ်းဆောင်ရည်၊ တည်ငြိမ်မှုနှင့် သုံးစွဲစဉ် အပူထွက်ခြင်းအတွက် တိုးတက်ကောင်းမွန်လာအောင် မွမ်းမံပေးကာ လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ကင်မရာ">
<feature>ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အချို့အခြေအနေများတွင် အဝေးရိုက်ကူးခြင်း၌ တောက်ပမှုနှင့် အရောင် အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။
ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အချို့အခြေအနေများတွင် အလှပုံအသားပေး ရုပ်ပုံ အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စွမ်းဆောင်ရည်">
<feature>ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အချို့အက်ပ်များကို ဖွင့်သည့်အခါ ရံဖန်ရံခါ ထစ်သည့်ပြဿနာကို ဖြေရှင်းပေးသည်။
ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အက်ပ်စတင်ချိန် လှုပ်ရှားမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်တွင် ရံဖန်ရံခါ ချိတ်ဆက်မှုမတည်ငြိမ်သည့် ပြဿနာကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပါဝါ သုံးစွဲမှု">
<feature>ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အချို့ဖြစ်ရပ်များတွင် ပါဝါ သုံးစွဲမှု မူမမှန်သည့် ပြဿနာကို ဖြေရှင်းပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="သုံးစွဲစဉ် အပူထွက်ခြင်း">
<feature>ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အချို့အခြေအနေများ၌ သုံးစွဲစဉ် အပူထွက်ခြင်းအတွက် အကောင်းဆုံးဖြစ်စေရန် ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ်">
<feature>သင့်စက်ကို ပိုမိုတည်ငြိမ်စွာ လုပ်ဆောင်နိုင်စေရန် ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် စနစ် တည်ငြိမ်မှုကို တိုးမြှင့်ပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံခြုံရေး">
<feature>စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (ဇူလိုင် 2024) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ HONOR လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို သိရှိရန် ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ်သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းသည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာကို ဖျက်မည် မဟုတ်သော်လည်း ကြိုတင်၍ ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်နေစဉ် ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခု ကြုံတွေ့ပါက အကူအညီရယူရန် HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆိုပါ သို့မဟုတ် HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ အႀကံျပဳထားေသာ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ားတြင္ ႐ုပ္ပုံ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္၊ အခ်ိဳ႕ျဖစ္ရပ္မ်ားတြင္ ပါဝါ သုံးစြဲမႈ မူမမွန္သည့္ ျပႆနာကို ေျဖရွင္းေပးၿပီး စနစ္ စြမ္းေဆာင္ရည္၊ တည္ၿငိမ္မႈႏွင့္ သုံးစြဲစဥ္ အပူထြက္ျခင္းအတြက္ တိုးတက္ေကာင္းမြန္လာေအာင္ မြမ္းမံေပးကာ လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ကင္မရာ">
<feature>ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ားတြင္ အေဝး႐ိုက္ကူးျခင္း၌ ေတာက္ပမႈႏွင့္ အေရာင္ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။
ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ားတြင္ အလွပုံအသားေပး ႐ုပ္ပုံ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စြမ္းေဆာင္ရည္">
<feature>ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အခ်ိဳ႕အက္ပ္မ်ားကို ဖြင့္သည့္အခါ ရံဖန္ရံခါ ထစ္သည့္ျပႆနာကို ေျဖရွင္းေပးသည္။
ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အက္ပ္စတင္ခ်ိန္ လႈပ္ရွားမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္တြင္ ရံဖန္ရံခါ ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈမတည္ၿငိမ္သည့္ ျပႆနာကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပါဝါ သုံးစြဲမႈ">
<feature>ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အခ်ိဳ႕ျဖစ္ရပ္မ်ားတြင္ ပါဝါ သုံးစြဲမႈ မူမမွန္သည့္ ျပႆနာကို ေျဖရွင္းေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="သုံးစြဲစဥ္ အပူထြက္ျခင္း">
<feature>ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ား၌ သုံးစြဲစဥ္ အပူထြက္ျခင္းအတြက္ အေကာင္းဆုံးျဖစ္ေစရန္ ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ္">
<feature>သင့္စက္ကို ပိုမိုတည္ၿငိမ္စြာ လုပ္ေဆာင္ႏိုင္ေစရန္ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ စနစ္ တည္ၿငိမ္မႈကို တိုးျမႇင့္ေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံျခံဳေရး">
<feature>စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ဇူလိုင္ 2024) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ HONOR လုံၿခဳံေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို သိရွိရန္ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းသည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာကို ဖ်က္မည္ မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း ႀကိဳတင္၍ ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ေနစဥ္ ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခု ႀကဳံေတြ႕ပါက အကူအညီရယူရန္ HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆိုပါ သို႔မဟုတ္ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, denne anbefalte oppdateringen optimerer bildeeffekten i enkelte scenarier, reparerer problemet med unormal batteribruk i enkelte scener, forbedrer systemytelsen, stabiliteten og opplevelsen av oppvarming, og innlemmer en sikkerhetsoppdatering.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen optimerer lysstyrken og fargeeffektene i telefotofotografering i enkelte scenarier.
Denne oppdateringen optimerer portrettfokusbildeeffekten i enkelte scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ytelse">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen reparerer problemet med tilfeldige forsinkelser når enkelte apper startes opp.
Denne oppdateringen optimerer problemet med tilfeldig reduksjon i bildehastighet i bevegelseseffekten for appoppstart.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Batteribruk">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen reparerer problemet med unormal batteribruk i enkelte scener.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opplevelse med oppvarming">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen optimerer opplevelsen med oppvarming i enkelte scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen forbedrer systemstabiliteten slik at enheten kjører jevnere.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhet">
<feature>Android-sikkerhetsoppdatering (juli 2024) er innlemmet for systemsikkerheten. For mer informasjon om sikkerhetsoppdateringer fra HONOR, besøk nettstedet vårt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notater:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke slette personopplysningene dine, men det anbefales likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer på forhånd.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, ring HONOR-kundeservice eller gå til HONOR-kundeservicesenteret for assistanse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, सिफारिस गरिएको यो अपडेटले केही परिदृश्यहरूमा फोटोको प्रभाव अप्टिमाइज गर्छ, र केही परिदृश्यमा असामान्य पावर खपतको समस्या समाधान गर्छ, प्रणालीको कार्यसम्पादन, स्थिरता र तात्ने अनुभव सुधार गर्छ र सुरक्षा प्याच समावेश गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="क्यामेरा">
<feature>यो अपडेटले केही परिदृश्यमा टेलिफोटो सुटिङको चम्किलोपन र रङको प्रभाव अप्टिमाइज गर्छ ।
यो अपडेटले केही परिदृश्यहरूमा पोर्ट्रेट फोकस इमेजिङ प्रभाव अप्टिमाइज गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कार्यसम्पादन">
<feature>यो अपडेटले केही एपहरू लन्च गर्दा अनियमित रूपमा ह्याङ हुने समस्या समाधान गर्छ ।
यो एपले एप सुरु गर्दा देखाइने मोसन प्रभावमा अनियमित रूपमा फ्रेम ड्रप हुने समस्या अप्टिमाइज गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="पावर खपत">
<feature>यो अपडेटले केही दृश्यमा असामान्य पावर खपतको समस्या समाधान गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="तात्ने अनुभव">
<feature>यो अपडेटले केही परिदृश्यहरूमा तात्ने अनुभव अप्टिमाइज गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्रणाली">
<feature>यो अपडेटले तपाईंको यन्त्रलाई थप स्थिर रूपमा चल्ने बनाउन प्रणालीको स्थिरतामा सुधार गरेको छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (जुलाई 2024) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेटबारे थप जानकारीका लागि, कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस्: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. यो अपडेट स्थापना गर्नाले तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटा मेटिने छैन, तर अझै पनि पहिले नै ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. अपडेटको समयमा तपाईंले कुनै पनि समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने, कृपया HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गर्नुहोस् वा सहायताका लागि HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा जानुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruiker, deze aanbevolen update optimaliseert het beeldeffect in bepaalde scenario's, lost het probleem van abnormaal energieverbruik in bepaalde scènes op, verbetert de prestaties, stabiliteit en opwarmingservaring van het systeem en bevat een beveiligingspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Deze update optimaliseert in bepaalde scenario's de helderheid en het kleureffect van telefoto-opnamen.
Deze update optimaliseert het portretscherpstelbeeldeffect in bepaalde scenario's.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prestaties">
<feature>Deze update lost het probleem van willekeurige vertraging bij het starten van bepaalde apps op.
Deze update optimaliseert het probleem van willekeurige frameverminderingen in het bewegingseffect bij het opstarten van apps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energieverbruik">
<feature>Deze update lost het probleem van abnormaal energieverbruik in bepaalde scènes op.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opwarmingservaring">
<feature>Deze update optimaliseert de opwarmingservaring in bepaalde scenario's.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systeem">
<feature>Deze update verbetert de systeemstabiliteit om uw apparaat stabieler te laten werken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Beveiliging">
<feature>Android-beveiligingspatch (juli 2024) is opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over HONOR-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Als u deze update installeert, worden uw persoonlijke gegevens niet gewist, maar een back-up vooraf wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, bel dan de HONOR-servicehotline of ga naar een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum voor ondersteuning.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଥିବା ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କିଛି ପରିଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ପ୍ରତିଛବିରେ ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ, କିଛି ଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ଅସାମାନ୍ୟ ପାୱାର୍ ଖର୍ଚ୍ଚକୁ ସୁଧାର କରେ, ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ କାର୍ଯ୍ୟଦକ୍ଷତା, ସ୍ଥିରତା ଏବଂ ଗରମ ହେବା ଅନୁଭୂତିକୁ ବିକାଶ କରେ, ଏବଂ ଏକ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="କ୍ୟାମେରା">
<feature>ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କିଛି ପରିଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ଟେଲିଫଟୋ ଶୁଟିଂର ଔଜ୍ଜଲ୍ୟତା ଏବଂ ରଙ୍ଗ ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ।
ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କିଛି ପରିଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ପୋର୍ଟ୍ରେଟ୍‌ ଫୋକସ୍‌ ପ୍ରତିଛବିରେ ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="କାର୍ଯ୍ୟଦକ୍ଷତା">
<feature>କିଛି ଆପ୍‌ ଲଞ୍ଚ କରିବା ବେଳେ ରେଣ୍ଡମ ଲ୍ୟାଗ୍‌ କରିବା ସମସ୍ୟାକୁ ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସୁଧାର କରେ।
ଆପ୍‌ ଷ୍ଟାର୍ଟଅପ୍‌ ମୋସନ୍ ପ୍ରଭାବରେ ଫ୍ରେମ୍ ରେଣ୍ଡମ ଭାବେ ହ୍ରାସ ହେବା ସମସ୍ୟାକୁ ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ପାୱାର୍ ଖର୍ଚ୍ଚ">
<feature>କେତେକ ନିର୍ଦ୍ଦିଷ୍ଟ ଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ଅସାମାନ୍ୟ ପାୱାର୍‌ ଖର୍ଚ୍ଚ ସମସ୍ୟାକୁ ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସୁଧାର କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଗରମ ହେବା ଅନୁଭୂତି">
<feature>ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କେତେକ ପରିଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ଗରମ ହେବା ଅନୁଭୂତିକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌">
<feature>ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡିଭାଇସ୍‌ ଅଧିକ ସ୍ଥିର ଭାବେ ଚଲାଇବାକୁ, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ ସ୍ଥିରତାକୁ ବିକାଶ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା">
<feature>Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ଜୁଲାଇ 2024) ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। HONOR ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ଲିଭାଇବ ନାହିଁ, କିନ୍ତୁ ଏହା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଏକ ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଦୟାକରି HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ସହାୟତା ପାଇଁ ଏକ HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੇ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਇਮੇਜਿੰਗ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਅਸਧਾਰਨ ਪਾਵਰ ਖਪਤ ਦੀ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਨੂੰ ਠੀਕ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਕਾਰਗੁਜ਼ਾਰੀ, ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਅਤੇ ਹੀਟਿੰਗ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਕੈਮਰਾ">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਟੈਲੀਫ਼ੇਟੋ ਸ਼ੂਟਿੰਗ ਦੀ ਚਮਕ ਅਤੇ ਰੰਗ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।
ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਪੋਰਟ੍ਰੇਟ ਫੋਕਸ ਇਮੇਜਿੰਗ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਕਾਰਗੁਜ਼ਾਰੀ">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੁਝ ਐਪਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਲਾਂਚ ਕਰਦੇ ਸਮੇਂ ਬੇਤਰਤੀਬੀ ਲੈਗਿੰਗ ਦੀ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਨੂੰ ਠੀਕ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।
ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਐਪ ਸਟਾਰਟਅੱਪ ਮੋਸ਼ਨ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਵਿੱਚ ਬੇਤਰਤੀਬੇ ਫ੍ਰੇਮ ਡ੍ਰੌਪਾਂ ਦੀ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਪਾਵਰ ਖਪਤ">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਅਸਧਾਰਨ ਪਾਵਰ ਖਪਤ ਸੰਬੰਧੀ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਨੂੰ ਠੀਕ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਹੀਟਿੰਗ ਅਨੁਭਵ">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਹੀਟਿੰਗ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸਿਸਟਮ">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਡਿਵਾਈਸ ਜ਼ਿਆਦਾ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਨਾਲ ਕੰਮ ਕਰੇਗਾ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ">
<feature>ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਜੁਲਾਈ 2024) ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। HONOR ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਲਈ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਮਿਟਾਇਆ ਨਹੀਂ ਜਾਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਹਾਇਤਾ ਲਈ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta zalecana aktualizacja optymalizuje efekty robienia zdjęć i rozwiązuje problem z nieprawidłowym zużyciem energii w niektórych sytuacjach, poprawia wydajność i stabilność systemu oraz zmniejsza nagrzewanie się i zawiera poprawkę zabezpieczeń.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aparat">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja optymalizuje jasność i efekt kolorystyczny podczas fotografowania z teleobiektywem w niektórych sytuacjach.
Ta aktualizacja optymalizuje efekt fotografowania z ostrością portretową w niektórych sytuacjach.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Wydajność">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja rozwiązuje problem losowych opóźnień podczas uruchamiania niektórych aplikacji.
Ta aktualizacja optymalizuje problem przypadkowych spadków liczby klatek na sekundę w efekcie ruchu podczas uruchamiania aplikacji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zużycie energii">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja rozwiązuje problem nieprawidłowego zużycia energii w niektórych sytuacjach.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nagrzewanie się">
<feature>W tej aktualizacji zoptymalizowano nagrzewanie się urządzenia w pewnych sytuacjach.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>W tej aktualizacji poprawiono stabilność systemu, dzięki czemu urządzenie działa bardziej niezawodnie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpieczenia">
<feature>Aktualizacja zawiera Poprawkę zabezpieczeń systemu Android (lipiec 2024 r.). Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń urządzeń HONOR można znaleźć w naszej witrynie internetowej: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie powoduje wymazania danych użytkownika, jednak zalecamy uprzednie wykonanie kopii zapasowej.
2. Jeśli podczas procesu aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, zadzwoń na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR, gdzie uzyskasz pomoc.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro(a) usuário(a), esta atualização recomendada otimiza o efeito de imagem em alguns cenários, corrige o problema de consumo anormal de energia em algumas cenas, melhora o desempenho do sistema, a estabilidade e a experiência de aquecimento, além de incorporar um patch de segurança.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Câmera">
<feature>Esta atualização otimiza o brilho e o efeito de cor da captura de teleobjetiva em alguns cenários.
Esta atualização otimiza o efeito de imagem de foco de retrato em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Desempenho">
<feature>Esta atualização corrige o problema de atraso aleatório ao iniciar alguns aplicativos.
Esta atualização otimiza o problema de quedas aleatórias de quadros no efeito de movimento de inicialização do aplicativo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de energia">
<feature>Esta atualização corrige o problema de consumo anormal de energia em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Experiência de aquecimento">
<feature>Esta atualização otimiza a experiência de aquecimento em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Esta atualização melhora a estabilidade do sistema, tornando seu dispositivo mais estável.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Patch de segurança do Android (julho de 2024) incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite nosso site: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não apagará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, ligue para a linha de atendimento ao cliente da HONOR ou vá à central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização recomendada otimiza o efeito da imagem em alguns cenários, corrige o problema do consumo anormal de energia em algumas cenas, melhora o desempenho do sistema, a estabilidade e a experiência de aquecimento e incorpora uma correção de segurança.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Câmara">
<feature>Esta atualização otimiza a luminosidade e o efeito de cor do disparo com teleobjetiva em alguns cenários.
Esta atualização otimiza o efeito da formação de imagem com focagem de retrato em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Desempenho">
<feature>Esta atualização corrige o problema de atrasos aleatórios no iniciar de algumas aplicações.
Esta atualização otimiza o problema das quedas aleatórias de fotogramas no efeito de movimento de arranque da aplicação.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de energia">
<feature>Esta atualização corrige o problema do consumo anormal de energia em algumas cenas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Experiência de aquecimento">
<feature>Esta atualização otimiza a experiência de aquecimento em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Esta atualização melhora a estabilidade do sistema para fazer com que o seu dispositivo funcione de forma mais estável.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Foi incorporada uma Correção de Segurança Android (julho de 2024) para segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não irá eliminar os seus dados pessoais, mas recomenda-se a realização de uma cópia de segurança prévia.
2. Se tiver problemas durante a atualização, ligue para a linha direta de assistência da HONOR ou dirija-se ao centro de apoio ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare recomandată optimizează efectul de imagine în anumite scenarii, rezolvă problema consumului anormal de energie în anumite secvențe, îmbunătățește performanța, stabilitatea și experiența privind încălzirea sistemului și încorporează o corecție de securitate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cameră foto">
<feature>Această actualizare optimizează luminozitatea și efectul de culoare al fotografierii telefoto în anumite scenarii.
Această actualizare optimizează efectul de imagine pentru focalizarea portretului în anumite scenarii.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performanță">
<feature>Această actualizare remediază problema întârzierilor aleatorii la lansarea unor aplicații.
Această actualizare optimizează problema scăderilor aleatorii de cadre în efectul de mișcare la pornirea aplicațiilor.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consum de energie">
<feature>Această actualizare remediază problema consulului anormal de energie în anumite secvențe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Experiența privind încălzirea">
<feature>Această actualizare optimizează experiența privind încălzirea în anumite scenarii.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Această actualizare îmbunătățește stabilitatea sistemului, făcând ca dispozitivul dvs. să ruleze mai stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Securitate">
<feature>Corecția de securitate Android (iulie 2024) a fost inclusă pentru securitatea sistemului. Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de securitate HONOR, vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu vă va șterge datele cu caracter personal, însă se recomandă totuși să faceți înainte o copie de rezervă a acestora.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, pentru suport apelați numărul de asistență HONOR sau mergeți la centrul de service pentru clienții HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы разработали это рекомендованное обновление, чтобы оптимизировать эффект отображения в некоторых сценариях, устранить проблему некорректного энергопотребления в некоторых сценариях, улучшить производительность, стабильность и нагрев системы, а также внедрить исправление безопасности.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Это обновление оптимизирует яркость и цветовой эффект телеобъектива в некоторых сценариях.
Это обновление оптимизирует эффект портретной фокусировки в некоторых сценариях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Производительность">
<feature>Это обновление устраняет проблему случайного зависания при запуске некоторых приложений.
Это обновление оптимизирует проблему случайной потери кадров эффекта движения при запуске приложения.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Энергопотребление">
<feature>В этом обновлении устранена проблема, связанная с некорректным энергопотреблением в некоторых сценариях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Нагрев">
<feature>В этом обновлении был оптимизирован процесс нагрева в некоторых сценариях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>Это обновление улучшает стабильность системы и, соответственно, работу вашего устройства.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безопасность">
<feature>В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (июль 2024 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности HONOR, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/ru/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не приведет к удалению ваших персональных данных, но мы рекомендуем сделать резервную копию всех важных данных, прежде чем приступить к установке.
2. При возникновении проблем во время обновления обратитесь за помощью на горячую линию службы поддержки HONOR или в сервисный центр для клиентов HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම නිර්දේශිත යාවත්කාලය සමහර අවස්ථාවලදී රූපකරණ ප්‍රයෝගය ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි, සමහර දර්ශනවල අසාමාන්‍ය බල පරිභෝජන ගැටළුව නිරාකරණය කරයි, පද්ධතියේ කාර්යසාධනය, ස්ථායීතාවය සහ රත්වීමේ අත්දැකීම වැඩි දියුණු කරයි, සහ ආරක්ෂක පැච් එකක් ඇතුළත් කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="කැමරාව">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය සමහර අවස්ථාවල දී දුරස්ථ ඡායාරූප රූගත කිරීමේ දීප්තිය සහ වර්ණ ප්‍රයෝගය ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.
මෙම යාවත්කාලය සමහර අවස්ථාවලදී ආලේඛ්‍යය නාභිගත කිරීමේ රූපකරණ ප්‍රයෝගය ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="කාර්යසාධනය">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය සමහර යෙදුම් දියත් කරන විට දී අහඹු පසුබෑමේ ගැටළුව නිරාකරණය කරයි.
මෙම යාවත්කාලය යෙදුම් ආරම්භක චලන ප්‍රයෝගයේ අහඹු රාමු බිඳ වැටීමේ ගැටළුව ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="බල පරිභෝජනය">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය සමහර සිදුවීම්වල දී අසාමාන්‍ය බල පරිභෝජන ගැටළුව ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="රත්වීමේ අත්දැකීම">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය සමහර අවස්ථාවල රත්වීමේ අත්දැකීම ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="පද්ධතිය">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය විසින් ඔබගේ උපාංගය වඩා ස්ථායීව ධාවනය කරවීමට පද්ධතියේ ස්ථායිතාවය වැඩිදියුණු කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ආරක්ෂාව">
<feature>පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2024 ජුලි) යොදාගෙන ඇත. HONOR ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7 වෙත යන්න</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්ත නොමකනු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් ඊට පෙර උපස්ථ කිරීමක් නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේ දී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, කරුණාකර HONOR සේවා ක්ෂණික ඇමතුම් අමතන්න නැතහොත් සහය සඳහා HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට යන්න.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený používateľ, táto odporúčaná aktualizácia optimalizuje zobrazovací efekt v niektorých scenároch, rieši problém s neobvyklou spotrebou energie pri niektorých scénach, zlepšuje výkon systému a stabilitu, znižuje zahrievanie a zahŕňa bezpečnostnú opravu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparát">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia optimalizuje jas a farebný efekt pri snímaní teleobjektívom v niektorých scenároch.
Táto aktualizácia optimalizuje zobrazovací efekt pri zaostrovaní na portréty v niektorých scenároch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Výkon">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia rieši problém náhodného oneskorenia pri spúšťaní niektorých aplikácií.
Táto aktualizácia optimalizuje problém náhodného zníženia počtu snímok v efekte pohybu pri spúšťaní aplikácií.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Spotreba energie">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia rieši problém abnormálnej spotreby energie v niektorých scénach.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zahrievanie">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia optimalizuje zahrievanie v niektorých situáciách.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia zlepšuje stabilitu systému, aby zariadenie fungovalo stabilnejšie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpečenie">
<feature>Súčasťou zabezpečenia systému je bezpečnostná oprava systému Android (z júla 2024). Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti HONOR, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštaláciou tejto aktualizácie nevymažete svoje osobné údaje, ale napriek tomu sa odporúča ich vopred zálohovať.
2. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytnú problémy, podporu môžete získať zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo návštevou Centra služieb zákazníkom HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, s to priporočeno posodobitvijo se v nekaterih situacijah optimizira učinek slikanja, v nekaterih situacijah je odpravljena težava neobičajne porabe energije, izboljšani so delovanje sistema, stabilnost in segrevanje naprave, vključen pa je tudi varnostni popravek.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>S to posodobitvijo sta v nekaterih situacijah optimizirana svetlost in barvni učinek pri fotografiranju s telefoto objektivom.
S to posodobitvijo se v nekaterih situacijah optimizira učinek slikanja v načinu izostritve portreta.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Učinkovitost delovanja">
<feature>S to posodobitvijo je odpravljena težava naključnih zakasnitev pri zagonu nekaterih aplikacij.
S to posodobitvijo je odpravljena težava, ko med zagonom aplikacije, ki prikazuje animacijo, niso prikazani vsi kadri.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poraba energije">
<feature>S to posodobitvijo se odpravi težava neobičajne porabe energije v nekaterih situacijah.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Izkušnja segrevanja">
<feature>S to posodobitvijo se optimizira izkušnja segrevanja naprave v nekaterih situacijah.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>S to posodobitvijo se izboljšuje stabilnost sistema za bolj zanesljivo delovanje naprave.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varnost">
<feature>Varnostni popravki za Android (julij 2024) so vključeni za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah HONOR obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Z namestitvijo te posodobitve vaši osebni podatki ne bodo izbrisani, vendar vseeno priporočamo, da jih predhodno varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodobitvijo naletite na težave, za podporo pokličite odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom izdelkov HONOR ali obiščite servisni center družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, den här rekommenderade uppdateringen optimerar bildeffekten i vissa scenarier, åtgärdar problemet med onormal energiförbrukning i vissa scener, förbättrar systemets prestanda, stabilitet och uppvärmning samt implementerar en säkerhetskorrigering.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Den här uppdateringen optimerar ljusstyrkan och färgeffekten vid fotografering med teleobjektiv i vissa scenarier.
Den här uppdateringen optimerar bildeffekten för porträttfokus i vissa scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prestanda">
<feature>Den här uppdateringen åtgärdar problemet med slumpmässig eftersläpning när vissa appar startas.
Den här uppdateringen optimerar problemet med slumpmässig minskning av bildhastighet i rörelseeffekten vid appstart.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energiförbrukning">
<feature>Den här uppdateringen åtgärdar problemet med onormal energiförbrukning i vissa scener.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uppvärmning">
<feature>Uppdateringen optimerar uppvärmningen i vissa scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Uppdateringen förbättrar systemets stabilitet så att enheten körs stabilare.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Säkerhet">
<feature>Android-säkerhetskorrigeringen (juli 2024) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för HONOR går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Den här uppdateringen raderar inga personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du gör en säkerhetskopia innan du installerar den.
2. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs servicecenter och få support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili linalopendekezwa linaboresha hali ya picha katika baadhi ya miktadha, linarekebisha hitilafu ya utumiaji nishati usio wa kawaida katika baadhi ya mandhari, linaboresha utendaji wa mfumo, uthabiti na hali ya kupata joto na linajumuisha rekebisho la usalama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Sasisho hili linaboresha athari ya mwangaza na rangi ya upigaji picha ya telefoto katika baadhi ya miktadha.
Sasisho hili linaboresha athari ya kuangazia picha wima katika baadhi ya miktadha.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Utendaji">
<feature>Sasisho hili linarekebisha tatizo la kujikokota kwa nasibu unapozindua baadhi ya programu.
Sasisho hili linaboresha hitilafu ya kiwango cha fremu kushuka kwa nasibu katika athari ya mwendo wa kuanzisha programu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Utumiaji nishati">
<feature>Sasisho hili linarekebisha tatizo la utumiaji nishati usio wa kawaida katika baadhi ya mandhari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hali ya kupata joto">
<feature>Sasisho hili linaboresha hali ya kupata joto katika baadhi ya miktadha.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mfumo">
<feature>Sasisho hili huboresa uthabiti wa mfumo ili kufanya kifaa chako kiendeshwe kwa uthabiti zaidi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Usalama">
<feature>Rekebisho la Usalama wa Android (Jul 2024) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa HONOR, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutafuta data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini hifadhi rudufu kabla ya kusakinisha bado inapendekezwa.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, tafadhali piga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au nenda kwenye kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha HONOR ili upate usaidizi.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படும் புதுப்பிப்பு சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் இமேஜிங் விளைவை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது, சில காட்சிகளில் அசாதாரண மின் நுகர்வுச் சிக்கலைச் சரிசெய்கிறது, சிஸ்டம் செயல்திறன், நிலைத்தன்மை மற்றும் சூடாகுதல் அனுபவத்தை மேம்படுத்துகிறது மற்றும் பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பைக் கொண்டுள்ளது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="கேமரா">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் டெலிபோட்டோ ஷூட்டிங்கின் ஒளிர்வு மற்றும் வண்ண விளைவை மேம்படுத்துகிறது.
இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் போர்ட்ரெயிட் ஃபோகஸ் இமேஜிங் விளைவை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="செயல்திறன்">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு, சில செயலிகளைத் தொடங்கும்போது ஏற்படும் தற்போக்குப் பின்னடைவின் சிக்கலைச் சரிசெய்கிறது.
இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு செயலித் துவக்கம் மோஷன் விளைவில் தற்போக்காக ஏற்படும் ஃபிரேம் டிராப்களின் சிக்கலை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="மின் நுகர்வு">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு சில காட்சிகளில் அசாதாரண மின் நுகர்வு சிக்கலைச் சரிசெய்கிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="சூடாகுதல் அனுபவம்">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் ஏற்படும் சூடாகுதல் அனுபவத்தை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="சிஸ்டம்">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பானது உங்கள் சாதனத்தை மேலும் நிலையாக இயங்கச் செய்யும் வகையில் சிஸ்டம் நிலைத்தன்மையை மேம்படுத்துகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பாதுகாப்பு">
<feature>சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (ஜூலை 2024) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. HONOR பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவை அழிக்காது, எனினும் தொடர்வதற்கு முன் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுக்குமாறு பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், உதவிக்காக HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைக்கவும் அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்லவும்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ సిఫార్సు చేయబడిన అప్‌డేట్ కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో ఇమేజింగ్ ప్రభావాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది, కొన్ని సీన్‌ల్లో అసాధారణ పవర్ వినియోగ సమస్యను పరిష్కరిస్తుంది, సిస్టమ్ పనితీరును, స్థిరత్వం మరియు వేడెక్కే అనుభవాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది మరియు భద్రతా ప్యాచ్‌ను చేర్చుతుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="కెమెరా">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో టెలిఫోటో షూటింగ్ యొక్క ప్రకాశవంతాన్ని మరియు రంగు ప్రభావాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది.
ఈ అప్‌డేట్ కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో పోర్ట్రెయిట్ ఫోకస్ ఇమేజింగ్ ప్రభావాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="పనితీరు">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ కొన్ని అప్లికేషన్‌లను లాంచ్ చేస్తున్నప్పుడు యాదృచ్ఛిక జాప్యం సమస్యను పరిష్కరిస్తుంది.
ఈ అప్‌డేట్ అప్లికేషన్ స్టార్టప్ మోషన్ ప్రభావంలో యాదృచ్చిక ఫ్రేమ్ తగ్గిపోయే సమస్య ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="పవర్ వాడకం">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ కొన్ని సీన్‌ల్లో అసాధారణ పవర్ వినియోగం సమస్యను పరిష్కరిస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="వేడెక్కే అనుభవం">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో వేడెక్కే అనుభవాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="సిస్టమ్">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ మీ పరికరం మరింత స్థిరంగా అమలు అయ్యేలా చేయడానికి సిస్టమ్ స్థిరత్వాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="భద్రత">
<feature>సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం Android సెక్యూరిటీ ప్యాచ్ (జూలై 2024) పొందుపరచబడింది. HONOR భద్రత నవీకరణల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్ సందర్శించండి https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వలన మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటా ఎరేజ్ చేయబడదు, కాని ముందుగా ఒక బ్యాకప్ తీసుకోవాలని సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీరు ఏవైనా సమస్యలను ఎదుర్కొన్నట్లయితే, దయచేసి మద్దతు కోసం HONOR సర్వీసు హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయండి లేదా HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి వెళ్ళండి.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตที่แนะนำครั้งนี้ปรับปรุงเอฟเฟ็กต์ภาพในบางสถานการณ์ แก้ไขปัญหาการใช้พลังงานผิดปกติในบางสถานการณ์ ปรับปรุงประสิทธิภาพ ความเสถียร และประสบการณ์ความร้อนของระบบ และรวมแพตช์รักษาความปลอดภัย</feature>
</features>
<features module="กล้องถ่ายรูป">
<feature>อัปเดตนี้ปรับปรุงความสว่างและเอฟเฟ็กต์สีของการถ่ายโทรภาพในบางสถานการณ์
อัปเดตนี้ปรับปรุงเอฟเฟ็กต์ภาพโฟกัสบุคคลในบางสถานการณ์</feature>
</features>
<features module="ประสิทธิภาพ">
<feature>อัปเดตนี้แก้ไขปัญหาความล่าช้าที่อาจเกิดขึ้นเมื่อเปิดใช้งานบางแอป
อัปเดตนี้ปรับปรุงปัญหาอัตราเฟรมตกที่อาจเกิดขึ้นในเอฟเฟ็กต์การเคลื่อนไหวเมื่อเริ่มแอป</feature>
</features>
<features module="การใช้พลังงาน">
<feature>อัปเดตนี้แก้ไขปัญหาการใช้พลังงานผิดปกติในบางสถานการณ์</feature>
</features>
<features module="ประสบการณ์ความร้อน">
<feature>อัปเดตนี้ปรับปรุงประสบการณ์ความร้อนในบางสถานการณ์</feature>
</features>
<features module="ระบบ">
<feature>อัปเดตนี้ปรับปรุงความเสถียรของระบบเพื่อให้อุปกรณ์ของคุณทำงานเสถียรมากขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="ความปลอดภัย">
<feature>มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัยของ Android (ก.ค. 2024) เพื่อการรักษาความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตการรักษาความปลอดภัยของ HONOR ได้ในเว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="โปรดทราบ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่ลบข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เราขอแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลไว้ล่วงหน้า
2. หากคุณพบปัญหาใดๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต ให้โทรติดต่อสายด่วนบริการ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้า HONOR เพื่อขอรับความช่วยเหลือ</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, ino-optimize ng inirerekomendang update na ito ang effect ng imaging sa ilang sitwasyon, inaayos ang isyu ng hindi normal na pagkonsumo sa baterya sa ilang sitwasyon, pinapahusay ang karanasan sa performance, stability, at pag-init ng system, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang liwanag at effect ng kulay sa pag-shoot ng telephoto sa ilang sitwasyon.
Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang effect ng imaging na portrait focus sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performance">
<feature>Inaayos ng update na ito ang problema ng random na pag-lag kapag inilulunsad ang ilang app.
Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang problema ng random na mga pag-drop ng frame sa effect ng paggalaw sa pag-start up ng app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pagkonsumo ng baterya">
<feature>Inaayos ng update na ito ang isyu ng hindi normal na pagkonsumo ng baterya sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Karanasan sa pag-init">
<feature>Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang karanasan sa pag-init sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Pinapahusay ng update na ito ang stability ng system para magawang tumakbo nang mas stable ang iyong device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Hulyo 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi mabubura ang iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa rin ang isang pag-back up bago gawin ito.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, ino-optimize ng inirerekomendang update na ito ang effect ng imaging sa ilang sitwasyon, inaayos ang isyu ng hindi normal na pagkonsumo sa baterya sa ilang sitwasyon, pinapahusay ang karanasan sa performance, stability, at pag-init ng system, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang liwanag at effect ng kulay sa pag-shoot ng telephoto sa ilang sitwasyon.
Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang effect ng imaging na portrait focus sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performance">
<feature>Inaayos ng update na ito ang problema ng random na pag-lag kapag inilulunsad ang ilang app.
Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang problema ng random na mga pag-drop ng frame sa effect ng paggalaw sa pag-start up ng app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pagkonsumo ng baterya">
<feature>Inaayos ng update na ito ang isyu ng hindi normal na pagkonsumo ng baterya sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Karanasan sa pag-init">
<feature>Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang karanasan sa pag-init sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Pinapahusay ng update na ito ang stability ng system para magawang tumakbo nang mas stable ang iyong device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Hulyo 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi mabubura ang iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa rin ang isang pag-back up bago gawin ito.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Değerli kullanıcımız, önerilen bu güncelleme ile bazı durumlarda görüntüleme efekti optimize edilmiş, bazı durumlarda anormal güç tüketimi sorunu giderilmiş, sistem performansı, kararlılık ve ısınma deneyimi iyileştirilmiş ve bir güvenlik yaması eklenmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Bu güncelleme ile bazı durumlarda telefoto çekimin parlaklık ve renk efekti optimize edilmiştir.
Bu güncelleme ile bazı durumlarda portre odak görüntüleme efekti optimize edilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performans">
<feature>Bu güncelleme ile bazı uygulamalar başlatılırken yaşanan rastgele gecikme sorunu giderilmiştir.
Bu güncelleme ile uygulama başlatma hareket efektinde yaşanan rastgele kare düşmesi sorunu optimize edilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güç tüketimi">
<feature>Bu güncelleme ile bazı durumlarda anormal güç tüketimi sorunu giderilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Isınma deneyimi">
<feature>Bu güncelleme ile bazı durumlarda ısınma deneyimi optimize edilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Bu güncelleme ile sistem kararlılığı iyileştirilerek cihazınız daha kararlı hale getirilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güvenlik">
<feature>Sistem güvenliği için Android Güvenlik Yamasını (Temmuz 2024) içermektedir. HONOR Güvenlik güncellemeleri ile ilgili daha fazla bilgi için lütfen web sitemizi ziyaret edin: https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi silmeyecektir, fakat yine de öncesinde yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşmanız durumunda destek için lütfen HONOR servisi yardım hattını arayın veya HONOR müşteri servisi merkezlerinden birine gidin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى كامېرانىڭ رەسىمگە تارتىش ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى، بىر قىسىم ئەھۋاللاردىكى توك بىنورمال خوراش مەسىلىسى ھەل قىلىنىدى، سىستېمىنىڭ ئىقتىدارى، مۇقىملىقى ۋە قىزغىنلىق تەسىراتى يۇقىرى كۆتۈرۈلدى، بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«كامېرا»">
<feature>بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى ئۇزۇن فوكۇسلۇق رەسىمگە تارتىشنىڭ يورۇقلۇق ۋە رەڭ ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى.
بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى پورترېت تەسۋىر ھاسىل قىلىش ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«ئىقتىدار»">
<feature>بىر قىسىم ئەپلەرنىڭ ئاندا-ساندا قېتىپ قېلىش مەسىلىسى ھەل قىلىندى.
بىر قىسىم ئەپلەرنىڭ قوزغىتىلغاندىكى ھەرىكەت ئۈنۈمىدە ئاندا-ساندا رام يوقاپ كېتىش مەسىلىسى ھەل قىلىندى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«توك سەرپىياتى»">
<feature>بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى بىنورمال توك خوراش مەسىلىسى ئوڭشالدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«قىزغىنلىق تەسىراتى»">
<feature>بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى قىزغىنلىق تەسىراتى يۇقىرى كۆتۈرۈلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«سىستېما»">
<feature>سىستېمىنىڭ مۇقىملىقى ئۆستۈرۈلۈپ، يانفونىڭىزنىڭ ئىجرا قىلىنىشى تېخىمۇ مۇقىملاشتۇرۇلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«بىخەتەرلىك»">
<feature>ئاندرويدنىڭ 2024-يىل 7-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتىنى زىيارەت قىلىڭ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركىسى مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановний користувачу, у цьому рекомендованому оновленні оптимізовано ефект обробки зображення в деяких сценаріях, вирішено проблему ненормального споживання енергії в деяких сценаріях, покращено продуктивність роботи системи, питання стабільності і нагріву, а також додано виправлення системи безпеки.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>У цьому оновленні оптимізовано ефект яскравості й кольору для зйомки телефотознімків у деяких сценаріях.
У цьому оновленні оптимізовано ефект обробки зображення в портретному фокусуванні в деяких сценаріях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Продуктивність">
<feature>У цьому оновленні вирішено проблему випадкової затримки під час запуску деяких додатків.
У цьому оновленні оптимізовано проблему випадкового падіння частоти кадрів під час запуску додатка.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Споживання енергії">
<feature>Це оновлення усуває проблему аномального енергоспоживання в деяких сценаріях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Питання нагріву">
<feature>У цьому оновленні оптимізовано питання нагріву в деяких ситуаціях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>У цьому оновленні підвищено стабільність роботи системи для надійнішої роботи пристрою.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безпека">
<feature>Виправлення для системи безпеки Android від липня 2024 року впроваджено для посилення безпеки системи. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки HONOR див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примітки." type="end">
<feature>1. Ваші особисті дані не буде видалено внаслідок установлення цього оновлення, але все ж радимо створити резервну копію заздалегідь.
2. Якщо під час оновлення у вас виникнуть будь-які проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію обслуговування користувачів HONOR або зверніться в сервісний центр HONOR по допомогу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>محترم صارف، یہ تجویز کردہ اپ ڈیٹ کچھ منظرناموں میں امیجنگ اثر کو بہتر بناتی ہے، کچھ مناظر میں بجلی کی غیر معمولی کھپت کے مسئلے کو حل کرتی ہے، سسٹم کی کارکردگی، استحکام اور حرارتی تجربے کو بہتر بناتی ہے، اور سکیورٹی پیچ شامل کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="کیمرہ">
<feature>یہ اپ ڈیٹ کچھ منظرناموں میں ٹیلی فوٹو شوٹنگ کی چمک اور رنگین اثر کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔
یہ اپ ڈیٹ کچھ منظرناموں میں پورٹریٹ فوکس امیجنگ کے اثر کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="کارکردگی">
<feature>یہ اپ ڈیٹ کچھ ایپس کو شروع کرتے وقت بے ترتیبانہ تاخیر کے مسئلے کو حل کرتی ہے۔
یہ اپ ڈیٹ ایپ اسٹارٹ اپ موشن کے اثر میں بے ترتیبانہ فریم ڈراپ کے مسئلے کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="بجلی کی کھپت">
<feature>یہ اپ ڈیٹ کچھ مناظر میں بجلی کی غیر معمولی کھپت کے مسئلے کو حل کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="حرارتی تجربہ">
<feature>یہ اپ ڈیٹ چند منظرناموں میں حرارتی تجربے کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سسٹم">
<feature>آپ کی ڈیوائس کو زیادہ مستحکم طریقے سے چلانے کے لیے یہ اپ ڈیٹ سسٹم کے استحکام کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سکیورٹی">
<feature>‏‏Android سکیورٹی پیچ (جولائی 2024) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ HONOR سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ ملاحظہ کریں: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں مٹے گا، لیکن پھر بھی پہلے سے بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2. اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو تعاون کے لیے براہ کرم HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کریں یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جائیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu tavsiya etiladigan yangilanishda ayrim holatlardagi tasvirlash effekti optimallandi, noodatiy quvvat sarfi muammosi tuzatildi, tizim unumdorligi, barqarorlik va qizish taassuroti yaxshilandi hamda xavfsizlik tuzatmasi kiritildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda ayrim holatlardagi telefoto tasvirga olish yorqinligi va rang effekti yaxshilandi.
Bu yangilanishda ayrim holatlardagi portret fokus tasvirlash effekti optimallandi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Unumdorlik">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda ayrim ilovalarni ishga tushirishda tasodifan yuz beradigan qotish muammosi tuzatildi.
Bu yangilanishda ilovani ishga tushirish harakati effektida kadrlar chastotasining tasodifan pasayib ketishi muammosi tuzatildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Quvvat sarfi">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda ayrim holatlardagi noodatiy quvvat sarfi muammosi tuzatildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qizish muammosi">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda ayrim holatlardagi qizish muammosi optimallandi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tizim">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda qurilmangiz yanada barqaror ishlashi uchun tizim barqarorligi oshirildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Xavfsizlik">
<feature>Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2024-yil, iyul) kiritildi. HONOR Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanish oʻrnatilsa shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringiz oʻchib ketmaydi, lekin ularni oldindan zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, yordam uchun HONOR xizmat markazi tezkor raqamiga murojaat qiling yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyuring.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật đề xuất này sẽ tối ưu hóa hiệu ứng chụp ảnh trong một số trường hợp, khắc phục sự cố tiêu thụ pin bất thường trong một số tình huống, cải thiện hiệu suất hệ thống, độ ổn định và trải nghiệm nóng máy, đồng thời tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Máy ảnh">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này tối ưu hóa hiệu ứng độ sáng và màu sắc chụp ảnh tele trong một số trường hợp.
Bản cập nhật này tối ưu hóa hiệu ứng chụp ảnh lấy nét ảnh chân dung trong một số trường hợp.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hiệu suất">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này khắc phục sự cố trễ ngẫu nhiên khi khởi chạy một số ứng dụng.
Bản cập nhật này tối ưu hóa vấn đề giảm khung hình ngẫu nhiên trong hiệu ứng chuyển động khi khởi động ứng dụng.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tiêu thụ pin">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này khắc phục sự cố tiêu thụ pin bất thường trong một số tình huống.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Trải nghiệm nóng máy">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này tối ưu hóa trải nghiệm nóng máy trong một số trường hợp.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hệ thống">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này cải thiện độ ổn định của hệ thống để giúp thiết bị của bạn chạy ổn định hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bảo mật">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này tích hợp Bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 7 năm 2024) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của HONOR, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ghi chú:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị xóa. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu trước.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新優化了部分場景相機拍攝成像效果，修復了部分場景異常耗電問題，提升了系統性能、穩定性和熱體驗，並整合了安全性修補程式，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相機】">
<feature>優化了部分場景下長焦拍攝的亮度、顏色效果。
優化了部分場景下人像對焦成像效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【性能】">
<feature>修復了部分應用程式啟動偶爾卡死的問題。
優化了應用程式啟動動畫效果偶爾停滯問題。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【功耗】">
<feature>修復了部分場景異常耗電的問題。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【熱體驗】">
<feature>提升了部分場景性能體驗。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>提升系統穩定性，讓您的手機運行更穩定。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>整合 Android 2024年7月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新最佳化在部分場景下的相機拍照成像效果，修復在部分場景下的異常耗電問題，提升系統效能、穩定性和熱體驗，並整合安全性修補程式，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相機】">
<feature>最佳化在部分場景下長焦拍攝的亮度、色彩效果。
最佳化在部分場景下的人像對焦成像效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【效能】">
<feature>修復部分應用程式啟動時可能當機的問題。
最佳化應用程式啟動時動畫可能丟棄影格的問題。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【電量消耗】">
<feature>修復在部分場景下的異常耗電問題。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【熱體驗】">
<feature>提升在部分場景下的熱體驗。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>提升系統穩定性，讓您的手機執行更穩定。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>整合 Android 2024 年 7 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
