<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新新增全局收藏、荣耀文档和桌面图标大小调节功能，优化部分场景相机拍照成像效果，修复部分场景异常耗电问题，提升系统性能、稳定性和热体验，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【全局收藏】">
<feature>全局收藏全新升级，三指下滑即可将图片、网页、文件等素材快速保存至收藏空间。点击展开收藏空间，长按单个或多个选中的内容即可拖拽至其他应用使用，也可同步至信任环中其他设备，跨设备共享收藏内容。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【荣耀文档】">
<feature>全新荣耀文档，全新交互界面，增加自定义标签、回收站功能，提升文档稳定性和兼容性，提供更丰富的使用体验。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【桌面图标】">
<feature>支持桌面图标大小调节，满足用户对图标大小的不同显示需求，体验路径：“设置->桌面和个性化->桌面设置->图标大小”。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【播放器】">
<feature>新增本地音乐播放器。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相机】">
<feature>优化部分场景下长焦拍摄的亮度、颜色效果。
优化部分场景下人像对焦成像效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【性能】">
<feature>修复部分应用启动概率卡死问题。
优化应用启动动效概率丢帧问题。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【功耗】">
<feature>修复部分场景异常耗电问题。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【热体验】">
<feature>提升部分场景热体验。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系统】">
<feature>提升系统稳定性，让您的手机运行更稳定。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>合入安卓2024年7月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update adds Global Favorites, HONOR Docs and the function of adjusting home screen icon size, optimizes the imaging effect in some scenarios, fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenes, improves the system performance, stability and heating experience, and incorporates a security patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Global Favorites">
<feature>This update brings newly upgraded Global Favorites. Swipe down with three fingers to save materials, such as images, web pages and files, to Favorites Space. Tap to expand Favorites Space, press and hold the selected one or multiple items to drag them to other apps, and you can also sync them to other MagicRing devices to share collected content across devices.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>This update provides brand-new HONOR Docs and interactive interface, adds custom labels, recycle bin and other functions, improves document stability and compatibility, and provides a better user experience.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Home screen icons">
<feature>The size of Home screen icons can be adjusted to meet the users' different needs. You can experience it by going to: Settings -> Home screen and style -> Home screen settings -> Icon size.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Player">
<feature>This update adds Music Player on device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>This update optimizes the brightness and color effect of telephoto shooting in some scenarios.
This update optimizes the portrait focus imaging effect in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performance">
<feature>This update fixes the problem of random lagging when launching some apps.
This update optimizes the problem of random frame drops in app startup motion effect.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Power consumption">
<feature>This update fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenes.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Heating experience">
<feature>This update optimizes the heating experience in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>This update improves the system stability to make your device run more stably.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android Security Patch (July 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service center for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ የሚመከር ዝማኔ ሁለገብ ተወዳጆችን፣ HONOR ሰነዶችን እና የመነሻ ገጽ አዶ መጠንን የማስተካከል ተግባርን ያክላል፣ በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች የምስል ተጽእኖን ያተባል፣ በአንዳንድ ትዕይንቶች ላይ ያልተለመደ የኃይል ፍጆታ ችግርን ያስተካክላል፣ የስርዓቱን አፈጻጸም፣ መረጋጋት እና ማሞቂያ ተሞክሮ ያሻሽላል እና የደህንነት መጠገኛን ያካትታል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ሁለገብ ተወዳጆች">
<feature>ይህ ዝማኔ አዲስ የተሻሻሉ ሁለገብ ተወዳጆችን ያመጣል። እንደ ምስሎች፣ ድረ-ገጾች እና ፋይሎች ያሉ ነገሮችን ወደ የተወዳጆች ቦታ ለማስቀመጥ በሶስት ጣቶች ወደ ታች ይጥረጉ። የተወዳጆች ቦታን ለማስፋት መታ ማድረግ፣ የተመረጡትን አንድ ወይም ብዙ ንጥሎችን ወደ ሌሎች መተግበሪያዎች ለመጎተት ተጭነው መያዝ፣ እና እንዲሁም የተሰበሰቡ ይዘቶችን በመሳሪያዎች ላይ ለማጋራት ከሌሎች MagicRing መሳሪያዎች ጋር ማመሳሰል ይችላሉ።</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR ሰነዶች">
<feature>ይህ ዝማኔ አዲስ የHONOR ሰነዶችን እና በይነተገናኝ በይነገጽ ያቀርባል፣ ብጁ መለያዎችን ይጨምራል፣ ሪሳይክል ቢን እና ሌሎች ተግባራትን፣ የሰነድ መረጋጋትን እና ተኳኋኝነትን ያሻሽላል እና የተሻለ የተጠቃሚ ተሞክሮ ይሰጣል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የመነሻ ገጽ አዶዎች">
<feature>የተጠቃሚዎችን የተለያዩ ፍላጎቶች ለማሟላት የመነሻ ገጽ አዶዎች መጠን ሊስተካከል ይችላል። ወደ ቅንብሮች -> መነሻ ገጽ እና ቅጥ -> የመነሻ ማያ ቅንብሮች -> የአዶ መጠን በመሄድ ሊሞክቱት ይችላሉ።</feature>
</features>
<features module="አጫዋች">
<feature>ይህ ዝማኔ በመሣሪያው ላይ የሙዚቃ አጫዋችን ያክላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ካሜራ">
<feature>ይህ ዝማኔ በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች የቴሌፎቶ የማንሳት ብሩህነት እና የቀለም ተጽእኖን ያተባል።
ይህ ዝማኔ በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች ላይ የቁም ምስል ትኩረትን ይተባል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="አፈጻጸም">
<feature>ይህ ዝማኔ አንዳንድ መተግበሪያዎችን ሲያስጀምሩ የዘፈቀደ መዘግየትን ችግር ያስተካክላል።
ይህ ዝማኔ በመተግበሪያ መጀመር እንቅስቃሴ ተጽእኖ ላይ የዘፈቀደ ፍሬም ማጥት ችግሮችን ያተባል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የኃይል ፍጆታ">
<feature>ይህ ዝማኔ በአንዳንድ ትዕይንቶች ላይ ያለውን ያልተለመደ የኃይል ፍጆታ ችግር ያስተካክላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የማሞቂያ ተሞክሮ">
<feature>ይህ ማሻሻያ በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች የማሞቂያ ተሞክሮን ያተባል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ስርዓት">
<feature>ይህ ዝማኔ መሳሪያዎ ይበልጥ በተረጋጋ ሁኔታ እንዲያስኬድ ለማድረግ የስርዓት መረጋጋትን ያሻሽላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ደህንነት">
<feature>ለስርዓት ደህንነት የአንድሮይድ የደህንነት መጠገኛን (ጁላይ 2024) ተካቷል። ስለ HONOR ደህንነት ዝማኔዎች ተጨማሪ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎን የእኛን ድር ጣቢያ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7 ይጎብኙ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፡-" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ማሻሻያ መጫን የእርስዎን የግል መረጃዎን አይደመስስም፣ ነገር ግን አስቀድሞ መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ አሁንም ይመከራል።
2. በማሻሻያው ወቅት ማንኛውም አይነት ችግር ካጋጠመዎት እባክዎን ወደ HONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር ይደውሉ ወይም ድጋፍ ለማግኘት ወደ HONOR የደንበኞች የአገልግሎት ማዕከል ይሂዱ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزي المستخدم، يضيف هذا التحديث الموصى به المفضلة العامة ومستندات HONOR ووظيفة ضبط حجم أيقونة الشاشة الرئيسية، ويحسّن تأثير التصوير في بعض السيناريوهات، ويصلح مشكلة استهلاك الطاقة غير الطبيعي في بعض الحالات، ويحسّن أداء النظام واستقراره ويعالج تجربة زيادة السخونة، ويضمّن تصحيح أمان.‬</feature>
</features>
<features module="المفضلة العامة">
<feature>يقدم هذا التحديث ميزة المفضلة العامة التي تمت ترقيتها مؤخرًا. اسحب لأسفل باستخدام ثلاث أصابع لحفظ المواد، مثل الصور وصفحات الويب والملفات، في المساحة المفضلة. اضغط لتوسيع المساحة المفضلة، واضغط باستمرار على العنصر المحدد أو العناصر المتعددة المحددة لسحبها إلى تطبيقات أخرى، ويمكنك أيضًا مزامنتها مع أجهزة MagicRing الأخرى لمشاركة المحتوى المجمع عبر الأجهزة.</feature>
</features>
<features module="مستندات HONOR">
<feature>يوفر هذا التحديث مستندات HONOR وواجهة تفاعلية جديدة تمامًا، ويضيف تسميات مخصصة وسلة المحذوفات ووظائف أخرى، ويحسّن استقرار المستندات وتوافقها، ويوفر تجربة مستخدم أفضل.</feature>
</features>
<features module="أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية">
<feature>يمكن تعديل حجم أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية لتلبية احتياجات المستخدمين المختلفة. يمكنك تجربة ذلك بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات -> الشاشة الرئيسية والنمط -> إعدادات الشاشة الرئيسية -> حجم الأيقونة.</feature>
</features>
<features module="المشغل">
<feature>يضيف هذا التحديث مشغل الموسيقى على الجهاز.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الكاميرا">
<feature>يحسّن هذا التحديث السطوع وتأثير الألوان عند تصوير لقطات مقربة في بعض السيناريوهات.‬
يحسّن هذا التحديث تأثير التصوير عن طريق التركيز على صور البورتريه في بعض السيناريوهات.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأداء">
<feature>يصلح هذا التحديث مشكلة التأخير العشوائي الذي يحدث عند تشغيل بعض التطبيقات.
يحسّن هذا التحديث مشكلة انخفاض معدل الإطارات بطريقة عشوائية في تأثير حركة بدء تشغيل التطبيق.</feature>
</features>
<features module="استهلاك الطاقة">
<feature>يُصلح هذا التحديث مشكلة استهلاك الطاقة غير الطبيعي في بعض الحالات.</feature>
</features>
<features module="تجربة زيادة السخونة">
<feature>يحسّن هذا التحديث تجربة زيادة السخونة في بعض السيناريوهات.</feature>
</features>
<features module="النظام">
<feature>يحسّن هذا التحديث استقرار النظام لجعل جهازك يعمل بشكل أكثر استقرارًا.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأمان">
<feature>تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (يوليو 2024) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في HONOR، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>1. لن يؤدي تثبيت هذا التحديث إلى مسح بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية مسبقًا.
2. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة HONOR أو انتقل إلى مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR للحصول على الدعم.‬</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই অনুমোদিত আপডেটটোৱে বিশ্বব্যাপী প্ৰিয়, HONOR Docs আৰু হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্নৰ আকাৰ মিলোৱাৰ ফাংচনটো যোগ কৰে, কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত ইমেজিং প্ৰভাৱ অনুকূলন কৰে, কিছুমান দৃশ্যত অস্বাভাৱিক পাৱাৰ খৰচৰ সমস্যাটো সমাধান কৰে, ছিষ্টেমৰ কাৰ্যদক্ষতা, স্থিৰতা আৰু গৰম হোৱাৰ অভিজ্ঞতা উন্নত কৰে আৰু এটা নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="বিশ্বব্যাপী প্ৰিয়">
<feature>এই আপডেটে নতুনকৈ আপগ্ৰেড কৰা বিশ্বব্যাপী প্ৰিয় লৈ আহে। প্ৰিয় স্থানত প্ৰতিচ্ছবিসমূহ, ৱেব পৃষ্ঠাসমূহ আৰু ফাইলসমূহৰ দৰে সামগ্ৰীবোৰ সংৰক্ষণ কৰিবলৈ তিনিটা আঙুলিৰে তললৈ ছোৱাইপ কৰক। প্ৰিয় স্থান বিস্তাৰ কৰিবলৈ টিপক, অন্য এপ্প্‌সমূহলৈ বাছনি কৰাটো বা একাধিক আইটেম টানিবলৈ সেইবোৰ দবাওক আৰু ধৰি থাকক আৰু সংগ্ৰহ কৰা সমল ডিভাইচসমূহৰ মাজত ভাগ-বতৰা কৰিবলৈ আপুনি লগতে অন্য MagicRing ডিভাইচসমূহলৈ সেইবোৰ ছিংক কৰিব পাৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>এই আপডেটটোৱে একেবাৰে নতুন HONOR Docs আৰু ইণ্টাৰেক্টিভ ইণ্টাৰফেচ প্ৰদান কৰে আৰু কাষ্টম লেবেল, ৰিচাইকল বিন আৰু অন্য ফাংচনসমূহ যোগ কৰে, নথিপত্ৰৰ স্থিৰতা আৰু সুসঙ্গতা উন্নত কৰে আৰু এটা উন্নত ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ অভিজ্ঞতা প্ৰদান কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্ন">
<feature>ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ বেলেগ বেলেগ প্ৰয়োজনবোৰ পূৰণ কৰিবলৈ হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্নৰ আকাৰ মিলাব পাৰি। আপুনি ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াৰ অভিজ্ঞতা ল'ব পাৰে: ছেটিংছ -> হোম স্ক্ৰীণ আৰু শৈলী -> হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ ছেটিংছ -> চিহ্নৰ আকাৰ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="প্লেয়াৰ">
<feature>এই আপডেটটোৱে ডিভাইচত সঙ্গীত প্লেয়াৰ যোগ কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="কেমেৰা">
<feature>এই আপডেটটোৱে কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত টেলিফটো শ্বুটিঙৰ উজ্জ্বলতা আৰু ৰঙৰ প্ৰভাৱ অনুকূলন কৰে।
এই আপডেটটোৱে কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত প'ৰ্ট্ৰেইট ফ'কাচ ইমেজিং প্ৰভাৱ অনুকূলন কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="কাৰ্যদক্ষতা">
<feature>এই আপডেটটোৱে কিছুমান এপ্প্‌ প্ৰাৰম্ভ কৰাৰ সময়ত যাদৃচ্ছিক লেগিঙৰ সমস্যাটো সমাধান কৰে।
এই আপডেটটোৱে এপ্প্‌ আৰম্ভণিৰ গতিৰ প্ৰভাৱত যাদৃচ্ছিক ফ্ৰেম কমাৰ সমস্যাটো অনুকূলন কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="পাৱাৰ খৰচ">
<feature>এই আপডেটটোৱে কিছুমান দৃশ্যত অস্বাভাৱিক পাৱাৰ খৰচৰ সমস্যাটো সমাধান কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গৰম হোৱাৰ অভিজ্ঞতা">
<feature>এই আপডেটটোৱে কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত গৰম হোৱাৰ অভিজ্ঞতা অনুকূলন কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ছিষ্টেম">
<feature>এই আপডেটটোৱে আপোনাৰ ডিভাইচ অধিক স্থিৰকৈ চলিব পৰা কৰিবলৈ ছিষ্টেমৰ স্থিৰতা উন্নত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিৰাপত্তা">
<feature>ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (জুলাই 2024) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। HONOR নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটা মোহৰা নহ'ব, কিন্তু তথাপিও তাৰ আগতে বেকআপ ল'বলৈ অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আপডেটৰ সময়ত আপুনি যদি কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হয়, তেন্তে সমৰ্থনৰ বাবে অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত ফোন কৰিব বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ যাব।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, tövsiyə edilən bu yeniləmə Qlobal Sevimliləri, HONOR Sənədləri və əsas ekran nişan ölçüsünü tənzimləmək funksiyasını əlavə edir, bəzi hallarda görüntü effektini optimallaşdırır, bəzi hallarda qeyri-normal enerji istehlakı problemini həll edir, sistemin performansını, sabitliyini və isitmə təcrübəsini yaxşılaşdırır, habelə təhlükəsizlik paketi daxil edir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qlobal Sevimlilər">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə yenicə təkmilləşdirilmiş Qlobal Sevimliləri təqdim edir. Şəkillər, veb-səhifələr və fayllar kimi materialları Sevimlilər Yerində saxlamaq üçün üç barmaqla aşağı çəkin. Sevimlilər Yerini genişləndirmək üçün toxunun, seçilmiş bir və ya bir neçə elementi digər proqramlara sürükləmək üçün basıb saxlayın və həmçinin toplanmış məzmunu cihazlar arasında paylaşmaq üçün onları digər MagicRing cihazlarına sinxronlaşdıra bilərsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Sənədlər">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə tamamilə yeni HONOR Sənədlər və interaktiv interfeys təqdim edir, fərdi etiketlər, zibil qutusu və digər funksiyalar əlavə edir, sənəd sabitliyini və uyğunluğu yaxşılaşdırır, habelə daha yaxşı istifadəçi təcrübəsi təmin edir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Əsas ekran nişanları">
<feature>Əsas ekran nişanlarının ölçüsü istifadəçilərin müxtəlif ehtiyaclarını ödəmək üçün tənzimlənə bilər. Bunu aşağıdakı bölmələrə keçməklə təcrübədən keçirə bilərsiniz: Parametrlər -> Əsas ekran və üslub -> Əsas ekran parametrləri -> Nişan ölçüsü.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pleyer">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə cihazda Musiqi Pleyeri əlavə edir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə bəzi hallarda telefoto çəkilişinin parlaqlığını və rəng effektini optimallaşdırır.
Bu yeniləmə bəzi hallarda portret fokusunun görüntü effektini optimallaşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performans">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə bəzi tətbiqləri işə salarkən təsadüfi gecikmə problemini həll edir.
Bu yeniləmə tətbiqin başlatma hərəkət effektində təsadüfi kadr düşmə problemini optimallaşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Enerji sərfiyyatı">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə bəzi hallarda qeyri-normal enerji sərfiyyatı problemini həll edir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="İsitmə təcrübəsi">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə bəzi hallarda isitmə təcrübəsini optimallaşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Bu yeniləmə cihazınızın daha stabil işləməsi üçün sistem stabilliyini təkmilləşdirir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Təhlükəsizlik">
<feature>Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android Təhlükəsizlik Paketi (Aprel 2024-cü il) daxil edilib. HONOR Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün veb-saytımıza daxil olun: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması ilə şəxsi məlumatlarınız silinməyəcək, lakin yenə də qabaqcadan ehtiyat nüsxənin çıxarılması tövsiyə edilir.
2. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlərlə qarşılaşsanız, dəstək üçün HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edin, yaxud HONOR müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə gedin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran sing disaranake iki nambahake Favorit Global, HONOR Docs, lan fungsi pangaturan ukuran ikon layar ngarep, ngoptimalake efek gambar ing sawetera skenario, ndandani masalah panggunaan daya sing ora normal ing sawetara adegan, ngapikake kinerja, stabilitas, lan pangalaman panas sistem, sarta nggabungake patch keamanan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favorit Global">
<feature>Panganyaran iki nyuguhake Favorit Global sing lagi wae ditingkatake. Usap mudhun nganggo telung driji kanggo nyimpen materi, kayata gambar, kaca web, lan file, menyang Enggon Favorit. Tutul kanggo nggedhekake Enggon Favorit, penet suwe item kapilih utawa akeh item kanggo diseret menyang apl liyane, lan sampeyan bisa uga nyinkronake item menyang piranti MagicRing kanggo mbage konten sing dikumpulake ing antarane piranti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Panganyaran ini nyedhiyakake antarmuka interaktif lan HONOR Docs sing anyar, nambahake label kustom, kranjang sampah, lan fungsi liyane, ngapikake kompatibilitas lan stabilitas dokumen, uga nyedhiyakake pengalaman pengguna sing luwih apik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikon Layar ngarep">
<feature>Ukuran ikon Layar ngarep bisa diatur kanggo nyukupi kabutuhan pangguna sing beda-beda. Sampeyan bisa nggunakake fitur iki kanthi mbukak: Setelan -> Layar ngarep lan gaya -> Setelan layar ngarep -> Ukuran ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pamuter">
<feature>Panganyaran iki nambahake Pamuter Musik ing piranti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Panganyaran iki ngoptimalake efek padhange lan warna panjupukan telefoto ing sawetara skenario.
Panganyaran iki ngoptimalake efek gambar fokus potret ing sawetara skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kinerja">
<feature>Panganyaran iki ndandani masalah nyendat random nalika ngluncurake sawetara apl.
Panganyaran iki ngoptimalake masalah frame acak mudhun ing efek obahan wiwitan apl.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panggunaan daya">
<feature>Panganyaran iki ndandani masalah panggunaan daya sing ora normal ing sawetara skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pangalaman panas">
<feature>Panganyaran iki ngoptimalake pangalaman panas ing sawetara skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Panganyaran iki ngapikake stabilitas sistem supaya piranti sampeyan mlaku kanthi luwih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Patch Keamanan Android (Juli 2024) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan HONOR bisa dideleng ing situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mbusak data pribadi sampeyan, nanging nggawe serep dhisik tetep disaranake.
2. Yen ana masalah sajrone proses panganyaran, telpona hotline layanan HONOR utawa bukak pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR kanggo njaluk dhukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem se dodaje Globalno omiljeno, HONOR dokumenti i funkcija prilagođavanja veličine ikone na početnom ekranu, optimizuje efekat slike u nekim scenarijima, rešava problem nenormalne potrošnje struje u nekim scenama, poboljšava sistem učinka, stabilnosti i iskustva sa zagrevanjem i ono sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globalno omiljeno">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem uvodi se nadograđena funkcija Globalno omiljeno. Prevucite nadole sa tri prsta da biste u Prostor za omiljeno sačuvali materijale poput slika, veb-stranica i datoteka. Dodirnite da biste proširili Prostor za omiljeno i pritisnite i držite jednu ili više izabranih stavki da biste ih prevlačili u druge aplikacije. Takođe možete da ih sinhronizujete sa uređajima koji podržavaju tehnologiju MagicRing da biste delili prikupljeni sadržaj na više uređaja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR dokumenta">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem isporučuje se potpuno nova aplikacija HONOR dokumenta i interaktivni interfejsovi, dodaju se prilagođene oznake, korpa za otpatke i druge funkcije, unapređuje se stabilnost i kompatibilnost dokumenata i poboljšava se korisničko iskustvo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikone na početnom ekranu">
<feature>Korisnik može u skladu sa svojim potrebama prilagoditi veličinu ikona na početnom ekranu. Putem sledeće putanje možete da promenite veličinu: Podešavanja -> Početni ekran i stil -> Podešavanja početnog ekrana -> Veličina ikone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Plejer">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem uređaju se dodaje Audio plejer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se optimizuje efekat osvetljaja i boje telefoto snimanja u nekim scenarijima.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizuje efekat slike fokusa na portretu u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Učinak">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se rešava problem nasumičnog kašnjenja kada se pokrenu neke aplikacije.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizuje problem nasumičnog pada rama kod efekta pokreta prilikom pokretanja aplikacije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se rešava problem nepravilne potrošnje energije u pojedinim situacijama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iskustvo sa zagrevanjem">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se optimizuje iskustvo zagrevanja u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem je poboljšana stabilnost sistema, zbog čega vaš uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (jul 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem se dodaje Globalno omiljeno, HONOR dokumenti i funkcija prilagođavanja veličine ikone na početnom ekranu, optimizuje efekat slike u nekim scenarijima, rešava problem nenormalne potrošnje struje u nekim scenama, poboljšava sistem učinka, stabilnosti i iskustva sa zagrevanjem i ono sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globalno omiljeno">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem uvodi se nadograđena funkcija Globalno omiljeno. Prevucite nadole sa tri prsta da biste u Prostor za omiljeno sačuvali materijale poput slika, veb-stranica i datoteka. Dodirnite da biste proširili Prostor za omiljeno i pritisnite i držite jednu ili više izabranih stavki da biste ih prevlačili u druge aplikacije. Takođe možete da ih sinhronizujete sa uređajima koji podržavaju tehnologiju MagicRing da biste delili prikupljeni sadržaj na više uređaja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR dokumenta">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem isporučuje se potpuno nova aplikacija HONOR dokumenta i interaktivni interfejsovi, dodaju se prilagođene oznake, korpa za otpatke i druge funkcije, unapređuje se stabilnost i kompatibilnost dokumenata i poboljšava se korisničko iskustvo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikone na početnom ekranu">
<feature>Korisnik može u skladu sa svojim potrebama prilagoditi veličinu ikona na početnom ekranu. Putem sledeće putanje možete da promenite veličinu: Podešavanja -> Početni ekran i stil -> Podešavanja početnog ekrana -> Veličina ikone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Plejer">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem uređaju se dodaje Audio plejer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se optimizuje efekat osvetljaja i boje telefoto snimanja u nekim scenarijima.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizuje efekat slike fokusa na portretu u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Učinak">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se rešava problem nasumičnog kašnjenja kada se pokrenu neke aplikacije.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizuje problem nasumičnog pada rama kod efekta pokreta prilikom pokretanja aplikacije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se rešava problem nepravilne potrošnje energije u pojedinim situacijama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iskustvo sa zagrevanjem">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se optimizuje iskustvo zagrevanja u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem je poboljšana stabilnost sistema, zbog čega vaš uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (jul 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem se dodaje Globalno omiljeno, HONOR dokumenti i funkcija prilagođavanja veličine ikone na početnom ekranu, optimizuje efekat slike u nekim scenarijima, rešava problem nenormalne potrošnje struje u nekim scenama, poboljšava sistem učinka, stabilnosti i iskustva sa zagrevanjem i ono sadrži bezbednosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globalno omiljeno">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem uvodi se nadograđena funkcija Globalno omiljeno. Prevucite nadole sa tri prsta da biste u Prostor za omiljeno sačuvali materijale poput slika, veb-stranica i datoteka. Dodirnite da biste proširili Prostor za omiljeno i pritisnite i držite jednu ili više izabranih stavki da biste ih prevlačili u druge aplikacije. Takođe možete da ih sinhronizujete sa uređajima koji podržavaju tehnologiju MagicRing da biste delili prikupljeni sadržaj na više uređaja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR dokumenta">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem isporučuje se potpuno nova aplikacija HONOR dokumenta i interaktivni interfejsovi, dodaju se prilagođene oznake, korpa za otpatke i druge funkcije, unapređuje se stabilnost i kompatibilnost dokumenata i poboljšava se korisničko iskustvo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikone na početnom ekranu">
<feature>Korisnik može u skladu sa svojim potrebama prilagoditi veličinu ikona na početnom ekranu. Putem sledeće putanje možete da promenite veličinu: Podešavanja -> Početni ekran i stil -> Podešavanja početnog ekrana -> Veličina ikone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Plejer">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem uređaju se dodaje Audio plejer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se optimizuje efekat osvetljaja i boje telefoto snimanja u nekim scenarijima.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizuje efekat slike fokusa na portretu u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Učinak">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se rešava problem nasumičnog kašnjenja kada se pokrenu neke aplikacije.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizuje problem nasumičnog pada rama kod efekta pokreta prilikom pokretanja aplikacije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se rešava problem nepravilne potrošnje energije u pojedinim situacijama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iskustvo sa zagrevanjem">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem se optimizuje iskustvo zagrevanja u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Ovim ažuriranjem je poboljšana stabilnost sistema, zbog čega vaš uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (jul 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Za više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта рэкамендаванае абнаўленне дадае функцыі «Глабальнае абранае», «HONOR Дакументы» і функцыю змянення памеру значкоў на галоўным экране, аптымізуе эфект візуалізацыі ў некаторых сцэнарыях, выпраўляе праблему анамальнага энергаспажывання ў некаторых сцэнах, павышае прадукцыйнасць і ўстойлівасць сістэмы, памяншае праблему награвання і ўключае выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Глабальнае абранае">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне ўводзіць абноўленую функцыю «Глабальнае абранае». Хутка правядзіце трыма пальцамі ўніз, каб захаваць у Прасторы абранага матэрыялы, такія як выявы, вэб-старонкі і файлы. Краніце, каб разгарнуць Прастору абранага, націсніце і ўтрымлівайце выбраны элемент або некалькі элементаў, каб перацягнуць іх у іншыя праграмы. Таксама вы можаце сінхранізаваць іх з іншымі прыладамі MagicRing, каб абагульваць сабранае змесціва паміж прыладамі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Дакументы">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне забяспечвае цалкам новую функцыю «HONOR Дакументы» і інтэрактыўны інтэрфейс, дадае карыстальніцкія меткі, сметніцу і іншыя функцыі, паляпшае надзейнасць і сумяшчальнасць дакументаў, а таксама паляпшае ўражанні ад выкарыстання.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Значкі галоўнага экрана">
<feature>Памер значкоў галоўнага экрана можна рэгуляваць у адпаведнасці з рознымі патрэбамі карыстальнікаў. Каб паспрабаваць гэту функцыю, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады -> Галоўны экран і стыль -> Налады галоўнага экрана -> Памер значка».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Прайгравальнік">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне дадае на прыладу Прайгравальнік музыкі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне аптымізуе яркасць і колеравы эфект здымкі тэлефотакамерай у некаторых сцэнарыях.
Гэта абнаўленне аптымізуе эфект партрэтнай факусіроўкі ў некаторых сцэнарыях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Прадукцыйнасць">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне ўстараняе праблему выпадковых затрымак пры запуску некаторых праграм.
Гэта абнаўленне выпраўляе праблему выпадковага пропуску кадраў у эфекце руху падчас запуску праграм.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Энергаспажыванне">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне ўстараняе праблему анамальнага энергаспажывання ў некаторых сцэнах.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Праблема награвання">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне памяншае награванне ў некаторых сцэнарыях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сістэма">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне павышае ўстойлівасць сістэмы, што робіць працу вашай прылады больш стабільнай.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бяспека">
<feature>Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (ліпень 2024 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі HONOR можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не сатрэ вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем загадзя зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, патэлефануйце на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або звярніцеся па дапамогу ў сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази препоръчителна актуализация добавя „Глобални любими“, HONOR Документи и функцията за регулиране размера на иконите на началния екран, оптимизира ефекта на заснемане на изображенията в някои ситуации, отстранява проблема с необичайното потребление на енергия в някои сцени, подобрява производителността на системата, стабилността и загряването и включва корекция за сигурност.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Глобални любими">
<feature>С тази препоръчителна актуализация се предоставя наскоро подобреното „Глобални любими“. Плъзнете надолу с три пръста, за да запазвате материали като изображения, уеб страници и файлове в „Пространство за любими“. Докоснете за разширяване на „Пространство за любими“, натиснете и задръжте избраните един или повече елементи, за да ги плъзнете към други приложения, а можете и да ги синхронизирате с други устройства в MagicRing, за да споделяте събраното съдържание на няколко устройства.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Документи">
<feature>Тази актуализация осигурява чисто нови HONOR Документи и интерактивен интерфейс, добавя персонализирани етикети, кошче и други функции, подобрява стабилността и съвместимостта на документите и осигурява по-добро потребителско изживяване.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Икони на началния екран">
<feature>Размерът на иконите на началния екран може да бъде зададен така, че да отговаря на различните нужди на потребителите. Можете да го изпробвате, като отидете на: „Настройки -> Стил и начален екран -> Настройки на началния екран -> Размер на икона“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Плейър">
<feature>С тази актуализация се добавя „Музикален плейър“ на устройството.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Тази актуализация оптимизира ефекта на яркост и цвят при заснемане на телефото в някои ситуации.
Тази актуализация оптимизира ефекта на портретното фокусиране при някои ситуации.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Производителност">
<feature>С тази актуализация се отстранява проблемът със случайното забавяне при стартиране на някои приложения.
Тази актуализация оптимизира проблема със случайното пропускане на кадри при ефекта на движение при стартиране на приложения.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Консумация на енергия">
<feature>С тази актуализация се отстранява проблемът с необичайното потребление на енергия при някои сцени.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Загряване">
<feature>В тази актуализация е оптимизирано загряването в някои ситуации.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>С тази актуализация се подобрява стабилността на системата, за да работи устройството ви по-стабилно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Защита">
<feature>Корекцията за сигурност на Android (юли 2024 г.) е включена за защита на системата. За още информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на HONOR посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да изтрие личните ви данни, но е препоръчително архивиране преди това.
2. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализирането, обадете се на обслужващата гореща линия на HONOR или посетете сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR за поддръжка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই সুপারিশকৃত আপডেটটি গ্লোবাল ফেভারিট, HONOR Docs এবং হোম স্ক্রিনের আইকনের মাপ সামঞ্জস্যপূর্ণ করার ফাংশন যোগ করে, কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে ইমেজিং ইফেক্টকে অপটিমাইজ করে, কিছু দৃশ্যে অস্বাভাবিক শক্তি খরচের সমস্যা সমাধান করে, সিস্টেমের কর্মক্ষমতা, স্থিতিশীলতা এবং গরম হওয়ার অভিজ্ঞতা উন্নত করে এবং একটি নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ অন্তর্ভুক্ত করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গ্লোবাল ফেভারিট">
<feature>এই আপডেটটি নতুন আপগ্রেড করা গ্লোবাল ফেভারিট নিয়ে আসে। ছবি, ওয়েব পেজ ও ফাইলের মতো জিনিসগুলি ফেভারিট স্পেসে সংরক্ষণ করতে তিনটি আঙুল দিয়ে নিচের দিকে সোয়াইপ করুন। ফেভারিট স্পেস প্রসারিত করতে ট্যাপ করুন, নির্বাচিত এক বা একাধিক আইটেমকে অন্যান্য অ্যাপে টেনে সেগুলি চাপুন এবং ধরে রাখুন, এবং সংগৃহীত কন্টেন্ট বিভিন্ন ডিভাইস জুড়ে শেয়ার করতে আপনি সেগুলিকে অন্যান্য MagicRing ডিভাইসের সাথে সিঙ্ক করতে পারেন।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>এই আপডেটটি একেবারে নতুন HONOR Docs এবং ইন্টারেক্টিভ ইন্টারফেস প্রদান করে, কাস্টম লেবেল যোগ করে, রিসাইকেল বিন এবং অন্যান্য ফাংশন যোগ করে, নথির স্থায়িত্ব এবং সামঞ্জস্য উন্নত করে এবং আরও ভালো ব্যবহারকারীর অভিজ্ঞতা প্রদান করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="হোম স্ক্রিন আইকন">
<feature>ব্যবহারকারীদের বিভিন্ন প্রয়োজন মেটাতে হোম স্ক্রিন আইকনগুলির আকার সামঞ্জস্যপূর্ণ করা যেতে পারে। আপনি এখানে গিয়ে এটি অনুভব করতে পারেন: সেটিংস -> হোম স্ক্রিন এবং স্টাইল -> হোম স্ক্রিন সেটিংস -> আইকনের আকার।</feature>
</features>
<features module="প্লেয়ার">
<feature>এই আপডেটটি ডিভাইসে মিউজিক প্লেয়ার যোগ করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ক্যামেরা">
<feature>এই আপডেটটি কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে টেলিফটো শুটিং-এর উজ্জ্বলতা এবং রঙের ইফেক্টকে অপটিমাইজ করে।
এই আপডেটটি কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে পোর্ট্রেট ফোকাস ইমেজিং ইফেক্টকে অপটিমাইজ করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="কর্মক্ষমতা">
<feature>এই আপডেটটি কিছু অ্যাপ চালু করার সময় এলোপাথাড়ি পিছিয়ে পড়ার সমস্যা সমাধান করে।
এই আপডেটটি অ্যাপ শুরু হওয়ার মোশন ইফেক্টে এলোপাথাড়ি ফ্রেম ড্রপের সমস্যাকে অপটিমাইজ করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="শক্তি খরচ">
<feature>এই আপডেটটি কিছু দৃশ্যে অস্বাভাবিক শক্তি খরচের সমস্যা সমাধান করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গরম হওয়ার অভিজ্ঞতা">
<feature>এই আপডেট কিছু ক্ষেত্রে গরম হওয়ার অভিজ্ঞতাকে অপটিমাইজ করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="সিস্টেম">
<feature>আপনার ডিভাইসকে আরও স্থিতিশীলভাবে চালানোর জন্য, এই আপডেটটি সিস্টেমের স্থিতিশীলতাকে আরও উন্নত করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিরাপত্তা">
<feature>সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (জুলাই 2024) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। HONOR-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, অনুগ্রহ করে আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="দ্রষ্টব্য:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটা মুছে যাবে না, তবে তা সত্ত্বেও আগে থেকে ব্যাকআপ নেওয়ার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. আপনি যদি আপডেটের সময় কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হন তাহলে অনুগ্রহ করে HONOR সার্ভিস হটলাইনে কল করুন বা সহায়তার জন্য HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে যান।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱོན་ཡོངས་བསྡུ་ཉར་དང་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཡིག་ཚགས། ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས་ཆེ་ཆུང་སྙོམ་སྒྲིག་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་པར་ཆས་ཀྱི་པར་ལེན་བརྙན་འགྲུབ་ཁྱད་ནུས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་གློག་ཟད་རྒྱུན་ལྡན་མིན་པའི་གནད་དོན་ཉམས་གསོ་བྱས་ཡོད། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་གཤིས་ནུས་དང་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན། ཚ་བའི་ཉམས་ལེན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད། བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདུས་གྲུབ་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【ཁྱོན་ཡོངས་བསྡུ་ཉར།】">
<feature>ཁྱོན་ཡོངས་བསྡུ་ཉར་ཡོངས་སུ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། མཛུག་གསུམ་ཐུར་དེད་ན་པར་རིས་དང་དྲ་ངོས། ཡིག་ཆ་སོགས་ཀྱི་མ་རྒྱུ་བསྡུ་ཉར་བར་སྟོང་དུ་མགྱོགས་མྱུར་ཉར་ཚགས་བྱ་ཆོག བརྡབས་ནས་བསྡུ་ཉར་བར་སྟོང་སྤེལ། བདམས་པའི་ནང་དོན་རྐྱང་བའམ་མང་པོར་ཡུན་རིང་གནོན་ན་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་གཞན་པར་འདྲུད་འཐེན་བྱས་ནས་བེད་སྤྱོད་ཆོག ཡིད་རྟོན་ཨ་ལོང་ཁྲོད་ཀྱི་སྒྲིག་ཆས་གཞན་པ་རུ་གོམ་མཉམ་བྱས་ནས་སྒྲིག་ཆས་བརྒལ་ནས་བསྡུ་ཉར་ནང་དོན་མཉམ་སྤྱོད་བྱ་ཆོག</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རུང་ཡོའོ་ཡིག་ཚགས།】">
<feature>གསར་རྐྱང་གི་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཡིག་ཚགས། གསར་རྐྱང་གི་སྤེལ་རེས་མཚམས་ངོས། རང་སྒྲིག་གི་རྟགས་བྱང་སྣོན་པ། སྙིགས་སྒམ་རྩོལ་ནུས། ཡིག་ཚགས་ཀྱི་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་དང་མཐུན་འགྲིག་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ནས། དེ་བས་སྣ་མང་གི་བེད་སྤྱོད་ཉམས་ལེན་མཁོ་འདོན་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས།】">
<feature>ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས་ཆེ་ཆུང་སྙོམ་སྒྲིག་བྱེད་པར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད། སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་རིས་རྟགས་ཆེ་ཆུང་མི་འདྲ་བའི་མངོན་སྟོན་དགོས་མཁོ་སོང་། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་ཅོག་ངོས་དང་སྒེར་གཤིས་ཅན། ཅོག་ངོས་སྒྲིག་འགོད། དེ་ནས་རིས་རྟགས་ཆེ་ཆུང་།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【གཏོང་ཆས།】">
<feature>རང་གནས་ཀྱི་རོལ་དབྱངས་གཏོང་ཆས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【པར་ཆས།】">
<feature>བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་འོག་ཏུ་མདོ་རིང་གི་པར་ལེན་གསལ་ཚད་དང་ཁ་དོག་ཁྱད་ནུས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད།
བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་འོག་གི་མིའི་གཟུགས་མདོ་སྒྲིག་དང་བརྙན་འགྲུབ་ཁྱད་ནུས་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【གཤིས་ནུས།】">
<feature>ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཁག་ཅིག་འགོ་སློང་སྐབས་སྲིད་ཕྱོད་ཅན་གྱི་ཐོགས་པའི་གནད་དོན་ཉམས་གསོ་བྱས་ཡོད།
ཉེར་སྤྱོད་འགོ་སློང་བའི་འགུལ་རྣམ་ཁྱད་ནུས་ཀྱི་སྲིད་ཕྱོད་ཅན་གྱི་བརྙན་པར་བོར་བའི་གནད་དོན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【ནུས་རྩོལ།】">
<feature>བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་གློག་ཟད་རྒྱུན་ལྡན་མིན་པའི་གནད་དོན་ཉམས་གསོ་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【ཚ་བའི་ཉམས་ལེན།】">
<feature>བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་ཚ་བའི་ཉམས་ལེན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བྱས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རྒྱུད་ཁོངས།】">
<feature>རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་འཁོར་སྐྱོད་བྱས་པ་སྔར་བས་བརྟན་འཇགས་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【བདེ་འཇགས།】">
<feature>ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2024 ལོའི་ཟླ་ 7 པའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་བསྡེབས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་ཇེ་བཟང་དུ་གཏོང་བ། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་ལ། རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས་ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/7 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་གསར་སྒྱུར་མ་བྱས་གོང་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ཡག་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་ལ་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ་ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་སྐུ་མགྲོན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་སོང་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་རེ་ཞུ་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje dodaje Globalne favorite, HONOR dokumente i funkciju prilagođavanja veličine ikona na početnom ekranu, optimizira efekat slika u određenim scenarijima, rješava problem neuobičajene potrošnje energije u određenim scenama, poboljšava performanse i stabilnost sistema te iskustvo sa zagrijavanjem i ugrađuje sigurnosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globalni favoriti">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje donosi nedavno nadograđene Globalne favorite. Prevucite trima prstima prema dolje da sačuvate materijale kao što su slike, web stranice i datoteke u Prostor za favorite. Dodirnite Prostor za favorite da ga raširite pa pritisnite i držite jednu ili više odabranih stavki da ih povučete u druge aplikacije. Možete ih i sinhronizirati s drugim MagicRing uređajima da dijelite prikupljeni sadržaj na svim uređajima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR dokumenti">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje pruža potpuno nove HONOR dokumente i interaktivni interfejs, dodaje prilagođene oznake, korpu za otpatke i druge funkcije, poboljšava stabilnost i kompatibilnost dokumenata te pruža bolje korisničko iskustvo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikone početnog ekrana">
<feature>Veličina ikona na početnom ekranu se može prilagoditi u skladu s različitim potrebama korisnika. Funkciju možete isprobati odlaskom u Postavke -> Početni ekran i stil -> Postavke početnog ekrana -> Veličina ikona.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Plejer">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje dodaje Muzički plejer na uređaj.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparat">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje optimizira efekat osvjetljenja i boje telefoto snimanja u određenim scenarijima.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizira efekat fokusiranja portretnih slika u određenim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performanse">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje rješava problem nasumičnog kašnjenja prilikom pokretanja određenih aplikacija.
Ovo ažuriranje optimizira problem nasumičnog gubljenja kadra u efektu kretanja prilikom pokretanja aplikacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje rješava problem neuobičajene potrošnje energije u određenim scenama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iskustvo sa zagrijavanjem">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje optimizira iskustvo sa zagrijavanjem u određenim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje poboljšava stabilnost sistema kako bi se omogućio stabilniji rad uređaja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (juli 2024) radi sigurnosti sistema. Više informacija o HONOR sigurnosnim ažuriranjima potražite na našoj web lokaciji https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja se neće izbrisati lični podaci, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització recomanada afegeix Preferits globals, Documents HONOR i la funció d'ajustar la mida de la icona de la pantalla inicial, optimitza l'efecte d'imatge en determinades situacions, soluciona el problema del consum d'energia anormal en algunes situacions, millora el rendiment del sistema, l'estabilitat i la sensació d'escalfament i incorpora un pedaç de seguretat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Preferits globals">
<feature>Aquesta actualització incorpora Preferits globals millorats recentment. Feu lliscar amb tres dits cap avall per desar contingut, com ara imatges, pàgines web i fitxers a l'Espai de Preferits. Toqueu per ampliar l'Espai de Preferits, manteniu premut l'element seleccionat o diversos elements per arrossegar-los a altres aplicacions, i també podeu sincronitzar-los amb altres dispositius MagicRing per compartir el contingut recopilat entre dispositius.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Documents HONOR">
<feature>Aquesta actualització ofereix Documents HONOR i una interfície interactiva totalment nova, afegeix etiquetes personalitzades, paperera de reciclatge i altres funcions, millora l'estabilitat i compatibilitat dels documents i proporciona una millor experiència d'usuari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Icones de la pantalla inicial">
<feature>La mida de les icones de la pantalla inicial pot ajustar-se per satisfer les diferents necessitats dels usuaris. Per provar-ho, aneu a: Configuració -> Pantalla inicial i estil -> Configuració de la pantalla inicial -> Mida de la icona.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Reproductor">
<feature>Aquesta actualització afegeix el Reproductor de música al dispositiu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Càmera">
<feature>Aquesta actualització optimitza la brillantor i l'efecte del color de la fotografia amb teleobjectiu en determinades situacions.
Aquesta actualització optimitza l'efecte d'imatge de l'enfocament del retrat en algunes situacions.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendiment">
<feature>Aquesta actualització soluciona el problema del retard aleatori en iniciar algunes aplicacions.
Aquesta actualització optimitza el problema de les caigudes de fotogrames aleatòries en l'efecte de moviment en iniciar una aplicació.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consum d'energia">
<feature>Aquesta actualització soluciona el problema del consum d'energia anormal en determinades situacions.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sensació d'escalfament">
<feature>Aquesta actualització optimitza la sensació d'escalfament en determinades situacions.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Aquesta actualització millora l'estabilitat del sistema, la qual cosa permet que el funcionament del dispositiu sigui més estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguretat">
<feature>S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (juliol del 2024) per a la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'HONOR, consulteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Si instal·leu aquesta actualització, les dades personals no s'esborraran, però us recomanem que en feu una còpia de seguretat.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o aneu al centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR per demanar assistència.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený uživateli, tato doporučená aktualizace přidává Globální oblíbené, HONOR Dokumenty a funkci úpravy velikosti ikony domovské obrazovky, optimalizuje obrazový efekt v některých situacích, opravuje problém neobvyklé spotřeby energie v některých případech, zlepšuje výkon systému, stabilitu a zahřívání, a instaluje bezpečnostní opravu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globální oblíbené">
<feature>Tato aktualizace přináší nově upgradované Globální oblíbené. Přejetím třemi prsty dolů uložíte materiály, jako jsou obrázky, webové stránky a soubory, do Prostoru oblíbených. Klepnutím rozbalte Prostor oblíbených, stiskněte a podržte vybranou jednu nebo více položek, abyste je přetáhli do jiných aplikací, a také je můžete synchronizovat s jinými zařízeními MagicRing a sdílet shromážděný obsah mezi zařízeními.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Dokumenty">
<feature>Tato aktualizace poskytuje zcela nové HONOR Dokumenty a interaktivní rozhraní, přidává vlastní štítky, odpadkový koš a další funkce, zlepšuje stabilitu a kompatibilitu dokumentů a poskytuje lepší uživatelské prostředí.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikony domovské obrazovky">
<feature>Velikost ikon na domovské obrazovce lze upravit tak, aby vyhovovala různým potřebám uživatelů. Můžete si to vyzkoušet tak, že přejdete na: Nastavení -> Domovská obrazovka a styl -> Nastavení domovské obrazovky -> Velikost ikony.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Přehrávač">
<feature>Tato aktualizace přidává do zařízení Přehrávač hudby.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparát">
<feature>Tato aktualizace optimalizuje jas a barevný efekt při fotografování teleobjektivem v některých scénách.
Tato aktualizace v některých scénách optimalizuje efekt zaostření na výšku.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Výkonnost">
<feature>Tato aktualizace opravuje problém náhodného zpoždění při spouštění některých aplikací.
Tato aktualizace optimalizuje problém náhodných vypuštěných snímků v pohybovém efektu při spuštění aplikace.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Spotřeba energie">
<feature>Tato aktualizace opravuje problém neobvyklé spotřeby energie v některých situacích.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zahřívání">
<feature>Tato aktualizace snižuje zahřívání zařízení v některých situacích.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Tato aktualizace vylepšuje stabilitu systému, aby zařízení pracovalo stabilněji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezpečnost">
<feature>Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (červenec 2024) pro systém Android zajišťující bezpečnost systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích HONOR najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalací této aktualizace nebudou vymazány vaše osobní údaje, ale přesto se doporučuje je předem zálohovat.
2. Pokud se během aktualizace setkáte s nějakými problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo si vyžádejte podporu v Centru služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger, denne anbefalede opdatering tilføjer Globale favoritter, HONOR Docs og funktionen med at justere ikonstørrelsen på startskærmen, optimerer billedeffekten i nogle scenarier, løser problemet med unormalt strømforbrug i visse scener, forbedrer systemets ydeevne, stabilitet og varmeoplevelse samt inkorporerer en sikkerhedsrettelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globale favoritter">
<feature>Denne opdatering tilføjer nyligt opgraderede Globale favoritter. Stryg nedad med tre fingre for at gemme materialer, såsom billeder, websider og filer, til Favorites Space. Tryk for at udvide Favorites Space, tryk på og hold det valgte element eller flere elementer for at trække dem til andre apps, og du kan også synkronisere dem til andre MagicRing-enheder for at dele indsamlet indhold på tværs af enheder.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Denne opdatering giver helt nye HONOR Docs og interaktiv brugerflade, tilføjer brugerdefinerede etiketter, papirkurv og andre funktioner, forbedrer dokumentstabilitet og kompatibilitet og giver en bedre brugeroplevelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikoner på startskærmen">
<feature>Ikonstørrelse på startskærmen kan justeres til at imødekomme brugernes forskellige behov. Du kan opleve det ved at gå til: Indstillinger -> Startskærm og stil -> Indstillinger for startskærm -> Ikonstørrelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Afspiller">
<feature>Denne opdatering tilføjer Musikafspiller på enheden.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Denne opdatering optimerer lysstyrken og farveeffekten på telefotooptagelser i nogle scenarier.
Denne opdatering optimerer billedeffekten med portrætfokus i nogle scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ydeevne">
<feature>Denne opdatering løser problemet med tilfældig lagging, når nogle apps startes.
Denne opdatering optimerer problemet med tilfældig lav FPS for bevægelseseffekten ved app-opstart.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Strømforbrug">
<feature>Denne opdatering løser problemet med unormalt strømforbrug i visse scener.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varmeoplevelse">
<feature>Denne opdatering optimerer varmeoplevelsen i nogle scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Denne opdatering forbedrer systemstabiliteten for at få din enhed til at køre mere stabilt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhed">
<feature>Android sikkerhedsrettelse (juli 2024) er blevet integreret for øget systemsikkerhed. For yderligere oplysninger om HONOR-sikkerhedsopdateringer kan du besøge vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering sletter ikke dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadigvæk at tage en sikkerhedskopi på forhånd.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du ringe til HONORs service-hotline eller gå til HONOR kundeservicecenter for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung fügt Globale Favoriten, HONOR Dokumente und die Funktion zum Anpassen der Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm hinzu, optimiert den Bildeffekt in einigen Szenarien, behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenen, verbessert die Systemleistung und -stabilität sowie das Erwärmungserlebnis und umfasst einen Sicherheitspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globale Favoriten">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung bietet neu aktualisierte Globale Favoriten. Streichen Sie mit drei Fingern nach unten, um Materialien wie Bilder, Webseiten und Dateien im Favoritenbereich zu speichern. Tippen Sie, um den Favoritenbereich zu erweitern, und halten Sie ein oder mehrere ausgewählte Elemente gedrückt, um sie in andere Apps zu ziehen. Sie können sie auch mit anderen MagicRing-Geräten synchronisieren, um erfasste Inhalte geräteübergreifend zu teilen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Dokumente">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung umfasst das brandneue HONOR Dokumente und eine interaktive Schnittstelle, fügt benutzerdefinierte Beschriftungen, einen Papierkorb und andere Funktionen hinzu, verbessert die Dokumentstabilität und -kompatibilität und bietet ein besseres Benutzererlebnis.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm">
<feature>Die Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm kann an die unterschiedlichen Bedürfnisse der Nutzer angepasst werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Einstellungen -> Startbildschirm und Stil -> Startbildschirmeinstellungen -> Symbolgröße.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Player">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung fügt Musik Player auf dem Gerät hinzu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung optimiert in einigen Szenarien die Helligkeit und Farbwirkung von Aufnahmen mit dem Teleobjektiv.
Diese Aktualisierung optimiert den Porträtfokus-Bildeffekt in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Leistung">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung behebt das Problem zufälliger Verzögerungen beim Starten einiger Apps.
Diese Aktualisierung optimiert das Problem zufälliger Framedrops im Bewegungseffekt beim App-Start.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stromverbrauch">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Erwärmungserlebnis">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung optimiert das Erwärmungserlebnis in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung verbessert die Systemstabilität, damit Ihr Gerät stabiler läuft.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Juli 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Durch die Installation dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch trotzdem empfohlen, im Vorfeld eine Datensicherung vorzunehmen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung fügt Globale Favoriten, HONOR Dokumente und die Funktion zum Anpassen der Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm hinzu, optimiert den Bildeffekt in einigen Szenarien, behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenen, verbessert die Systemleistung und -stabilität sowie das Erwärmungserlebnis und umfasst einen Sicherheitspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globale Favoriten">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung bietet neu aktualisierte Globale Favoriten. Streichen Sie mit drei Fingern nach unten, um Materialien wie Bilder, Webseiten und Dateien im Favoritenbereich zu speichern. Tippen Sie, um den Favoritenbereich zu erweitern, und halten Sie ein oder mehrere ausgewählte Elemente gedrückt, um sie in andere Apps zu ziehen. Sie können sie auch mit anderen MagicRing-Geräten synchronisieren, um erfasste Inhalte geräteübergreifend zu teilen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Dokumente">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung umfasst das brandneue HONOR Dokumente und eine interaktive Schnittstelle, fügt benutzerdefinierte Beschriftungen, einen Papierkorb und andere Funktionen hinzu, verbessert die Dokumentstabilität und -kompatibilität und bietet ein besseres Benutzererlebnis.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm">
<feature>Die Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm kann an die unterschiedlichen Bedürfnisse der Nutzer angepasst werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Einstellungen -> Startbildschirm und Stil -> Startbildschirmeinstellungen -> Symbolgröße.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Player">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung fügt Musik Player auf dem Gerät hinzu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung optimiert in einigen Szenarien die Helligkeit und Farbwirkung von Aufnahmen mit dem Teleobjektiv.
Diese Aktualisierung optimiert den Porträtfokus-Bildeffekt in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Leistung">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung behebt das Problem zufälliger Verzögerungen beim Starten einiger Apps.
Diese Aktualisierung optimiert das Problem zufälliger Framedrops im Bewegungseffekt beim App-Start.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stromverbrauch">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Erwärmungserlebnis">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung optimiert das Erwärmungserlebnis in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung verbessert die Systemstabilität, damit Ihr Gerät stabiler läuft.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Juli 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Durch die Installation dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch trotzdem empfohlen, im Vorfeld eine Datensicherung vorzunehmen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung fügt Globale Favoriten, HONOR Dokumente und die Funktion zum Anpassen der Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm hinzu, optimiert den Bildeffekt in einigen Szenarien, behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenen, verbessert die Systemleistung und -stabilität sowie das Erwärmungserlebnis und umfasst einen Sicherheitspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globale Favoriten">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung bietet neu aktualisierte Globale Favoriten. Streichen Sie mit drei Fingern nach unten, um Materialien wie Bilder, Webseiten und Dateien im Favoritenbereich zu speichern. Tippen Sie, um den Favoritenbereich zu erweitern, und halten Sie ein oder mehrere ausgewählte Elemente gedrückt, um sie in andere Apps zu ziehen. Sie können sie auch mit anderen MagicRing-Geräten synchronisieren, um erfasste Inhalte geräteübergreifend zu teilen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Dokumente">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung umfasst das brandneue HONOR Dokumente und eine interaktive Schnittstelle, fügt benutzerdefinierte Beschriftungen, einen Papierkorb und andere Funktionen hinzu, verbessert die Dokumentstabilität und -kompatibilität und bietet ein besseres Benutzererlebnis.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm">
<feature>Die Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm kann an die unterschiedlichen Bedürfnisse der Nutzer angepasst werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Einstellungen -> Startbildschirm und Stil -> Startbildschirmeinstellungen -> Symbolgröße.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Player">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung fügt Musik Player auf dem Gerät hinzu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung optimiert in einigen Szenarien die Helligkeit und Farbwirkung von Aufnahmen mit dem Teleobjektiv.
Diese Aktualisierung optimiert den Porträtfokus-Bildeffekt in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Leistung">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung behebt das Problem zufälliger Verzögerungen beim Starten einiger Apps.
Diese Aktualisierung optimiert das Problem zufälliger Framedrops im Bewegungseffekt beim App-Start.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stromverbrauch">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Erwärmungserlebnis">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung optimiert das Erwärmungserlebnis in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Diese Aktualisierung verbessert die Systemstabilität, damit Ihr Gerät stabiler läuft.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Juli 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Durch die Installation dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch trotzdem empfohlen, im Vorfeld eine Datensicherung vorzunehmen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η προτεινόμενη ενημέρωση προσθέτει την εφαρμογή «Όλα τα αγαπημένα», τα Έγγραφα HONOR και τη λειτουργία προσαρμογής μεγέθους του εικονιδίου αρχικής οθόνης, βελτιστοποιεί το αποτέλεσμα απεικόνισης σε ορισμένα σενάρια, διορθώνει το πρόβλημα μη φυσιολογικής κατανάλωσης ενέργειας σε ορισμένες σκηνές, βελτιώνει την εμπειρία απόδοσης, σταθερότητας και θέρμανσης του συστήματος και ενσωματώνει μια ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Όλα τα αγαπημένα">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση φέρνει την πρόσφατα αναβαθμισμένη εφαρμογή «Όλα τα αγαπημένα». Σύρετε προς τα κάτω με τρία δάχτυλα για να αποθηκεύσετε το υλικό, όπως εικόνες, ιστοσελίδες και αρχεία, στον Χώρο αγαπημένων. Πατήστε για να αναπτύξετε τον Χώρο αγαπημένων, πατήστε παρατεταμένα το επιλεγμένο στοιχείο ή πολλά στοιχεία για να τα σύρετε σε άλλες εφαρμογές και μπορείτε επίσης να τα συγχρονίσετε με άλλες συσκευές MagicRing για να πραγματοποιήσετε κοινή χρήση του περιεχομένου που έχετε συλλέξει μεταξύ συσκευών.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Έγγραφα HONOR">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση παρέχει τα ολοκαίνουργια Έγγραφα HONOR και διαδραστικό περιβάλλον εργασίας, προσθέτει τις προσαρμοσμένες ετικέτες, τον κάδο ανακύκλωσης και άλλες λειτουργίες, βελτιώνει τη σταθερότητα και τη συμβατότητα των εγγράφων και παρέχει καλύτερη εμπειρία χρήστη.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Εικονίδια αρχικής οθόνης">
<feature>Το μέγεθος των εικονιδίων της αρχικής οθόνης μπορεί να προσαρμοστεί για να ανταποκρίνεται στις διαφορετικές ανάγκες των χρηστών. Μπορείτε να δοκιμάσετε αυτή τη λειτουργία μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις -> Αρχική οθόνη και στυλ -> Ρυθμίσεις αρχικής οθόνης -> Μέγεθος εικονιδίου.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Πρόγραμμα αναπαραγωγής">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση προσθέτει το Πρόγραμμα αναπαραγωγής μουσικής στη συσκευή.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Κάμερα">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιστοποιεί τη φωτεινότητα και την ποιότητα χρωμάτων της λήψης με τηλεφακό σε ορισμένα σενάρια.
Αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιστοποιεί το αποτέλεσμα απεικόνισης εστίασης σε κατακόρυφη προβολή σε ορισμένα σενάρια.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Επιδόσεις">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση διορθώνει το πρόβλημα της τυχαίας καθυστέρησης κατά την εκκίνηση ορισμένων εφαρμογών.
Αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιστοποιεί το πρόβλημα των τυχαίων μειώσεων καρέ στο εφέ κίνησης της εκκίνησης εφαρμογών.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Κατανάλωση ενέργειας">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση διορθώνει το πρόβλημα της μη φυσιολογικής κατανάλωσης ενέργειας σε ορισμένες σκηνές.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Εμπειρία θέρμανσης">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιστοποιεί την εμπειρία θέρμανσης σε ορισμένα σενάρια.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σύστημα">
<feature>Αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιώνει τη σταθερότητα του συστήματος για να λειτουργεί η συσκευή σας πιο σταθερά.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ασφάλεια">
<feature>Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Ιούλιος 2024) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας HONOR, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα διαγράψει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, ωστόσο συνιστάται προηγουμένως η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας.
2. Εάν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, καλέστε την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή της HONOR ή μεταβείτε στο κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR για υποστήριξη.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update adds Global Favourites, HONOR Docs and the function of adjusting home screen icon size, optimises the imaging effect in some scenarios, fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenes, improves the system performance, stability and heating experience, and incorporates a security patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Global Favorites">
<feature>This update brings newly upgraded Global Favorites. Swipe down with three fingers to save materials, such as images, web pages and files, to Favorites Space. Tap to expand Favorites Space, press and hold the selected one or multiple items to drag them to other apps, and you can also sync them to other MagicRing devices to share collected content across devices.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>This update provides brand-new HONOR Docs and interactive interface, adds custom labels, recycle bin and other functions, improves document stability and compatibility, and provides a better user experience.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Home screen icons">
<feature>The size of Home screen icons can be adjusted to meet the users' different needs. You can experience it by going to: Settings -> Home screen and style -> Home screen settings -> Icon size.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Player">
<feature>This update adds Music Player on device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>This update optimises the brightness and colour effect of telephoto shooting in some scenarios.
This update optimises the portrait focus imaging effect in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performance">
<feature>This update fixes the problem of random lagging when launching some apps.
This update optimises the problem of random frame drops in app startup motion effect.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Power consumption">
<feature>This update fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenes.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Heating experience">
<feature>This update optimises the heating experience in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>This update improves the system stability to make your device run more stably.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android Security Patch (July 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service centre for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, esta actualización recomendada añade Favoritos, Documentos de HONOR y la función de ajustar el tamaño de los iconos de la pantalla principal, optimiza el efecto de imagen en algunos escenarios, soluciona el problema del consumo anormal de energía en algunos casos, mejora el rendimiento del sistema, la estabilidad y la experiencia de calentamiento e incorpora un parche de seguridad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favoritos">
<feature>Esta actualización incluye una actualización reciente de Favoritos. Deslice tres dedos hacia abajo para guardar materiales, como imágenes, páginas web y archivos, en el Espacio de Favoritos. Toque para expandir el Espacio de Favoritos, mantenga pulsado uno o varios elementos seleccionados para arrastrarlos a otras aplicaciones, y también puede sincronizarlos con otros dispositivos MagicRing para compartir el contenido recopilado entre dispositivos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Documentos de HONOR">
<feature>Esta actualización proporciona la nueva funcionalidad Documentos de HONOR y una interfaz interactiva, agrega etiquetas personalizadas, papelera de reciclaje y otras funcionalidades, mejora la estabilidad y compatibilidad de los documentos y brinda una mejor experiencia de usuario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iconos de la pantalla principal">
<feature>El tamaño de los iconos de la pantalla principal se puede ajustar para satisfacer las diferentes necesidades de los usuarios. Puede experimentarlo si va a: Ajustes -> Pantalla principal y estilo -> Ajustes pantalla principal -> Tamaño de icono.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Reproductor">
<feature>Esta actualización añade un reproductor de música al dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>Esta actualización optimiza el brillo y el efecto de color de las fotos con teleobjetivo en algunos escenarios.
Esta actualización optimiza el efecto de imagen de enfoque de retrato en algunos escenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendimiento">
<feature>Esta actualización soluciona el problema del retraso aleatorio al iniciar algunas aplicaciones.
Esta actualización optimiza el problema de las caídas aleatorias de fotogramas en el efecto de movimiento de inicio de la aplicación.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de energía">
<feature>Esta actualización soluciona el problema del consumo de energía anormal en algunas escenas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Experiencia de calentamiento">
<feature>Esta actualización optimiza la experiencia de calentamiento en algunos escenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Esta actualización mejora la estabilidad del sistema para que el dispositivo funcione de manera más estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (julio de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Aunque la instalación de esta actualización no eliminará sus datos personales, se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad antes.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para obtener ayuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario: esta actualización recomendada agrega Favoritos globales, HONOR Docs y la función de ajustar el tamaño de los íconos de la pantalla principal, optimiza el efecto de imagen en algunos escenarios, soluciona el problema del consumo de energía anormal en algunas escenas, mejora el rendimiento del sistema, la estabilidad y la experiencia de calentamiento, y se incorpora un parche de seguridad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favoritos globales">
<feature>Esta actualización incluye una actualización reciente de Favoritos globales. Desliza tres dedos hacia abajo para guardar materiales, como imágenes, páginas web y archivos, en el Espacio favoritos. Toque para expandir el Espacio favoritos, mantenga presionado uno o varios elementos seleccionados para arrastrarlos a otras aplicaciones, y también puede sincronizarlos con otros dispositivos MagicRing para compartir el contenido recopilado entre dispositivos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Esta actualización proporciona la nueva aplicación HONOR Docs y una interfaz interactiva, agrega etiquetas personalizadas, papelera de reciclaje y otras funciones, mejora la estabilidad y compatibilidad de los documentos y brinda una mejor experiencia de usuario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Íconos de la pantalla principal">
<feature>El tamaño de los íconos de la pantalla principal se puede ajustar para satisfacer las diferentes necesidades de los usuarios. Para realizar este cambio, vaya a Ajustes -> Pantalla principal y estilo -> Ajustes de pantalla principal -> Tamaño de ícono.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Reproductor">
<feature>Esta actualización agrega un Reproductor de música en el dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>Esta actualización optimiza el brillo y el efecto de color de la toma con teleobjetivo en algunos escenarios.
Esta actualización optimiza el efecto de imagen de enfoque vertical en algunos escenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendimiento">
<feature>Esta actualización soluciona el problema del retraso aleatorio al iniciar algunas aplicaciones.
Esta actualización optimiza el problema de las caídas aleatorias de fotogramas en el efecto de movimiento de inicio de la aplicación.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de energía">
<feature>Esta actualización soluciona el problema del consumo de energía anormal en algunas escenas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Experiencia de calentamiento">
<feature>Esta actualización optimiza la experiencia de calentamiento en algunos escenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Esta actualización mejora la estabilidad del sistema para hacer que el dispositivo funcione de manera más estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (julio de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Esta actualización no eliminará sus datos personales; sin embargo, le recomendamos hacer una copia de respaldo de los datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visite el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja! See soovitatav värskendus lisab globaalsed lemmikud, HONORi dokumendid ja avakuva ikoonide suuruse kohandamise funktsiooni, optimeerib mõnes olukorras pildiefekti, lahendab mõnes olukorras ebanormaalse energiatarbimise probleemi, parandab süsteemi tööd ja stabiilsust, vähendab kuumaks minemise esinemist ning sisaldab turvapaika.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globaalsed lemmikud">
<feature>See värskendus uuendab globaalseid lemmikuid. Materjalide, nagu piltide, veebilehtede ja failide salvestamiseks lemmikute ruumi nipsake kolme sõrmega alla. Puudutage, et laiendada lemmikute ruumi, vajutage pikalt ühte või mitut valitud üksust, et lohistada need teistesse rakendustesse, samuti saate need teiste MagicRingi seadmetega sünkroonida, et jagada kogutud sisu seadmete vahel.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONORi dokumendid">
<feature>See värskendus sisaldab uhiuut HONORi dokumente ja interaktiivset liidest, lisab kohandatud sildid, prügikasti ja muud funktsioonid, parandab dokumentide stabiilsust ja ühilduvust ning võimaldab paremat kasutajakogemust.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Avakuva ikoonid">
<feature>Avakuva ikoonide suurust saab kohandada vastavalt kasutajate vajadustele. Selle funktsiooni kasutamiseks avage Sätted -> Avakuva ja stiil -> Avakuva sätted -> Ikooni suurus.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mängija">
<feature>See värskendus lisab seadmesse muusikamängija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kaamera">
<feature>See värskendus optimeerib mõnes olukorras telefoto jäädvustamisel heleduse ja värviefekti.
See värskendus optimeerib mõnes olukorras portreefookuse pildiefekti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Jõudlus">
<feature>See värskendus parandab mõne rakenduse käivitamisel esineva juhusliku pika reaktsiooniaja probleemi.
See värskendus optimeerib juhusliku kaadri kustutamise probleemi rakenduse käivitamisel liikumisefektis.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energiakulu">
<feature>See värskendus lahendab mõnes olukorras ebanormaalse energiatarbimise probleemi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kuumaks minemise esinemine">
<feature>See värskendus optimeerib mõnes olukorras kuumaks minemise esinemist.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Süsteem">
<feature>See värskendus parandab süsteemi stabiilsust ja muudab seadme töö stabiilsemaks.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvalisus">
<feature>Lisati süsteemi turvalisemaks muutev Androidi turvapaik (juuli 2024). Lisateavet HONORi turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei kustuta teie isikuandmeid, kuid eelnev varundamine on siiski soovitatav.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, helistage HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või minge toe saamiseks HONORi klienditeeninduskeskusesse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile agurgarria, gomendatutako eguneratze honetan, Gogoko orokorrak, HONOR Docs eta hasierako pantailako ikonoaren tamaina doitzeko funtzioa gehitu dira, optimizatu egin da agertoki batzuetako irudi-efektua, egoera batzuetan bateriaren kontsumo anormalaren arazoa konpondu da, sistemaren errendimendua, egonkortasuna eta beroketa-esperientzia hobetu dira, eta segurtasun-adabaki bat gehitu da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gogoko orokorrak">
<feature>Eguneratze honetan duela gutxi bertsio-berritutako Gogoko orokorrak gehitu dira. Irristatu hiru hatz behera materialak Gogokoen gunean gordetzeko, hala nola irudiak, web-orria eta fitxategiak. Sakatu Gogokoen gunea zabaltzeko, eduki sakatuta hautatutako elementu bat edo hainbat elementu beste aplikazio batzuetara arrastatzeko, eta beste MagicRing gailu batzuetara ere sinkroniza ditzakezu gailuetan bildutako edukia partekatzeko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Eguneratze honek HONOR Docs eta interfaze interaktibo guztiz berriak dakartza, eta, gainera, etiketa pertsonalizatuak gehitu dira, bai zakarrontzia eta beste funtzio batzuk ere, dokumentuen egonkortasuna eta bateragarritasuna hobetzen ditu eta erabiltzaile-esperientzia hobea eskaintzen du.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hasierako pantailako ikonoak">
<feature>Erabiltzaileen beharrak betetze aldera, hasierako pantailako ikonoen tamaina egokitu daiteke. Egokitzeko, joan Ezarpenak > Hasierako pantaila eta estiloa > Hasierako pantailako ezarpenak > Ikonoen tamaina atalera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Erreproduzigailua">
<feature>Eguneratze honetan musika-erreproduzigailua gehitu da gailuan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Eguneratze honetan, agertoki batzuetan teleobjektibo bidezko tiroaren distira eta kolore efektua optimizatu dira.
Eguneratze honetan, zenbait agertokitan erretratuaren ikuspegi irudiaren efektua optimizatu da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Errendimendua">
<feature>Eguneratze honetan, aplikazio batzuk abiaraztean ausazko atzerapenaren arazoa konpondu da.
Eguneratze honetan, optimizatu egin da fotogramen ausazko erortzeen arazoa mugimendu-efektuan, aplikazio bat abiaraztean.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bateriaren kontsumoa">
<feature>Eguneratze honetan ezohiko bateriaren kontsumoaren arazoa konpondu da egoera batzuetan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Berokuntza-esperientzia">
<feature>Eguneratze honetan, berokuntza-esperientzia hobetu da zenbait agertokitan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Eguneratze honetan sistemaren egonkortasuna hobetu da, gailuak hobeto funtziona dezan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurtasuna">
<feature>Android-en segurtasun-adabakia (2024ko uzt.) gehitu da sistema seguru egoteko. HONOR Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago nahi izanez gero, joan gure webgunera: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzen baduzu ere, zure datu pertsonalak ez dira ezabatuko, baina, hala ere, instalatu aurretik haien babeskopia bat egitea gomendatzen da.
2. Eguneratze-prozesuan arazoren bat izanez gero, deitu HONOR zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara edo joan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora laguntza jasotzeko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی پیشنهادی «موارد دلخواه سراسری»، HONOR Docs و عملکرد تنظیم اندازه آیکون صفحۀ اصلی را اضافه می‌کند، جلوۀ تصویربرداری را در برخی از سناریوها بهینه می‌کند، مشکل مصرف غیرعادی نیرو در برخی شرایط را برطرف می‌کند، عملکرد سیستم، پایداری و تجربه گرمایش را بهبود می‌بخشد و یک وصله امنیتی در آن گنجانده شده است.</feature>
</features>
<features module="موارد دلخواه سراسری">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی «موارد دلخواه سراسری» جدیداً ارتقایافته را ارائه می‌دهد. برای ذخیره کردن محتواها، از قبیل تصاویر، صفحات وب و فایل‌ها در «فضای موارد دلخواه»، با سه انگشت به سمت پایین بکشید. برای گستردن «فضای موارد دلخواه»، ضربه بزنید، یک یا چند مورد انتخاب‌شده را فشار دهید و نگه دارید تا آنها را به برنامه‌های دیگر بکشید، و همچنین می‌توانید آنها را با سایر دستگاه‌های MagicRing همگام‌سازی کنید تا محتوای جمع‌آوری‌شده را در بین دستگاه‌ها به اشتراک بگذارید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏HONOR Docs">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی ‏HONOR Docs و رابط تعاملی کاملاً جدیدی را ارائه می‌کند، برچسب‌های سفارشی، سطل بازیابی و عملکردهای دیگر را اضافه می‌کند، پایداری و سازگاری سند را بهبود می‌بخشد و تجربه کاربری بهتری را ارائه می‌دهد.</feature>
</features>
<features module="آیکون‌های صفحه اصلی">
<feature>اندازه آیکون‌های «صفحۀ اصلی» را می‌توان برای برآوردن نیازهای مختلف کاربران تنظیم کرد. می‌توانید آن را با رفتن به این قسمت تجربه کنید: تنظیمات -> صفحۀ اصلی و سبک -> تنظیمات صفحۀ اصلی -> اندازۀ آیکون.</feature>
</features>
<features module="پخش‌کننده">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی «پخش‌کنندۀ موسیقی» را به دستگاه اضافه می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="دوربین">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی روشنایی و جلوه رنگ تصویربرداری تله‌فوتو را در برخی سناریوها بهینه می‌کند.
این به‌روزرسانی جلوه تصویربرداری فوکوس پرتره را در برخی سناریوها بهینه می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="عملکرد">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی مشکل تأخیر تصادفی هنگام راه‌اندازی برخی برنامه‌ها را برطرف می‌کند.
این به‌روزرسانی مشکل افت فریم تصادفی در جلوه حرکتی راه‌اندازی برنامه را بهینه می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="مصرف نیرو">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی مشکل مصرف غیرعادی نیرو در برخی شرایط را برطرف می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="تجربه گرمایش">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی، تجربه گرمایش در برخی شرایط را بهینه می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="سیستم">
<feature>این به‌روزرسانی پایداری سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد تا دستگاه شما عملکرد پایدارتری داشته باشد.</feature>
</features>
<features module="امنیت">
<feature>برای حفظ امنیت سیستم، وصلۀ امنیتی Android (ژوئیه ۲۰۲۴) گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر دربارۀ به‌روزرسانی‌های امنیتی HONOR، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما به این نشانی مراجعه کنید: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="نکات:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏۱. با نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما پاک نخواهد شد، اما همچنان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام این به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.
‏‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، لطفاً جهت دریافت پشتیبانی با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä suositeltu päivitys lisää Globaalit suosikit, HONOR Docsin ja toiminnon aloitusnäytön kuvakekoon säätämistä varten, optimoi kuvaustehosteen joissakin tilanteissa, korjaa epätavallisen virrankulutuksen ongelman joissakin tilanteissa, parantaa järjestelmän suorituskykyä, vakautta ja lämpökokemusta ja sisältää turvallisuuskorjauksen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globaalit suosikit">
<feature>Tämä päivitys tuo käyttöön äskettäin päivitetyt Globaalit suosikit. Tallenna materiaaleja, kuten kuvia, verkkosivuja ja tiedostoja, Suosikkien tilaan pyyhkäisemällä alas kolmella sormella. Laajenna Suosikkien tila napauttamalla, paina ja pidä valittua kohdetta tai kohteita ja vedä ne muihin sovelluksiin, ja voit myös synkronoida ne muihin MagicRing-laitteisiin, jolloin voit jakaa kerättyä sisältöä laitteiden välillä.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Tämä päivitys tarjoaa täysin uuden HONOR Docsin ja interaktiivisen liittymän, lisää mukautetut merkinnät, roskakorin ja muita toimintoja, parantaa asiakirjojen vakautta ja yhteensopivuutta ja antaa paremman käyttökokemuksen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aloitusnäytön kuvakkeet">
<feature>Aloitusnäytön kuvakkeiden kokoa voi säätää käyttäjän eri tarpeiden mukaan. Voit ottaa sen käyttöön kohdasta: Asetukset -> Aloitusnäyttö ja tyyli -> Aloitusnäytön asetukset -> Kuvakkeen koko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Soitin">
<feature>Tämä päivitys lisää Musiikkisoittimen laitteeseen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Tämä päivitys optimoi teleobjektiivikuvauksen kirkkauden ja väritehosteen joissakin tilanteissa.
Tämä päivitys optimoi muotokuvan tarkennuksen kuvaustehosteen joissakin tilanteissa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Suorituskyky">
<feature>Tämä päivitys korjaa satunnaisen viiveongelman joidenkin sovellusten käynnistyksessä.
Tämä päivitys korjaa sovelluksen käynnistysanimaation satunnaisen kuvien putoamisen ongelman.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Virrankulutus">
<feature>Tämä päivitys korjaa epätavallisen virrankulutuksen ongelman joissakin tilanteissa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lämpökokemus">
<feature>Tämä päivitys optimoi lämpökokemuksen joissakin tilanteissa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Järjestelmä">
<feature>Tämä päivitys parantaa järjestelmän vakautta, jotta laite toimisi vakaammin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvallisuus">
<feature>Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (heinäkuu 2024) on sisällytetty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja HONORin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on verkkosivustollamme: https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei poista henkilökohtaisia tietojasi, mutta ne on silti suositeltavaa varmuuskopioida etukäteen.
2. Jos päivityksessä ilmenee ongelmia, soita HONORin palvelunumeroon tai mene valtuutettuun HONOR-asiakaspalvelukeskukseen tukea varten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée ajoute Favoris globaux, HONOR Docs et la fonction de réglage de la taille des icônes de l'écran d'accueil, optimise l'effet d'imagerie dans certains scénarios, corrige le problème de consommation d'énergie anormale dans certaines scènes, améliore les performances, la stabilité et l'expérience d'échauffement du système et intègre un correctif de sécurité.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favoris globaux">
<feature>Cette mise à jour apporte des Favoris globaux nouvellement mis à niveau. Faites glisser trois doigts vers le bas pour enregistrer des éléments, tels que des images, des pages Web et des fichiers, dans l'Espace Favoris. Appuyez pour développer l'Espace Favoris, appuyez sur le ou les éléments sélectionnés et maintenez la pression pour les déplacer vers d'autres applications. Vous pouvez également les synchroniser avec d'autres appareils MagicRing pour partager le contenu collecté entre plusieurs appareils.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Cette mise à jour fournit un tout nouveau HONOR Docs et une interface interactive, ajoute des étiquettes personnalisées, une corbeille et d'autres fonctions, améliore la stabilité et la compatibilité des documents et offre une meilleure expérience utilisateur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Icônes de l'écran d'accueil">
<feature>La taille des icônes de l'écran d'accueil peut être ajustée pour répondre aux différents besoins des utilisateurs. Vous pouvez en faire l'expérience en allant dans : Paramètres -> Écran d'accueil et style -> Paramètres de l'écran d'accueil -> Taille de l'icône.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lecteur">
<feature>Cette mise à jour ajoute un lecteur de musique sur l'appareil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Appareil photo">
<feature>Cette mise à jour optimise la luminosité et l'effet de couleur des prises de vue au téléobjectif dans certains scénarios.
Cette mise à jour optimise l'effet d'imagerie de la mise au point en mode portrait dans certains scénarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performance">
<feature>Cette mise à jour corrige le problème de ralentissement aléatoire lors du lancement de certaines applications.
Cette mise à jour optimise le problème de pertes d'images aléatoires dans l'effet de mouvement au démarrage des applications.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consommation d'énergie">
<feature>Cette mise à jour corrige le problème de consommation d'énergie anormale dans certaines scènes.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Expérience d'échauffement">
<feature>Cette mise à jour optimise l'expérience d'échauffement dans certains scénarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>Cette mise à jour améliore la stabilité du système de votre appareil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Le correctif de sécurité Android (juillet 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'effacera pas vos données personnelles, mais une sauvegarde préalable est tout de même recommandée.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée ajoute Favoris globaux, HONOR Docs et la fonction de réglage de la taille des icônes de l'écran d'accueil, optimise l'effet d'imagerie dans certains scénarios, corrige le problème de consommation d'énergie anormale dans certaines scènes, améliore les performances, la stabilité et l'expérience d'échauffement du système et intègre un correctif de sécurité.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favoris globaux">
<feature>Cette mise à jour apporte des Favoris globaux nouvellement mis à niveau. Faites glisser trois doigts vers le bas pour enregistrer des éléments, tels que des images, des pages Web et des fichiers, dans l'Espace Favoris. Appuyez pour développer l'Espace Favoris, appuyez sur le ou les éléments sélectionnés et maintenez la pression pour les déplacer vers d'autres applications. Vous pouvez également les synchroniser avec d'autres appareils MagicRing pour partager le contenu collecté entre plusieurs appareils.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Cette mise à jour fournit un tout nouveau HONOR Docs et une interface interactive, ajoute des étiquettes personnalisées, une corbeille et d'autres fonctions, améliore la stabilité et la compatibilité des documents et offre une meilleure expérience utilisateur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Icônes de l'écran d'accueil">
<feature>La taille des icônes de l'écran d'accueil peut être ajustée pour répondre aux différents besoins des utilisateurs. Vous pouvez en faire l'expérience en allant dans : Paramètres -> Écran d'accueil et style -> Paramètres de l'écran d'accueil -> Taille de l'icône.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lecteur">
<feature>Cette mise à jour ajoute un lecteur de musique sur l'appareil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Appareil photo">
<feature>Cette mise à jour optimise la luminosité et l'effet de couleur des prises de vue au téléobjectif dans certains scénarios.
Cette mise à jour optimise l'effet d'imagerie de la mise au point en mode portrait dans certains scénarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performance">
<feature>Cette mise à jour corrige le problème de ralentissement aléatoire lors du lancement de certaines applications.
Cette mise à jour optimise le problème de pertes d'images aléatoires dans l'effet de mouvement au démarrage des applications.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consommation d'énergie">
<feature>Cette mise à jour corrige le problème de consommation d'énergie anormale dans certaines scènes.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Expérience d'échauffement">
<feature>Cette mise à jour optimise l'expérience d'échauffement dans certains scénarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>Cette mise à jour améliore la stabilité du système de votre appareil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Le correctif de sécurité Android (juillet 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'effacera pas vos données personnelles, mais une sauvegarde préalable est tout de même recommandée.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario: esta actualización recomendada engade Favoritos globais, HONOR Docs e a función de axuste do tamaño da icona da pantalla de inicio, optimiza o efecto de creación de imaxes en certos escenarios, soluciona o problema co consumo de enerxía anormal e certas escenas, mellora o rendemento, a estabilidade e a temperatura do sistema, e incorpora un parche de seguranza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favoritos globais">
<feature>Esta actualización incorpora a versión recentemente mellorada de Favoritos globais. Pase tres dedos cara a abaixo para gardar en Espazo de favoritos os materiais, como imaxes, páxinas web e ficheiros. Toque para expandir Espazo de favoritos, prema sen soltar un ou varios elementos para arrastralos a outras aplicacións e sincroníceos con outros dispositivos con MagicRing para compartir o contido recompilado entre dispositivos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Esta actualización fornece a nova aplicación HONOR Docs e unha interface interactiva, engade etiquetas personalizadas, unha papeleira de reciclaxe e outras funcións, mellora a compatibilidade e a estabilidade dos documentos, e fornece unha mellor experiencia do usuario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iconas da pantalla de inicio">
<feature>O tamaño das iconas da pantalla de inicio pódese axustar para adaptalo ás diferentes necesidades dos usuarios. Pode probar a facelo indo a Configuración -> Pantalla de inicio e estilo -> Configuración da pantalla de inicio -> Tamaño de iconas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Reprodutor">
<feature>Esta actualización engade Reprodutor de música no dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cámara">
<feature>Esta actualización optimiza a luminosidade e o efecto de cor do disparo con teleobxectivo en certos casos.
Esta actualización optimiza o efecto de enfoque de imaxes en modo retrato en certos casos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendemento">
<feature>Esta actualización soluciona o problema de retrasos ao iniciar certas aplicacións.
Esta actualización optimiza o problema de caídas de fotogramas aleatorias no efecto de movemento de inicio de aplicacións.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de enerxía">
<feature>Esta actualización soluciona o problema do consumo de enerxía anómalo nalgúns casos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Temperatura">
<feature>Esta actualización optimiza a experiencia de temperatura elevada en determinadas situacións.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Esta actualización mellora a estabilidade do sistema para que o dispositivo funcione dun xeito máis estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguranza">
<feature>Incorpórase o parche de seguranza de Android (xullo de 2024) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información acerca das actualizacións de seguranza de HONOR, visite o noso sitio web: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ao instalar esta actualización non se eliminarán os seus datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar antes unha copia de seguranza.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou visite un centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ ભલામણ કરેલ અપડેટ સાર્વત્રિક મનપસંદ, HONOR Docs અને હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્નના કદને સમાયોજિત કરવાનું ફંક્શન ઉમેરે છે, કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં ઇમેજિંગ પ્રભાવને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે, કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં અસામાન્ય પાવર વપરાશની સમસ્યાને ઠીક કરે છે, સિસ્ટમની કામગીરી, સ્થિરતા અને ગરમ થવાના અનુભવને સુધારે છે અને સુરક્ષા પેચનો સમાવેશ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સાર્વત્રિક મનપસંદ">
<feature>આ અપડેટ નવાં અપગ્રેડ કરેલા સાર્વત્રિક મનપસંદ લાવે છે. છબીઓ, વેબ પેજિસ અને ફાઇલો જેવી સામગ્રીને મનપસંદ જગ્યામાં સાચવવા માટે ત્રણ આંગળીઓથી નીચે સ્વાઇપ કરો. મનપસંદ જગ્યાને વિસ્તૃત કરવા માટે ટૅપ કરો, પસંદ કરેલી એક અથવા બહુવિધ આઇટમને અન્ય એપ્લિકેશન પર ખેંચવા માટે તેને દબાવી રાખો અને તમે એકત્રિત કરેલી સામગ્રીને સમગ્ર ઉપકરણો પર શેર કરવા માટે તેમને અન્ય MagicRing ઉપકરણો સાથે પણ સિંક કરી શકો છો.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>આ અપડેટ તદ્દન નવાં HONOR Docs અને ઇન્ટરેક્ટિવ ઇન્ટરફેસ પ્રદાન કરે છે, કસ્ટમ લેબલ્સ, રિસાઇકલ બિન અને અન્ય કાર્યો ઉમેરે છે, દસ્તાવેજની સ્થિરતા અને સુસંગતતા સુધારે છે અને વધુ સારો વપરાશકર્તા અનુભવ પ્રદાન કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્ન">
<feature>હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્નોનું કદ વપરાશકર્તાઓની વિવિધ જરૂરિયાતોને પૂરી કરવા માટે સમાયોજિત કરી શકાય છે. તમે અહીં જઈને તેનો અનુભવ કરી શકો છો: સેટિંગ્સ -> હોમ સ્ક્રીન અને શૈલી -> હોમ સ્ક્રીન સેટિંગ -> ચિહ્નનું કદ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="પ્લેયર">
<feature>આ અપડેટ ઉપકરણ પર સંગીત પ્લેયર ઉમેરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="કૅમેરા">
<feature>આ અપડેટ કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં ટેલિફોટો શૂટિંગના ચળકાટ અને રંગના પ્રભાવને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે.
આ અપડેટ કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં પોર્ટ્રેટ ફોકસ ઇમેજિંગ પ્રભાવને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="કામગીરી">
<feature>આ અપડેટ કેટલિક એપ્લિકેશન્સ લૉન્ચ કરતી વખતે યાદૃચ્છિક વિલંબની સમસ્યાને ઠીક કરે છે.
આ અપડેટ એપ્લિકેશન સ્ટાર્ટઅપ મોશન પ્રભાવમાં યાદૃચ્છિક ફ્રેમ ડ્રોપની સમસ્યાને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="પાવર વપરાશ">
<feature>આ અપડેટ કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં અસાધારણ પાવર વપરાશની સમસ્યાને ઠીક કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ગરમ થવાનો અનુભવ">
<feature>આ અપડેટ કેટલિક પરિસ્થિતિઓ માટે ગરમ થવાના અનુભવને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સિસ્ટમ">
<feature>તમારું ઉપકરણ વધુ સ્થિર રીતે ચલાવવા આ અપડેટ સિસ્ટમની સ્થિરતામાં સુધારો કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સુરક્ષા">
<feature>Android સુરક્ષા પેચ (જુલાઈ 2024) સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. HONOR સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7 ની મુલાકાત લો</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારો વ્યક્તિગત ડેટા ભૂંસાઈ જશે નહીં, પરંતુ અગાઉથી બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો કૃપા કરીને HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરો અથવા સમર્થન માટે HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્ર પર જાઓ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अनुशंसित अद्यतन से वैश्विक पसंदीदा, HONOR Docs और होम स्क्रीन आइकन का आकार समायोजित करने का फ़ंक्शन जोड़ा जाता है, कुछ परिदृश्यों में इमेजिंग प्रभाव को अनुकूलित किया जाता है, कुछ दृश्यों में असामान्य पॉवर उपभोग की समस्या ठीक की जाती है, सिस्टम के प्रदर्शन, स्थिरता और हीटिंग अनुभव में सुधार किया जाता है और सुरक्षा पैच शामिल किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="वैश्विक पसंदीदा">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से हाल ही में अपग्रेड किए गए वैश्विक पसंदीदा को शामिल किया जाता है। छवियाँ, वेब पेज और फ़ाइलें जैसी सामग्रियों को पसंदीदा स्पेस में सहेजने के लिए तीन उंगलियों से नीचे की ओर स्वाइप करें। पसंदीदा स्पेस का विस्तार करने के लिए टैप करें, चयनित एक या कई आइटम को अन्य ऐप्स पर खींचने के लिए दबाकर रखें और आप डिवाइसेस पर एकत्र की गई सामग्री को साझा करने के लिए उन्हें अन्य MagicRing डिवाइसेस पर सिंक भी कर सकते हैं।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से बिल्कुल नया HONOR Docs और इंटरैक्टिव इंटरफ़ेस दिया जाता है, कस्टम लेबल, रिसायकल बिन और अन्य फ़ंक्शन जोड़े जाते हैं, दस्तावेज़ की स्थिरता और संगतता में सुधार किया जाता है और बेहतर उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव दिया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="होम स्क्रीन के आइकन">
<feature>होम स्क्रीन के आइकन का आकार उपयोगकर्ताओं की अलग-अलग आवश्यकताओं को पूरा करने के लिए समायोजित किया जा सकता है। आप यहाँ जाकर इसका अनुभव कर सकते हैं: सेटिंग्स -> होम स्क्रीन और शैली -> होम स्क्रीन सेटिंग्स -> आइकन का आकार।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्लेयर">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से डिवाइस पर म्यूज़िक प्लेयर जोड़ा जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कैमरा">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से कुछ परिदृश्यों में टेलीफ़ोटो शूटिंग की चमक और रंग प्रभाव को अनुकूलित किया जाता है।
इस अद्यतन से कुछ परिदृश्यों में पोर्ट्रेट फ़ोकस इमेजिंग प्रभाव को अनुकूलित किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्रदर्शन">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से कुछ ऐप्स लॉन्च करते समय रैंडम लैगिंग की समस्या को ठीक किया जाता है।
इस अद्यतन से ऐप स्टार्टअप गति प्रभाव में रैंडम फ़्रेम ड्रॉप की समस्या को ठीक किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="पॉवर उपभोग">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से, कुछ दृश्यों में असामान्य पॉवर उपभोग की समस्या को ठीक किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="हीटिंग अनुभव">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से, कुछ परिदृश्यों में हीटिंग अनुभव को अनुकूलित किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>इस अद्यतन से सिस्टम स्थिरता में सुधार किया जाता है, ताकि आपके डिवाइस को अधिक स्थिर रूप से चलाया जा सके।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>सिस्टम की सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (जुलाई, 2024) शामिल किया गया है। HONOR सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7 पर जाएँ</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो सहायता के लिए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करें या सहायता के लिए HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाएँ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se preporučenim ažuriranjem dodaju Globalne omiljene stavke, HONOR Dokumenti i funkcija podešavanja veličine ikona na početnom zaslonu, optimizira se efekt slike u nekim scenarijima, rješava se problem neuobičajeno velike potrošnje energije u nekim scenama, poboljšavaju se performanse, stabilnost i zagrijavanje sustava, a implementirana je i sigurnosna zakrpa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globalne omiljene stavke">
<feature>Ovim se ažuriranjem nadograđuje postojeća značajka Globalne omiljene stavke. Kliznite prema dolje trima prstima za spremanje materijala, kao što su slike, web-mjesta i datoteke, u Prostor za omiljene stavke. Dodirnite za proširenje Prostora za omiljene stavke, pritisnite i držite odabranu jednu ili više stavki za povlačenje u druge aplikacije, a možete ih i sinkronizirati s drugim MagicRing uređajima za dijeljenje prikupljenog sadržaja na više uređaja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Dokumenti">
<feature>Ovo ažuriranje pruža potpuno novu aplikaciju HONOR Dokumenti i interaktivno sučelje, dodaju se prilagođene oznake, koš za otpatke i druge funkcije, poboljšava se stabilnost i kompatibilnost dokumenta i poboljšano je korisničko iskustvo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikone na početnom zaslonu">
<feature>Veličina ikona na početnom zaslonu može se prilagoditi različitim potrebama korisnika. Možete isprobati odlaskom na: Postavke -> Početni zaslon i stil -> Postavke početnog zaslona -> Veličina ikone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Reproduktor">
<feature>Ovim se ažuriranjem na uređaj dodaje reproduktor glazbe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparat">
<feature>Ovim se ažuriranjem optimizira svjetlina i efekt boja za telefotografsko snimanje u nekim scenarijima.
Ovim se ažuriranjem optimizira efekt fokusiranja na portret u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performanse">
<feature>Ovim se ažuriranjem rješava problem nasumičnog kašnjenja prilikom pokretanja nekih aplikacija.
Ovim se ažuriranjem optimizira problem nasumičnog preskakanja sličica tijekom pokretanja aplikacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Ovim se ažuriranjem rješava problem neuobičajeno velike potrošnje energije u nekim scenama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iskustvo zagrijavanja">
<feature>Ovim se ažuriranjem optimizira iskustvo zagrijavanja u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sustav">
<feature>Ovim se ažuriranjem poboljšava stabilnost sustava pa uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (srpanj 2024.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke HONOR Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalacijom ovog ažuriranja neće se izbrisati vaši osobni podaci, ali preporučujemo da ipak prije ažuriranja izradite sigurnosnu kopiju.
2. Ako tijekom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za pomoć nazovite telefonsku korisničku službu tvrtke HONOR ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku tvrtke HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez az ajánlott frissítés bevezeti a Globális kedvencek és a HONOR Dokumentumok funkciókat, lehetővé teszi a főképernyő ikonméretének beállítását, bizonyos helyzetekben optimalizálja a képalkotási hatást, megszünteti a bizonyos jeleneteknél előforduló rendellenes energiafogyasztást, javítja a rendszer teljesítményét, stabilitását és melegedését, és egy biztonsági javítást is tartalmaz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globális kedvencek">
<feature>Ennek a frissítésnek köszönhetően elérhetővé válik a Globális kedvencek vadonatúj verziója. Csúsztassa lefelé három ujját a különböző tartalmak, például képek, weboldalak és fájlok mentéséhez a Kedvencek terébe. Koppintson a Kedvencek tere megnyitásához, tartson nyomva egy vagy több elemet más alkalmazásokba történő átvitelhez, valamint szinkronizálhatja azokat más MagicRing készülékekkel, hogy megoszthassa az összegyűjtött tartalmat a készülékek között.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Dokumentumok">
<feature>Ez a frissítés bevezeti a vadonatúj HONOR Dokumentumokat és az interaktív kezelőfelületet, egyedi címkékkel, szemetessel és további funkciókkal egészíti ki, javítja a dokumentumok stabilitását és kompatibilitását, illetve magasabb szintű felhasználói élményt biztosít.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Főképernyő ikonok">
<feature>A Főképernyő ikonjainak mérete hozzáigazítható a különböző felhasználói igényekhez. Ehhez a következő menüpontot kell használnia: Beállítások -> Főképernyő és stílus -> Főképernyőbeállítások -> Ikon mérete.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lejátszó">
<feature>Ez a frissítés bevezeti a Zenelejátszót a készüléken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Ez a frissítés bizonyos helyzetekben optimalizálja a telefotós fényképezés fényerejét és színhatását.
Ez a frissítés bizonyos helyzetekben optimalizálja a portréfókusz képi hatását.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Teljesítmény">
<feature>Ez a frissítés megszünteti az egyes alkalmazások elindításakor jelentkező véletlenszerű késést.
Ez a frissítés megszünteti az alkalmazások indításakor véletlenszerűen jelentkező képkockakieséseket.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energiafogyasztás">
<feature>Ez a frissítés bizonyos esetekben kijavítja a nem megfelelő energiafogyasztással kapcsolatos problémát.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Melegedés">
<feature>Ez a frissítés bizonyos helyzetekben optimalizálja a melegedést.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendszer">
<feature>Ez a frissítés javítja a rendszer stabilitását, így a készülék zökkenőmentesebben működik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biztonság">
<feature>Tartalmazza a rendszer biztonságát fokozó Android biztonsági javítást (2024. július). A HONOR biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. E frissítés telepítése nem törli a személyes adatokat, de javasoljuk, hogy készítsen előtte biztonsági mentést.
2. Ha problémába ütközik a frissítés során, hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini menambahkan Favorit Global, HONOR Dokumen, dan fungsi menyesuaikan ukuran ikon layar beranda, mengoptimalkan efek pencitraan di beberapa skenario, memperbaiki masalah konsumsi daya abnormal di beberapa skenario, meningkatkan kinerja sistem, stabilitas, dan pengalaman pemanasan, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favorit Global">
<feature>Pembaruan ini menghadirkan Favorit Global yang baru ditingkatkan. Gesek ke bawah dengan tiga jari untuk menyimpan materi, seperti gambar, halaman web, dan file, menuju Ruang Favorit. Ketuk untuk memperluas Ruang Favorit, tekan dan tahan satu atau beberapa item yang dipilih untuk menyeretnya ke aplikasi lain, dan Anda juga dapat menyinkronkannya ke perangkat MagicRing lainnya untuk membagikan konten yang telah dikumpulkan ke beberapa perangkat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Dokumen">
<feature>Pembaruan ini menghadirkan HONOR Dokumen dan antarmuka interaktif, menambahkan label khusus, tempat sampah, dan fungsi lainnya, meningkatkan stabilitas dan kompatibilitas dokumen, serta menghadirkan pengalaman pengguna yang lebih baik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikon layar beranda">
<feature>Ukuran ikon layar Beranda dapat disesuaikan untuk memenuhi kebutuhan pengguna yang berbeda-beda. Anda dapat menikmatinya dengan membuka: Pengaturan -> Layar beranda dan gaya -> Pengaturan layar beranda -> Ukuran ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pemutar">
<feature>Pembaruan ini menambahkan Pemutar Musik pada perangkat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Pembaruan ini mengoptimal kecerahan dan efek warna pengambilan gambar telefoto di beberapa skenario.
Pembaruan ini mengoptimalkan efek pencitraan fokus potret di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kinerja">
<feature>Pembaruan ini memperbaiki masalah lag acak saat meluncurkan beberapa aplikasi.
Pembaruan ini mengoptimalkan masalah penurunan bingkai yang acak saat efek gerakan memulai aplikasi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Konsumsi daya">
<feature>Pembaruan ini memperbaiki masalah konsumsi daya abnormal di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pengalaman pemanasan">
<feature>Pembaruan ini mengoptimalkan pengalaman pemanasan di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Pembaruan ini meningkatkan stabilitas sistem agar pengoperasian perangkat Anda lebih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Penambal Keamanan Android (Juli 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan menghapus data pribadi Anda, tetapi masih disarankan untuk melakukan pencadangan sebelumnya.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, silakan hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan dukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini menambahkan Favorit Global, HONOR Dokumen, dan fungsi menyesuaikan ukuran ikon layar beranda, mengoptimalkan efek pencitraan di beberapa skenario, memperbaiki masalah konsumsi daya abnormal di beberapa skenario, meningkatkan kinerja sistem, stabilitas, dan pengalaman pemanasan, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favorit Global">
<feature>Pembaruan ini menghadirkan Favorit Global yang baru ditingkatkan. Gesek ke bawah dengan tiga jari untuk menyimpan materi, seperti gambar, halaman web, dan file, menuju Ruang Favorit. Ketuk untuk memperluas Ruang Favorit, tekan dan tahan satu atau beberapa item yang dipilih untuk menyeretnya ke aplikasi lain, dan Anda juga dapat menyinkronkannya ke perangkat MagicRing lainnya untuk membagikan konten yang telah dikumpulkan ke beberapa perangkat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Dokumen">
<feature>Pembaruan ini menghadirkan HONOR Dokumen dan antarmuka interaktif, menambahkan label khusus, tempat sampah, dan fungsi lainnya, meningkatkan stabilitas dan kompatibilitas dokumen, serta menghadirkan pengalaman pengguna yang lebih baik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikon layar beranda">
<feature>Ukuran ikon layar Beranda dapat disesuaikan untuk memenuhi kebutuhan pengguna yang berbeda-beda. Anda dapat menikmatinya dengan membuka: Pengaturan -> Layar beranda dan gaya -> Pengaturan layar beranda -> Ukuran ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pemutar">
<feature>Pembaruan ini menambahkan Pemutar Musik pada perangkat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Pembaruan ini mengoptimal kecerahan dan efek warna pengambilan gambar telefoto di beberapa skenario.
Pembaruan ini mengoptimalkan efek pencitraan fokus potret di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kinerja">
<feature>Pembaruan ini memperbaiki masalah lag acak saat meluncurkan beberapa aplikasi.
Pembaruan ini mengoptimalkan masalah penurunan bingkai yang acak saat efek gerakan memulai aplikasi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Konsumsi daya">
<feature>Pembaruan ini memperbaiki masalah konsumsi daya abnormal di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pengalaman pemanasan">
<feature>Pembaruan ini mengoptimalkan pengalaman pemanasan di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Pembaruan ini meningkatkan stabilitas sistem agar pengoperasian perangkat Anda lebih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Penambal Keamanan Android (Juli 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan menghapus data pribadi Anda, tetapi masih disarankan untuk melakukan pencadangan sebelumnya.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, silakan hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan dukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato aggiunge Preferiti globali, Documenti HONOR e la funzione di regolazione delle dimensioni delle icone della schermata Home, ottimizza l'effetto delle immagini in determinati scenari, risolve il consumo anomalo di energia in certi scenari, migliora le prestazioni, la stabilità e la gestione termica e incorpora una patch di sicurezza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Preferiti globali">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento introduce una nuova versione dei Preferiti globali. Scorri verso il basso con tre dita per salvare materiali, come immagini, pagine Web e file, nello Spazio preferiti. Tocca per espandere lo Spazio preferiti, tieni premuto uno o più elementi selezionati per trascinarli su altre app o sincronizzali con altri dispositivi MagicRing per condividere i contenuti raccolti su più dispositivi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Documenti HONOR">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento fornisce una versione rinnovata di Documenti HONOR e un'interfaccia interattiva, aggiunge le etichette personalizzate, il cestino e altre funzioni e migliora la stabilità e la compatibilità dei documenti nonché l'esperienza utente.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Icone schermata Home">
<feature>Le dimensioni delle icone della schermata Home possono essere modificate in base alle proprie esigenze. Per provare questa funzione, vai su Impostazioni -> Schermata Home e stile -> Impostazioni schermata Home -> Dimensioni delle icone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lettore">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento aggiunge il lettore musicale al dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotocamera">
<feature>L'aggiornamento ottimizza la luminosità e gli effetti colore delle riprese con teleobiettivo in determinati scenari.
Questo aggiornamento ottimizza la messa a fuoco dell'immagine nei ritratti in determinati scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prestazioni">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento risolve il problema del ritardo casuale all'avvio di alcune app.
Questo aggiornamento ottimizza il problema della perdita casuale di fotogrammi nell'effetto movimento all'avvio dell'app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo di energia">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento risolve il problema del consumo di energia anomalo in alcuni scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gestione termica">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento ottimizza la gestione termica in alcuni scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento migliora la stabilità del sistema, per garantire un funzionamento più stabile del dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (luglio 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non comporta l'eliminazione delle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato aggiunge Preferiti globali, Documenti HONOR e la funzione di regolazione delle dimensioni delle icone della schermata Home, ottimizza l'effetto delle immagini in determinati scenari, risolve il consumo anomalo di energia in certi scenari, migliora le prestazioni, la stabilità e la gestione termica e incorpora una patch di sicurezza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Preferiti globali">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento introduce una nuova versione dei Preferiti globali. Scorri verso il basso con tre dita per salvare materiali, come immagini, pagine Web e file, nello Spazio preferiti. Tocca per espandere lo Spazio preferiti, tieni premuto uno o più elementi selezionati per trascinarli su altre app o sincronizzali con altri dispositivi MagicRing per condividere i contenuti raccolti su più dispositivi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Documenti HONOR">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento fornisce una versione rinnovata di Documenti HONOR e un'interfaccia interattiva, aggiunge le etichette personalizzate, il cestino e altre funzioni e migliora la stabilità e la compatibilità dei documenti nonché l'esperienza utente.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Icone schermata Home">
<feature>Le dimensioni delle icone della schermata Home possono essere modificate in base alle proprie esigenze. Per provare questa funzione, vai su Impostazioni -> Schermata Home e stile -> Impostazioni schermata Home -> Dimensioni delle icone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lettore">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento aggiunge il lettore musicale al dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotocamera">
<feature>L'aggiornamento ottimizza la luminosità e gli effetti colore delle riprese con teleobiettivo in determinati scenari.
Questo aggiornamento ottimizza la messa a fuoco dell'immagine nei ritratti in determinati scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prestazioni">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento risolve il problema del ritardo casuale all'avvio di alcune app.
Questo aggiornamento ottimizza il problema della perdita casuale di fotogrammi nell'effetto movimento all'avvio dell'app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo di energia">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento risolve il problema del consumo di energia anomalo in alcuni scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gestione termica">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento ottimizza la gestione termica in alcuni scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Questo aggiornamento migliora la stabilità del sistema, per garantire un funzionamento più stabile del dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (luglio 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non comporta l'eliminazione delle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה מוסיף את 'מועדפים גלובליים', את '‏HONOR Docs ואת הפונקציה של התאמת גודל הסמל של מסך הבית, ממטב את אפקט ההדמיה בתרחישים מסוימים, פותר את הבעיה של צריכת חשמל חריגה בסצנות מסוימות, משפר את ביצועי המערכת, את יציבותה ואת חוויית החימום, ומשלב תיקון אבטחה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מועדפים גלובליים">
<feature>עדכון זה מביא עימו את 'מועדפים גלובליים' ששודרג לאחרונה. החלק כלפי מטה בשלוש אצבעות כדי לשמור חומרים, כגון תמונות, דפי אינטרנט וקבצים, אל 'מרחב מועדפים'. הקש כדי להרחיב את 'מרחב מועדפים', לחץ והחזק פריט נבחר אחד או יותר, ותוכל לסנכרן אותם להתקני MagicRing אחרים כדי לשתף תוכן שנאסף בין התקנים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏‏HONOR Docs">
<feature>עדכון זה מספק HONOR Docs חדש לגמרי וממשק אינטראקטיבי, מוסיף תוויות מותאמות אישית, סל מחזור ופונקציות אחרות, משפר את היציבות והתאימות של המסמכים, ומספק חוויית משתמש טובה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="סמלי מסך הבית">
<feature>ניתן להתאים את גודל הסמלים של מסך הבית כדי לענות על הצרכים השונים של המשתמשים. ניתן להתנסות בכך על-ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' -> 'מסך הבית וסגנון' -> 'הגדרות מסך הבית' -> 'גודל סמל'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="נגן">
<feature>עדכון זה מוסיף את 'נגן מוזיקה' להתקן.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מצלמה">
<feature>עדכון זה ממטב את הבהירות ואת אפקט הצבע של צילום טלפוטו בתרחישים מסוימים.
עדכון זה ממטב את אפקט ההדמיה של מיקוד דיוקן בתרחישים מסוימים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ביצועים">
<feature>עדכון זה פותר את הבעיה של השתהות אקראית בעת הפעלת יישומים מסוימים.
עדכון זה ממטב את הבעיה של נפילת מסגרות אקראית באפקט התנועה בעת הפעלת היישום.</feature>
</features>
<features module="צריכת חשמל">
<feature>עדכון זה פותר את הבעיה של צריכת חשמל חריגה בסצנות מסוימות.</feature>
</features>
<features module="חוויית החימום">
<feature>עדכון זה ממטב את חוויית החימום בתרחישים מסוימים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מערכת">
<feature>עדכון זה משפר את יציבות המערכת כדי לגרום להתקן שלך לפעול בצורה יציבה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מיולי 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תמחק את הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לבצע גיבוי מראש.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה מוסיף את 'מועדפים גלובליים', את '‏HONOR Docs ואת הפונקציה של התאמת גודל הסמל של מסך הבית, ממטב את אפקט ההדמיה בתרחישים מסוימים, פותר את הבעיה של צריכת חשמל חריגה בסצנות מסוימות, משפר את ביצועי המערכת, את יציבותה ואת חוויית החימום, ומשלב תיקון אבטחה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מועדפים גלובליים">
<feature>עדכון זה מביא עימו את 'מועדפים גלובליים' ששודרג לאחרונה. החלק כלפי מטה בשלוש אצבעות כדי לשמור חומרים, כגון תמונות, דפי אינטרנט וקבצים, אל 'מרחב מועדפים'. הקש כדי להרחיב את 'מרחב מועדפים', לחץ והחזק פריט נבחר אחד או יותר, ותוכל לסנכרן אותם להתקני MagicRing אחרים כדי לשתף תוכן שנאסף בין התקנים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏‏HONOR Docs">
<feature>עדכון זה מספק HONOR Docs חדש לגמרי וממשק אינטראקטיבי, מוסיף תוויות מותאמות אישית, סל מחזור ופונקציות אחרות, משפר את היציבות והתאימות של המסמכים, ומספק חוויית משתמש טובה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="סמלי מסך הבית">
<feature>ניתן להתאים את גודל הסמלים של מסך הבית כדי לענות על הצרכים השונים של המשתמשים. ניתן להתנסות בכך על-ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' -> 'מסך הבית וסגנון' -> 'הגדרות מסך הבית' -> 'גודל סמל'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="נגן">
<feature>עדכון זה מוסיף את 'נגן מוזיקה' להתקן.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מצלמה">
<feature>עדכון זה ממטב את הבהירות ואת אפקט הצבע של צילום טלפוטו בתרחישים מסוימים.
עדכון זה ממטב את אפקט ההדמיה של מיקוד דיוקן בתרחישים מסוימים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ביצועים">
<feature>עדכון זה פותר את הבעיה של השתהות אקראית בעת הפעלת יישומים מסוימים.
עדכון זה ממטב את הבעיה של נפילת מסגרות אקראית באפקט התנועה בעת הפעלת היישום.</feature>
</features>
<features module="צריכת חשמל">
<feature>עדכון זה פותר את הבעיה של צריכת חשמל חריגה בסצנות מסוימות.</feature>
</features>
<features module="חוויית החימום">
<feature>עדכון זה ממטב את חוויית החימום בתרחישים מסוימים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מערכת">
<feature>עדכון זה משפר את יציבות המערכת כדי לגרום להתקן שלך לפעול בצורה יציבה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מיולי 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תמחק את הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לבצע גיבוי מראש.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様。この推奨更新では、グローバルお気に入り、HONOR Docs、ホーム画面のサイズ調整機能が追加され、一部の状況での画像処理効果が最適化され、一部の状況での異常な消費電力の問題が修正され、システムの性能、安定性、高温化体験が改善され、セキュリティパッチが組み込まれます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="グローバルお気に入り">
<feature>今回の更新では、新たにアップグレードされたグローバルお気に入りが導入されました。3本の指で下にスワイプし、画像、Webページ、ファイルなどの項目をお気に入りスペースに保存できます。タップしてお気に入りスペースを展開し、1つ以上のアイテムを長押しして選択することで、他のアプリにドラッグできるほか、他のMagicRingデバイスに同期して集めたコンテンツをデバイス間で共有できます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>今回の更新で、最新のHONOR Docsとインタラクティブなインターフェースが提供され、カスタムラベル、ごみ箱、およびその他の機能の追加、文書の安定性と互換性の改善、より良いユーザー体験の提供が行われました。</feature>
</features>
<features module="ホーム画面アイコン">
<feature>ホーム画面のアイコンのサイズを必要に応じて調整できるようになりました。この機能は[設定] -> [ホーム画面とスタイル] -> [ホーム画面設定] -> [アイコンのサイズ]に移動して利用できます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="プレーヤー">
<feature>今回の更新で、デバイスの音楽プレーヤーが追加されました。</feature>
</features>
<features module="カメラ">
<feature>この推奨更新では、一部の状況での望遠撮影の明るさと色彩効果が最適化されます。
この推奨更新では、一部の状況でのポートレートフォーカスの画像処理効果が最適化されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="性能">
<feature>この推奨更新では、一部のアプリの起動時に発生する不規則な遅延の問題が修正されます。
この推奨更新では、アプリ起動時のモーション効果で発生する不規則なコマ落ちの問題が最適化されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="消費電力">
<feature>今回の更新によって、一部の状況における異常な消費電力の問題が修正されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="高温体験">
<feature>今回の更新では、一部の状況における高温体験が最適化されました。</feature>
</features>
<features module="システム">
<feature>今回の更新では、システムの安定性が改善され、デバイスがより安定して動作するようになります。</feature>
</features>
<features module="セキュリティ">
<feature>システムセキュリティのためにAndroidセキュリティパッチ（2024年7月）が組み込まれました。HONORのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください：https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報が消去されることはありませんが、事前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターでサポートを受けてください。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ეს რეკომენდებული განახლება ამატებს გლობალურ რჩეულებს, HONOR Docs-ს და საწყის ეკრანზე პიქტოგრამების ზომის რეგულირების ფუნქციას, ახდენს გამოსახულების ეფექტის ოპტიმიზებას ზოგიერთ სცენარში, აგვარებს ენერგიის არანორმალური მოხმარების პრობლემას ზოგიერთ გარემოებაში, აუმჯობესებს სისტემის მუშაობას, სტაბილურობასა და გადახურებასთან დაკავშირებულ გამოცდილებას და ჩართავს უსაფრთხოების შესწორებას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="გლობალური რჩეულები">
<feature>ეს განახლება გაწვდით ახლად გაუმჯობესებულ გლობალურ რჩეულებს. ქვემოთ ჩამოუსვით სამი თითით, რათა რჩეულების სივრცეში შეინახოთ მასალები, როგორიცაა სურათები, ვებგვერდები და ფაილები. შეეხეთ რჩეულების სივრცის გასაშლელად, ხანგრძლივად დააჭირეთ არჩეულ ერთ ან რამდენიმე ელემენტს სხვა აპებში გადასატანად, ასევე შეგიძლიათ მათი სინქრონიზება MagicRing-ის სხვა მოწყობილობებთან, რათა მოწყობილობებს შორის გააზიაროთ შეგროვებული კონტენტი.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>ეს განახლება გთავაზობთ სრულიად ახალ HONOR Docs-ს და ინტერაქტიულ ინტერფეისს, ამატებს მორგებულ ეტიკეტებს, სანაგვე კალათასა და სხვა ფუნქციებს, აუმჯობესებს დოკუმენტების სტაბილურობასა და თავსებადობას და უზრუნველყოფს მომხმარებლის უკეთეს გამოცდილებას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამები">
<feature>საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამების ზომა შეიძლება დარეგულირდეს მომხმარებლის საჭიროებების შესაბამისად. ამის გაკეთება შეგიძლიათ მენიუში: პარამეტრები -> საწყისი ეკრანი და სტილი -> საწყისი ეკრანის პარამეტრები -> პიქტოგრამის ზომა.</feature>
</features>
<features module="პლეერი">
<feature>ეს განახლება მოწყობილობაში ამატებს მუსიკის პლეერს.</feature>
</features>
<features module="კამერა">
<feature>ეს განახლება ახდენს ტელეფოტო გადაღების სიკაშკაშისა და ფერის ეფექტის ოპტიმიზებას ზოგიერთ სცენარში.
ეს განახლება ახდენს პორტრეტის ფოკუსის გამოსახულების ეფექტის ოპტიმიზებას ზოგიერთ სცენარში.</feature>
</features>
<features module="მუშაობის ხარისხი">
<feature>ეს განახლება აგვარებს ზოგიერთი აპის გაშვებისას შემთხვევითი ჩამორჩენის პრობლემას.
ეს განახლება ახდენს აპის გაშვებისას მოძრაობის ეფექტში ჩარჩოს შემთხვევითი დაყოფის პრობლემას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ენერგიის მოხმარება">
<feature>ეს განახლება აღმოფხვრის ზოგიერთ სცენაში ენერგიის არანორმალურ მოხმარებასთან დაკავშირებულ პრობლემას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="გადახურებასთან დაკავშირებული გამოცდილება">
<feature>ეს განახლება ახდენს გადახურების ოპტიმიზებას ზოგიერთ სცენარში.</feature>
</features>
<features module="სისტემა">
<feature>ეს განახლება აუმჯობესებს სისტემის სტაბილურობას, რის შედეგადაც მოწყობილობა უფრო სტაბილურად მუშაობს.</feature>
</features>
<features module="უსაფრთხოება">
<feature>სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის ჩაირთო Android უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (2024 წლის ივლისი). HONOR-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ გამოიწვევს თქვენი პერსონალური მონაცემების წაშლას, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. განახლების დროს პრობლემების წარმოქმნის შემთხვევაში, მხარდაჭერისთვის დარეკეთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან მიმართეთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл ұсынылған жаңарту «Глобалды таңдаулылар» мүмкіндігін, HONOR Docs қолданбасын және негізгі экран белгішесі өлшемін реттеу функциясын қосады, кейбір сценарийлерде кескіндеу әсерін оңтайландырады, кейбір көріністерде қалыпсыз қуат тұтыну мәселесін шешеді, жүйе өнімділігін, тұрақтылығын және жылыту тәжірибесін жақсартады және қауіпсіздік патчын біріктіреді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Глобалды таңдаулылар">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту жаңадан жаңартылған «Глобалды таңдаулылар» мүмкіндігін әкеледі. Кескіндер, веб-беттер мен файлдар сияқты материалдарды Таңдаулылар кеңістігіне сақтау үшін үш саусақпен төмен қарай жанап өтіңіз. Таңдаулылар кеңістігін кеңейту үшін түртіп, таңдалған бір немесе бірнеше элементті басқа қолданбаларға сүйреп апару үшін басып тұрыңыз, сондай-ақ жиналған мазмұнды құрылғылар арасында бөлісу үшін оларды басқа MagicRing құрылғыларымен синхрондауға болады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту жап-жаңа HONOR Docs пен интерактивті интерфейсті қамтамасыз етеді, реттелетін белгілерді, себетті және басқа функцияларды қосады, құжат тұрақтылығы мен үйлесімділігін жақсартады және жақсырақ пайдаланушы тәжірибесін қамтамасыз етеді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Негізгі экран белгішелері">
<feature>Негізгі экран белгішелерінің өлшемін пайдаланушылардың әртүрлі қажеттіліктеріне сай реттеуге болады. Келесіге өту арқылы оны қолданып көруге болады: «Параметрлер» -> «Негізгі экран және стиль» -> «Негізгі экран параметрлері» -> «Белгіше өлшемі».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ойнатқыш">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту құрылғыға «Музыка ойнатқыш» мүмкіндігін қосады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту кейбір сценарийлерде телефотосурет түсірудің жарықтығы мен түс әсерін оңтайландырады.
Бұл жаңарту кейбір сценарийлерде портрет фокусын кескіндеу әсерін оңтайландырады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Өнімділік">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту кейбір қолданбаларды іске қосқан кезде кездейсоқ кешігу мәселесін шешеді.
Бұл жаңарту қолданбаны іске қосу қозғалысы әсеріндегі кадрдың кездейсоқ түсу мәселесін оңтайландырады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қуат тұтыну">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту кейбір көріністерде қалыпсыз қуат тұтыну мәселесін шешеді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Жылыту тәжірибесі">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту кейбір сценарийлерде жылыту тәжірибесін оңтайландырады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Жүйе">
<feature>Бұл жаңарту жүйенің тұрақтылығын жақсартып, құрылғыңыздың тұрақтырақ жұмыс істеуіне мүмкіндік береді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қауіпсіздік">
<feature>Android қауіпсіздік патчы (шілде, 2024) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. HONOR қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнатсаңыз, жеке деректер өшпейді, бірақ бұрынғы сақтық көшірме әлі де ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту барысында мәселелер орын алса, қолдау алу үшін HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне хабарласыңыз немесе HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына барыңыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពដែលបានណែនាំនេះបញ្ចូលសំណព្វសកល, HONOR Docs និងមុខងារលៃតម្រូវទំហំរូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម, ធ្វើឱ្យបែបផែនរូបភាពប្រសើរឡើងនៅក្នុងសេណារីយោមួយចំនួន, ដោះស្រាយបញ្ហានៃការប្រើប្រាស់​ថាមពលខុសប្រក្រតីក្នុងទិដ្ឋភាពមួយចំនួន, កែលម្អប្រតិបត្តិការប្រព័ន្ធ ស្ថិរភាព និងបទពិសោធកម្ដៅ និងរួមបញ្ចូលបំណះសន្តិសុខ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="សំណព្វសកល">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះនាំមកជូននូវសំណព្វសកលដែលបានអាប់គ្រេតថ្មី។ វាសម្រាមដៃបីចុះក្រោម ដើម្បីរក្សាទុកសម្ភារៈនានាដូចជា រូបភាព ទំព័របណ្ដាញ និងឯកសារ ទៅលំហសំណព្វ។ ប៉ះដើម្បីពង្រីកលំហសំណព្វ សង្កត់ឱ្យជាប់លើធាតុមួយឬច្រើនដែលបានជ្រើសរើស ដើម្បីចុចអូសធាតុទាំងនោះទៅកម្មវិធីផ្សេងទៀត ហើយអ្នកក៏អាចធ្វើសមកាលកម្មធាតុទាំងនោះទៅឧបករណ៍ MagicRing ផ្សេងទៀតផងដែរ ដើម្បីចែករំលែកខ្លឹមសារដែលបានប្រមូលឆ្លងឧបករណ៍នានា។</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះផ្ដល់ HONOR Docs និងផ្ទៃអន្តរកម្មដ៏ថ្មីសន្លាង បញ្ចូលស្លាកតាមតម្រូវការ ធុងសម្រាម និងមុខងារផ្សេងទៀត កែលម្អស្ថិរភាព និងភាពត្រូវគ្នារបស់ឯកសារ និងផ្ដល់បទពិសោធន៍អ្នកប្រើកាន់តែប្រសើរ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="រូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម">
<feature>ទំហំរូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើមអាចត្រូវបានលៃតម្រូវ ដើម្បីបំពេញតាមតម្រូវការខុសៗគ្នារបស់អ្នកប្រើ។ អ្នកអាចទទួលបទពិសោធប្រើប្រាស់វាបានដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ -> អេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម និងរចនាប័ទ្ម -> ការកំណត់អេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម -> ទំហំរូបតំណាង។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កម្មវិធីចាក់">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះបញ្ចូលកម្មវិធីចាក់តន្រ្តីនៅលើឧបករណ៍។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កាមេរ៉ា">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យកម្រិតពន្លឺ និងបែបផែនពណ៌នៃការថតរូបពីចម្ងាយប្រសើរឡើងក្នុងសេណារីយោមួយចំនួន។
បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យបែបផែនរូបភាពផ្ដោតនៃរូបភាពពាក់កណ្តាលខ្លួនប្រសើរឡើងក្នុងសេណារីយោមួយចំនួន។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ប្រតិបត្តិការ">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះដោះស្រាយបញ្ហានៃការដើរស្ទួកៗដោយចៃដន្យ នៅពេលបើកដំណើរការកម្មវិធីមួយចំនួន។
បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យបញ្ហានៃការធ្លាក់ហ្វ្រេមដោយចៃដន្យក្នុងបែបផែនចលនាចាប់ផ្ដើមកម្មវិធីប្រសើរឡើង។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ការប្រើប្រាស់​ថាមពល">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះដោះស្រាយបញ្ហានៃការប្រើប្រាស់​ថាមពលខុសប្រក្រតីនៅក្នុងឆាកមួយចំនួន។</feature>
</features>
<features module="បទពិសោធកម្ដៅ">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះធ្វើឱ្យ​បទពិសោធកម្ដៅ​ប្រសើរឡើង​ក្នុង​សេណារីយោ​មួយចំនួន។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ប្រព័ន្ធ">
<feature>បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះកែលម្អស្ថិរភាពប្រព័ន្ធ ដើម្បីធ្វើឱ្យឧបករណ៍របស់អ្នកដំណើរការបានកាន់តែមានស្ថិរភាព។</feature>
</features>
<features module="សន្តិសុខ">
<feature>បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (មិថុនា 2024) ត្រូវបាន​រួមបញ្ចូល​សម្រាប់​សន្តិសុខ​ប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់​ព័ត៌មាន​បន្ថែម​អំពី​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​សន្តិសុខ HONOR សូមចូលទៅ​គេហទំព័រ​របស់យើង https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​លុបទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ចេញទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបបញ្ហាណាមួយក្នុងអំឡុងពេល​ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព សូមហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សផ្នែកសេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​សេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR ដើម្បី​ទទួលបាន​ជំនួយ។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಿದ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಗ್ಲೋಬಲ್ ಫೇವರೆಟ್ಸ್, HONOR Docs ಮತ್ತು ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ನ ಗಾತ್ರವನ್ನು ಸರಿಹೊಂದಿಸುವ ಕಾರ್ಯವನ್ನು ಸೇರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಇಮೇಜಿಂಗ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ, ಕೆಲವು ದೃಶ್ಯಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಅಸಹಜ ಪವರ್ ಬಳಕೆಯ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಯನ್ನು ಪರಿಹರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಕಾರ್ಯಕ್ಷಮತೆ, ಸ್ಥಿರತೆ ಮತ್ತು ಬಿಸಿಯಾಗುವಿಕೆಯ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಗ್ಲೋಬಲ್ ಫೇವರೆಟ್ಸ್">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಹೊಸದಾಗಿ ನವೀಕರಿಸಿದ ಗ್ಲೋಬಲ್ ಫೇವರೆಟ್ಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ತರುತ್ತದೆ. ಚಿತ್ರಗಳು, ವೆಬ್ ಪುಟಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ಫೈಲ್‌ಗಳಂತಹ ವಸ್ತುಗಳನ್ನು ಫೇವರೆಟ್ಸ್ ಸ್ಪೇಸ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಉಳಿಸಲು ಮೂರು ಬೆರಳುಗಳಿಂದ ಕೆಳಕ್ಕೆ ಸ್ವೈಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ. ಫೇವರೆಟ್ಸ್ ಸ್ಪೇಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ವಿಸ್ತರಿಸಲು ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ, ಆಯ್ಕೆಮಾಡಿದ ಒಂದು ಅಥವಾ ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಐಟಂಗಳನ್ನು ಇತರ ಆ್ಯಪ್‌ಗಳಿಗೆ ಎಳೆಯಲು ಒತ್ತಿ ಹಿಡಿದುಕೊಳ್ಳಿ ಮತ್ತು ಸಾಧನಗಳಾದ್ಯಂತ ಸಂಗ್ರಹಿಸಿದ ವಿಷಯವನ್ನು ಹಂಚಿಕೊಳ್ಳಲು ನೀವು ಅವುಗಳನ್ನು ಇತರ MagicRing ಸಾಧನಗಳಿಗೆ ಸಹ ಸಿಂಕ್ ಮಾಡಬಹುದು.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಹೊಚ್ಚಹೊಸ HONOR Docs ಮತ್ತು ಸಂವಾದಾತ್ಮಕ ಇಂಟರ್‌ಫೇಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ಒದಗಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ಕಸ್ಟಮ್ ಲೇಬಲ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು, ಮರುಬಳಕೆ ಕೋಶ ಮತ್ತು ಇತರ ಕಾರ್ಯಗಳನ್ನು ಸೇರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ಡಾಕ್ಯುಮೆಂಟ್ ಸ್ಥಿರತೆ ಮತ್ತು ಹೊಂದಾಣಿಕೆಯನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಉತ್ತಮ ಬಳಕೆದಾರ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಒದಗಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳು">
<feature>ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ವಿವಿಧ ಅಗತ್ಯಗಳನ್ನು ಪೂರೈಸಲು ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳ ಗಾತ್ರವನ್ನು ಸರಿಹೊಂದಿಸಬಹುದು. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನೀವು ಇದರ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು -> ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮತ್ತು ಶೈಲಿ -> ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು -> ಐಕಾನ್ ಗಾತ್ರ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಪ್ಲೇಯರ್">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಸಾಧನದಲ್ಲಿ ಸಂಗೀತ ಪ್ಲೇಯರ್ ಅನ್ನು ಸೇರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಕ್ಯಾಮರಾ">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಟೆಲಿಫೋಟೋ ಶೂಟಿಂಗ್‌ನ ಹೊಳಪು ಮತ್ತು ಬಣ್ಣದ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.
ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಭಾವಚಿತ್ರ ಫೋಕಸ್ ಇಮೇಜಿಂಗ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಕಾರ್ಯಕ್ಷಮತೆ">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು, ಕೆಲವು ಆ್ಯಪ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಪ್ರಾರಂಭಿಸುವಾಗ ಕಂಡುಬರುವ ಯಾದೃಚ್ಛಿಕ ಮಂದಗತಿಯ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಯನ್ನು ಪರಿಹರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.
ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಸ್ಟಾರ್ಟ್‌ಅಪ್ ಮೋಷನ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಯಾದೃಚ್ಛಿಕ ಫ್ರೇಮ್ ಡ್ರಾಪ್‌ಗಳ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಯನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಪವರ್ ಬಳಕೆ">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಕೆಲವು ದೃಶ್ಯಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಅಸಹಜ ವಿದ್ಯುತ್ ಬಳಕೆಯ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಯನ್ನು ಪರಿಹರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಬಿಸಿಯಾಗುವಿಕೆ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆ">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಉಂಟಾಗುವ ಬಿಸಿಯಾಗುವಿಕೆ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ">
<feature>ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಸಾಧನವನ್ನು ಹೆಚ್ಚು ಸ್ಥಿರವಾಗಿ ರನ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಸ್ಥಿರತೆಯನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಭದ್ರತೆ">
<feature>ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ಜುಲೈ 2024) ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. HONOR ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್‌ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸಿದರೆ ಇದು ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಅಳಿಸುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ಮುಂಚಿತವಾಗಿ ಬ್ಯಾಕ್‍ಅಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ ಇಡಬೇಕೆಂದು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ಅಥವಾ ಬೆಂಬಲಕ್ಕಾಗಿ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಹೋಗಿ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 권장 업데이트는 글로벌 즐겨찾기, HONOR 문서 및 홈 화면 아이콘 크기 조정 기능 추가, 일부 시나리오에서 이미징 효과 최적화, 일부 장면에서 비정상적인 소비 전력 문제 수정, 시스템 성능, 안정성 및 발열 경험 개선, 보안 패치 통합 등을 포함하고 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="글로벌 즐겨찾기">
<feature>이번 업데이트에서는 새롭게 업그레이드된 글로벌 즐겨찾기가 제공됩니다. 세 손가락으로 아래로 스와이프하면 이미지, 웹 페이지, 파일 등의 자료를 즐겨찾기 공간에 저장할 수 있습니다. 탭하여 즐겨찾기 공간을 확장하고 선택한 하나 또는 여러 항목을 길게 눌러 다른 앱으로 드래그할 수 있으며, 다른 매직링 장치와 동기화하여 수집된 콘텐츠를 여러 장치에서 공유할 수도 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR 문서">
<feature>이 업데이트는 새로운 HONOR 문서와 대화형 인터페이스를 제공하고 사용자 설정 라벨, 휴지통 및 기타 기능이 추가되고 문서 안정성과 호환성이 개선되어 더 나은 사용자 경험을 제공합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="홈 화면 아이콘">
<feature>홈 화면 아이콘의 크기는 사용자의 다양한 요구에 맞게 조정할 수 있습니다. 설정 -> 홈 화면 및 스타일 -> 홈 화면 설정 -> 아이콘 크기로 이동하여 체험해 볼 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="플레이어">
<feature>이 업데이트는 장치에 음악 플레이어를 추가합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="카메라">
<feature>이 업데이트는 일부 시나리오에서 망원 촬영의 밝기 및 색상 효과를 최적화합니다.
이 업데이트는 일부 시나리오에서 세로 보기 초점 이미징 효과를 최적화합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="성능">
<feature>이 업데이트는 일부 앱을 실행할 때 무작위로 지연되는 문제를 해결합니다.
이 업데이트는 앱 시작 모션 효과의 무작위 프레임 드롭 문제를 최적화합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="소비 전력">
<feature>이 업데이트는 일부 장면에서 비정상적인 소비 전력 문제를 해결합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="발열 경험">
<feature>이번 업데이트로 일부 시나리오에서 발열 경험이 최적화됩니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="시스템">
<feature>이 업데이트에서는 장치가 더 안정적으로 실행될 수 있도록 시스템 안정성이 개선됩니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="보안">
<feature>시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2024년 7월)가 통합되었습니다. HONOR 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 다음에 있는 당사 웹사이트를 방문하세요. https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터는 삭제되지 않지만, 사전에 백업하시기를 권장합니다.
2. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터로 가서 지원을 받으십시오.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ຮຽນ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ທີ່​ແນະ​ນຳນີ້ເພີ່ມ Global Favorites, HONOR Docs ແລະ ຟັງ​ຊັນ​ຂອງ​ການ​ປັບ​ຂະ​ໜາດ​ໄອ​ຄອນ​​ໃນໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ, ປັບ​ເອັບ​ເຝັກຮູບ​ພາບ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ພາບ​ການ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ, ແກ້​ໄຂ​ບັນ​ຫາ​ຂອງ​ການ​ໃຊ້​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານ​ຜິ​ດ​ປົກ​ກະ​ຕິ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ການ, ປັບ​ປຸງ​ປະ​ສິດ​ທິ​ພາບ​, ​ຄວາມ​ສະ​ຖຽນ ແລະ ປະ​ສົບ​ການ​ການ​ເຮັດຄວາມ​ຮ້ອນຂອງລະ​ບົບ ແລະ ລວມເອົາ​ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ເຂົ້າ​ກັນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Global Favorites">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້ນຳ​ເອົາ Global Favorites ທີ່​ອັບ​ເກ​ຣດ​ໃໝ່​ມາ​ໃຫ້. ປັດ​ລົງ​ລຸ່ມ​ດ້ວຍ​​ນິ້ວ​ມື​ສາມ​ນິ້ວ ເພື່ອ​ບັນ​ທຶກສື່ ເຊັ່ນ: ຮູບ​ພາບ, ໜ້າ​ເວັບ ແລະ ໄຟ​ລ໌ ໃສ່ Favorites Space. ແຕະ​ເພື່ອ​ຂະ​ຫຍາຍ Favorites Space, ກົດ​ໜຶ່ງ ຫຼື ຫຼາຍ​ລາຍ​ການ​ທີ່​ເລືອກ​ຄ້າງ​ໄວ້ ເພື່ອ​ລາກ​ພວກ​ມັນ​ໄປ​ຫາ​ແອັບ​ອື່ນໆ ແລະ ທ່ານ​ຍັງ​ສາ​ມາດ​ຊິງ​ຄ໌​ພວ​ກ​ມັນ​ໄປ​ຫາ​ອຸ​ປະ​ກອນ MagicRing ອື່ນໆ ເພື່ອ​ແຊ​ຣ໌​ເນື້ອ​ຫາ​ທີ່​ເກັບ​ເອົາ​ຂ້າມ​ອຸ​ປະ​ກອນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ໃຫ້ HONOR Docs ແລະ ໜ້າປະ​ສານແບບໂຕ້ຕອບໃໝ່, ເພີ່ມ​ປ້າຍແບບ​ກຳນົດ​ເອງ, ຖັງຂີ້​ເຫຍື້ອ ແລະ ຟັງ​ຊັນ​ອື່ນໆ, ປັບ​ປຸງ​ຄວາມ​ສະ​ຖຽນ ແລະ ຄວາມເຂົ້າ​ກັນ​ໄດ້​ຂອງ​ເອ​ກະ​ສານ ແລະ ໃຫ້​ປະ​ສົບ​ການ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້​ທີ່​ດີກວ່າ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໄອ​ຄອນໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ">
<feature>​ສາ​ມາດ​ປັບຂະ​ໜາດ​ຂອງໄອ​ຄອນໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ​ເພື່ອ​ໃຫ້​ຕອບ​ສະ​ໜອງໄດ້​ຕ​າມ​ຄວາມ​ຕ້ອງ​ການ​ທີ່​ແຕກ​ຕ່າງ​ກັນ​ຂອງ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້. ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ສຳ​ຜັດ​ປະ​ສົບ​ການມັນ​ໄດ້​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ -> ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ ແລະ ຮູບ​ແບບ -> ການຕັ້ງຄ່າໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ -> ຂະ​ໜາດ​ໄອ​ຄອນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ເຄື່ອງຫຼິ້ນ">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ເພີ່ມ​ເຄື່ອງຫຼິ້ນ​ດົນ​ຕີ​ໃນ​ອຸ​ປະ​ກອນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ກ້ອງຖ່າຍຮູບ">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ປັບ​ຄວາມແຈ້ງ ແລະ ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ສີ​ຂອງການ​ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບ​​ໄລ​ຍະ​ໄກ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ພາບ​ການ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ.
ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້ປັບເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ຮູບ​ພາບໂຟ​ກັ​ສ​ຮູບ​ເຄິ່ງ​​ຕົວໃນບາງສະພາບການ​ໃຫ້ເໝາະສົມ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ປະ​ສິດ​ທິ​ພາບ">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ບັນ​ຫາຄວາມ​​ຊັກ​ຊ້າ​ແບບ​ສຸ່ມ ເມື່ອ​ເປີດ​ໃ​ຊ້​ບາງ​ແອັບ.
ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ປັບບັນ​ຫາ​ຂອງ​ເຟ​ຣມ​ສຸ່ມ​ຕົກ​ໃນ​ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ການ​ເຄື່ອນ​ໄຫວ​ເມື່ອ​ເລີ່ມ​ຕົ້ນ​ແອັບ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="​ການ​ໃຊ້​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານ">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ບັນ​ຫາ​​ການ​ໃຊ້​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານ​​ຜິດ​ປົກ​ກະ​ຕິ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ການ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ປະ​ສົບ​ການ​ເຮັດ​ຄວາມ​ຮ້ອນ">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້ປັບປະ​ສົບການເຮັດ​ຄວາມ​ຮ້ອນໃນບາງສະພາບການໃຫ້ເໝາະສົມ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ລະບົບ">
<feature>ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້ປັບປຸງຄວາມສະຖຽນຂອງລະບົບ ເພື່ອເຮັດໃຫ້ອຸປະກອນຂອງທ່ານເຮັດວຽກໄດ້ສະຖຽນຍິ່ງຂຶ້ນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
<feature>ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ກໍ​ລະ​ກົດ 2024) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ HONOR, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການຕິດຕັ້ງການອັບເດດນີ້ຈະບໍ່ລຶບຂໍ້ມູນສ່ວນຕົວຂອງທ່ານ, ແຕ່ຂໍແນະນຳໃຫ້ທ່ານສຳຮອງຂໍ້ມູນໄວ້ລ່ວງໜ້າ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ກະລຸນາໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR ເພື່ອຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šiuo rekomenduojamu naujiniu įtraukiami visuotiniai parankiniai, HONOR dokumentai, pakoreguojamas pradžios ekrano piktogramos dydis, kai kuriuose scenarijuose, optimizuojamas vaizdavimo efektas, kai kuriose scenose išsprendžiama neįprastų energijos sąnaudų problema, pagerinamas sistemos našumas, stabilumas ir kaitimo patirtis, taip pat įtraukiama saugumo pataisa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Visuotiniai parankiniai">
<feature>Šiuo naujiniu į įrenginį įtraukiama naujai patobulinta visuotinių parankinių funkcija. Norėdami į parankinių erdvę įrašyti medžiagą, pavyzdžiui, vaizdus, tinklalapius ir failus, braukite žemyn trimis pirštais. Paliesdami išskleiskite parankinių erdvę, tada paspauskite ir palaikykite pasirinktą vieną ar kelis elementus, kad galėtumėte juos vilkti į kitas programas. Taip pat galite juos sinchronizuoti su kitais „MagicRing“ įrenginiais ir bendrinti surinktą turinį įvairiuose įrenginiuose.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR dokumentai">
<feature>Šis naujinimas suteikia visiškai naujus HONOR dokumentus ir interaktyvią sąsają, prideda pasirinktinių etikečių, šiukšlių dėžę ir kitas funkcijas, pagerina dokumentų stabilumą ir suderinamumą bei suteikia geresnę naudotojo patirtį.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pradžios ekrano piktogramos">
<feature>Pradžios ekrano piktogramų dydį galima reguliuoti atsižvelgiant į skirtingus naudotojų poreikius. Šią funkciją galite išbandyti nueidami į „Nustatymai > Pradžios ekranas ir stilius > Pradžios ekrano nuostatos > Piktogramos dydis“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Leistuvė">
<feature>Šiuo naujiniu į įrenginį įtraukiama Muzikos leistuvė.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Šiuo naujiniu kai kuriuose scenarijuose optimizuojamas šviesumas ir spalvų efektas fotografuojant teleobjektyvu.
Šiuo naujiniu kai kuriuose scenarijuose optimizuojamas portreto fokusavimo vaizdo efektas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Našumas">
<feature>Šiuo naujiniu išsprendžiama atsitiktinio vėlavimo paleidžiant kai kurias programėles problema.
Šiuo naujiniu optimizuojama atsitiktinių kadrų dingimo problema, susijusi su programėlės paleidimo judesio efektu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energijos sąnaudos">
<feature>Šiuo naujiniu kai kuriose scenose išsprendžiama neįprastų energijos sąnaudų problema.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kaitimo patirtis">
<feature>Šiuo naujiniu kai kuriuose scenarijuose optimizuojama kaitimo patirtis.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Šiuo naujiniu pagerinamas sistemos stabilumas, kad įrenginys veiktų stabiliau.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Saugumas">
<feature>Siekiant užtikrinti sistemos saugumą, įtraukta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2024 m. liepos mėn.). Jei reikia daugiau informacijos apie HONOR saugumo naujinius, apsilankykite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos:" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį atnaujinimą, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys ištrinti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama iš anksto padaryti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Jei atnaujinimo metu kyla problemų, skambinkite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba kreipkitės pagalbos į HONOR priežiūros centrą.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo ieteicamo atjauninājumu tiek pievienota globālā izlase, lietotne HONOR dokumenti un sākuma ekrāna ikonas izmēra pielāgošanas funkcija, optimizēts attēlveidošanas efekts dažos scenārijos, novērsts neparasts enerģijas patēriņš dažos ainās, uzlabota sistēmas veiktspēja, stabilitāte un sildīšanas pieredze, kā arī iekļauts drošības ielāps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globālā izlase">
<feature>Šis atjauninājums nodrošina tikko jaunināto globālo izlasi. Velciet uz leju ar trim pirkstiem, lai izlases vietā saglabātu materiālus, piemēram, attēlus, tīmekļa lapas un failus. Pieskarieties, lai izvērstu izlases vietu, nospiediet un turiet atlasīto vienu vai vairākus vienumus, lai vilktu tos uz citām lietotnēm, un varat arī sinhronizēt tos ar citām MagicRing ierīcēm, lai kopīgotu savākto saturu dažādās ierīcēs.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR dokumenti">
<feature>Ar šo atjauninājumu tiek nodrošināta pilnīgi jauna lietotne HONOR dokumenti un interaktīvais interfeiss, pievienotas pielāgotas etiķetes, atkritne un citas funkcijas, uzlabota dokumentu stabilitāte un saderība, kā arī nodrošinātas labākas lietošanas iespējas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sākuma ekrāna ikonas">
<feature>Sākuma ekrāna ikonu izmēru var pielāgot, lai atbilstu lietotāju dažādajām vajadzībām. Varat to izbaudīt, atverot: Iestatījumi -> Sākuma ekrāns un stils -> Sākuma ekrāna iestatījumi -> Ikonas izmērs.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Atskaņotājs">
<feature>Ar šo atjauninājumu ierīcē ir pievienots mūzikas atskaņotājs.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Ar šo atjauninājumu dažos gadījumos tiek optimizēts telefoto uzņemšanas spilgtums un krāsu efekts.
Ar šo atjauninājumu dažos gadījumos tiek optimizēts portreta fokusa attēlveidošanas efekts.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Veiktspēja">
<feature>Šis atjauninājums novērš nejaušas kavēšanās problēmu, palaižot dažas lietotnes.
Ar šo atjauninājumu tiek optimizēta nejaušu kadru kritumu problēma lietotnes startēšanas kustības efektā.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Enerģijas patēriņš">
<feature>Šis atjauninājums novērš neparastu enerģijas patēriņa problēmu dažos scenārijos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sildīšanas pieredze">
<feature>Ar šo atjauninājumu ir optimizēta sildīšanas pieredze dažiem scenārijiem.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistēma">
<feature>Ar šo atjauninājumu ir uzlabota sistēmas stabilitāte, padarot jūsu ierīci stabilāku.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Drošība">
<feature>Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2024. gada jūlijs). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par HONOR drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Instalējot šo atjauninājumu, jūsu personas dati netiks dzēsti, taču joprojām ir ieteicams iepriekš izveidot dublējumu.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, lūdzu, zvaniet HONOR uzziņu dienestam vai dodieties uz HONOR klientu servisa centru, lai saņemtu atbalstu.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अनुशंसित अपडेट ग्लोबल पसिन्नगर सभ, HONOR डॉक्स आ होम स्क्रीन आइकन आकार समायोजित करबाक फंक्शन जोड़ैत अछि, किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे इमेजिंग प्रभाव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि, किछु दृश्य सभ मे असामान्य बिजलीक खपत केर समस्याक समाधान करैत अछि, सिस्टमक कार्य-क्षमता, स्थिरता आ गरम होयबाक अनुभव मे सुधार करैत अछि आओर सुरक्षा पैच समाविष्ट करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ग्लोबल पसिन्नगर सभ">
<feature>ई अपडेट नव अपग्रेड कयल गेल ग्लोबल पसिन्नगर सभ अनैत अछि। इमेज, वेब पेज आ फाइल सभ सन सामग्री सभ केँ पसिन्नगर स्पेस मे संरक्षित करबाक लेल तीन आँगुर सँ निचां दिस स्वाइप करू। पसिन्नगर स्पेस केँ विस्तारित करबाक लेल टैप करू, चयनित एकटा वा एकाधिक वस्तु सभ केँ अन्य एप सभ पर खींचबाक लेल ओकरासभ केँ दबाउ आ थामि कए राखू आओर संग्रहित कंटेंट केँ डिवाइस सभक बीच साझा करबाक लेल अहाँ ओकरासभ केँ अन्य MagicRing डिवाइस सभ सँ सिंक्रोनाइज कए सकैत छी।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR डॉक्स">
<feature>ई अपडेट एकदम नव HONOR डॉक्स आ इंटरैक्टिव इंटरफेस प्रदान करैत अछि, अनुकूलन लेबल, रीसायकल बिन आ अन्य फंक्शन जोड़ैत अछि, डॉक्युमेंट स्थिरता आ संगतता मे सुधार करैत अछि आओर एकटा बेहतर उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव प्रदान करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="होम स्क्रीन आइकन सभ">
<feature>उपयोगकर्ता सभक विभिन्न आवश्यकता सभ केँ पूरा करबाक लेल होम स्क्रीन आइकन केर आकार केँ समायोजित कयल जा सकैत अछि। अहाँ एहि मे जा कए एकरा अनुभव कए सकैत छी: सेटिंग्स -> होम स्क्रीन आ शैली -> होम स्क्रीनक सेटिंग्स -> आइकनक आकार।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्लेयर">
<feature>ई अपडेट डिवाइस पर म्यूजिक प्लेयर जोड़ैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कैमरा">
<feature>ई अपडेट किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे टेलीफोटो शूटिंग केर चमक आ रंग प्रभाव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि।
ई अपडेट किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे पोर्ट्रेट फोकस इमेजिंग प्रभाव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कार्य-प्रदर्शन">
<feature>ई अपडेट किछु एप सभ आरंभ करैत काल रैंडम लैग केर समस्याक समाधान करैत अछि।
ई अपडेट एप शुरू करैत काल केर मोशन प्रभाव मे रैंडम फ्रेम ड्रॉप केर समस्या केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="बिजलीक खपत">
<feature>ई अपडेट किछु दृश्य सभ मे असामान्य बिजलीक खपत केर समस्याक समाधान करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गरम होयबाक अनुभव">
<feature>किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे ई अपडेट गरम होयबाक अनुभव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>ई अपडेट सिस्टमक स्थिरता मे सुधार कयलक अछि, जाहि सँ अहाँक डिवाइस बेसी स्थिर रूप सँ चलि सकए।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (जुलाई 2024) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहि मेटायत मुदा पहिने सँ एकटा बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' सहायताक लेल कृपाकए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन केँ कॉल करू वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाउ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E te kaiwhakamahi, ka tāpiri tēnei whakahōutanga manako i Ngā Makau Aowhānui, HONOR Docs me te taumahi o te whakarite i te rahi ata mata kāinga, ka arotau i te pānga atahanga ki ētahi tauari, ka whakatika i te take o te whakapetonga hiko rerekē i ētahi tirohanga, ka whakapai ake i te mahinga pūnaha, te mauritanga me te wheako whakamātao, ā, ka whakauru i tētahi āpure haumarutanga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Makau Aowhānui">
<feature>Ka kawea mai e tēnei whakahōu Ngā Makau Aowhānui noa kua whakamohoatia. Miri whakararo me ngā matimati e toru hei tiaki rauemi, pēnei i ngā atahanga, ngā whārangi tukutuku me ngā kōnae, ki te Mokowā ngā Makau. Pato hei whakaroha i te Mokowā ngā Makau, pēhi me te pupuri i ngā tūemi kua tīpakohia hei tō ki tētahi atu taupānga, ā, ka taea hoki e koe te tukutahi ki ētahi atu pūrere MagicRing hei tiri ihirangi kohikohi puta noa i ngā pūrere.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Mā tēnei whakahōu e tuku i ngā HONOR Docs hōu me te atanga tauwhiti hōu, ka tāpiri tapanga ritenga, te ipu para me tētahi atu taumahi, ka whakapai ake i te taimautanga tuhinga me te hototahitanga, ā, ka tuku wheako kaiwhakamahi pai ake.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā tohu mata kāinga">
<feature>Ka taea te huri i te rahi o ngā ata mata Kāinga kia tutuki ai ngā hiahia rerekē o ngā kaiwhakamahi. Ka taea e koe te wheako mā te haere: Ngā Tautuhinga - > Mata Kāinga me te kāhua - > Ngā tautuhinga mata kāinga - > rahi Ata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pūpāpāho">
<feature>Ka tāpiri tēnei whakahōu i te Pūpurei puoro i runga i te pūrere.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kāmera">
<feature>Ka arotautia e tēnei whakahōu te tīahonga me te pānga tae o te tākaro arotahiroa i ētahi tauari.
Ka arotautia e tēnei whakahōu te rākeitanga atahanga pānga arotahi poutū i ētahi tauari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mahinga">
<feature>Ka whakatika tēnei whakahōu i te raruraru o te takamuri matapōkere ina whakarewatanga i ētahi taupānga.
Ka arotau e tēnei whakahōu te raruraru o te tāpare matapōkere e taka ana i roto i te rākeitanga pānga whakaoho taupānga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Whakapetonga hiko">
<feature>Mā tēnei whakahōu e whakatika te take o te whakapetonga hiko rerekē i ētahi tirohanga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Te whakawera wheako">
<feature>Ka arotau e tēnei whakahōu te wheako whakawera i ētahi tauari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pūnaha">
<feature>Mā tēnei whakahōu ka whakapai ake i te taimautanga pūnaha kia pai ake ai te haere o tō pūrere.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Haumarutanga">
<feature>Kua whakaurua te Āpure Haumarutanga Android (Hōngongoi 2024) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga HONOR, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore te tāuta i tēnei whakahōu e ūkui i ō raraunga whaiaro, engari e manakohia tonutia ana tētahi pūrua i mua.
2. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōutanga, waea atu koa ki te waewera ratonga HONOR, ka haere rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki HONOR hei tautoko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова препорачано ажурирање ги додава Глобални омилени, HONOR Docs и функцијата за прилагодување на големината на иконите на почетниот екран, го оптимизира ефектот на сликање во некои сценарија, го исправа проблемот на абнормална потрошувачка на енергија во некои сцени, ги подобрува перформансите на системот, стабилноста и искуството со греењето и вградува безбедносна крпеница.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Глобални омилени">
<feature>Ова ажурирање ја носи новонадградената Глобални омилени. Поминете надолу со три прста за да зачувате материјали, како што се слики, веб-страници и датотеки, во Простор за омилени. Допрете за да ја проширите Простор за омилени, притиснете и задржете врз избраната ставка или повеќе ставки за да ги повлечете кон други апликации, а може и да ги синхронизирате со други уреди со MagicRing за споделување на собраната содржина меѓу уредите.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Ова ажурирање обезбедува сосем нови HONOR Docs и интерактивен интерфејс, додава приспособени ознаки, канта за отпадоци и други функции, ги подобрува стабилноста и компатибилноста на документите и обезбедува подобро корисничко искуство.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Икони на почетниот екран">
<feature>Големината на иконите на почетниот екран може да се прилагоди за да се задоволат различните потреби на корисниците. Може да го искусите тоа со одење во: Нагодување -> Почетен екран и стил -> Поставки за почетниот екран -> Големина на икони.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Репродуктор">
<feature>Ова ажурирање ја додава Репродуктор на музика на уредот.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Ова ажурирање го оптимизира ефектот на осветленоста и боите при телефотографско сликање во некои сценарија.
Ова ажурирање го оптимизира ефектот на сликање со фокус за портрет во некои сценарија.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Перформанси">
<feature>Ова ажурирање го исправа проблемот на случајно одложување кога се вклучуваат некои апликации.
Ова ажурирање го оптимизира проблемот со случајни опаѓања во кадрите на ефектот на движење при стартување на апликациите.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Потрошувачка на енергија">
<feature>Ова ажурирање го поправа проблемот на абнормална потрошувачка на енергија во некои сцени.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Искуство со греењето">
<feature>Ова ажурирање го оптимизира искуството со греењето во некои сценарија.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>Ова ажурирање ја подобрува стабилноста на системот за уредот да работи постабилно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безбедност">
<feature>Вградена е безбедносна крпеница за Android (јули 2024) за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за ажурирања на безбедноста од HONOR, посетете ја нашата веб-локација https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да ги избрише вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува однапред да направите резервна копија.
2. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, повикајте го телефонскиот број на службата на HONOR или одете во центарот за услуги за корисници на HONOR за да добиете поддршка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്ന അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഗ്ലോബൽ ഫേവറിറ്റ്‌സ്, HONOR Docs, ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കൺ വലുപ്പം ക്രമീകരിക്കൽ പ്രവർത്തനം എന്നിവ ചേർക്കുകയും ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ ഇമേജിംഗ് ഇഫക്റ്റ് ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുകയും ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ അസ്വാഭാവിക വൈദ്യുതി ഉപഭോഗത്തിന്റെ പ്രശ്‌നം പരിഹരിക്കുകയും സിസ്റ്റം പ്രകടനവും സ്ഥിരതയും താപനില ഉയരൽ അനുഭവവും മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ഒരു സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ഗ്ലോബൽ ഫേവറിറ്റ്‌സ്">
<feature>ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പുതുതായി അപ്‌ഗ്രേഡ് ചെയ്‌ത 'ഗ്ലോബൽ ഫേവറിറ്റ്‌സ്' കൊണ്ടുവരുന്നു. ഇമേജുകളും വെബ് പേജുകളും ഫയലുകളും പോലുള്ള മെറ്റീരിയലുകൾ ഫേവറിറ്റ്‌സ് സ്‌പെയ്‌സിൽ സംരക്ഷിക്കാൻ മൂന്ന് വിരലുകൾ ഉപയോഗിച്ച് താഴേക്ക് സ്വൈപ്പ് ചെയ്യുക. 'ഫേവറിറ്റ്‌സ് സ്‌പെയ്‌സ്' വികസിപ്പിക്കാൻ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുക, മറ്റ് ആപ്പുകളിലേക്ക് തിരഞ്ഞെടുത്ത ഒന്നോ അതിലധികമോ ഇനങ്ങൾ ഡ്രാഗ് ചെയ്യാൻ അവ അമർത്തിപ്പിടിക്കുക, ഇതിനുപുറമേ ശേഖരിച്ച ഉള്ളടക്കം ഉപകരണങ്ങളിലുടനീളം പങ്കിടാനായി നിങ്ങൾക്ക് അവ മറ്റ് MagicRing ഉപകരങ്ങളുമായി സമന്വയിപ്പിക്കാനും കഴിയും.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പുതുപുത്തൻ HONOR Docs-ഉം സംവേദനാത്മക ഇന്റർഫേസും നൽകുകയും ഇഷ്‌ടാനുസൃത ലേബലുകൾ, റീസൈക്കിൾ ബിൻ, മറ്റ് പ്രവർത്തനങ്ങൾ എന്നിവ ചേർക്കുകയും ഡോക്യുമെന്റ് സ്ഥിരതയും അനുയോജ്യതയും മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ഒരു മികച്ച ഉപയോക്തൃ അനുഭവം നൽകുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കണുകൾ">
<feature>ഉപയോക്താക്കളുടെ വ്യത്യസ്‌ത ആവശ്യകതകൾ നിറവേറ്റാനായി ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കണുകളുടെ വലുപ്പം ക്രമീകരിക്കാൻ കഴിയും. നിങ്ങൾക്ക് ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് അനുഭവിച്ചറിയാം: ക്രമീകരണം -> ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനും ശൈലിയും -> ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ക്രമീകരണം -> ഐക്കൺ വലുപ്പം.</feature>
</features>
<features module="പ്ലെയർ">
<feature>ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഉപകരണത്തിൽ സംഗീത പ്ലെയർ ചേർക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ക്യാമറ">
<feature>ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ ടെലിഫോട്ടോ ഷൂട്ടിംഗിന്റെ പ്രകാശവും വർണ്ണ ഇഫക്റ്റും ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു.
ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ പോർട്രെയ്‌റ്റ് ഫോക്കസ് ഇമേജിംഗ് ഇഫക്റ്റ് ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="പ്രകടനം">
<feature>ചില ആപ്പുകൾ സമാരംഭിക്കുമ്പോഴുള്ള റാൻഡം ലാഗ് ചെയ്യലിന്റെ പ്രശ്‌നം ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പരിഹരിക്കുന്നു.
ആപ്പ് ആരംഭിക്കുമ്പോൾ ചലന ഇഫക്റ്റിൽ ഉണ്ടാകുന്ന റാൻഡം ഫ്രെയിം ഡ്രോപ്പുകളുടെ പ്രശ്‌നം ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പരിഹരിക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="വൈദ്യുതി ഉപഭോഗം">
<feature>ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ അസ്വാഭാവിക വൈദ്യുതി ഉപഭോഗത്തിന്റെ പ്രശ്‌നം ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് പരിഹരിക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="താപനില ഉയരൽ അനുഭവം">
<feature>ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ താപനില ഉയരൽ അനുഭവം ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സിസ്റ്റം">
<feature>നിങ്ങളുടെ ഉപകരണം കൂടുതൽ സ്ഥിരതയോടെ പ്രവർത്തിക്കാൻ ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് സിസ്റ്റം സ്ഥിരത മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സുരക്ഷ">
<feature>സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (ജൂലൈ 2024) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. HONOR സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ ഔദ്യോഗിക വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് ആയ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7 സന്ദർശിക്കുക</feature>
</features>
<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ മായ്‌ക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും മുൻകൂട്ടി ഒരു ബാക്കപ്പ് എടുത്തുവയ്‌ക്കാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കായി HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү санал болгож буй шинэчлэлтээр Global Favorites, HONOR Docs, үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зургийн хэмжээг тохируулах функцийг нэмж, зарим тохиолдол дахь дүрсний эффектийг оновчилж, зарим тохиолдол дахь хэвийн бус эрчим хүчний хэрэглээний асуудлыг засаж, системийн гүйцэтгэл, тогтвортой байдал, халдаг байдлыг сайжруулж, хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг багтаав.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Global Favorites">
<feature>Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр шинээр сайжруулсан Global Favorites-г хүргэнэ. Зураг, веб хуудас, файл гэх мэт материалыг Favorites Space-д хадгалахын тулд гурван хуруугаараа доош зурна уу. Favorites Space-г дэлгэхийн тулд товшиж, сонгосон нэг эсвэл хэд хэдэн зүйл дээр удаан дараад бусад апликэйшн рүү чирнэ үү. Мөн та цуглуулсан контентоо төхөөрөмж хооронд хуваалцахын тулд тэдгээрийг бусад MagicRing төхөөрөмжтэй синхрончилж болно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Энэ шинэчлэлтээр цоо шинэ HONOR Docs, интерактив интерфейстэй болж, тусгай шошго, хогийн сав, бусад функц нэмэн, бичиг баримтын тогтвортой байдал, нийцтэй байдлыг нэмэгдүүлж, хэрэглэгчийн туршлагыг сайжруулав.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зураг">
<feature>Үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зургийн хэмжээг хэрэглэгчдийн янз бүрийн хэрэгцээнд нийцүүлэн тохируулах боломжтой. Та Тохиргоо -> Үндсэн дэлгэц ба хэв маяг -> Үндсэн дэлгэцийн тохиргоо -> Шигтгээ зургийн хэмжээ рүү очиж үүнийг туршиж болно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тоглуулагч">
<feature>Энэ шинэчлэлтээр төхөөрөмж дээр Хөгжим тоглуулагч нэмсэн.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камер">
<feature>Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр зарим тохиолдол дахь телефото зураг авалтын тодролт, өнгөний эффектийг оновчилсон.
Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр зарим тохиолдол дахь хөрөг зургийн фокустай дүрслэлийн эффектийг оновчилсон.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Гүйцэтгэл">
<feature>Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр зарим апликэйшнийг эхлүүлэх үед санамсаргүй хоцрох асуудлыг зассан.
Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр апликэйшн эхлүүлэх хөдөлгөөний нөлөөнд санамсаргүй фрэйм унах асуудлыг оновчилсон.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Эрчим хүчний хэрэглээ">
<feature>Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр зарим тохиолдол дахь хэвийн бус эрчим хүчний хэрэглээний асуудлыг зассан.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Халдаг байдал">
<feature>Энэ шинэчлэлтээр зарим тохиолдолд халдаг байдлыг оновчилсон.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр таны төхөөрөмжийг илүү тогтвортой ажиллуулахын тулд системийн тогтвортой байдлыг нэмэгдүүлэв.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хамгаалалт">
<feature>Системийн хамгаалалтад зориулж Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2024 оны долдугаар сар) багтаав. HONOR-н хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэл авах бол манай дараах вебсайтад зочилно уу: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгахад таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч урьдчилан нөөцлөхийг зөвлөж байна.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад аливаа асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төвд зочилж тусламж авна уу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे शिफारस केलेले अद्यतन जागतिक आवडते, HONOR दस्तऐवज आणि मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्‍ह आकार समायोजित करण्याचे कार्य जोडते, काही परिस्थितींमध्ये प्रतिमांचा प्रभाव ऑप्टिमाइझ करते, काही दृश्यांमध्ये असामान्य पॉवर वापराच्या समस्येचे निराकरण करते, सिस्टम कार्यप्रदर्शन, स्थिरता आणि गरम होण्याचा अनुभव सुधारते आणि सुरक्षितता पॅच समाविष्ट करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="जागतिक आवडते">
<feature>हे अद्यतन नव्याने अपग्रेड केलेले जागतिक आवडते आणते. प्रतिमा, वेब पृष्ठे आणि फाइल्स यांसारखी सामग्री, फेव्हरेट स्पेस मध्ये जतन करण्यासाठी तीन बोटांनी खाली स्वाइप करा. फेव्हरेट स्पेसचा विस्तार करण्यासाठी टॅप करा, निवडलेले एक किंवा एकापेक्षा जास्त आयटम्स अन्य ॲप्सवर ड्रॅग करण्यासाठी ते दाबा आणि धरून ठेवा आणि आपण संकलित केलेली सामग्री उपकरणांवर सामायिक करण्यासाठी त्यांना अन्य MagicRing उपकरणांवर देखील सिंक्रोनाइझ करू शकता.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR दस्तऐवज">
<feature>हे अद्यतन अगदी नवीन HONOR दस्तऐवज आणि परस्पर संवाद प्रदान करते, सानुकूल लेबल्स, रिसायकल बिन आणि अन्य फंक्शन्स जोडते, दस्तऐवज स्थिरता आणि सुसंगतता सुधारते आणि एक अधिक चांगला वापरकर्ता अनुभव प्रदान करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्ह">
<feature>वापरकर्त्यांच्या विविध गरजा पूर्ण करण्यासाठी मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्हांचा आकार समायोजित केला जाऊ शकतो. येथे जाऊन आपण याचा अनुभव घेऊ शकता: सेटिंग्ज -> मुख्य स्क्रीन आणि शैली -> मुख्य स्क्रीन सेटिंग्ज -> चिन्हाचा आकार.</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्‍लेयर">
<feature>हे अद्यतन उपकरणावर Music प्लेयर जोडते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="कॅमेरा">
<feature>हे अद्यतन काही परिस्थितींमध्ये टेलीफोटो शूटिंगचा ब्राइटनेस आणि कलर प्रभाव ऑप्टिमाइझ करते.
हे अद्यतन काही परिस्थितींमध्ये पोर्ट्रेट फोकस प्रतिमांचा प्रभाव ऑप्टिमाइझ करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="कार्यप्रदर्शन">
<feature>हे अद्यतन काही ॲप्स लाँच करताना रँडम लॅगिंगच्या समस्येचे निराकरण करते.
हे अद्यतन ॲप स्टार्टअप मोशन इफेक्टमध्ये यादृच्छिक फ्रेम ड्रॉपची समस्या ऑप्टिमाइझ करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="पॉवर वापर">
<feature>हे अद्यतन काही दृश्यांमध्ये असामान्य पॉवर वापराच्या समस्येचे निराकरण करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="गरम होण्याचा अनुभव">
<feature>हे अद्यतन काही परिस्थितींमध्ये गरम होण्याचा अनुभव ऑप्टिमाइझ करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>हे अद्यतन आपले उपकरण अधिक स्थिरपणे चालण्‍यासाठी सिस्‍टम स्‍थिरता सुधारते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षितता">
<feature>सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षितता पॅच (जुलै 2024) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. HONOR सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7 वर जा</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्थापित केल्याने आपला वैयक्तिक डेटा मिटणार नाही, परंतु आधीच बॅकअप घेण्याची अजूनही शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करा किंवा समर्थनासाठी HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जा.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini yang disyorkan ini menambah Kegemaran Global, HONOR Docs serta fungsi melaraskan saiz ikon skrin utama, mengoptimumkan kesan pengimejan dalam beberapa senario, membetulkan isu penggunaan kuasa yang tidak normal dalam beberapa latar, meningkatkan prestasi sistem, kestabilan dan pengalaman pemanasan serta memasukkan tampalan keselamatan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kegemaran Global">
<feature>Kemas kini ini memperkenalkan Kegemaran Global yang baru dinaik taraf. Leret ke bawah dengan tiga jari untuk menyimpan bahan, seperti imej, halaman web dan fail, pada Ruang Kegemaran. Ketik untuk mengembangkan Ruang Kegemaran, tekan dan tahan satu atau berbilang item pilihan untuk diseret kepada aplikasi lain dan anda juga boleh menyegerakkan kandungan yang dikumpulkan kepada peranti MagicRing yang lain untuk berkongsi merentas peranti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Kemas kini ini menyediakan HONOR Docs serta antara muka interaktif serba baharu, menambah label tersuai, tong kitar semula dan fungsi lain, meningkatkan kestabilan serta keserasian dokumen dan memberikan pengalaman pengguna yang lebih baik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikon skrin utama">
<feature>Saiz ikon Skrin utama boleh dilaraskan untuk memenuhi keperluan pengguna yang berbeza. Anda boleh mencuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan -> Skrin utama dan gaya -> Tetapan skrin utama -> Saiz ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pemain">
<feature>Kemas kini ini menambahkan Pemain Muzik pada peranti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Kemas kini ini mengoptimumkan kecerahan dan kesan warna penangkapan telefoto dalam beberapa senario.
Kemas kini ini mengoptimumkan kesan pengimejan fokus potret dalam beberapa senario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prestasi">
<feature>Kemas kini ini membetulkan masalah bebatan rawak semasa melancarkan beberapa aplikasi.
Kemas kini ini mengoptimumkan masalah kejatuhan bingkai rawak dalam kesan gerakan permulaan aplikasi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Penggunaan kuasa">
<feature>Kemas kini ini membetulkan isu penggunaan kuasa yang tidak normal dalam beberapa latar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pengalaman pemanasan">
<feature>Kemas kini ini mengoptimumkan pengalaman pemanasan dalam beberapa senario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Kemas kini ini meningkatkan kestabilan sistem untuk membolehkan peranti anda berjalan dengan lebih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keselamatan">
<feature>Tampalan Keselamatan Android (Jul 2024) telah dimasukkan untuk keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan HONOR, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Pemasangan kemas kini ini tidak akan memadamkan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda disyorkan agar masih membuat sandaran terlebih dahulu.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, sila hubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau pergi ke pusat khidmat pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan sokongan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ အကြံပြုထားသော ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် ဂလိုဘယ် အကြိုက်ဆုံး၊ HONOR Docs နှင့် ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် အိုင်ကွန်အရွယ်အစား ချိန်ညှိသည့် လုပ်ဆောင်ချက် ထည့်ပေးထားသည်၊ အချို့အခြေအနေများတွင် ရုပ်ပုံ အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်၊ အချို့ဖြစ်ရပ်များတွင် ပါဝါ သုံးစွဲမှု မူမမှန်သည့် ပြဿနာကို ဖြေရှင်းပေးပြီး စနစ် စွမ်းဆောင်ရည်၊ တည်ငြိမ်မှုနှင့် သုံးစွဲစဉ် အပူထွက်ခြင်းအတွက် တိုးတက်ကောင်းမွန်လာအောင် မွမ်းမံပေးကာ လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ဂလိုဘယ် အကြိုက်ဆုံး">
<feature>ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် လောလောလတ်လတ် အဆင့်မြှင့်တင်ထားသော ဂလိုဘယ် အကြိုက်ဆုံးကို ပေးအပ်ထားသည်။ ရုပ်ပုံများ၊ ဝက်ဘ်စာမျက်နှာများနှင့် ဖိုင်များကဲ့သို့ ပစ္စည်းများကို Favorites Space တွင် သိမ်းဆည်းရန် လက်သုံးချောင်းဖြင့် အောက်သို့ ပွတ်ဆွဲပါ။ Favorites Space ကို ဖြန့်ရန် နှိပ်ပါ၊ ရွေးချယ်ထားသောတစ်ခု သို့မဟုတ် များစွာကို ဖိ၍နှိပ်ထားပြီး ၎င်းတို့ကို အခြားအက်ပ်များဆီသို့ ဆွဲရွှေ့ပါ၊ စုဆောင်းထားသော အကြောင်းအရာကို စက်များအကြား မျှဝေရန် ၎င်းတို့ကို အခြား MagicRing စက်များသို့လည်း ချိန်ကိုက်နိုင်သည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အသစ်စက်စက် HONOR Docs နှင့် အပြန်အလှန်တုံ့ပြန် ဆောင်ရွက်နိုင်သော ကြားခံစနစ်ကို ပံ့ပိုးပေးသည်၊ စိတ်ကြိုက် အညွှန်းများ၊ အမှိုက်ပုံးနှင့် အခြားလုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များကို ထည့်ပေးထားပြီး စာရွက်စာတမ်း တည်မြဲမှုနှင့် ကိုက်ညီနိုင်စွမ်းကို မြှင့်တင်ပေးကာ သုံးစွဲသူ အတွေ့အကြုံ ပိုကောင်းစေရန် ထောက်ကူပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် အိုင်ကွန်များ">
<feature>သုံးစွဲသူများ၏ လိုအပ်ချက်အမျိုးမျိုးနှင့် ကိုက်ညီစေရန် ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် အိုင်ကွန်များ၏ အရွယ်အစားကို ချိန်ညှိနိုင်သည်။ သင်သည် ဆက်တင် -> ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်နှင့် စတိုင် -> ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် ဆက်တင် -> အိုင်ကွန် အရွယ်အစားသို့ သွား၍ ၎င်းကို တွေ့ကြုံသုံးစွဲနိုင်သည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Player">
<feature>ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် စက်တွင် Music Player ထည့်ထားသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ကင်မရာ">
<feature>ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အချို့အခြေအနေများတွင် အဝေးရိုက်ကူးခြင်း၌ တောက်ပမှုနှင့် အရောင် အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။
ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အချို့အခြေအနေများတွင် အလှပုံအသားပေး ရုပ်ပုံ အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စွမ်းဆောင်ရည်">
<feature>ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အချို့အက်ပ်များကို ဖွင့်သည့်အခါ ရံဖန်ရံခါ ထစ်သည့်ပြဿနာကို ဖြေရှင်းပေးသည်။
ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အက်ပ်စတင်ချိန် လှုပ်ရှားမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်တွင် ရံဖန်ရံခါ ချိတ်ဆက်မှုမတည်ငြိမ်သည့် ပြဿနာကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပါဝါ သုံးစွဲမှု">
<feature>ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အချို့ဖြစ်ရပ်များတွင် ပါဝါ သုံးစွဲမှု မူမမှန်သည့် ပြဿနာကို ဖြေရှင်းပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="သုံးစွဲစဉ် အပူထွက်ခြင်း">
<feature>ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် အချို့အခြေအနေများ၌ သုံးစွဲစဉ် အပူထွက်ခြင်းအတွက် အကောင်းဆုံးဖြစ်စေရန် ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ်">
<feature>သင့်စက်ကို ပိုမိုတည်ငြိမ်စွာ လုပ်ဆောင်နိုင်စေရန် ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် စနစ် တည်ငြိမ်မှုကို တိုးမြှင့်ပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံခြုံရေး">
<feature>စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (ဇူလိုင် 2024) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ HONOR လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို သိရှိရန် ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ်သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းသည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာကို ဖျက်မည် မဟုတ်သော်လည်း ကြိုတင်၍ ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်နေစဉ် ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခု ကြုံတွေ့ပါက အကူအညီရယူရန် HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆိုပါ သို့မဟုတ် HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ အႀကံျပဳထားေသာ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ ဂလိုဘယ္ အႀကိဳက္ဆုံး၊ HONOR Docs ႏွင့္ ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ အိုင္ကြန္အ႐ြယ္အစား ခ်ိန္ညႇိသည့္ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္ ထည့္ေပးထားသည္၊ အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ားတြင္ ႐ုပ္ပုံ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္၊ အခ်ိဳ႕ျဖစ္ရပ္မ်ားတြင္ ပါဝါ သုံးစြဲမႈ မူမမွန္သည့္ ျပႆနာကို ေျဖရွင္းေပးၿပီး စနစ္ စြမ္းေဆာင္ရည္၊ တည္ၿငိမ္မႈႏွင့္ သုံးစြဲစဥ္ အပူထြက္ျခင္းအတြက္ တိုးတက္ေကာင္းမြန္လာေအာင္ မြမ္းမံေပးကာ လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ဂလိုဘယ္ အႀကိဳက္ဆုံး">
<feature>ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ ေလာေလာလတ္လတ္ အဆင့္ျမႇင့္တင္ထားေသာ ဂလိုဘယ္ အႀကိဳက္ဆုံးကို ေပးအပ္ထားသည္။ ႐ုပ္ပုံမ်ား၊ ဝက္ဘ္စာမ်က္ႏွာမ်ားႏွင့္ ဖိုင္မ်ားကဲ့သို႔ ပစၥည္းမ်ားကို Favorites Space တြင္ သိမ္းဆည္းရန္ လက္သုံးေခ်ာင္းျဖင့္ ေအာက္သို႔ ပြတ္ဆြဲပါ။ Favorites Space ကို ျဖန႔္ရန္ ႏွိပ္ပါ၊ ေ႐ြးခ်ယ္ထားေသာတစ္ခု သို႔မဟုတ္ မ်ားစြာကို ဖိ၍ႏွိပ္ထားၿပီး ၎တို႔ကို အျခားအက္ပ္မ်ားဆီသို႔ ဆြဲေ႐ႊ႕ပါ၊ စုေဆာင္းထားေသာ အေၾကာင္းအရာကို စက္မ်ားအၾကား မွ်ေဝရန္ ၎တို႔ကို အျခား MagicRing စက္မ်ားသို႔လည္း ခ်ိန္ကိုက္ႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အသစ္စက္စက္ HONOR Docs ႏွင့္ အျပန္အလွန္တုံ႔ျပန္ ေဆာင္႐ြက္ႏိုင္ေသာ ၾကားခံစနစ္ကို ပံ့ပိုးေပးသည္၊ စိတ္ႀကိဳက္ အၫႊန္းမ်ား၊ အမႈိက္ပုံးႏွင့္ အျခားလုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ားကို ထည့္ေပးထားၿပီး စာ႐ြက္စာတမ္း တည္ၿမဲမႈႏွင့္ ကိုက္ညီႏိုင္စြမ္းကို ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးကာ သုံးစြဲသူ အေတြ႕အႀကဳံ ပိုေကာင္းေစရန္ ေထာက္ကူေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ား">
<feature>သုံးစြဲသူမ်ား၏ လိုအပ္ခ်က္အမ်ိဳးမ်ိဳးႏွင့္ ကိုက္ညီေစရန္ ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ား၏ အ႐ြယ္အစားကို ခ်ိန္ညႇိႏိုင္သည္။ သင္သည္ ဆက္တင္ -> ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ႏွင့္ စတိုင္ -> ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ ဆက္တင္ -> အိုင္ကြန္ အ႐ြယ္အစားသို႔ သြား၍ ၎ကို ေတြ႕ႀကဳံသုံးစြဲႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Player">
<feature>ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ စက္တြင္ Music Player ထည့္ထားသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ကင္မရာ">
<feature>ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ားတြင္ အေဝး႐ိုက္ကူးျခင္း၌ ေတာက္ပမႈႏွင့္ အေရာင္ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။
ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ားတြင္ အလွပုံအသားေပး ႐ုပ္ပုံ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စြမ္းေဆာင္ရည္">
<feature>ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အခ်ိဳ႕အက္ပ္မ်ားကို ဖြင့္သည့္အခါ ရံဖန္ရံခါ ထစ္သည့္ျပႆနာကို ေျဖရွင္းေပးသည္။
ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အက္ပ္စတင္ခ်ိန္ လႈပ္ရွားမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္တြင္ ရံဖန္ရံခါ ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈမတည္ၿငိမ္သည့္ ျပႆနာကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပါဝါ သုံးစြဲမႈ">
<feature>ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အခ်ိဳ႕ျဖစ္ရပ္မ်ားတြင္ ပါဝါ သုံးစြဲမႈ မူမမွန္သည့္ ျပႆနာကို ေျဖရွင္းေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="သုံးစြဲစဥ္ အပူထြက္ျခင္း">
<feature>ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ား၌ သုံးစြဲစဥ္ အပူထြက္ျခင္းအတြက္ အေကာင္းဆုံးျဖစ္ေစရန္ ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ္">
<feature>သင့္စက္ကို ပိုမိုတည္ၿငိမ္စြာ လုပ္ေဆာင္ႏိုင္ေစရန္ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ စနစ္ တည္ၿငိမ္မႈကို တိုးျမႇင့္ေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံျခံဳေရး">
<feature>စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ဇူလိုင္ 2024) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ HONOR လုံၿခဳံေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို သိရွိရန္ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းသည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာကို ဖ်က္မည္ မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း ႀကိဳတင္၍ ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ေနစဥ္ ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခု ႀကဳံေတြ႕ပါက အကူအညီရယူရန္ HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆိုပါ သို႔မဟုတ္ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, denne anbefalte oppdateringen legger til Globale favoritter, HONOR Dokumenter og funksjonen for justering av størrelsen på startskjermikoner, optimerer bildeeffekten i enkelte scenarier, reparerer problemet med unormal batteribruk i enkelte scener, forbedrer systemytelsen, stabiliteten og opplevelsen av oppvarming, og innlemmer en sikkerhetsoppdatering.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globale favoritter">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen gir deg den nylig oppgraderte Globale favoritter. Sveip ned med tre fingre for å lagre materialer som bilder, nettsider og filer til Favorites Space. Trykk for å utvide Favorites Space, og trykk og hold på ett eller flere valgte elementer for å dra dem til andre apper. Du kan også synkronisere dem til andre MagicRing-enheter for å dele innhentet innhold på tvers av enheter.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Dokumenter">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen gir splitter nye HONOR Dokumenter og interaktivt grensesnitt, legger til egendefinerte etiketter, søppelkasse og andre funksjoner, forbedrer dokumentstabilitet og -kompatibilitet, samt gir en bedre brukeropplevelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Startskjermikoner">
<feature>Størrelsen på startskjermikoner kan justeres for å møte de ulike behovene til brukerne. Du kan oppleve den ved å gå til: Innstillinger -> Startskjerm og stil -> Innstillinger for startskjerm -> Ikonstørrelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Spiller">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen legger til Musikkspiller på enheten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen optimerer lysstyrken og fargeeffektene i telefotofotografering i enkelte scenarier.
Denne oppdateringen optimerer portrettfokusbildeeffekten i enkelte scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ytelse">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen reparerer problemet med tilfeldige forsinkelser når enkelte apper startes opp.
Denne oppdateringen optimerer problemet med tilfeldig reduksjon i bildehastighet i bevegelseseffekten for appoppstart.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Batteribruk">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen reparerer problemet med unormal batteribruk i enkelte scener.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opplevelse med oppvarming">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen optimerer opplevelsen med oppvarming i enkelte scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Denne oppdateringen forbedrer systemstabiliteten slik at enheten kjører jevnere.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhet">
<feature>Android-sikkerhetsoppdatering (juli 2024) er innlemmet for systemsikkerheten. For mer informasjon om sikkerhetsoppdateringer fra HONOR, besøk nettstedet vårt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notater:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke slette personopplysningene dine, men det anbefales likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer på forhånd.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, ring HONOR-kundeservice eller gå til HONOR-kundeservicesenteret for assistanse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, सिफारिस गरिएको यो अपडेटले ग्लोबल मनपर्नेहरू, HONOR कागजात र गृह स्क्रिन आइकनको आकार मिलाउने सुविधा समावेश गर्छ, केही परिदृश्यहरूमा फोटोको प्रभाव अप्टिमाइज गर्छ, र केही परिदृश्यमा असामान्य पावर खपतको समस्या समाधान गर्छ, प्रणालीको कार्यसम्पादन, स्थिरता र तात्ने अनुभव सुधार गर्छ र सुरक्षा प्याच समावेश गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ग्लोबल मनपर्नेहरू">
<feature>यो अपडेटले भर्खरै अपग्रेड गरिएको ग्लोबल मनपर्नेहरू उपलब्ध गराउँछ । छवि, वेब पेज र फाइलहरूलाई मनपर्नेहरू स्पेसमा बचत गर्न तीन औँलाले तलतिर स्वाइप गर्नुहोस् । मनपर्नेहरू स्पेस विस्तृत गर्न ट्याप गर्नुहोस्, चयन गरिएको वा धेरै वटा वस्तुहरूलाई तानेर अन्य एपमा लैजान थिचिराख्नुहोस् र तपाईं विभिन्न यन्त्रका बिचमा सङ्कलन गरिएका सामग्री साझा गर्न तिनलाई अन्य MagicRing यन्त्रहरूमा समक्रमण गर्न पनि सक्नुहुन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR कागजात">
<feature>यो अपडेटले बिल्कुलै नयाँ HONOR कागजात र अन्तरक्रियात्मक इन्टरफेस प्रदान गर्छ, अनुकूलन गरिएका लेबल, रिसाइकल बिन र अन्य प्रकार्यहरू समावेश गर्छ, कागजातको स्थिरता तथा कम्प्याटिबिलिटी सुधार गर्छ र अझ राम्रो प्रयोगकर्ता अनुभव प्रदान गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरू">
<feature>प्रयोगकर्ताका फरक फरक आवश्यकताहरू पूरा गर्नका लागि गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरूको आकार बदल्न मिल्छ । तपाईंले यहाँ गएर यसको अनुभव लिन सक्नुहुन्छ: सेटिङहरू -> गृह स्क्रिन र शैली -> गृह स्क्रिन सेटिङहरू -> आइकनको साइज ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्लेयर">
<feature>यो अपडेटले यन्त्रमा संगीत प्लेयर समावेश गरेको छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="क्यामेरा">
<feature>यो अपडेटले केही परिदृश्यमा टेलिफोटो सुटिङको चम्किलोपन र रङको प्रभाव अप्टिमाइज गर्छ ।
यो अपडेटले केही परिदृश्यहरूमा पोर्ट्रेट फोकस इमेजिङ प्रभाव अप्टिमाइज गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="कार्यसम्पादन">
<feature>यो अपडेटले केही एपहरू लन्च गर्दा अनियमित रूपमा ह्याङ हुने समस्या समाधान गर्छ ।
यो एपले एप सुरु गर्दा देखाइने मोसन प्रभावमा अनियमित रूपमा फ्रेम ड्रप हुने समस्या अप्टिमाइज गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="पावर खपत">
<feature>यो अपडेटले केही दृश्यमा असामान्य पावर खपतको समस्या समाधान गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="तात्ने अनुभव">
<feature>यो अपडेटले केही परिदृश्यहरूमा तात्ने अनुभव अप्टिमाइज गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्रणाली">
<feature>यो अपडेटले तपाईंको यन्त्रलाई थप स्थिर रूपमा चल्ने बनाउन प्रणालीको स्थिरतामा सुधार गरेको छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (जुलाई 2024) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेटबारे थप जानकारीका लागि, कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस्: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. यो अपडेट स्थापना गर्नाले तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटा मेटिने छैन, तर अझै पनि पहिले नै ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. अपडेटको समयमा तपाईंले कुनै पनि समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने, कृपया HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गर्नुहोस् वा सहायताका लागि HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा जानुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruiker, deze aanbevolen update voegt Globale favorieten, HONOR Docs en de functie voor het aanpassen van de grootte van startschermpictogrammen toe, optimaliseert het beeldeffect in bepaalde scenario's, lost het probleem van abnormaal energieverbruik in bepaalde scènes op, verbetert de prestaties, stabiliteit en opwarmingservaring van het systeem en bevat een beveiligingspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globale favorieten">
<feature>Deze update brengt nieuw geüpgradede Globale favorieten. Veeg met drie vingers naar beneden om materialen, zoals afbeeldingen, webpagina's en bestanden, op te slaan in Favorietenruimte. Tik om Favorietenruimte uit te klappen, houd het geselecteerde item of de meerdere geselecteerde items ingedrukt om ze naar andere apps te slepen en u kunt ze ook synchroniseren met andere MagicRing-apparaten om verzamelde inhoud tussen apparaten te delen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Deze update biedt een gloednieuwe HONOR Docs en interactieve interface, voegt aangepaste labels, prullenbak en andere functies toe, verbetert de stabiliteit en compatibiliteit van documenten en biedt een betere gebruikerservaring.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pictogrammen op het Startscherm">
<feature>De grootte van de pictogrammen op het Startscherm kan worden aangepast aan de verschillende behoeften van de gebruikers. U kunt het ervaren door te gaan naar: Instellingen -> Startscherm en stijl -> Startscherminstellingen -> Pictogramgrootte.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Speler">
<feature>Deze update voegt Muziekspeler aan het apparaat toe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Deze update optimaliseert in bepaalde scenario's de helderheid en het kleureffect van telefoto-opnamen.
Deze update optimaliseert het portretscherpstelbeeldeffect in bepaalde scenario's.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prestaties">
<feature>Deze update lost het probleem van willekeurige vertraging bij het starten van bepaalde apps op.
Deze update optimaliseert het probleem van willekeurige frameverminderingen in het bewegingseffect bij het opstarten van apps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energieverbruik">
<feature>Deze update lost het probleem van abnormaal energieverbruik in bepaalde scènes op.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opwarmingservaring">
<feature>Deze update optimaliseert de opwarmingservaring in bepaalde scenario's.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systeem">
<feature>Deze update verbetert de systeemstabiliteit om uw apparaat stabieler te laten werken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Beveiliging">
<feature>Android-beveiligingspatch (juli 2024) is opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over HONOR-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Als u deze update installeert, worden uw persoonlijke gegevens niet gewist, maar een back-up vooraf wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, bel dan de HONOR-servicehotline of ga naar een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum voor ondersteuning.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଥିବା ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ଗ୍ଲୋବାଲ୍‌ ମନପସନ୍ଦଗୁଡ଼ିକ, HONOR ଡକସ୍‌ ଏବଂ ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଆଇକନ୍ ଆକାର ଆଡଜଷ୍ଟ କରିବା ଫଙ୍କସନ୍ ଯୋଡ଼େ, କିଛି ପରିଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ପ୍ରତିଛବିରେ ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ, କିଛି ଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ଅସାମାନ୍ୟ ପାୱାର୍ ଖର୍ଚ୍ଚକୁ ସୁଧାର କରେ, ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ କାର୍ଯ୍ୟଦକ୍ଷତା, ସ୍ଥିରତା ଏବଂ ଗରମ ହେବା ଅନୁଭୂତିକୁ ବିକାଶ କରେ, ଏବଂ ଏକ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଗ୍ଲୋବାଲ୍‌ ମନପସନ୍ଦଗୁଡ଼ିକ">
<feature>ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ରେ ନୂତନ ଭାବେ ଅପଗ୍ରେଡ୍ ହୋଇଥିବା ଗ୍ଲୋବାଲ୍‌ ମନପସନ୍ଦଗୁଡ଼ିକ ରହିଛି। ପ୍ରତିଛବି, ୱେବ୍‌ ପୃଷ୍ଠା ଏବଂ ଫାଇଲ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ପରି ମେଟେରିଆଲ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ମନପସନ୍ଦ ସ୍ପେସ୍‌ରେ ସଞ୍ଚୟ କରିବାକୁ ତିନୋଟି ଆଙ୍ଗୁଠିରେ ତଳକୁ ସ୍ୱାଇପ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ। ମନପସନ୍ଦ ସ୍ପେସ୍‌ ସମ୍ପ୍ରସାରଣ କରିବାକୁ ଟ୍ୟାପ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ, ମନୋନୀତ ଗୋଟିକ କିମ୍ବା ଏକାଧିକ ଆଇଟମ୍ ଅନ୍ୟ ଆପସ୍‌କୁ ଡ୍ରାଗ୍ କରିବାକୁ ସେଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଦବାନ୍ତୁ ଏବଂ ଧରି ରଖନ୍ତୁ, ଏବଂ ସଂଗୃହୀତ ବିଷୟବସ୍ତୁ ସମସ୍ତ ଡିଭାଇସ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକରେ ଅଂଶୀଦାର କରିବାକୁ ଆପଣ ସେଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଅନ୍ୟ MagicRing ଡିଭାଇସ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକରେ ସିଙ୍କ୍ ମଧ୍ୟ କରିପାରିବେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR ଡକସ୍">
<feature>ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସମ୍ପୂର୍ଣ୍ଣ-ନୂତନ HONOR ଡକସ୍ ଏବଂ ଇଣ୍ଟରାକ୍ଟିଭ୍ ଇଣ୍ଟରଫେସ୍ ପ୍ରଦାନ କରେ, କଷ୍ଟମ୍ ଲେବଲ୍‌, ରିସାଇକେଲ୍‌ ବିନ୍ ତଥା ଅନ୍ୟାନ୍ୟ ଫଙ୍କସନ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଯୋଡ଼େ, ଡକ୍ୟୁମେଣ୍ଟ ସ୍ଥିରତା ଏବଂ ସୁସଙ୍ଗତତା ବିକାଶ କରେ, ଏବଂ ଏକ ଉତ୍ତମ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ଅନୁଭୂତି ପ୍ରଦାନ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଆଇକନଗୁଡିକ">
<feature>ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକର ଆକାର ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତାଙ୍କ ବିଭିନ୍ନ ଆବଶ୍ୟକତା ପୂରଣ କରିବାକୁ ଆଡଜଷ୍ଟ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଆପଣ ଏହାର ଅନୁଭୂତି ନେଇପାରିବେ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ -> ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଏବଂ ଷ୍ଟାଇଲ୍‌ -> ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ସେଟିଂସ୍ -> ଆଇକନ୍ ଆକାର।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ପ୍ଲେୟାର୍">
<feature>ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ଡିଭାଇସ୍‌ରେ ସଙ୍ଗୀତ ପ୍ଲେୟାର୍ ଯୋଡ଼େ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="କ୍ୟାମେରା">
<feature>ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କିଛି ପରିଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ଟେଲିଫଟୋ ଶୁଟିଂର ଔଜ୍ଜଲ୍ୟତା ଏବଂ ରଙ୍ଗ ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ।
ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କିଛି ପରିଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ପୋର୍ଟ୍ରେଟ୍‌ ଫୋକସ୍‌ ପ୍ରତିଛବିରେ ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="କାର୍ଯ୍ୟଦକ୍ଷତା">
<feature>କିଛି ଆପ୍‌ ଲଞ୍ଚ କରିବା ବେଳେ ରେଣ୍ଡମ ଲ୍ୟାଗ୍‌ କରିବା ସମସ୍ୟାକୁ ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସୁଧାର କରେ।
ଆପ୍‌ ଷ୍ଟାର୍ଟଅପ୍‌ ମୋସନ୍ ପ୍ରଭାବରେ ଫ୍ରେମ୍ ରେଣ୍ଡମ ଭାବେ ହ୍ରାସ ହେବା ସମସ୍ୟାକୁ ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ପାୱାର୍ ଖର୍ଚ୍ଚ">
<feature>କେତେକ ନିର୍ଦ୍ଦିଷ୍ଟ ଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ଅସାମାନ୍ୟ ପାୱାର୍‌ ଖର୍ଚ୍ଚ ସମସ୍ୟାକୁ ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସୁଧାର କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଗରମ ହେବା ଅନୁଭୂତି">
<feature>ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କେତେକ ପରିଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ଗରମ ହେବା ଅନୁଭୂତିକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌">
<feature>ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡିଭାଇସ୍‌ ଅଧିକ ସ୍ଥିର ଭାବେ ଚଲାଇବାକୁ, ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ ସ୍ଥିରତାକୁ ବିକାଶ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା">
<feature>Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ଜୁଲାଇ 2024) ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। HONOR ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ଲିଭାଇବ ନାହିଁ, କିନ୍ତୁ ଏହା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଏକ ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଦୟାକରି HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ସହାୟତା ପାଇଁ ଏକ HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੇ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਗਲੋਬਲ ਮਨਪਸੰਦਾਂ, HONOR ਦਸਤਾਵੇਜ਼ ਅਤੇ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਆਕਾਰ ਨੂੰ ਵਿਵਸਥਿਤ ਕਰਨ ਦੇ ਫੰਕਸ਼ਨ ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਇਮੇਜਿੰਗ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਅਸਧਾਰਨ ਪਾਵਰ ਖਪਤ ਦੀ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਨੂੰ ਠੀਕ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਕਾਰਗੁਜ਼ਾਰੀ, ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਅਤੇ ਹੀਟਿੰਗ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਗਲੋਬਲ ਮਨਪਸੰਦਾਂ">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਬਿਲਕੁਲ ਨਵੀਆਂ ਅੱਪਗ੍ਰੇਡ ਕੀਤੀਆਂ ਗਲੋਬਲ ਮਨਪਸੰਦਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਚਿੱਤਰਾਂ, ਵੈੱਬ ਪੰਨਿਆਂ ਅਤੇ ਫ਼ਾਈਲਾਂ ਵਰਗੀਆਂ ਸਮੱਗਰੀਆਂ ਨੂੰ ਮਨਪਸੰਦ ਥਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਤਿੰਨ ਉਂਗਲਾਂ ਨਾਲ ਹੇਠਾਂ ਵੱਲ ਸਵਾਈਪ ਕਰੋ। ਮਨਪਸੰਦ ਥਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਫੈਲਾਉਣ ਲਈ, ਚੁਣੀ ਗਈ ਇੱਕ ਆਈਟਮ ਜਾਂ ਚੁਣੀਆਂ ਗਈਆਂ ਮਲਟੀਪਲ ਆਈਟਮਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਡ੍ਰੈਗ ਕਰ ਕੇ ਹੋਰ ਐਪਾਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਲੈ ਜਾਣ ਲਈ ਦਬਾ ਕੇ ਰੱਖੋ, ਅਤੇ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਇਕੱਤਰ ਕੀਤੀ ਸਮੱਗਰੀ ਨੂੰ ਡਿਵਾਈਸਾਂ ਵਿਚਕਾਰ ਸਾਂਝਾ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਉਨ੍ਹਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਹੋਰ MagicRing ਡਿਵਾਈਸਾਂ ਨਾਲ ਸਿੰਕ ਵੀ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR ਦਸਤਾਵੇਜ਼">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਬਿਲਕੁਲ ਨਵਾਂ HONOR ਦਸਤਾਵੇਜ਼ ਅਤੇ ਇੰਟਰੈਕਟਿਵ ਇੰਟਰਫੇਸ ਪ੍ਰਦਾਨ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਕਸਟਮ ਲੇਬਲਾਂ, ਰੀਸਾਈਕਲ ਬਿਨ ਅਤੇ ਹੋਰ ਫੰਕਸ਼ਨਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਦਸਤਾਵੇਜ਼ ਦੀ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਅਤੇ ਅਨੁਕੂਲਤਾ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਬਿਹਤਰ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਪ੍ਰਦਾਨ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਹੋਮ ਸਕਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨ">
<feature>ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰਾਂ ਦੀਆਂ ਵਿਭਿੰਨ ਲੋੜਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਪੂਰਾ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨਾਂ ਦਾ ਆਕਾਰ ਵਿਵਸਥਿਤ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਤੁਸੀਂ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਦਾ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ -> ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਅਤੇ ਸ਼ੈਲੀ -> ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ -> ਆਈਕੋਨ ਦਾ ਆਕਾਰ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਪਲੇਅਰ">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਡਿਵਾਈਸ 'ਤੇ ਸੰਗੀਤ ਪਲੇਅਰ ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਕੈਮਰਾ">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਟੈਲੀਫ਼ੇਟੋ ਸ਼ੂਟਿੰਗ ਦੀ ਚਮਕ ਅਤੇ ਰੰਗ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।
ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਪੋਰਟ੍ਰੇਟ ਫੋਕਸ ਇਮੇਜਿੰਗ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਕਾਰਗੁਜ਼ਾਰੀ">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੁਝ ਐਪਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਲਾਂਚ ਕਰਦੇ ਸਮੇਂ ਬੇਤਰਤੀਬੀ ਲੈਗਿੰਗ ਦੀ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਨੂੰ ਠੀਕ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।
ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਐਪ ਸਟਾਰਟਅੱਪ ਮੋਸ਼ਨ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਵਿੱਚ ਬੇਤਰਤੀਬੇ ਫ੍ਰੇਮ ਡ੍ਰੌਪਾਂ ਦੀ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਪਾਵਰ ਖਪਤ">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਅਸਧਾਰਨ ਪਾਵਰ ਖਪਤ ਸੰਬੰਧੀ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਨੂੰ ਠੀਕ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਹੀਟਿੰਗ ਅਨੁਭਵ">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਹੀਟਿੰਗ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸਿਸਟਮ">
<feature>ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਡਿਵਾਈਸ ਜ਼ਿਆਦਾ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਨਾਲ ਕੰਮ ਕਰੇਗਾ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ">
<feature>ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਜੁਲਾਈ 2024) ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। HONOR ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਲਈ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਮਿਟਾਇਆ ਨਹੀਂ ਜਾਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਹਾਇਤਾ ਲਈ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta zalecana aktualizacja dodaje Ulubione globalne, Dokumenty HONOR i funkcję dostosowywania wielkości ikon na ekranie głównym, optymalizuje efekty robienia zdjęć i rozwiązuje problem z nieprawidłowym zużyciem energii w niektórych sytuacjach, poprawia wydajność i stabilność systemu oraz zmniejsza nagrzewanie się i zawiera poprawkę zabezpieczeń.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ulubione globalne">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja obejmuje nowo ulepszone Ulubione globalne. Po przeciągnięciu trzema palcami w dół można zapisywać materiały, takie jak obrazy, strony internetowe i pliki, w Przestrzeni ulubionych. Po dotknięciu Przestrzeni ulubionych w celu jej rozwinięcia można nacisnąć i przytrzymać wybrany element lub więcej elementów, aby przeciągnąć je do innych aplikacji. Można także synchronizować je z innymi urządzeniami w MagicRing, aby udostępniać zebrane materiały na różnych urządzeniach.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Dokumenty HONOR">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja zawiera zupełnie nowe Dokumenty HONOR oraz interaktywny interfejs, niestandardowe etykiety, kosz i inne funkcje, zwiększa stabilność i zgodność dokumentów oraz zapewnia większy komfort użytkowania.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikony na ekranie głównym">
<feature>Rozmiar ikon na Ekranie głównym można dostosować do różnych potrzeb użytkowników. W tym celu wybierz Ustawienia -> Ekran główny i styl -> Ustawienia ekranu głównego -> Rozmiar ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Odtwarzacz">
<feature>W tej aktualizacji dodano Odtwarzacz muzyki na urządzeniu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aparat">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja optymalizuje jasność i efekt kolorystyczny podczas fotografowania z teleobiektywem w niektórych sytuacjach.
Ta aktualizacja optymalizuje efekt fotografowania z ostrością portretową w niektórych sytuacjach.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Wydajność">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja rozwiązuje problem losowych opóźnień podczas uruchamiania niektórych aplikacji.
Ta aktualizacja optymalizuje problem przypadkowych spadków liczby klatek na sekundę w efekcie ruchu podczas uruchamiania aplikacji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zużycie energii">
<feature>Ta aktualizacja rozwiązuje problem nieprawidłowego zużycia energii w niektórych sytuacjach.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nagrzewanie się">
<feature>W tej aktualizacji zoptymalizowano nagrzewanie się urządzenia w pewnych sytuacjach.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>W tej aktualizacji poprawiono stabilność systemu, dzięki czemu urządzenie działa bardziej niezawodnie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpieczenia">
<feature>Aktualizacja zawiera Poprawkę zabezpieczeń systemu Android (lipiec 2024 r.). Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń urządzeń HONOR można znaleźć w naszej witrynie internetowej: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie powoduje wymazania danych użytkownika, jednak zalecamy uprzednie wykonanie kopii zapasowej.
2. Jeśli podczas procesu aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, zadzwoń na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR, gdzie uzyskasz pomoc.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro(a) usuário(a), esta atualização recomendada adiciona os Favoritos globais, o HONOR Docs e a função de ajuste do tamanho do ícone da tela inicial, otimiza o efeito de imagem em alguns cenários, corrige o problema de consumo anormal de energia em algumas cenas, melhora o desempenho do sistema, a estabilidade e a experiência de aquecimento, além de incorporar um patch de segurança.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favoritos globais">
<feature>Esta atualização recomendada introduz a melhoria recente dos Favoritos globais. Deslize para baixo com três dedos para salvar materiais, como imagens, páginas de internet e arquivos, ao Espaço de favoritos. Toque para expandir o Espaço de favoritos, pressione e segure um ou mais itens selecionados para arrastá-los até outros aplicativos. Você também pode sincronizá-los a outros dispositivos MagicRing para compartilhar conteúdos coletados entre dispositivos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Esta atualização oferece HONOR Docs e uma interface interativa totalmente novos, adiciona etiquetas personalizadas, lixeira e outras funções, além de melhorar a estabilidade e compatibilidade dos documentos e fornecer uma experiência de usuário melhor.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ícones da tela inicial">
<feature>O tamanho dos ícones da Tela inicial podem ser ajustados para atender às diferentes necessidades dos usuários. Você pode experimentar acessando: Configurações -> Tela inicial e estilo -> Configurações da tela inicial ->Tamanho do ícone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Player">
<feature>Esta atualização adiciona o Player de música no dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Câmera">
<feature>Esta atualização otimiza o brilho e o efeito de cor da captura de teleobjetiva em alguns cenários.
Esta atualização otimiza o efeito de imagem de foco de retrato em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Desempenho">
<feature>Esta atualização corrige o problema de atraso aleatório ao iniciar alguns aplicativos.
Esta atualização otimiza o problema de quedas aleatórias de quadros no efeito de movimento de inicialização do aplicativo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de energia">
<feature>Esta atualização corrige o problema de consumo anormal de energia em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Experiência de aquecimento">
<feature>Esta atualização otimiza a experiência de aquecimento em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Esta atualização melhora a estabilidade do sistema, tornando seu dispositivo mais estável.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Patch de segurança do Android (julho de 2024) incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite nosso site: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não apagará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, ligue para a linha de atendimento ao cliente da HONOR ou vá à central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização recomendada adiciona os Favoritos globais, os HONOR Docs e a função de ajustar o tamanho do ícone do ecrã inicial, otimiza o efeito da imagem em alguns cenários, corrige o problema do consumo anormal de energia em algumas cenas, melhora o desempenho do sistema, a estabilidade e a experiência de aquecimento e incorpora uma correção de segurança.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Favoritos globais">
<feature>Esta atualização inclui os Favoritos globais recentemente atualizados. Deslize para baixo com três dedos para guardar materiais, tais como imagens, páginas web e ficheiros no Espaço Favoritos. Toque para expandir o Espaço Favoritos, prima continuamente o item selecionado ou vários itens para os arrastar para outras aplicações e pode também sincronizá-los com outros dispositivos MagicRing para partilhar o conteúdo recolhido entre dispositivos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Esta atualização disponibiliza os mais recentes HONOR Docs e uma interface interativa, adiciona etiquetas personalizadas, reciclagem e outras funções, melhora a estabilidade e a compatibilidade dos documentos e proporciona uma melhor experiência do utilizador.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ícones do ecrã inicial">
<feature>O tamanho dos ícones do ecrã inicial podem ser ajustados para satisfazer as diferentes necessidades dos utilizadores. Poderá experimentá-lo, acedendo a: Definições -> Ecrã inicial e estilo -> Definições do ecrã inicial -> Tamanho do ícone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Leitor">
<feature>Esta atualização adiciona o Leitor de música no dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Câmara">
<feature>Esta atualização otimiza a luminosidade e o efeito de cor do disparo com teleobjetiva em alguns cenários.
Esta atualização otimiza o efeito da formação de imagem com focagem de retrato em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Desempenho">
<feature>Esta atualização corrige o problema de atrasos aleatórios no iniciar de algumas aplicações.
Esta atualização otimiza o problema das quedas aleatórias de fotogramas no efeito de movimento de arranque da aplicação.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de energia">
<feature>Esta atualização corrige o problema do consumo anormal de energia em algumas cenas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Experiência de aquecimento">
<feature>Esta atualização otimiza a experiência de aquecimento em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Esta atualização melhora a estabilidade do sistema para fazer com que o seu dispositivo funcione de forma mais estável.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Foi incorporada uma Correção de Segurança Android (julho de 2024) para segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não irá eliminar os seus dados pessoais, mas recomenda-se a realização de uma cópia de segurança prévia.
2. Se tiver problemas durante a atualização, ligue para a linha direta de assistência da HONOR ou dirija-se ao centro de apoio ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare recomandată adaugă Favorite globale, Documente HONOR și funcția de ajustarea dimensiunii pictogramelor pe ecranul de pornire, optimizează efectul de imagine în anumite scenarii, rezolvă problema consumului anormal de energie în anumite secvențe, îmbunătățește performanța, stabilitatea și experiența privind încălzirea sistemului și încorporează o corecție de securitate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Funcția Favorite globale">
<feature>Această actualizare include o nouă versiune a funcției Favorite globale. Treceți cu trei degete în jos pentru a salva materiale, cum ar fi imagini, pagini web și fișiere, în Spațiu favorite. Atingeți pentru a extinde Spațiu favorite și apăsați lung unul sau mai multe elemente selectate pentru a le trage în alte aplicații. De asemenea, puteți sincroniza aceste elemente cu alte dispozitive MagicRing pentru a partaja conținutul colectat între dispozitive.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Documente HONOR">
<feature>Această actualizare oferă o versiune complet nouă pentru Documente HONOR și o interfață interactivă, adaugă etichete personalizate, coșul de reciclare și alte funcții, îmbunătățește stabilitatea și compatibilitatea documentelor și oferă o experiență îmbunătățită de utilizare.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pictogramele de pe ecranul de pornire">
<feature>Dimensiunea pictogramelor de pe ecranul de pornire poate fi ajustată pentru a satisface diferitele nevoi ale utilizatorilor. Puteți accesa această funcție din Setări -> Ecran de pornire și stil -> Setări ecran de pornire -> Dimensiunea pictogramei.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Player">
<feature>Această actualizare adaugă aplicația Player de muzică pe dispozitiv.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cameră foto">
<feature>Această actualizare optimizează luminozitatea și efectul de culoare al fotografierii telefoto în anumite scenarii.
Această actualizare optimizează efectul de imagine pentru focalizarea portretului în anumite scenarii.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performanță">
<feature>Această actualizare remediază problema întârzierilor aleatorii la lansarea unor aplicații.
Această actualizare optimizează problema scăderilor aleatorii de cadre în efectul de mișcare la pornirea aplicațiilor.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consum de energie">
<feature>Această actualizare remediază problema consulului anormal de energie în anumite secvențe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Experiența privind încălzirea">
<feature>Această actualizare optimizează experiența privind încălzirea în anumite scenarii.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Această actualizare îmbunătățește stabilitatea sistemului, făcând ca dispozitivul dvs. să ruleze mai stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Securitate">
<feature>Corecția de securitate Android (iulie 2024) a fost inclusă pentru securitatea sistemului. Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de securitate HONOR, vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu vă va șterge datele cu caracter personal, însă se recomandă totuși să faceți înainte o copie de rezervă a acestora.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, pentru suport apelați numărul de asistență HONOR sau mergeți la centrul de service pentru clienții HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы разработали это рекомендованное обновление, чтобы добавить функцию Мое избранное, приложение HONOR Документы и функцию для настройки размера значков на рабочем экране, оптимизировать эффект отображения в некоторых сценариях, устранить проблему некорректного энергопотребления в некоторых сценариях, улучшить производительность, стабильность и нагрев системы, а также внедрить исправление безопасности.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Мое избранное">
<feature>В этом обновлении реализована совершенно новая служба Мое избранное. Сохраняйте изображения, веб-страницы и файлы в пространстве Favorites Space, просто проводя по экрану вниз тремя пальцами. Разворачивайте Favorites Space нажатием, перетаскивайте выбранные элементы в другие приложения, а также синхронизируйте сохраненный контент с другими устройствами MagicRing.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Документы">
<feature>Это обновление добавляет новое приложение HONOR Документы и интерактивный интерфейс, добавляет пользовательские метки, корзину и другие функции, повышает стабильность и совместимость документов, а также повышает удобство использования устройства.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Значки рабочего экрана">
<feature>Вы можете настроить размер рабочего стола нужным вам образом. Для этого выберите Настройки > Рабочий экран и стиль > Настройки экрана > Размер значков.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Плеер">
<feature>Это обновление добавляет Аудиоплеер.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>Это обновление оптимизирует яркость и цветовой эффект телеобъектива в некоторых сценариях.
Это обновление оптимизирует эффект портретной фокусировки в некоторых сценариях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Производительность">
<feature>Это обновление устраняет проблему случайного зависания при запуске некоторых приложений.
Это обновление оптимизирует проблему случайной потери кадров эффекта движения при запуске приложения.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Энергопотребление">
<feature>В этом обновлении устранена проблема, связанная с некорректным энергопотреблением в некоторых сценариях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Нагрев">
<feature>В этом обновлении был оптимизирован процесс нагрева в некоторых сценариях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>Это обновление улучшает стабильность системы и, соответственно, работу вашего устройства.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безопасность">
<feature>В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (июль 2024 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности HONOR, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/ru/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не приведет к удалению ваших персональных данных, но мы рекомендуем сделать резервную копию всех важных данных, прежде чем приступить к установке.
2. При возникновении проблем во время обновления обратитесь за помощью на горячую линию службы поддержки HONOR или в сервисный центр для клиентов HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම නිර්දේශිත යාවත්කාලය ගෝලීය ප්‍රියතමයන්, HONOR Docs සහ මුල් තිර අයිකනයේ ප්‍රමාණය සීරු මාරු කිරීමේ ක්‍රියාකාරිත්වය එක් කරයි, සමහර අවස්ථාවල රූපකරණ ප්‍රයෝගය ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි, සමහර අවස්ථාවල දී අසාමාන්‍ය බල පරිභෝජනයේ ගැටළුව නිරාකරණය කරයි, පද්ධතියේ කාර්යසාධනය, ස්ථාවරත්වය සහ රත්වීමේ අත්දැකීම වැඩි දියුණු කරයි, සහ ආරක්ෂක පැච් එකක් ඇතුළත් කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ගෝලීය ප්‍රියතමයන්">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය අලුතින් උත්ශ්‍රේණිගත කරන ලද ගෝලීය ප්‍රියතමයන් ගෙන එයි. රූප, වෙබ් පිටු සහ ගොනු වැනි ද්‍රව්‍ය, ප්‍රියතමයන් ඉඩ වෙත සුරැකීමට ඇඟිලි තුනකින් පහළට ස්වයිප් කරන්න. ප්‍රියතමයන් ඉඩ පුළුල් කිරීමට තට්ටු කරන්න, තෝරන ලද අයිතම එකක් හෝ කිහිපයක් වෙනත් යෙදුම් වෙත ඇදගෙන යාමට ඒවා ඔබාගෙන සිටින්න, සහ ඔබට උපාංග හරහා රැස් කළ අන්තර්ගතය හුවමාරු කරන්නට වෙනත් MagicRing උපාංග වෙත ඒවා සමමුහුර්ත කිරීමට ද හැකියාව ඇත.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය නවතම HONOR Docs සහ අන්තර්ක්‍රියාකාරී අතුරුමුහුණත සපයයි, අභිරුචි ලේබල්, ප්‍රතිචක්‍රීකරණ බඳුන් සහ වෙනත් ක්‍රියාකාරීත්ව එක් කරයි, ලේඛන ස්ථායීතාව සහ අනුකූලතාවය වැඩි දියුණු කරයි, සහ වඩා හොඳ පරිශීලක අත්දැකීමක් සපයයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="මුල් තිර අයිකන">
<feature>මුල් තිර අයිකනවල ප්‍රමාණය පරිශීලකයින්ගේ විවිධ අවශ්‍යතා සපුරාලීමට සීරු මාරු කළ හැකිවනු ඇත. ඔබට මෙම මාර්ගයෙන් එය අත්විඳිය හැකිය: සැකසුම් -> මුල් තිරය සහ විලාසය -> මුල් තිර සැකසුම් -> අයිකනයේ ප්‍රමාණය.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ප්ලේයරය">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය උපාංගය මත සංගීත ප්ලේයරය එක් කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="කැමරාව">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය සමහර අවස්ථාවල දී දුරස්ථ ඡායාරූප රූගත කිරීමේ දීප්තිය සහ වර්ණ ප්‍රයෝගය ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.
මෙම යාවත්කාලය සමහර අවස්ථාවලදී ආලේඛ්‍යය නාභිගත කිරීමේ රූපකරණ ප්‍රයෝගය ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="කාර්යසාධනය">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය සමහර යෙදුම් දියත් කරන විට දී අහඹු පසුබෑමේ ගැටළුව නිරාකරණය කරයි.
මෙම යාවත්කාලය යෙදුම් ආරම්භක චලන ප්‍රයෝගයේ අහඹු රාමු බිඳ වැටීමේ ගැටළුව ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="බල පරිභෝජනය">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය සමහර සිදුවීම්වල දී අසාමාන්‍ය බල පරිභෝජන ගැටළුව ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="රත්වීමේ අත්දැකීම">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය සමහර අවස්ථාවල රත්වීමේ අත්දැකීම ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="පද්ධතිය">
<feature>මෙම යාවත්කාලය විසින් ඔබගේ උපාංගය වඩා ස්ථායීව ධාවනය කරවීමට පද්ධතියේ ස්ථායිතාවය වැඩිදියුණු කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ආරක්ෂාව">
<feature>පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2024 ජුලි) යොදාගෙන ඇත. HONOR ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7 වෙත යන්න</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්ත නොමකනු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් ඊට පෙර උපස්ථ කිරීමක් නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේ දී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, කරුණාකර HONOR සේවා ක්ෂණික ඇමතුම් අමතන්න නැතහොත් සහය සඳහා HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට යන්න.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený používateľ, táto odporúčaná aktualizácia pridáva Globálne obľúbené, HONOR Dokumenty a funkciu úpravy veľkosti ikon na domovskej obrazovke, optimalizuje zobrazovací efekt v niektorých scenároch, rieši problém s neobvyklou spotrebou energie pri niektorých scénach, zlepšuje výkon systému a stabilitu, znižuje zahrievanie a zahŕňa bezpečnostnú opravu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globálne obľúbené">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia prináša inovovanú funkciu Globálne obľúbené. Potiahnutím tromi prstami nadol uložte materiály, ako sú obrázky, webové stránky a súbory, do Priestoru obľúbených. Ťuknutím rozbaľte Priestor obľúbených, stlačte a podržte jednu alebo viacero vybratých položiek, aby ste ich potiahli do iných aplikácií alebo synchronizovali s inými zariadeniami MagicRing a zdieľali zhromaždený obsah medzi zariadeniami.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Dokumenty">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia poskytuje úplne novú aplikáciu HONOR Dokumenty a interaktívne rozhranie, pridáva vlastné štítky, odpadkový kôš a ďalšie funkcie, zlepšuje stabilitu a kompatibilitu dokumentov a poskytuje lepšiu používateľskú skúsenosť.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikony na domovskej obrazovke">
<feature>Veľkosť ikon na domovskej obrazovke možno upraviť tak, aby vyhovovala rôznym potrebám používateľov. Môžete to vyskúšať v časti: Nastavenia -> Domovská obrazovka a štýl -> Nastavenia domovskej obrazovky -> Veľkosť ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prehrávač">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia pridáva Prehrávač hudby v zariadení.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fotoaparát">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia optimalizuje jas a farebný efekt pri snímaní teleobjektívom v niektorých scenároch.
Táto aktualizácia optimalizuje zobrazovací efekt pri zaostrovaní na portréty v niektorých scenároch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Výkon">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia rieši problém náhodného oneskorenia pri spúšťaní niektorých aplikácií.
Táto aktualizácia optimalizuje problém náhodného zníženia počtu snímok v efekte pohybu pri spúšťaní aplikácií.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Spotreba energie">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia rieši problém abnormálnej spotreby energie v niektorých scénach.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zahrievanie">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia optimalizuje zahrievanie v niektorých situáciách.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Táto aktualizácia zlepšuje stabilitu systému, aby zariadenie fungovalo stabilnejšie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpečenie">
<feature>Súčasťou zabezpečenia systému je bezpečnostná oprava systému Android (z júla 2024). Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti HONOR, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštaláciou tejto aktualizácie nevymažete svoje osobné údaje, ale napriek tomu sa odporúča ich vopred zálohovať.
2. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytnú problémy, podporu môžete získať zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo návštevou Centra služieb zákazníkom HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, s to priporočeno posodobitvijo sta dodani aplikaciji Zbirka priljubljenih HONOR Dokumenti ter funkcija prilagajanja velikosti ikone za začetni zaslon, v nekaterih situacijah je optimiziran učinek slikanja, v nekaterih situacijah je odpravljena težava neobičajne porabe energije, izboljšani so delovanje sistema, stabilnost in segrevanje naprave, vključen pa je tudi varnostni popravek.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zbirka priljubljenih">
<feature>Ta priporočena posodobitev uvaja nedavno nadgrajeno Zbirko priljubljenih. Podrsnite navzdol s tremi prsti, da shranite vsebino, kot so slike, spletne strani in datoteke, v Prostor za priljubljene. Dotaknite se, da razširite Prostor za priljubljene, pritisnite in zadržite izbrani element oz. več elementov, da jih povlečete v druge aplikacije, lahko pa jih tudi sinhronizirate v druge naprave MagicRing, da vsebino delite v več napravah.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Dokumenti">
<feature>Ta posodobitev vključuje popolnoma novo aplikacijo HONOR Dokumenti in interaktivni vmesnik, doda oznake po meri, koš in druge funkcije, izboljša stabilnost in združljivost dokumentov ter zagotavlja boljšo uporabniško izkušnjo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikone na začetnem zaslonu">
<feature>Velikost ikon na začetnem zaslonu je mogoče prilagoditi, da ustreza različnim potrebam vsakega uporabnika. To lahko preizkusite tako, da izberete: Nastavitve -> Začetni zaslon in slog -> Nastavitve začetnega zaslona -> Velikost ikone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Predvajalnik">
<feature>S to posodobitvijo je v napravo dodana aplikacija Predvajalnik glasbe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>S to posodobitvijo sta v nekaterih situacijah optimizirana svetlost in barvni učinek pri fotografiranju s telefoto objektivom.
S to posodobitvijo se v nekaterih situacijah optimizira učinek slikanja v načinu izostritve portreta.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Učinkovitost delovanja">
<feature>S to posodobitvijo je odpravljena težava naključnih zakasnitev pri zagonu nekaterih aplikacij.
S to posodobitvijo je odpravljena težava, ko med zagonom aplikacije, ki prikazuje animacijo, niso prikazani vsi kadri.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poraba energije">
<feature>S to posodobitvijo se odpravi težava neobičajne porabe energije v nekaterih situacijah.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Izkušnja segrevanja">
<feature>S to posodobitvijo se optimizira izkušnja segrevanja naprave v nekaterih situacijah.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>S to posodobitvijo se izboljšuje stabilnost sistema za bolj zanesljivo delovanje naprave.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varnost">
<feature>Varnostni popravki za Android (julij 2024) so vključeni za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah HONOR obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Z namestitvijo te posodobitve vaši osebni podatki ne bodo izbrisani, vendar vseeno priporočamo, da jih predhodno varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodobitvijo naletite na težave, za podporo pokličite odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom izdelkov HONOR ali obiščite servisni center družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, den här rekommenderade uppdateringen lägger till Globala favoriter, HONOR Docs och funktionen att justera storleken på startsidans ikoner, optimerar bildeffekten i vissa scenarier, åtgärdar problemet med onormal energiförbrukning i vissa scener, förbättrar systemets prestanda, stabilitet och uppvärmning samt implementerar en säkerhetskorrigering.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Globala favoriter">
<feature>Den här uppdateringen omfattar nyligen uppgraderade Globala favoriter. Svep nedåt med tre fingrar för att spara innehåll, som bilder, webbsidor och filer, i Utrymme för favoriter. Tryck för att expandera Utrymme för favoriter, håll ned på ett eller flera valda objekt och dra dem till andra appar. Du kan också synkronisera dem till andra MagicRing-enheter för att dela samlat innehåll mellan enheter.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Den här uppdateringen tillhandahåller helt nya HONOR Docs och interaktivt gränssnitt, lägger till anpassade etiketter, papperskorgen och andra funktioner, förbättrar stabiliteten och kompatibiliteten för dokument samt ger en bättre användarupplevelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikoner på startsidan">
<feature>Storleken på startsidans ikoner kan justeras för att passa användarnas olika behov. Du kan prova själv genom att gå till: Inställningar -> Startsida och stil -> Inställningar för startsidan -> Ikonstorlek.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Spelare">
<feature>Den här uppdateringen lägger till Musikspelare på enheten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Den här uppdateringen optimerar ljusstyrkan och färgeffekten vid fotografering med teleobjektiv i vissa scenarier.
Den här uppdateringen optimerar bildeffekten för porträttfokus i vissa scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prestanda">
<feature>Den här uppdateringen åtgärdar problemet med slumpmässig eftersläpning när vissa appar startas.
Den här uppdateringen optimerar problemet med slumpmässig minskning av bildhastighet i rörelseeffekten vid appstart.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energiförbrukning">
<feature>Den här uppdateringen åtgärdar problemet med onormal energiförbrukning i vissa scener.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uppvärmning">
<feature>Uppdateringen optimerar uppvärmningen i vissa scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Uppdateringen förbättrar systemets stabilitet så att enheten körs stabilare.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Säkerhet">
<feature>Android-säkerhetskorrigeringen (juli 2024) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för HONOR går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Den här uppdateringen raderar inga personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du gör en säkerhetskopia innan du installerar den.
2. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs servicecenter och få support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili linalopendekezwa linaongeza Vipendwa vya Kimataifa, Hati za HONOR na kipengele cha kurekebisha ukubwa wa aikoni za skrini ya mwanzo, linaboresha hali ya picha katika baadhi ya miktadha, linarekebisha hitilafu ya utumiaji nishati usio wa kawaida katika baadhi ya mandhari, linaboresha utendaji wa mfumo, uthabiti na hali ya kupata joto na linajumuisha rekebisho la usalama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Vipendwa vya Kimataifa">
<feature>Sasisho hili huleta Vipendwa vya Kimataifa vilivyosombezwa hivi karibuni. Telezesha chini kwa vidole viwili ili kuokoa nyenzo, kama vile picha, kurasa za wavuti na faili, kwenye Nafasi ya Vipendwa. Gusa ili kupanua Nafasi ya Vipendwa, bofya na ushikilie iliyochaguliwa au vipengee kadhaa ili kuvikokota kwenye programu zingine na pia unaweza kuzilandanisha kwenye vifaa vingine vya MagicRing ili kushiriki maudhui yaliyokusanywa kwenye vifaa vingine.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hati za HONOR">
<feature>Sasisho hili linatoa Hati za HONOR na kiolesura kipya shirikishi, linaongeza lebo maalum, kijalala na vipengele vingine, linaboresha uthabiti na utangamanaji wa hati na linatoa uzoefu bora wa mtumiaji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikoni za skrini ya mwanzo">
<feature>Ukubwa wa ikoni za Skrini ya mwanzo vinaweza kurekebishwa ili kufikia mahitaji tofauti ya watumiaji. Unaweza kuipata kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio -> Skrini ya kwanza na mtindo -> Mipangilio ya skrini ya mwanzo -> Ukubwa wa ikoni.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kichezaji">
<feature>Sasisho hili linaongeza Kichezaji Muziki kwenye kifaa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Sasisho hili linaboresha athari ya mwangaza na rangi ya upigaji picha ya telefoto katika baadhi ya miktadha.
Sasisho hili linaboresha athari ya kuangazia picha wima katika baadhi ya miktadha.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Utendaji">
<feature>Sasisho hili linarekebisha tatizo la kujikokota kwa nasibu unapozindua baadhi ya programu.
Sasisho hili linaboresha hitilafu ya kiwango cha fremu kushuka kwa nasibu katika athari ya mwendo wa kuanzisha programu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Utumiaji nishati">
<feature>Sasisho hili linarekebisha tatizo la utumiaji nishati usio wa kawaida katika baadhi ya mandhari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hali ya kupata joto">
<feature>Sasisho hili linaboresha hali ya kupata joto katika baadhi ya miktadha.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mfumo">
<feature>Sasisho hili huboresa uthabiti wa mfumo ili kufanya kifaa chako kiendeshwe kwa uthabiti zaidi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Usalama">
<feature>Rekebisho la Usalama wa Android (Jul 2024) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa HONOR, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutafuta data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini hifadhi rudufu kabla ya kusakinisha bado inapendekezwa.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, tafadhali piga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au nenda kwenye kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha HONOR ili upate usaidizi.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படும் புதுப்பிப்பு குளோபல் பிடித்தவை, HONOR டாக்ஸ் மற்றும் முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான் அளவைச் சரிசெய்யும் செயல்பாடு ஆகியவற்றைச் சேர்க்கிறது, சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் இமேஜிங் விளைவை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது, சில காட்சிகளில் அசாதாரண மின் நுகர்வுச் சிக்கலைச் சரிசெய்கிறது, சிஸ்டம் செயல்திறன், நிலைத்தன்மை மற்றும் சூடாகுதல் அனுபவத்தை மேம்படுத்துகிறது மற்றும் பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பைக் கொண்டுள்ளது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="குளோபல் பிடித்தவை">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு புதிதாக மேம்படுத்தப்பட்ட குளோபல் பிடித்தவையைக் கொண்டுவருகிறது. படங்கள், வலைப் பக்கங்கள் மற்றும் கோப்புகள் போன்ற ஆவணங்களைப் பிடித்தவை ஸ்பேஸில் சேமிக்க, மூன்று விரல்களால் கீழ்நோக்கி ஸ்வைப் செய்யவும். பிடித்தவை ஸ்பேஸை விரிவுபடுத்த தட்டவும், தேர்ந்தெடுக்கப்பட்ட ஒன்று அல்லது பல உருப்படிகளைப் பிற செயலிகளுக்கு இழுக்க அவற்றை அழுத்திப் பிடிக்கவும், சேகரிக்கப்படும் உள்ளடக்கத்தைச் சாதனங்கள் இடையே பகிர, பிற MagicRing சாதனங்களுடன் ஒத்திசைக்கலாம்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR டாக்ஸ்">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு புத்தம்புதிய HONOR டாக்ஸ் மற்றும் ஊடாடும் இடைமுகத்தை வழங்குகிறது, தனிப்பயன் லேபிள்கள், மறுசுழற்சிக் கூடை மற்றும் பிற செயல்பாடுகளைச் சேர்க்கிறது, ஆவண நிலைத்தன்மை மற்றும் இணக்கத்தன்மையை மேம்படுத்துகிறது, சிறந்த பயனர் அனுபவத்தை வழங்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான்கள்">
<feature>முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான்களின் அளவைப் பயனர்களின் வெவ்வேறு தேவைகளைப் பூர்த்தி செய்வதற்காகச் சரிசெய்யலாம். இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் நீங்கள் அதைப் பயன்படுத்தலாம்: அமைப்புகள் -> முகப்புத் திரை மற்றும் ஸ்டைல் -> முகப்புத் திரை அமைப்புகள் -> ஐகான் அளவு.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பிளேயர்">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு சாதனத்தில் இசைப் பிளேயரைச் சேர்க்கிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="கேமரா">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் டெலிபோட்டோ ஷூட்டிங்கின் ஒளிர்வு மற்றும் வண்ண விளைவை மேம்படுத்துகிறது.
இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் போர்ட்ரெயிட் ஃபோகஸ் இமேஜிங் விளைவை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="செயல்திறன்">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு, சில செயலிகளைத் தொடங்கும்போது ஏற்படும் தற்போக்குப் பின்னடைவின் சிக்கலைச் சரிசெய்கிறது.
இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு செயலித் துவக்கம் மோஷன் விளைவில் தற்போக்காக ஏற்படும் ஃபிரேம் டிராப்களின் சிக்கலை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="மின் நுகர்வு">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு சில காட்சிகளில் அசாதாரண மின் நுகர்வு சிக்கலைச் சரிசெய்கிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="சூடாகுதல் அனுபவம்">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் ஏற்படும் சூடாகுதல் அனுபவத்தை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="சிஸ்டம்">
<feature>இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பானது உங்கள் சாதனத்தை மேலும் நிலையாக இயங்கச் செய்யும் வகையில் சிஸ்டம் நிலைத்தன்மையை மேம்படுத்துகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பாதுகாப்பு">
<feature>சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (ஜூலை 2024) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. HONOR பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவை அழிக்காது, எனினும் தொடர்வதற்கு முன் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுக்குமாறு பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், உதவிக்காக HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைக்கவும் அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்லவும்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ సిఫార్సు చేయబడిన అప్‌డేట్ గ్లోబల్ ఇష్టాలు, HONOR డాక్స్ మరియు హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నం పరిమాణాన్ని సర్దుబాటు చేయడానికి ఫంక్షన్‌ను జోడిస్తుంది, కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో ఇమేజింగ్ ప్రభావాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది, కొన్ని సీన్‌ల్లో అసాధారణ పవర్ వినియోగ సమస్యను పరిష్కరిస్తుంది, సిస్టమ్ పనితీరును, స్థిరత్వం మరియు వేడెక్కే అనుభవాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది మరియు భద్రతా ప్యాచ్‌ను చేర్చుతుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="గ్లోబల్ ఇష్టాలు">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ కొత్తగా అప్‌గ్రేడ్ చేసిన గ్లోబల్ ఇష్టాలను అందిస్తుంది, చిత్రాలు, వెబ్ పేజీలు మరియు ఫైల్స్ వంటి మెటీరియల్స్‌ను ఇష్టాల స్పేస్‌కు సేవ్ చేయడానికి మూడు వేళ్లతో కిందికి స్వైప్ చేయండి. ఇష్టాల స్పేస్‌ను విస్తరించడానికి ట్యాప్ చేయండి, ఎంచుకున్న ఒకటి లేదా పలు ఐటమ్‌లను ఇతర అప్లికేషన్‌లకు లాగడానికి నొక్కి, పట్టుకోండి మరియు మీరు పరికరాల వ్యాప్తంగా సేకరించిన కంటెంట్‌ను భాగస్వామ్యం చేయడానికి వాటిని ఇతర MaginRing పరికరాలకు కూడా సమకాలీకరించవచ్చు.​</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR డాక్స్">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ సరికొత్త HONOR డాక్స్ మరియు ఇంటరాక్టివ్ ఇంటర్‌ఫేస్‌ను అందిస్తుంది, అనుకూల లేబుల్‌లు, రీసైకిల్ బిన్ మరియు ఇతర ఫంక్షన్‌లను జోడిస్తుంది, పత్రం స్థిరత్వం మరియు అనుకూతలను మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది మరియు ఉత్తమ వినియోగదారు అనుభవాన్ని అందిస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాలు">
<feature>వినియోగదారుల విభిన్న అవసరాలకు తగినట్లు హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాల పరిమాణాన్ని సర్దుబాటు చేయవచ్చు. మీరు ఇక్కడికి వెళ్లి దానిని ఆనందించవచ్చు: సెట్టింగ్‌లు -> హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ మరియు శైలి -> హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ సెట్టింగ్‌లు -> చిహ్నం పరిమాణం.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ప్లేయర్">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ పరికరంలో సంగీతం ప్లేయర్‌ను జోడిస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="కెమెరా">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో టెలిఫోటో షూటింగ్ యొక్క ప్రకాశవంతాన్ని మరియు రంగు ప్రభావాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది.
ఈ అప్‌డేట్ కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో పోర్ట్రెయిట్ ఫోకస్ ఇమేజింగ్ ప్రభావాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="పనితీరు">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ కొన్ని అప్లికేషన్‌లను లాంచ్ చేస్తున్నప్పుడు యాదృచ్ఛిక జాప్యం సమస్యను పరిష్కరిస్తుంది.
ఈ అప్‌డేట్ అప్లికేషన్ స్టార్టప్ మోషన్ ప్రభావంలో యాదృచ్చిక ఫ్రేమ్ తగ్గిపోయే సమస్య ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="పవర్ వాడకం">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ కొన్ని సీన్‌ల్లో అసాధారణ పవర్ వినియోగం సమస్యను పరిష్కరిస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="వేడెక్కే అనుభవం">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో వేడెక్కే అనుభవాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="సిస్టమ్">
<feature>ఈ అప్‌డేట్ మీ పరికరం మరింత స్థిరంగా అమలు అయ్యేలా చేయడానికి సిస్టమ్ స్థిరత్వాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="భద్రత">
<feature>సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం Android సెక్యూరిటీ ప్యాచ్ (జూలై 2024) పొందుపరచబడింది. HONOR భద్రత నవీకరణల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్ సందర్శించండి https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వలన మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటా ఎరేజ్ చేయబడదు, కాని ముందుగా ఒక బ్యాకప్ తీసుకోవాలని సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీరు ఏవైనా సమస్యలను ఎదుర్కొన్నట్లయితే, దయచేసి మద్దతు కోసం HONOR సర్వీసు హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయండి లేదా HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి వెళ్ళండి.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตที่แนะนำครั้งนี้เพิ่มรายการโปรดทั่วไป HONOR Docs และฟังก์ชันของการปรับแต่งขนาดไอคอนหน้าจอหลัก ปรับปรุงเอฟเฟ็กต์ภาพในบางสถานการณ์ แก้ไขปัญหาการใช้พลังงานผิดปกติในบางสถานการณ์ ปรับปรุงประสิทธิภาพ ความเสถียร และประสบการณ์ความร้อนของระบบ และรวมแพตช์รักษาความปลอดภัย</feature>
</features>
<features module="รายการโปรดทั่วไป">
<feature>การอัปเดตครั้งนี้มีการเพิ่มรายการโปรดทั่วไปที่ได้รับการอัปเกรดเป็นรูปแบบใหม่ ปัดนิ้วลงด้วยสามนิ้วเพื่อบันทึกสื่อต่างๆ เช่น รูปภาพ หน้าเว็บ และไฟล์ต่างๆ ไปยังพื้นที่รายการโปรด แตะเพื่อขยายพื้นที่รายการโปรด กดค้างไว้ที่อย่างน้อยหนึ่งรายการเพื่อลากไปยังแอปอื่น และคุณจะซิงค์ไปยังอุปกรณ์ MagicRing เครื่องอื่นได้ด้วย เพื่อแบ่งปันเนื้อหาที่เก็บรวบรวมระหว่างอุปกรณ์ต่างๆ</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>การอัปเดตครั้งนี้มอบอินเทอร์เฟซ HONOR Docs โฉมใหม่แบบอินเทอร์แอกทีฟ เพิ่มป้ายแบบกำหนดเอง ถังขยะรีไซเคิล และฟังก์ชันอื่นๆ รวมถึงพัฒนาความเสถียรและการทำงานร่วมกันของเอกสาร และมอบประสบการณ์การใช้งานของผู้ใช้ที่ดียิ่งขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="ไอคอนหน้าจอหลัก">
<feature>ปรับขนาดไอคอนหน้าจอหลักเพื่อให้เป็นไปตามความต้องการที่ต่างกันของผู้ใช้ได้ คุณสามารถลองได้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า -> หน้าจอหลักและสไตล์ -> การตั้งค่าหน้าจอหลัก -> ขนาดไอคอน</feature>
</features>
<features module="เครื่องเล่น">
<feature>การอัปเดตครั้งนี้เพิ่มเครื่องเล่นเพลงบนอุปกรณ์</feature>
</features>
<features module="กล้องถ่ายรูป">
<feature>อัปเดตนี้ปรับปรุงความสว่างและเอฟเฟ็กต์สีของการถ่ายโทรภาพในบางสถานการณ์
อัปเดตนี้ปรับปรุงเอฟเฟ็กต์ภาพโฟกัสบุคคลในบางสถานการณ์</feature>
</features>
<features module="ประสิทธิภาพ">
<feature>อัปเดตนี้แก้ไขปัญหาความล่าช้าที่อาจเกิดขึ้นเมื่อเปิดใช้งานบางแอป
อัปเดตนี้ปรับปรุงปัญหาอัตราเฟรมตกที่อาจเกิดขึ้นในเอฟเฟ็กต์การเคลื่อนไหวเมื่อเริ่มแอป</feature>
</features>
<features module="การใช้พลังงาน">
<feature>อัปเดตนี้แก้ไขปัญหาการใช้พลังงานผิดปกติในบางสถานการณ์</feature>
</features>
<features module="ประสบการณ์ความร้อน">
<feature>อัปเดตนี้ปรับปรุงประสบการณ์ความร้อนในบางสถานการณ์</feature>
</features>
<features module="ระบบ">
<feature>อัปเดตนี้ปรับปรุงความเสถียรของระบบเพื่อให้อุปกรณ์ของคุณทำงานเสถียรมากขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="ความปลอดภัย">
<feature>มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัยของ Android (ก.ค. 2024) เพื่อการรักษาความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตการรักษาความปลอดภัยของ HONOR ได้ในเว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="โปรดทราบ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่ลบข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เราขอแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลไว้ล่วงหน้า
2. หากคุณพบปัญหาใดๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต ให้โทรติดต่อสายด่วนบริการ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้า HONOR เพื่อขอรับความช่วยเหลือ</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, idinaragdag ng inirerekomendang update na ito ang Mga Global na Paborito, HONOR Docs, at ang function ng pag-adjust sa laki ng icon sa home screen, ino-optimize ang effect ng imaging sa ilang sitwasyon, inaayos ang isyu ng hindi normal na pagkonsumo sa baterya sa ilang sitwasyon, pinapahusay ang karanasan sa performance, stability, at pag-init ng system, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Global na Paborito">
<feature>Nagdadala ang update na ito ng bagong na-upgrade na Mga Global na Paborito. Mag-swipe pababa gamit ang tatlong daliri para mag-save ng mga materyal, gaya ng mga larawan, web page, at file, sa Espasyo ng Mga Paborito. I-tap para i-expand ang Espasyo ng Mga Paborito, pindutin nang matagal ang isa o maraming item para i-drag ang mga ito sa iba pang app, at puwede mo ring i-sync ang mga ito sa iba pang MagicRing device para ibahagi ang nakolektang content sa mga device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Nagbibigay ang update na ito ng bagong HONOR Docs at interactive na interface, idinaragdag ang mga custom na label, recycle bin at iba pang function, pinapahusay ang stability at compatibility ng dokumento, at nagbibigay ng mas magandang karanasan ng user.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga icon sa home screen">
<feature>Puwedeng i-adjust ang laki ng mga icon ng Home screen para matugunan ang ibat ibang pangangailangan ng mga user. Puwede mo itong maranasan sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting -> Home screen at estilo -> Mga setting ng home screen -> Laki ng icon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Player">
<feature>Idinaragdag ng update na ito ang Player ng Musika sa device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang liwanag at effect ng kulay sa pag-shoot ng telephoto sa ilang sitwasyon.
Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang effect ng imaging na portrait focus sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performance">
<feature>Inaayos ng update na ito ang problema ng random na pag-lag kapag inilulunsad ang ilang app.
Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang problema ng random na mga pag-drop ng frame sa effect ng paggalaw sa pag-start up ng app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pagkonsumo ng baterya">
<feature>Inaayos ng update na ito ang isyu ng hindi normal na pagkonsumo ng baterya sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Karanasan sa pag-init">
<feature>Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang karanasan sa pag-init sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Pinapahusay ng update na ito ang stability ng system para magawang tumakbo nang mas stable ang iyong device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Hulyo 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi mabubura ang iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa rin ang isang pag-back up bago gawin ito.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, idinaragdag ng inirerekomendang update na ito ang Mga Global na Paborito, HONOR Docs, at ang function ng pag-adjust sa laki ng icon sa home screen, ino-optimize ang effect ng imaging sa ilang sitwasyon, inaayos ang isyu ng hindi normal na pagkonsumo sa baterya sa ilang sitwasyon, pinapahusay ang karanasan sa performance, stability, at pag-init ng system, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Global na Paborito">
<feature>Nagdadala ang update na ito ng bagong na-upgrade na Mga Global na Paborito. Mag-swipe pababa gamit ang tatlong daliri para mag-save ng mga materyal, gaya ng mga larawan, web page, at file, sa Espasyo ng Mga Paborito. I-tap para i-expand ang Espasyo ng Mga Paborito, pindutin nang matagal ang isa o maraming item para i-drag ang mga ito sa iba pang app, at puwede mo ring i-sync ang mga ito sa iba pang MagicRing device para ibahagi ang nakolektang content sa mga device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Nagbibigay ang update na ito ng bagong HONOR Docs at interactive na interface, idinaragdag ang mga custom na label, recycle bin at iba pang function, pinapahusay ang stability at compatibility ng dokumento, at nagbibigay ng mas magandang karanasan ng user.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga icon sa home screen">
<feature>Puwedeng i-adjust ang laki ng mga icon ng Home screen para matugunan ang ibat ibang pangangailangan ng mga user. Puwede mo itong maranasan sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting -> Home screen at estilo -> Mga setting ng home screen -> Laki ng icon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Player">
<feature>Idinaragdag ng update na ito ang Player ng Musika sa device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang liwanag at effect ng kulay sa pag-shoot ng telephoto sa ilang sitwasyon.
Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang effect ng imaging na portrait focus sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performance">
<feature>Inaayos ng update na ito ang problema ng random na pag-lag kapag inilulunsad ang ilang app.
Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang problema ng random na mga pag-drop ng frame sa effect ng paggalaw sa pag-start up ng app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pagkonsumo ng baterya">
<feature>Inaayos ng update na ito ang isyu ng hindi normal na pagkonsumo ng baterya sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Karanasan sa pag-init">
<feature>Ino-optimize ng update na ito ang karanasan sa pag-init sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Pinapahusay ng update na ito ang stability ng system para magawang tumakbo nang mas stable ang iyong device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang Panseguridad na Patch ng Android (Hulyo 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi mabubura ang iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa rin ang isang pag-back up bago gawin ito.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Değerli kullanıcımız, önerilen bu güncelleme ile Gelişmiş Favoriler, HONOR Docs ve başlangıç ekranı simge boyutunu ayarlama işlevi eklenmiş, bazı durumlarda görüntüleme efekti optimize edilmiş, bazı durumlarda anormal güç tüketimi sorunu giderilmiş, sistem performansı, kararlılık ve ısınma deneyimi iyileştirilmiş ve bir güvenlik yaması eklenmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gelişmiş Favoriler">
<feature>Sayın kullanıcı; önerilen bu güncelleme yeni yükseltilen Gelişmiş Favoriler'i ekler. Görüntüler, web sayfaları ve dosyalar gibi materyalleri Favoriler Alanı'na kaydetmek için üç parmağınızla aşağı kaydırın. Favoriler Alanı'nı genişletmek için dokunun, seçilen bir veya daha fazla öğeyi basılı tutarak diğer uygulamalara sürükleyin; ayrıca toplanan içeriği cihazlar arasında paylaşmak için bunları diğer MagicRing cihazlarıyla da senkronize edebilirsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Bu güncelleme yepyeni HONOR Docs ile etkileşimli arayüzü sunar, özel etiketler, geri dönüşüm kutusu ve diğer işlevler ekler, belge tutarlılığını ve uyumluluğunu iyileştirir, daha iyi bir kullanıcı deneyimi sunar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Başlangıç ekranı simgeleri">
<feature>Başlangıç ekranı simgelerinin boyutları, farklı kullanıcı ihtiyaçlarını karşılamak için ayarlanabilir. Ayarlar -> Başlangıç ekranı ve stil -> Başlangıç ekranı ayarları -> Simge boyutu adımlarını takip ederek bunu deneyimleyebilirsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oynatıcı">
<feature>Bu güncelleme ile cihaza Müzik Oynatıcı eklendi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Bu güncelleme ile bazı durumlarda telefoto çekimin parlaklık ve renk efekti optimize edilmiştir.
Bu güncelleme ile bazı durumlarda portre odak görüntüleme efekti optimize edilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Performans">
<feature>Bu güncelleme ile bazı uygulamalar başlatılırken yaşanan rastgele gecikme sorunu giderilmiştir.
Bu güncelleme ile uygulama başlatma hareket efektinde yaşanan rastgele kare düşmesi sorunu optimize edilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güç tüketimi">
<feature>Bu güncelleme ile bazı durumlarda anormal güç tüketimi sorunu giderilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Isınma deneyimi">
<feature>Bu güncelleme ile bazı durumlarda ısınma deneyimi optimize edilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Bu güncelleme ile sistem kararlılığı iyileştirilerek cihazınız daha kararlı hale getirilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güvenlik">
<feature>Sistem güvenliği için Android Güvenlik Yamasını (Temmuz 2024) içermektedir. HONOR Güvenlik güncellemeleri ile ilgili daha fazla bilgi için lütfen web sitemizi ziyaret edin: https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi silmeyecektir, fakat yine de öncesinde yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşmanız durumunda destek için lütfen HONOR servisi yardım hattını arayın veya HONOR müşteri servisi merkezlerinden birine gidin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا پۈتۈن دائىرىلىك يىغما، روڭياۋ پۈتۈكى ۋە ئۈستەليۈزى سىنبەلگىسىنىڭ چوڭلۇقىنى تەڭشەش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى كامېرانىڭ رەسىمگە تارتىش ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى، بىر قىسىم ئەھۋاللاردىكى توك بىنورمال خوراش مەسىلىسى ھەل قىلىنىدى، سىستېمىنىڭ ئىقتىدارى، مۇقىملىقى ۋە قىزغىنلىق تەسىراتى يۇقىرى كۆتۈرۈلدى، بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«پۈتۈن دائىرىلىك يىغما»">
<feature>پۈتۈن دائىرىلىك يىغما پۈتۈنلەي يېڭىلاندى، ئۈچ بارماقتا تۆۋەنگە سىيرىپلا رەسىم، توربەت، ھۆججەت قاتارلىق خام ماتېرىياللارنى يىغىش بوشلۇقىغا تېز ساقلاشقا بولىدۇ. يىغىش بوشلۇقىنى چېكىپ يايغاندىن كېيىن، تاللانغان بىر ياكى بىر قانچە مەزمۇننى ئۇزۇن بېسىپ باشقا ئەپلەرگە سۆرەپ تاشلاپلا ئىشلەتكىلى بولىدۇ، يەنە ئىشەنچ ھالقىسىدىكى باشقا ئۈسكۈنىلەرگە ماسقەدەملەپ، يىغقان مەزمۇننى ئۈسكۈنە ھالقىپ ئورتاقلاشقىلى بولىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«روڭياۋ پۈتۈكى»">
<feature>‏پۈتۈنلەي يېڭى روڭياۋ پۈتۈكىدە پۈتۈنلەي يېڭى ئالاقە ئارايۈزى، ئىختىيارىي خەتكۈچ، سېۋەت ئىقتىدارى قوشۇلۇپ، پۈتۈك مۇقىملىقى ۋە ماسلىشىشچانلىقى ئۆستۈرۈلدى، تېخىمۇ مول ئىشلىتىش تەسىراتى تەمىنلەيدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«ئۈستەليۈزى سىنبەلگىلىرى»">
<feature>ئۈستەليۈزىدىكى سىنبەلگە چوڭلۇقىنى تەڭشەشنى قوللاپ، ئىشلەتكۈچىلەرنىڭ سىنبەلگە چوڭلۇقىنى ئوخشىمىغان چوڭلۇقتا كۆرسىتىش ئېھتىياجىنى قاندۇرىدۇ، سىناش يولى: «تەڭشەك > ئۈستەليۈزى ۋە خاسلاشتۇرۇش > ئۈستەليۈزى تەڭشىكى > سىنبەلگە چوڭلۇقى».</feature>
</features>
<features module="«قويغۇچ»">
<feature>ئۈسكۈنىدىكى مۇزىكا قويغۇچ يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«كامېرا»">
<feature>بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى ئۇزۇن فوكۇسلۇق رەسىمگە تارتىشنىڭ يورۇقلۇق ۋە رەڭ ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى.
بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى پورترېت تەسۋىر ھاسىل قىلىش ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«ئىقتىدار»">
<feature>بىر قىسىم ئەپلەرنىڭ ئاندا-ساندا قېتىپ قېلىش مەسىلىسى ھەل قىلىندى.
بىر قىسىم ئەپلەرنىڭ قوزغىتىلغاندىكى ھەرىكەت ئۈنۈمىدە ئاندا-ساندا رام يوقاپ كېتىش مەسىلىسى ھەل قىلىندى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«توك سەرپىياتى»">
<feature>بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى بىنورمال توك خوراش مەسىلىسى ئوڭشالدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«قىزغىنلىق تەسىراتى»">
<feature>بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى قىزغىنلىق تەسىراتى يۇقىرى كۆتۈرۈلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«سىستېما»">
<feature>سىستېمىنىڭ مۇقىملىقى ئۆستۈرۈلۈپ، يانفونىڭىزنىڭ ئىجرا قىلىنىشى تېخىمۇ مۇقىملاشتۇرۇلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«بىخەتەرلىك»">
<feature>ئاندرويدنىڭ 2024-يىل 7-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتىنى زىيارەت قىلىڭ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركىسى مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановний користувачу, у цьому рекомендованому оновленні додано функцію "Улюблені з будь-якого екрана", HONOR Docs і функцію регулювання розміру піктограм на головному екрані, оптимізовано ефект обробки зображення в деяких сценаріях, вирішено проблему ненормального споживання енергії в деяких сценаріях, покращено продуктивність роботи системи, питання стабільності і нагріву, а також додано виправлення системи безпеки.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Улюблені з будь-якого екрана">
<feature>Це оновлення впроваджує оновлений додаток "Улюблені з будь-якого екрана". Проведіть трьома пальцями вниз, щоб зберегти матеріали, як-от зображення, вебсторінки й файли, в додаток "Favorites Space". Торкніться, щоб розгорнути "Favorites Space", натисніть і утримуйте вибрані один або кілька елементів, щоб перетягнути їх до інших додатків, а також їх можна синхронізувати з іншими пристроями MagicRing, щоб обмінюватися зібраним вмістом між пристроями.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>У цьому оновленні впроваджено абсолютно новий додаток HONOR Docs та інтерактивний інтерфейс, додано користувацькі мітки, кошик та інші функції, покращено стабільність і сумісність документів і забезпечено кращу взаємодію з користувачем.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Піктограми на головному екрані">
<feature>Розмір піктограм на головному екрані можна настроювати відповідно до потреб користувача. Щоб зробити це, перейдіть у меню "Налаштування" -> "Головний екран і стиль" -> "Налаштування головного екрана" -> "Розмір піктограми".</feature>
</features>
<features module="Програвач">
<feature>У цьому оновленні додано Музичний програвач для пристрою.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Камера">
<feature>У цьому оновленні оптимізовано ефект яскравості й кольору для зйомки телефотознімків у деяких сценаріях.
У цьому оновленні оптимізовано ефект обробки зображення в портретному фокусуванні в деяких сценаріях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Продуктивність">
<feature>У цьому оновленні вирішено проблему випадкової затримки під час запуску деяких додатків.
У цьому оновленні оптимізовано проблему випадкового падіння частоти кадрів під час запуску додатка.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Споживання енергії">
<feature>Це оновлення усуває проблему аномального енергоспоживання в деяких сценаріях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Питання нагріву">
<feature>У цьому оновленні оптимізовано питання нагріву в деяких ситуаціях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>У цьому оновленні підвищено стабільність роботи системи для надійнішої роботи пристрою.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безпека">
<feature>Виправлення для системи безпеки Android від липня 2024 року впроваджено для посилення безпеки системи. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки HONOR див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примітки." type="end">
<feature>1. Ваші особисті дані не буде видалено внаслідок установлення цього оновлення, але все ж радимо створити резервну копію заздалегідь.
2. Якщо під час оновлення у вас виникнуть будь-які проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію обслуговування користувачів HONOR або зверніться в сервісний центр HONOR по допомогу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>محترم صارف، یہ تجویز کردہ اپ ڈیٹ عالمی من پسند، HONOR Docs اور ہوم اسکرین آئیکن سائز کو ایڈجسٹ کرنے کا فنکشن شامل کرتی ہے، کچھ منظرناموں میں امیجنگ اثر کو بہتر بناتی ہے، کچھ مناظر میں بجلی کی غیر معمولی کھپت کے مسئلے کو حل کرتی ہے، سسٹم کی کارکردگی، استحکام اور حرارتی تجربے کو بہتر بناتی ہے، اور سکیورٹی پیچ شامل کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="عالمی من پسند">
<feature>یہ اپ ڈیٹ نئی اپ گریڈ شدہ عالمی من پسند لاتی ہے۔ مواد، جیسے تصاویر، ویب صفحات اور فائلز کو، من پسند اسپیس میں محفوظ کرنے کے لیے تین انگلیوں سے نیچے کی طرف سوائپ کریں۔ من پسند اسپیس کو پھیلانے کے لیے ٹیپ کریں، منتخب شدہ ایک یا زیادہ آئٹمز کو دیگر ایپس پر گھسیٹنے کے لیے دبائیں اور تھامیں، اور آپ ان کو دیگر MagicRing ڈیوائسز کے ساتھ بھی ہم آہنگ کر سکتے ہیں تاکہ جمع کردہ مواد کو ڈیوائس پر شیئر کریں۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏‏HONOR Docs">
<feature>یہ اپ ڈیٹ بالکل نئی HONOR Docs اور انٹرایکٹو انٹرفیس فراہم کرتی ہے، حسب ضرورت لیبلز، ری سائیکل بن اور دیگر فنکشنز کو شامل کرتی ہے، دستاویز کے استحکام اور مطابقت پذیری کو بہتر بناتی ہے، اور صارف کا بہتر تجربہ فراہم کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="ہوم اسکرین آئیکنز">
<feature>ہوم اسکرین آئیکنز کا سائز صارفین کی مختلف ضروریات کو پورا کرنے کے لیے ایڈجسٹ کیا جا سکتا ہے۔ آپ درج ذیل پر جا کر تجربہ کر سکتے ہیں: ترتیبات -> ہوم اسکرین اور طرز -> ہوم اسکرین کی ترتیبات -> آئیکن کا سائز۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="پلیئر">
<feature>یہ اپ ڈیٹ ڈیوائس پر موسیقی کا پلیئر شامل کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="کیمرہ">
<feature>یہ اپ ڈیٹ کچھ منظرناموں میں ٹیلی فوٹو شوٹنگ کی چمک اور رنگین اثر کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔
یہ اپ ڈیٹ کچھ منظرناموں میں پورٹریٹ فوکس امیجنگ کے اثر کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="کارکردگی">
<feature>یہ اپ ڈیٹ کچھ ایپس کو شروع کرتے وقت بے ترتیبانہ تاخیر کے مسئلے کو حل کرتی ہے۔
یہ اپ ڈیٹ ایپ اسٹارٹ اپ موشن کے اثر میں بے ترتیبانہ فریم ڈراپ کے مسئلے کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="بجلی کی کھپت">
<feature>یہ اپ ڈیٹ کچھ مناظر میں بجلی کی غیر معمولی کھپت کے مسئلے کو حل کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="حرارتی تجربہ">
<feature>یہ اپ ڈیٹ چند منظرناموں میں حرارتی تجربے کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سسٹم">
<feature>آپ کی ڈیوائس کو زیادہ مستحکم طریقے سے چلانے کے لیے یہ اپ ڈیٹ سسٹم کے استحکام کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سکیورٹی">
<feature>‏‏Android سکیورٹی پیچ (جولائی 2024) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ HONOR سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ ملاحظہ کریں: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں مٹے گا، لیکن پھر بھی پہلے سے بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2. اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو تعاون کے لیے براہ کرم HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کریں یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جائیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu tavsiya etiladigan yangilanishda Global saqlash, HONOR Docs va bosh ekrandagi belgilar hajmini oʻzgartirish funksiyasi kiritildi, ayrim holatlardagi tasvirlash effekti optimallandi, ayrim holatlarda quvvatning noodatiy sarflanishi muammosi tuzatildi, tizim unumdorligi, barqarorligi va qizish muammosi optimallandi hamda xavfsizlik tuzatmasi kiritildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Global saqlash">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda yangilangan Global saqlash funksiyasi taqdim etildi. Materiallarni, masalan, rasmlar, veb-sahifalar va fayllarni Saralanganlar xotirasiga saqlash uchun uchta barmoq bilan pastga torting. Saralanganlar xotirasi oynasini yoyish uchun bosing, boshqa ilovalarga tortib tashlash uchun tanlangan bir yoki bir nechta elementni bosib turing, jamlangan kontentni qurilmalararo ulashish uchun ularni boshqa MagicRing qurilmalariga sinxronlashingiz ham mumkin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Docs">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda mutlaqo yangi HONOR Docs va interaktiv interfeys taqdim etildi, maxsus yorliqlar, chiqitdon va boshqa funksiyalar qoʻshildi, hujjat barqarorligi va muvofiqligi optimallandi hamda yanada yaxshi foydalanuvchi taassuroti taqdim etildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bosh ekran belgisi">
<feature>Bosh ekrandagi belgilarning hajmi foydalanuvchilarning turli ehtiyojlarini qondirish uchun sozlanishi mumkin. Uni bu yerda sinashingiz mumkin: Sozlamalar -> Bosh ekran va uslub -> Bosh ekran sozlamalari -> Belgilar hajmi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pleyer">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda qurilmadagi Musiqa pleyeri qoʻshildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kamera">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda ayrim holatlardagi telefoto tasvirga olish yorqinligi va rang effekti yaxshilandi.
Bu yangilanishda ayrim holatlardagi portret fokus tasvirlash effekti optimallandi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Unumdorlik">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda ayrim ilovalarni ishga tushirishda tasodifan yuz beradigan qotish muammosi tuzatildi.
Bu yangilanishda ilovani ishga tushirish harakati effektida kadrlar chastotasining tasodifan pasayib ketishi muammosi tuzatildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Quvvat sarfi">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda ayrim holatlardagi noodatiy quvvat sarfi muammosi tuzatildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qizish muammosi">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda ayrim holatlardagi qizish muammosi optimallandi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tizim">
<feature>Bu yangilanishda qurilmangiz yanada barqaror ishlashi uchun tizim barqarorligi oshirildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Xavfsizlik">
<feature>Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2024-yil, iyul) kiritildi. HONOR Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanish oʻrnatilsa shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringiz oʻchib ketmaydi, lekin ularni oldindan zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, yordam uchun HONOR xizmat markazi tezkor raqamiga murojaat qiling yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyuring.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật đề xuất này bổ sung Mục ưa thích toàn cục, HONOR Tài liệu và chức năng điều chỉnh kích thước biểu tượng màn hình chính, tối ưu hóa hiệu ứng chụp ảnh trong một số trường hợp, khắc phục sự cố tiêu thụ pin bất thường trong một số tình huống, cải thiện hiệu suất hệ thống, độ ổn định và trải nghiệm nóng máy, đồng thời tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mục ưa thích toàn cục">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này mang đến Mục ưa thích toàn cục mới ưu việt. Vuốt xuống bằng ba ngón tay để lưu các tài liệu, chẳng hạn như hình ảnh, trang web và tệp tin vào Không gian ưa thích. Chạm để mở rộng Không gian ưa thích, nhấn và giữ một hoặc nhiều mục đã chọn để kéo các mục đó sang các ứng dụng khác và bạn cũng có thể đồng bộ các mục đó với các thiết bị MagicRing khác nhằm chia sẻ nội dung được thu thập trên các thiết bị.</feature>
</features>
<features module="HONOR Tài liệu">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này cung cấp HONOR Tài liệu và giao diện tương tác hoàn toàn mới, bổ sung nhãn tùy chỉnh, thùng rác và các chức năng khác, cải thiện độ ổn định và khả năng tương thích của tài liệu, đồng thời cung cấp trải nghiệm người dùng tốt hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biểu tượng Màn hình chính">
<feature>Có thể điều chỉnh kích thước biểu tượng Màn hình chính để đáp ứng các nhu cầu khác nhau của người dùng. Bạn có thể trải nghiệm tính năng này bằng cách vào: Cài đặt -> Phong cách và màn hình chính -> Cài đặt màn hình chính -> Kích thước biểu tượng.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Trình phát">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này bổ sung Trình phát nhạc trên thiết bị.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Máy ảnh">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này tối ưu hóa hiệu ứng độ sáng và màu sắc chụp ảnh tele trong một số trường hợp.
Bản cập nhật này tối ưu hóa hiệu ứng chụp ảnh lấy nét ảnh chân dung trong một số trường hợp.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hiệu suất">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này khắc phục sự cố trễ ngẫu nhiên khi khởi chạy một số ứng dụng.
Bản cập nhật này tối ưu hóa vấn đề giảm khung hình ngẫu nhiên trong hiệu ứng chuyển động khi khởi động ứng dụng.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tiêu thụ pin">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này khắc phục sự cố tiêu thụ pin bất thường trong một số tình huống.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Trải nghiệm nóng máy">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này tối ưu hóa trải nghiệm nóng máy trong một số trường hợp.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hệ thống">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này cải thiện độ ổn định của hệ thống để giúp thiết bị của bạn chạy ổn định hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bảo mật">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này tích hợp Bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 7 năm 2024) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của HONOR, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ghi chú:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị xóa. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu trước.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新新增了全局最愛、榮耀文件和主屏幕圖標大小調節功能，優化了部分場景相機拍攝成像效果，修復了部分場景異常耗電問題，提升了系統性能、穩定性和熱體驗，並整合了安全性修補程式，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【全局最愛】">
<feature>全局最愛全新升級。三指向下滑動即可將圖片、網頁、檔案等素材快速儲存至最愛空間。輕觸展開最愛空間，長按單個或多個選取的內容即可拖拽至其他應用程式使用，也可同步至信任環中的其他裝置，跨裝置分享最愛內容。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【榮耀文件】">
<feature>全新榮耀文件，全新互動介面，增加自訂標籤和資源回收桶功能，提升文件穩定性和兼容性，提供更豐富的使用體驗。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【主屏幕圖標】">
<feature>支援主屏幕圖標大小調節，滿足用戶對圖標大小的不同顯示需求，體驗路徑：「設定->主屏幕和個人化->主屏幕設定->圖標大小」。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【播放器】">
<feature>新增本機音樂播放器。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相機】">
<feature>優化了部分場景下長焦拍攝的亮度、顏色效果。
優化了部分場景下人像對焦成像效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【性能】">
<feature>修復了部分應用程式啟動偶爾卡死的問題。
優化了應用程式啟動動畫效果偶爾停滯問題。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【功耗】">
<feature>修復了部分場景異常耗電的問題。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【熱體驗】">
<feature>提升了部分場景性能體驗。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>提升系統穩定性，讓您的手機運行更穩定。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>整合 Android 2024年7月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新新增全域最愛、榮耀文件和桌面圖示大小調整功能，最佳化在部分場景下的相機拍照成像效果，修復在部分場景下的異常耗電問題，提升系統效能、穩定性和熱體驗，並整合安全性修補程式，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【全域最愛】">
<feature>全新升級全域最愛，三指向下滑動即可將圖片、網頁、檔案等素材快速儲存至我的最愛空間。輕觸可展開我的最愛空間，長按單個或多個選取的內容即可拖曳至其他應用程式中使用，也可以同步至信任環中的其他裝置，跨裝置共享我的最愛內容。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【榮耀文件】">
<feature>全新榮耀文件，全新互動介面，增加自訂標籤、資源回收筒功能，提升文件穩定性和相容性，提供更豐富的使用體驗。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【桌面圖示】">
<feature>支援桌面圖示大小調整，滿足使用者對圖示大小的不同顯示需求，體驗路徑：「設定 -> 桌面和個人化 -> 桌面設定 -> 圖示大小」。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【播放器】">
<feature>新增本機音樂播放器。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相機】">
<feature>最佳化在部分場景下長焦拍攝的亮度、色彩效果。
最佳化在部分場景下的人像對焦成像效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【效能】">
<feature>修復部分應用程式啟動時可能當機的問題。
最佳化應用程式啟動時動畫可能丟棄影格的問題。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【電量消耗】">
<feature>修復在部分場景下的異常耗電問題。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【熱體驗】">
<feature>提升在部分場景下的熱體驗。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>提升系統穩定性，讓您的手機執行更穩定。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>整合 Android 2024 年 7 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/7</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
