<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次升级为您推出全新MagicOS 8.0系统，新系统更流畅、更安全、更好用、更省电，桌面更好玩，交互更高效便捷，推荐您更新体验。更多功能解锁敬请期待后续版本更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="丝滑流畅">
<feature>【流畅动效】采用了全新基于人因的动效设计，更自然舒适。</feature>
<feature>【重载流畅】提升多应用并行场景的稳定流畅体验，如边看边买时，购物比价和小窗直播/视频都流畅。</feature>
<feature>【空间压缩】文件无损压缩技术，释放更多存储空间。体验路径：系统管家->清理加速->存储空间压缩。</feature>
</features>
<features module="玩转桌面">
<feature>【桌面快捷服务】长按应用图标拖拽展开快捷功能，应用高频服务一键直达。</feature>
<feature>【全新文件夹】全新设计，提供了更多文件夹尺寸，桌面个性化定制更灵活。可通过长按文件夹，拖拽边框，自由调节。</feature>
<feature>【卡片堆叠】桌面卡片呈现更丰富，支持同尺寸卡片堆叠，上下滑动可切换卡片，节省更多桌面空间。</feature>
<feature>【常驻应用】扩容桌面底部的常驻应用，您可新增常驻应用；拖动分隔线展开或隐藏最近应用图标。</feature>
<feature>【悬浮窗】窗口支持多档尺寸调节，支持等比缩放大小，提升使用体验。</feature>
</features>
<features module="智慧高效">
<feature>【荣耀任意门】全新荣耀任意门，长按文字、图片左右拖拽触发任意门，快捷分享至应用或服务，观影购物、搜索分享、打印收藏等服务一步直达，化繁为简、省时省心。</feature>
<feature>【收藏空间】全局收藏全新升级，万物皆可收藏，将图文、网页、视频、文件等素材快速收藏并显示到收藏空间，轻松收藏素材。点击展开收藏空间，长按单个或多个选中的内容，可拖出至其他应用使用。还可同步至信任环中其他设备，跨设备共享收藏的内容。</feature>
<feature>【个人事务助手】从日程工具到个人事务助手，日程全收纳。散落的日程自动解析帮您录入，“我的一天”全天事务清晰呈现，为您提供高效的个人事务管理服务。</feature>
<feature>【信任环】MagicRing技术持续突破，秒级组网，支持多业务并发，更多设备和服务加入信任环，以人为中心，应用跨端接续，服务高效流转。</feature>
<feature>【荣耀文档】全新荣耀文档，全新交互界面，增加自定义标签、回收站等功能，提升文档稳定性和兼容性，提供更丰富的使用体验。</feature>
<feature>【荣耀笔记】荣耀笔记接入信任环，支持跨设备调用拍照、文档扫描能力；支持手写笔记内容搜索功能，让笔记随心所欲。</feature>
</features>
<features module="安全守护">
<feature>【屏幕共享保护】屏幕共享时，对方无法看到您的通知和消息。当系统检测到存在诈骗风险时，会主动示警并保护您的关键信息不泄露，如个人账号、密码、短信验证码等，保护您的财产安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="便捷好用">
<feature>【熄屏快拍】双击音量下键新增“熄屏快拍”功能。体验路径：设置->辅助功能->快捷启动及手势->快捷功能启动。</feature>
<feature>【助眠显示】基于AI能力个性化匹配生理节律，智能调节屏幕色温，助您在夜晚获得更佳睡眠。体验路径：设置->显示和亮度->护眼与睡眠->助眠显示。</feature>
<feature>【系统应用】新增荣耀游戏中心、荣耀视频、荣耀音乐、荣耀阅读、应用市场等，欢迎您体验使用。浏览器、应用助手等应用全面升级，为您提供更好的体验。</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1、本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2、请务必确保平板有10GB以上的内部存储空间，否则会有升级失败的风险。（查看存储空间方法：设置 -> 存储）。
3、因部分第三方应用与MagicOS 8.0不兼容，更新后可能会出现第三方应用无法正常使用的情况（如闪退、卡顿、耗电等）。建议您在应用市场尝试将该应用更新至最新版本，若仍无法解决问题，请您耐心等待应用更新信息，并及时更新。
4、升级后，系统进行自优化适配，可能会出现发热、耗电快、卡顿或充电慢的问题，正常使用2-3天后会恢复正常。建议升级完成后将平板灭屏充电1~2小时以上再重启平板，以保证平板应用快速适配完。
5、如果您在使用过程中遇到任何问题，请访问“我的荣耀”应用或访问荣耀官方服务网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us 寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear users, this update has launched brand-new MagicOS 8.0 for you. The new system is smoother, safer, easier to use, more power-saving, and the home screen is more fun. We recommend you to update. Please stay tuned for upcoming version updates to unlock more features.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Smooth and seamless">
<feature>【Smooth animations】A brand-new, human-centered motion design is incorporated for a more natural and comfortable experience. </feature>
<feature>【Smooth heavy loading】Improve the stable and smooth performance of multi-app parallel scenarios. For example, when shopping while watching live streams/videos, both comparing prices and mini-window live streams/videos are smooth.</feature>
<feature>【Storage】Lossless file compression releases more storage space. You can experience it by going to: System Manager -> Cleanup -> Storage.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Explore the home screen">
<feature>【Quick services on home screen】Press and hold the app icon and drag to display the shortcuts, and you can directly access high-frequency services.</feature>
<feature>【New folder】A brand-new design provides more folder sizes, making customized home screen more flexible. You can adjust the folder freely by pressing and holding it and dragging the border.</feature>
<feature>【Card stack】More cards are presented on home screen. This update supports the stacking of cards of the same size, saving more space on home screen. You can swipe up and down to switch cards.</feature>
<feature>【Pinned Apps】Expand the space for pinned apps at the bottom of the home screen to add new pinned apps. Drag the divider to expand or hide recent apps.</feature>
<feature>【Floating window】The window supports multi-level size adjustment and proportionally scaling up/down to enhance the using experience.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Smart and Efficient">
<feature>【Magic Portal】This update has provided brand-new HONOR Magic Portal. You can tap and hold text or images and drag them left or right to invoke Magic Portal and quickly share it to apps or services. You can have direct access to services watching movie and shopping, searching and sharing, printing and collection. Magic Portal makes things easier and save much time for you.</feature>
<feature>【Favorites Space】Global Favorites has been newly upgraded, and everything can be collected. Images, texts, web pages, videos, files and other materials can be quickly collected and displayed in the Favorites Space, making it easy to collect materials. Tap to expand Favorites Space, touch and hold the selected one or multiple items, then you can drag them out to other apps. You can also synchronize them to MagicRing devices to share collected content across devices.</feature>
<feature>【Personal Assistant】The schedule tool has been upgraded to Personal Assistant to include all the schedules. This function can automatically analyze scattered schedules and record them. All-day affairs will clearly display in “My Daily schedule”, providing you with efficient personal affairs management.</feature>
<feature>【MagicRing】MagicRing technology continues to make breakthroughs, with second-level networking, supporting multi-service concurrency. More devices and services join MagicRing. MagicRing is people-centered, where applications are connected across devices, and services are efficiently transferred.</feature>
<feature>【HONOR Docs】This update has provided brand-new HONOR Docs and interactive interface, added custom labels, recycle bin and other functions, improved document stability and compatibility, and provided a better user experience.</feature>
<feature>【HONOR Notes】HONOR Notes is connected to MagicRing, supports to invoke shooting and document scanning across devices. It also supports content search for handwritten notes so that you can take notes as you wish.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security Guard">
<feature>【Screen sharing protection】When you are sharing screen, the other party cannot see your notifications and messages. When the system detects the risk of fraud, it will proactively alert you and protect your key information from leakage, such as personal account, password, SMS verification code, etc., to protect your property security.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Convenient and easy to use">
<feature>【Ultra Snapshot】Double-press the Volume Down button to enable Ultra Snapshot. You can Experience by going to: Settings -> Accessibility features -> Shortcuts and gestures -> Quick Launch.</feature>
<feature>【Circadian Night Display】Based on AI capabilities, this feature can personalizedly match circadian rhythm and intelligently adjust the screen color temperature to help you get better sleep at night. You can experience it by going to: Settings -> Display and brightness > Eye Comfort and Sleep -> Circadian Night Display.</feature>
<feature>【System Apps】HONOR Game Center, HONOR Video, HONOR Music, HONOR Reader and AppGallery are added. Welcome to have a try. Browser, AppAssistant and some other applications undergo comprehensive upgrade to provide you with better experience.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. This update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended. 
2. Please make sure your tablet has more than 10GB of free space, or the update may fail. (To check your storage space, go to Settings > Storage). 
3. Some third-party apps may not be compatible with MagicOS 8.0 and may malfunction after the update (such as crash, lag, and abnormal power consumption). Please update your apps to the latest version in App Market. If the problems persist, please wait for upcoming app updates and upgrade in time. 
4. After updating, the system will adjust its settings to apply the optimizations. In the process, the tablet may become hot, consume power fast, lag, or charge slowly. But it will return to normal in 2-3 days of use. After the update is done and before restarting the tablet, we recommend charging it with the screen off for more than 1~2 hours to ensure the optimizations are applied. 
5. If you encounter any problem during use, you can get our support by going to My HONOR or visiting our website at https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us.</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
