<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新灵动胶囊支持美团、美团外卖和百度骑行导航显示，支持智慧识物-购物功能，提升图库、相机使用以及通话体验，优化通知栏和状态栏显示效果，修复部分场景异常耗电问题，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【图库】">
<feature>新增相机水印可编辑功能，可自行添加和还原水印，体验路径：图库>水印照片>编辑>水印图标。
新增AI消除功能，智能消除照片中的路人、杂物等，一键拯救废片，体验路径：图库>图片>编辑>AI消除。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【灵动胶囊】">
<feature>支持美团、美团外卖和百度骑行导航显示（注：美团App需升级至12.21.405及以上版本、美团外卖App需升级至8.28.3及以上版本、百度地图App需升级至20.2.0.1390及以上版本）。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【相机】">
<feature>新增流光快门功能，支持对流动光源轨迹的抓拍，体验路径：相机>更多>流光快门。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【智慧多窗】">
<feature>新增分屏保存功能，分屏状态下点击分屏线中间按钮，可将分屏组合以图标形式保存在桌面，后续通过点击该图标即可快捷打开此分屏组合。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【平行空间】">
<feature>新增防跟踪功能，体验路径：平行空间>设置>位置和广告>防位置跟踪或防广告跟踪。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【智慧视觉】">
<feature>新增支持智慧识物-购物功能。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【通知栏】">
<feature>优化部分场景通知栏布局、动效以及图标显示效果。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【功耗】">
<feature>修复部分场景异常耗电问题。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>合入安卓2024年8月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更多精彩功能介绍，请访问“玩机技巧”应用。
3. 如果您在使用过程中遇到任何问题，请访问“我的荣耀”应用或访问荣耀官方服务网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us 寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update brings new functions and enhancements for a smoother experience. Magic Capsule now displays Meituan, Meituan Delivery and Baidu Map for cycling, and you can be redirected to the shopping page after AI object recognition. This release also improves the user experience of Gallery, Camera and calls, optimizes the display effect of notification panel and status bar. The issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenarios is fixed, and a security patch is incorporated.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Watermarks can now be added and removed as desired. You can experience it by going to: Gallery > Watermarked photos > Edit > Watermarks.
AI Eraser is integrated to intelligently remove the passers-by and other unwanted elements from images effortlessly with a single tap. You can experience it by going to: Gallery > Select a photo > Edit > AI Eraser.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Meituan, Meituan Delivery and Baidu Map for cycling navigation can display on Magic Capsule (Note: Meituan needs to be upgraded to 12.21.405 or above, Meituan Delivery to 8.28.3 or above, Baidu Maps to 20.2.0.1390 or above).</feature>
</features>
<features module="Camera">
<feature>The new Light painting function is able to capture the trajectory of moving light source. You can experience it by going to: Camera > More > LIGHT PAINTING.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>App combinations in split-screen mode can now be saved. In split-screen mode, tap the button in the middle of the divider to save the combination as an icon on the home screen. Tap the icon enables quick access to the combination.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Parallel Space">
<feature>Anti-tracking function is incorporated. Experience it by going to: Parallel Space > Settings > Location and advertising > Select Location preferences or Ad preferences.</feature>
</features>
<features module="AI Lens">
<feature>You can be redirected to the shopping page after AI object recognition.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notification panel">
<feature>The layout, motion effect and icon display effect of the notification panel are optimized in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Power consumption">
<feature>Fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android Security Patch (August 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. Check out more information on product features in the Tips app.
3. If you encounter any problem during use, please get support by going to My HONOR or visiting our website: https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us.</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
