<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新新增分屏保存、相机水印编辑以及眼动追踪功能，优化通知栏显示效果和桌面动效，修复部分场景异常耗电问题，提升系统稳定性，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【智慧多窗】">
<feature>新增分屏保存功能，分屏状态下点击分屏线中间按钮，可将分屏组合以图标形式保存在桌面，后续通过点击该图标即可快捷打开此分屏组合。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【图库】">
<feature>新增相机水印编辑功能，可自行添加和还原水印，体验路径：拍照>打开照片>编辑>水印>水印选择：原图、文字水印、相框水印。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【眼动追踪】">
<feature>新增眼动追踪功能，在距离屏幕20~50厘米处眼睛正对屏幕，无需手动操作，通过注视即可快捷展开相关横幅通知或查看详细内容，体验路径：设置>智慧助手>眼动追踪。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【通知栏】">
<feature>优化通知栏布局显示，界面呈现更加简洁美观。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【动效】">
<feature>优化桌面动效一致性。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【功耗】">
<feature>修复部分场景异常耗电问题。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系统】">
<feature>提升系统稳定性，让您的手机运行更稳定。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>合入安卓2024年8月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, with this recommended update, you can save app combinations in split-screen mode. This update also introduces Eye Tracking, and allows watermarks to be edited. Additionally, this release optimizes the display effect of notification panel and the motion effect on home screen, fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenarios, improves the system stability, and incorporates a security patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>App combinations in split-screen mode can now be saved. In split-screen mode, tap the button in the middle of the divider to save the combination as an icon on the home screen. Tap the icon enables quick access to the combination.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Watermarks can now be added and removed as desired. Experience it by going to: Take a photo > Open the photo > Edit > Watermark > Watermark options: Original, Text watermark, Frame watermark.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eye Tracking">
<feature>Eye Tracking is included, allowing a quick access to the notifications and the detailed content without manual operation when your eyes are directly facing the screen at a distance of 20-50 cm. Experience it by going to: Settings > Assistant > Eye Tracking.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notification panel">
<feature>The layout of notification panel is optimized, making the interface more streamlined and visually appealing.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Motion effect">
<feature>Optimizes the motion effect consistency on the home screen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Power consumption">
<feature>Fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Improves the system stability to make your device run more stably.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android security patch (Aug 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service center for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ በዚህ የሚመከር ዝማኔ የመተግበሪያ ጥምረቶችን በተከፈለ ማያ ሁነታ ማስቀመጥ ይችላሉ። ይህ ዝማኔ የአይን ክትትልንም ያስተዋውቃል፣ እና ጌጥሽልሞችን ማርትዕ ያስችላል። በተጨማሪም፣ ይህ ልቀት በየማሳወቂያ ስሌዳ የማሳያ ተጽእኖ እና በመነሻ ገጽ ላይ ያለውን የእንቅስቃሴ ተጽእኖ ያተባል፣ በአንዳንድ ሁኔታዎች ላይ ያልተለመደ የኃይል ፍጆታ ችግርን ያስተካክላል፣ የስርዓቱን መረጋጋት ያሻሽላል እና የደህንነት መጠገኛን ያካትታል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ብዙ-መስኮት">
<feature>አሁን በተከፈለ ማያ ገጽ ያሉ የመተግበሪያ ውህዶች ሊቀመጡ ይችላሉ። በተከፈለ ማያ ገጽ ሁነታ፣ ውህዱን በመነሻ ማያ ገጽ ላይ እንደ አዶ ለማስቀመጥ በአከፋፋዩ መሃል ያለውን አዝራር መታ ያድርጉ። አዶውን መታ ማድረግ ወደ ውህዱ ፈጣን መዳረሻ ያስችላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የሥነ ጥበብ ማዕከል">
<feature>ጌጥሽልሞች አሁን እንደተፈለገው ሊታከሉ እና ሊወገዱ ይችላሉ። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ፎቶ ያንሱ > ፎቶውን ይክፈቱ > አርትዕ > ጌጥሽልም > ጌጥሽልም አማራጮች፦ የመጀመሪያው፣ የጽሑፍ ጌጥሽልም፣ የክፈፍ ጌጥሽልም።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የአይን ክትትል">
<feature>አይኖችዎ ከ20-50 ሳ.ሜ ርቀት ላይ በቀጥታ ወደ ማያ ገጹ ሲመለከቱ ያለ የእጅ እንቅስቃሴ ማሳወቂያዎችን እና ዝርዝር ይዘቱን በፍጥነት እንዲደርሱበት የሚያስችል የአይን ክትትል ተካትቷል። ወደሚከተለው በመሄድ ይሞክሩት፦ ቅንብሮች > ረዳት > የአይን ክትትል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማሳወቂያ ሰሌዳ">
<feature>የማሳወቂያ ፓነል አቀማመጥ ተስተካክሏል፣ በይነገጹን ይበልጥ የተሳለጠ እና ለዕይታ ማራኪ ያደርገዋል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የእንቅስቃሴ ተፅዕኖ">
<feature>በመነሻ ማያ ገጽን ላይ ያለውን የእንቅስቃሴ ተፅዕኖ ወጥነት ያመቻቻል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የኃይል ፍጆታ">
<feature>ይህ ዝማኔ በአንዳንድ ትዕይንቶች ላይ ያለውን ያልተለመደ የኃይል ፍጆታ ችግር ያስተካክላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ስርዓት">
<feature>የስርዓት መረጋጋትን አሻሽሏል፣ ይህም መሳሪያዎ ስራውን በተጨማሪ መረጋጋት እንዲያካሄድ ያደርገዋል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ደህንነት">
<feature>ለስርዓት ደህንነት የአንድሮይድ የደህንነት መጠገኛን (ጃን 2024) ተካቷል። ስለ HONOR ደህንነት ማዘመኛዎች ተጨማሪ መረጃ ለማግኘት እባክዎን የእኛን ድረ-ገጽ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8 ይጎብኙ</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ማሻሻያ መጫን የእርስዎን የግል መረጃዎን አያስቀርም፣ ነገር ግን አስቀድሞ መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ አሁንም ይመከራል።
2. በማሻሻያው ወቅት ማንኛውም አይነት ችግር ካጋጠመዎት እባክዎን ወደ HONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር ይደውሉ ወይም ድጋፍ ለማግኘት ወደ HONOR የደንበኞች የአገልግሎት ማዕከል ይሂዱ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، مع هذا التحديث الموصى به، يمكنك حفظ مجموعات تطبيقات في وضع تقسيم الشاشة. يقدم هذا التحديث أيضًا ميزة "تتبع حركة العين" ويسمح بتعديل العلامات المائية. بالإضافة إلى ذلك، يحسّن هذا الإصدار تأثير عرض لوحة الإشعارات وتأثير الحركة على الشاشة الرئيسية، ويُصلح مشكلة استهلاك الطاقة غير الطبيعي في بعض السيناريوهات، ويحسّن استقرار النظام، ويضمّن تصحيح أمان.</feature>
</features>
<features module="النوافذ المتعددة">
<feature>يمكن الآن حفظ مجموعات التطبيقات في وضع تقسيم الشاشة. في وضع تقسيم الشاشة، اضغط على الزر الموجود في منتصف المقسم لحفظ المجموعة كأيقونة على الشاشة الرئيسية. يؤدي الضغط على الأيقونة إلى تمكين الوصول السريع إلى المجموعة.</feature>
</features>
<features module="المعرض">
<feature>يمكن الآن إضافة العلامات المائية وإزالتها كما تقتضي الحاجة. يمكنك تجربتها بالانتقال إلى: التقاط صورة > فتح الصورة > تعديل > علامة مائية > خيارات العلامة المائية: الأصلية، علامة مائية على هيئة نص، علامة مائية على هيئة إطار.</feature>
</features>
<features module="تتبع حركة العين">
<feature>تم تضمين ميزة تتبع حركة العين، مما يسمح بالوصول السريع إلى الإشعارات والمحتوى التفصيلي دون الحاجة إلى التشغيل اليدوي عند مواجهة عينيك للشاشة بشكل مباشر على مسافة من 20 إلى 50 سم. يمكنك تجربة هذه الميزة بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات > المساعد > تتبع حركة العين.</feature>
</features>
<features module="لوحة الإشعارات">
<feature>تم تحسين تخطيط لوحة الإشعارات، مما يجعل الواجهة أكثر تنظيمًا وجاذبية من الناحية البصرية.</feature>
</features>
<features module="تأثير الحركة">
<feature>يحسّن تناسق تأثير الحركة على الشاشة الرئيسية.</feature>
</features>
<features module="استهلاك الطاقة">
<feature>يُصلح مشكلة استهلاك الطاقة غير الطبيعي في بعض السيناريوهات.</feature>
</features>
<features module="النظام">
<feature>يحسّن استقرار النظام لجعل جهازك يعمل بشكل أكثر استقرارًا.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الأمان">
<feature>تم تضمين تصحيح أمان أندرويد (أغسطس 2024) لأمان النظام. لمزيد من المعلومات حول تحديثات الأمان في HONOR، يرجى زيارة موقعنا على الويب https://www.honor.com/ae-ar/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>1. لن يؤدي تثبيت هذا التحديث إلى مسح بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن من المستحسن إجراء عملية نسخ احتياطي مسبقًا.
2. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة HONOR أو انتقل إلى مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR للحصول على الدعم.‬</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই অনুমোদিত আপডেটৰ সৈতে আপুনি স্প্লিট-স্ক্ৰীণ মোডত এপ্প্‌ৰ সংমিশ্ৰণ সংৰক্ষণ কৰিব পাৰে। এই আপডেটটোৱে চকু ট্ৰেক কৰাৰো পৰিচয় কৰায় আৰু ৱাটাৰমাৰ্কসমূহ সম্পাদনা কৰিবলৈ অনুমতি দিয়ে। অতিৰিক্তভাৱে, এই মুক্তিয়ে অধিসূচনা পেনেলৰ ডিচপ্লেৰ প্ৰভাৱ আৰু হোম স্ক্ৰীণত গতিৰ প্ৰভাৱ অনুকূলন কৰে, কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত অস্বাভাৱিক পাৱাৰ খৰচৰ সমস্যা সমাধান কৰে, ছিষ্টেমৰ স্থিৰতা উন্নত কৰে আৰু এটা নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="মাল্টি-উইণ্ড'">
<feature>এতিয়া স্প্লিট-স্ক্ৰীণ মোডত এপ্প্‌ৰ সংমিশ্ৰণ সংৰক্ষণ কৰিব পাৰি। স্প্লিট-স্ক্ৰীণ মোডত, হোম স্ক্ৰীণত সংমিশ্ৰণক এটা চিহ্ন ৰূপে সংৰক্ষণ কৰিবলৈ ডিভাইডাৰৰ মাজত থকা বুটামটো টিপক। চিহ্নটো টিপিলে সংমিশ্ৰণলৈ দ্ৰুত প্ৰৱেশ সক্ষম কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গেলাৰী">
<feature>ৱাটাৰমাৰ্কসমূহ এতিয়া ইচ্ছা অনুসৰি যোগ কৰিব আৰু আঁতৰাব পাৰি। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াৰ অভিজ্ঞতা লওক: এখন ফটো লওক > ফটো খোলক > সম্পাদনা কৰক > ৱাটাৰমাৰ্ক > ৱাটাৰমাৰ্কৰ বিকল্পসমূহ: মূল, পাঠ ৱাটাৰমাৰ্ক, ফ্ৰেম ৱাটাৰমাৰ্ক।</feature>
</features>
<features module="চকু ট্ৰেক কৰা">
<feature>চকু ট্ৰেক কৰা অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হয়, যিয়ে আপোনাৰ চকু 20-50 cm দূৰত্বত পোনপটীয়াকৈ স্ক্ৰীণখনৰ ফালে থকাৰ সময়ত মেনুৱেল কাৰ্য অবিহনে অধিসূচনাসমূহ আৰু বিস্তৃত সমললৈ দ্ৰুত প্ৰৱেশৰ অনুমতি দিয়ে। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াৰ অভিজ্ঞতা লওক: ছেটিংছ > সহায়ক > চকু ট্ৰেক কৰা।</feature>
</features>
<features module="অধিসূচনা পেনেল">
<feature>অধিসূচনা পেনেলৰ লেআউট অনুকূলন কৰা হয়, যিয়ে ইণ্টাৰফেচ অধিক সুসংগত আৰু দৃশ্যমানভাৱে আকৰ্ষণীয় বনায়।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গতিৰ প্ৰভাৱ">
<feature>হোম স্ক্ৰীণত গতিৰ প্ৰভাৱৰ সংগতি অনুকূলন কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="পাৱাৰ খৰচ">
<feature>কিছুমান পৰিস্থিতিত অস্বাভাৱিক পাৱাৰ খৰচৰ সমস্যাটো সমাধান কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ছিষ্টেম">
<feature>আপোনাৰ ডিভাইচ অধিক স্থিৰতাৰে চলাবলৈ ছিষ্টেমৰ স্থিৰতা উন্নত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিৰাপত্তা">
<feature>ছিষ্টেমৰ নিৰাপত্তাৰ বাবে Android নিৰাপত্তাৰ পেচ (আগষ্ট 2024) অন্তৰ্ভুক্ত কৰা হৈছে। HONOR নিৰাপত্তা আপডেটৰ বিষয়ে অধিক তথ্যৰ বাবে, অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি আমাৰ ৱেবছাইট দৰ্শন কৰক: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটা মোহৰা নহ'ব, কিন্তু তথাপিও তাৰ আগতে বেকআপ ল'বলৈ অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আপডেটৰ সময়ত আপুনি যদি কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হয়, তেন্তে সমৰ্থনৰ বাবে অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত ফোন কৰিব বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ যাব।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, tövsiyə edilən bu yeniləmə ilə siz proqram kombinasiyalarını bölünmüş ekran rejimində saxlaya bilərsiniz. Bu yeniləmə Gözün izlənilməsi xüsusiyyətini də təqdim edir və su nişanlarını redaktə etməyə imkan verir. Bundan əlavə, bu buraxılış bildiriş panelinin displey effektini və əsas ekranda hərəkət effektini optimallaşdırır, bəzi hallarda qeyri-normal enerji sərfiyyatı problemini həll edir, sistem sabitliyini yaxşılaşdırır və təhlükəsizlik paketi daxil edir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="İki Pəncərəli">
<feature>Artıq bölünmüş ekran rejimində proqram kombinasiyaları yadda saxlanıla bilər. Bölünmüş ekran rejimində kombinasiyanı əsas ekranda nişan kimi yadda saxlamaq üçün bölücünün ortasındakı düyməyə toxunun. Nişana toxunmaq kombinasiyaya sürətli daxil olmaq imkanı verir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qalereya">
<feature>Su nişanları artıq istədiyiniz kimi əlavə edilə və silinə bilər. Aşağıdakı bölməyə keçərək bunu təcrübədən keçirin: Foto çəkin > Fotonu açın > Redaktə edin > Su nişanı > Su nişanı seçimləri: Orijinal, Mətn su nişanı, Çərçivə su nişanı.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gözün izlənilməsi">
<feature>Gözləriniz birbaşa ekrana 20-50 sm məsafədə baxdıqda manual işləmədən bildirişlərə və təfərrüatlı məzmuna sürətli giriş imkanı verən Gözün izlənilməsi daxildir. Bu bölmələrə keçərək sınayın: Parametrlər > Yardımçı > Gözün izlənilməsi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bildiriş paneli">
<feature>Bildiriş panelinin tərtibatı optimallaşdırılaraq interfeysi daha rasional və vizual olaraq cəlbedici edir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hərəkət effekti">
<feature>Əsas ekranda hərəkət effektinin ardıcıllığını optimallaşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Enerji sərfiyyatı">
<feature>Bəzi hallarda qeyri-normal enerji sərfiyyatı problemini həll edir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Cihazınızın daha stabil işləməsi üçün sistem stabilliyini təkmilləşdirir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Təhlükəsizlik">
<feature>Sistem təhlükəsizliyi üçün Android təhlükəsizlik paketi (Avqust 2024-cü il) daxil edilib. HONOR Təhlükəsizlik yeniləmələri haqqında ətraflı məlumat üçün veb-saytımıza daxil olun: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması ilə şəxsi məlumatlarınız silinməyəcək, lakin yenə də qabaqcadan ehtiyat nüsxənin çıxarılması tövsiyə edilir.
2. Bu yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlərlə qarşılaşsanız, dəstək üçün HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edin, yaxud HONOR müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə gedin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, kanthi penganyaran sing disaranake iki, sampeyan bisa nyimpen kombinasi apl ing mode layar misah. Panganyaran iki uga ngenalake Nglacak Mripat, lan ngidini pangeditan watermark. Saliyane iku, rilis iki ngoptimalake efek tampilan panel notifikasi lan efek obahan ing layar ngarep, ndandani masalah panggunaan daya sing ora normal ing sawetara skenario, ngapikake kastabilan sistem, lan nggabungake patch keamanan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Kombinasi apl ing mode layar misah saiki bisa disimpen. Ing mode layar misah, tutul tombol ing tengahe pamisah kanggo nyimpen kombinasi minangka ikon ing layar ngarep. Nutul ikon kasebut bakal ngaktifake akses cepet menyang kombinasi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Watermark saiki bisa ditambahake lan dibusak miturut kekarepan sampeyan. Gunakake fungsi iki kanthi mbukak: Jupuk foto > Bukak foto > Edit > Watermark > Opsi watermark: Asli, Watermark teks, Watermark pigurah.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nglacak Mripat">
<feature>Nglacak Mripat dilebokake saengga ngidini akses cepet menyang notifikasi lan rincian konten tanpa operasi manual nalika mripat sampeyan madhep langsung menyang layar ing adohe 20–50 cm. Gunakake fungsi iki kanthi mbukak: Setelan > Assistant > Nglacak Mripat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panel notifikasi">
<feature>Tatanan panel notifikasi dioptimalake saengga antarmukane dadi luwih ringkes lan tampilane luwih apik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efek obahan">
<feature>Ngoptimalake konsistensi efek obahan ing layar ngarep.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panggunaan daya">
<feature>Ndandani masalah panggunaan daya sing ora normal ing sawetara skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Ngapikake kastabilan sistem supaya piranti mlaku kanthi luwih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Patch keamanan Android (Agustus 2024) wis digabungake kanggo keamanan sistem. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan panganyaran Keamanan HONOR bisa dideleng ing situs web kita https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mbusak data pribadi sampeyan, nanging nggawe serep dhisik tetep disaranake.
2. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, ubungi hotline layanan HONOR utawa tekani pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR kanggo njaluk dukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem možete da sačuvate kombinacije aplikacija u režimu podeljenog ekrana. Ovo ažuriranje takođe uvodi Praćenje očiju i omogućava da se izmene vodeni žigovi. Pored toga, ovo izdanje optimizuje efekat prikazivanja table sa obaveštenjima i efekat kretanja na početnom ekranu, rešava problem prekomerne potrošnje energije u nekim scenarijima, poboljšava stabilnost sistema i uključuje bezbednosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Više prozora">
<feature>Kombinacije aplikacija u režimu podeljenog ekrana sada mogu da se sačuvaju. U režimu podeljenog ekrana dodirnite dugme u sredini razdelnika da biste sačuvali kombinaciju kao ikonu na početnom ekranu. Dodirivanje ikone omogućava brzi pristup kombinaciji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Vodeni žigovi sada mogu da se dodaju i uklanjaju prema želji. Iskusite to tako što ćete otići na opciju: Napravi fotografiju > Otvori fotografiju > Izmeni > Vodeni žig > Opcije vodenog žiga: Original, Tekstualni vodeni žig, Vodeni žig sa okvirom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Praćenje očiju">
<feature>Praćenje očiju je uključeno i omogućava brzi pristup obaveštenjima i detaljnom sadržaju bez ručnih radnji kada su oči direktno naspram ekrana na razdaljini od 20-50 cm. Iskusite to tako što ćete otići na opciju: Podešavanja > Asistent > Praćenje očiju.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tabla sa obaveštenjima">
<feature>Raspored table sa obaveštenjima je optimizovan, tako da je interfejs unapređen i vizuelno primamljiviji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efekat pokreta">
<feature>Optimizuje doslednost efekta kretanja na početnom ekranu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Rešava problem nepravilne potrošnje energije u pojedinim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Poboljšava stabilnost sistema, zbog čega vaš uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (avg 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Da biste dobili više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem možete da sačuvate kombinacije aplikacija u režimu podeljenog ekrana. Ovo ažuriranje takođe uvodi Praćenje očiju i omogućava da se izmene vodeni žigovi. Pored toga, ovo izdanje optimizuje efekat prikazivanja table sa obaveštenjima i efekat kretanja na početnom ekranu, rešava problem prekomerne potrošnje energije u nekim scenarijima, poboljšava stabilnost sistema i uključuje bezbednosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Više prozora">
<feature>Kombinacije aplikacija u režimu podeljenog ekrana sada mogu da se sačuvaju. U režimu podeljenog ekrana dodirnite dugme u sredini razdelnika da biste sačuvali kombinaciju kao ikonu na početnom ekranu. Dodirivanje ikone omogućava brzi pristup kombinaciji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Vodeni žigovi sada mogu da se dodaju i uklanjaju prema želji. Iskusite to tako što ćete otići na opciju: Napravi fotografiju > Otvori fotografiju > Izmeni > Vodeni žig > Opcije vodenog žiga: Original, Tekstualni vodeni žig, Vodeni žig sa okvirom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Praćenje očiju">
<feature>Praćenje očiju je uključeno i omogućava brzi pristup obaveštenjima i detaljnom sadržaju bez ručnih radnji kada su oči direktno naspram ekrana na razdaljini od 20-50 cm. Iskusite to tako što ćete otići na opciju: Podešavanja > Asistent > Praćenje očiju.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tabla sa obaveštenjima">
<feature>Raspored table sa obaveštenjima je optimizovan, tako da je interfejs unapređen i vizuelno primamljiviji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efekat pokreta">
<feature>Optimizuje doslednost efekta kretanja na početnom ekranu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Rešava problem nepravilne potrošnje energije u pojedinim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Poboljšava stabilnost sistema, zbog čega vaš uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (avg 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Da biste dobili više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem možete da sačuvate kombinacije aplikacija u režimu podeljenog ekrana. Ovo ažuriranje takođe uvodi Praćenje očiju i omogućava da se izmene vodeni žigovi. Pored toga, ovo izdanje optimizuje efekat prikazivanja table sa obaveštenjima i efekat kretanja na početnom ekranu, rešava problem prekomerne potrošnje energije u nekim scenarijima, poboljšava stabilnost sistema i uključuje bezbednosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Više prozora">
<feature>Kombinacije aplikacija u režimu podeljenog ekrana sada mogu da se sačuvaju. U režimu podeljenog ekrana dodirnite dugme u sredini razdelnika da biste sačuvali kombinaciju kao ikonu na početnom ekranu. Dodirivanje ikone omogućava brzi pristup kombinaciji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Vodeni žigovi sada mogu da se dodaju i uklanjaju prema želji. Iskusite to tako što ćete otići na opciju: Napravi fotografiju > Otvori fotografiju > Izmeni > Vodeni žig > Opcije vodenog žiga: Original, Tekstualni vodeni žig, Vodeni žig sa okvirom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Praćenje očiju">
<feature>Praćenje očiju je uključeno i omogućava brzi pristup obaveštenjima i detaljnom sadržaju bez ručnih radnji kada su oči direktno naspram ekrana na razdaljini od 20-50 cm. Iskusite to tako što ćete otići na opciju: Podešavanja > Asistent > Praćenje očiju.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tabla sa obaveštenjima">
<feature>Raspored table sa obaveštenjima je optimizovan, tako da je interfejs unapređen i vizuelno primamljiviji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efekat pokreta">
<feature>Optimizuje doslednost efekta kretanja na početnom ekranu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Rešava problem nepravilne potrošnje energije u pojedinim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Poboljšava stabilnost sistema, zbog čega vaš uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezbednost">
<feature>Integrisana je bezbednosna zakrpa za Android (avg 2024.) za bezbednost sistema. Da biste dobili više informacija o bezbednosnim ažuriranjima koja sprovodi kompanija HONOR, posetite naš veb-sajt: https://www.honor.com/rs/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта рэкамендаванае абнаўленне дазваляе захоўваць камбінацыі праграм у рэжыме раздзельнага экрана. Гэта версія ўводзіць функцыю «Адсочванне позірку» і дазваляе рэдагаваць вадзяныя знакі. Акрамя таго, у гэтай версіі аптымізаваны эфект адлюстравання панэлі апавяшчэнняў і эфект руху на галоўным экране, выпраўлена праблема анамальнага энергаспажывання ў некаторых сцэнарыях, палепшана ўстойлівасць сістэмы. Таксама гэта абнаўленне ўключае выпраўленне сістэмы бяспекі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Многааконнасць">
<feature>Цяпер можна захоўваць камбінацыі праграм у рэжыме раздзельнага экрана. У рэжыме раздзельнага экрана націсніце на кнопку ў сярэдзіне раздзяляльніка, захаваць камбінацыю ў выглядзе значка на галоўным экране. Націснуўшы на значок, вы зможаце хутка аднавіць камбінацыю.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерэя">
<feature>Цяпер вадзяныя знакі можна дадаваць і выдаляць па жаданні. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Зрабіць фота > Адкрыць фота > Рэдагаваць > Вадзяны знак > Тыпы вадзянога знака: арыгінал, тэкставы вадзяны знак, вадзяны знак-рамка».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Адсочванне позірку">
<feature>Дададзена функцыя «Адсочванне позірку». Яна дазваляе атрымаць хуткі доступ да апавяшчэнняў і падрабязнага змесціва без неабходнасці выконваць дзеянні ўручную, калі вашы вочы глядзяць прама на экран з адлегласці 20–50 см. Каб паспрабаваць, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады > Памочнік > Адсочванне позірку».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Панэль апавяшчэнняў">
<feature>Аптымізавана кампаноўка панэлі апавяшчэнняў: інтэрфейс стаў больш зручным і прывабным.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Эфект руху">
<feature>Аптымізавана плаўнасць эфекту руху на галоўным экране.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Энергаспажыванне">
<feature>Гэта абнаўленне ўстараняе праблему анамальнага энергаспажывання ў некаторых сцэнарыях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сістэма">
<feature>Устойлівасць сістэмы павышана, што робіць працу прылады больш стабільнай.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бяспека">
<feature>Для павышэння бяспекі сістэмы ўключана выпраўленне функцый бяспекі Android (жнівень 2024 г.). Больш інфармацыі аб абнаўленні сістэмы бяспекі HONOR можна знайсці на нашым афіцыйным вэб-сайце: https://www.honor.com/by/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі:" type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не сатрэ вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем загадзя зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, патэлефануйце на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або звярніцеся па дапамогу ў сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, с тази препоръчителна актуализация можете да запазвате комбинации от приложения в режим на разделен екран. С тази актуализация се въвежда и „Проследяване на очи“ и се дава възможност за редактиране на водни знаци. Освен това тази версия оптимизира ефекта на показване на панела за известия и ефекта на движение на началния екран, отстранява проблема с необичайното потребление на енергия при някои ситуации, подобрява стабилността на системата и включва корекция за сигурност.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Няколко прозореца">
<feature>Комбинациите от приложения в режим на разделен екран вече могат да се запазват. В режим на разделен екран докоснете бутона в средата на разделителя, за да запазите комбинацията като икона на началния екран. Докосването на иконата позволява бърз достъп до комбинацията.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерия">
<feature>Водните знаци вече могат да се добавят и премахват по желание. Изпробвайте това, като отидете на: „Направете снимка > Отворете снимката > Редактиране > Воден знак > Опции за воден знак: Без ефекти, текстови воден знак, рамка с воден знак“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Проследяване на очи">
<feature>Включена е функцията „Проследяване на очи“, която позволява бърз достъп до известията и подробното съдържание без ръчно управление, когато очите ви са директно насочени към екрана на разстояние 20 – 50 см. Изпробвайте това, като отидете на адрес: „Настройки > Асистент > Проследяване на очи“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Панел за известия">
<feature>Оформлението на панела за известия е оптимизирано, което прави интерфейса по-рационален и визуално привлекателен.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ефект на движение">
<feature>Оптимизира последователността на ефекта на движение на началния екран.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Консумация на енергия">
<feature>Отстранява проблема с необичайната консумация на енергия при някои ситуации.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>Подобрява стабилността на системата, за да работи устройството ви по-стабилно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сигурност">
<feature>Корекцията за сигурност на Android (август 2024 г.) е включена за защита на системата. За още информация относно актуализациите за сигурност на HONOR посетете нашия уебсайт https://www.honor.com/bg/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да изтрие личните ви данни, но е препоръчително архивиране преди това.
2. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализирането, обадете се на обслужващата гореща линия на HONOR или посетете сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR за поддръжка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই সুপারিশকৃত আপডেটের মাধ্যমে, আপনি স্প্লিট-স্ক্রিন মোডে অ্যাপের সংমিশ্রণগুলি সংরক্ষণ করতে পারেন। এছাড়াও এই আপডেটটি আই ট্র্যাকিং-এর সূচনা করে এবং ওয়াটারমার্ক সম্পাদনা করতে দেয়। এছাড়াও এই রিলিজটি বিজ্ঞপ্তি প্যানেলের ডিসপ্লে ইফেক্ট এবং হোম স্ক্রিনে মোশন ইফেক্টকে অপটিমাইজ করে, কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে অস্বাভাবিক শক্তি খরচের সমস্যা সমাধান করে, সিস্টেমের স্থিতিশীলতা উন্নত করে এবং এতে একটি নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ অন্তর্ভুক্ত আছে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="মাল্টি উইন্ডো">
<feature>স্প্লিট-স্ক্রিন মোডে অ্যাপের সংমিশ্রণগুলি এখন সংরক্ষণ করা যেতে পারে। স্প্লিট-স্ক্রিন মোডে, সংমিশ্রণটিকে হোম স্ক্রিনে একটি আইকন হিসাবে সংরক্ষণ করতে বিভাজকের মাঝখানের বাটনটি ট্যাপ করুন। আইকনটি ট্যাপ করলে সংমিশ্রণটিতে কুইক অ্যাক্সেস সক্রিয় করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="গ্যালারি">
<feature>এখন ইচ্ছামত ওয়াটারমার্ক যোগ করা এবং মুছে ফেলা যায়। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: একটি ফটো তুলুন > ফটোটি খুলুন > সম্পাদনা করুন > ওয়াটারমার্ক > ওয়াটারমার্কের বিকল্প: মূল, টেক্সট ওয়াটারমার্ক, ফ্রেম ওয়াটারমার্ক।</feature>
</features>
<features module="আই ট্র্যাকিং">
<feature>আই ট্র্যাকিং অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে, যা আপনার চোখগুলি 20-50 সেমি দূরত্বে সরাসরি স্ক্রিনের দিকে মুখ করে থাকলে ম্যানুয়াল কাজ ছাড়াই বিজ্ঞপ্তি এবং বিস্তারিত বিষয়বস্তুতে কুইক অ্যাক্সেস দেয়। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস > সহকারী > আই ট্র্যাকিং।</feature>
</features>
<features module="বিজ্ঞপ্তি প্যানেল">
<feature>বিজ্ঞপ্তি প্যানেলের লেআউটটি অপটিমাইজ করা হয়েছে, যা ইন্টারফেসটিকে আরও সুবিন্যস্ত এবং চাক্ষুষভাবে আকর্ষণীয় করে তুলেছে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="মোশন ইফেক্ট">
<feature>হোম স্ক্রিনে মোশন ইফেক্টের ধারাবাহিকতা অপটিমাইজ করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="শক্তি খরচ">
<feature>কিছু পরিস্থিতিতে অস্বাভাবিক শক্তি খরচের সমস্যা সমাধান করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="সিস্টেম">
<feature>আপনার ডিভাইসকে আরও স্থিতিশীলভাবে চলার জন্য সিস্টেমের স্থিতিশীলতা উন্নত করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নিরাপত্তা">
<feature>সিস্টেমের নিরাপত্তার জন্য Android নিরাপত্তা প্যাচ (আগস্ট 2024) অন্তর্ভুক্ত করা হয়েছে। HONOR-এর নিরাপত্তা আপডেটগুলি সম্পর্কে আরো তথ্যের জন্য, অনুগ্রহ করে আমাদের ওয়েবসাইট দেখুন https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটা মুছে যাবে না, তবে তা সত্ত্বেও আগে থেকে ব্যাকআপ নেওয়ার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. আপনি আপডেটের সময় কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে HONOR সার্ভিস হটলাইনে কল করুন বা সহায়তার জন্য HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে যান।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིས་གསར་སྒྱུར་དུ་ཡོལ་བགོ་ཉར་ཚགས་དང་པར་ཆས་ཆུ་དཔར་རྩོམ་སྒྲིག མིག་འགུལ་རྗེས་སྙེག་བཅས་ཀྱི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། བརྡ་ཐོའི་ཚན་བྱང་གི་མངོན་སྟོན་ཁྱད་ནུས་དང་ཅོག་ངོས་འགུལ་ཁྱད་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་གློག་ཟད་རྒྱུན་ལྡན་མིན་པའི་གནད་དོན་ཉམས་གསོ་བྱས་ཡོད། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད། བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདུས་གྲུབ་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རིག་ལྡན་སྒྲོམ་མང་།】">
<feature>ཡོལ་བགོ་ཉར་ཚགས་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཡོལ་བགོའི་རྣམ་པའི་འོག་ཏུ་ཡོལ་བགོའི་ཐིག་གི་བར་གྱི་མཐེབ་ལ་བརྡབས་ན། ཡོལ་བགོའི་ཚོགས་སྒྲིག་རིས་རྟགས་རྣམ་པས་ཅོག་ངོས་སུ་ཉར་ཚགས་བྱ་ཆོག རྗེས་སུ་རིས་རྟགས་འདི་རྡེབ་པ་བརྒྱུད་ནས་མགྱོགས་མྱུར་གྱིས་ཡོལ་བགོ་ཚོགས་སྒྲིག་འདི་ཁ་ཕྱེ་ཆོག</feature>
</features>
<features module="【པར་མཛོད།】">
<feature>པར་ཆས་ཆུ་དཔར་རྩོམ་སྒྲིག་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཆུ་དཔར་རང་ཉིད་ཀྱིས་སྣོན་པ་དང་སོར་ལོག་བྱ་ཆོག ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། པར་ལེན་ནས་འདྲ་པར་ཁ་ཕྱེ་བ། དེ་ནས་རྩོམ་སྒྲིག དེ་ནས་ཆུ་དཔར། དེ་ནས་ཆུ་དཔར་འདེམས་པ་སྟེ། ཐོག་མའི་པར་དང་ཡི་གེའི་ཆུ་དཔར། པར་སྒྲོམ་གྱི་ཆུ་དཔར།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【མིག་འགུལ་རྗེས་སྙེག】">
<feature>མིག་འགུལ་རྗེས་སྙེག་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། བརྙན་ཡོལ་དང་བར་ཐག་ལི་སྨི་ 20 ནས་ 50 བར་དུ་མིག་བརྙན་ཡོལ་ལ་གཏད་ན། ལག་འགུལ་གྱིས་བཀོལ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་མི་དགོས་པར། བལྟ་བ་བརྒྱུད་ནས་མགྱོགས་མྱུར་གྱིས་འབྲེལ་ཡོད་ཀྱི་འཕྲེད་འཇོག་གི་བརྡ་ཐོ་སྤེལ་བའམ་ཞིབ་ཕྲའི་ནང་དོན་ལ་ལྟ་ཞིབ་བྱ་ཆོག ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་རིག་ལྡན་ལག་རོགས། དེ་ནས་མིག་འགུལ་རྗེས་སྙེག</feature>
</features>
<features module="【བརྡ་ཐོའི་ཚན་བྱང་།】">
<feature>བརྡ་ཐོའི་ཚན་བྱང་གི་བཀོད་སྒྲིག་མངོན་སྟོན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད། མཚམས་ངོས་འགྲེམ་སྟོན་དེ་བས་སྟབས་བདེ་དང་མཛེས་པོ་ཡིན།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【འགུལ་ཁྱད།】">
<feature>ཅོག་ངོས་འགུལ་ཁྱད་ཀྱི་གཅིག་གྱུར་རང་བཞིན་ལེགས་སྒྱུར་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【ནུས་རྩོལ།】">
<feature>བཟོ་ལྗོངས་ཁག་ཅིག་གི་གློག་ཟད་རྒྱུན་ལྡན་མིན་པའི་གནད་དོན་ཉམས་གསོ་བྱས་ཡོད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རྒྱུད་ཁོངས】">
<feature>རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བརྟན་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་སྟེ། ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་གྱི་འཁོར་སྐྱོད་སྔར་ལས་བརྟན་འཇགས་སུ་གཏོང་དགོས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【བདེ་འཇགས།】">
<feature>ཨན་སྒྲོའི་ 2024 ལོའི་ཟླ་བ་ 8 པའི་བདེ་འཇགས་ལྷན་པ་འདྲེས་འཇུག་བྱས་ཏེ། རྒྱུད་ཁོངས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་རང་བཞིན་སྟོབས་སྒྱུར་བྱེད། རུང་ཡོའོ་མཉེན་ཆས་ཀྱི་བདེ་འཇགས་གསར་སྒྱུར་ནང་དོན་སྐོར་གྱི་ཆ་འཕྲིན་རུང་ཡོའོ་གཞུང་ཕྱོགས་དྲ་ཚིགས https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/8 ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་གསར་སྒྱུར་མ་བྱས་གོང་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ཡག་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་ལ་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ་ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་སྐུ་མགྲོན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་སོང་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་རེ་ཞུ་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, uz ovo preporučeno ažuriranje možete pohranjivati kombinacije aplikacija u načinu rada s podijeljenim ekranom. Ovo ažuriranje uvodi i Praćenje oka te omogućava uređivanje vodenih žigova. Osim toga, ovo izdanje optimizira efekat prikaza panela za obavještenja i efekat kretanja na početnom ekranu, rješava problem neuobičajene potrošnje energije u određenim scenarijima, poboljšava stabilnost sistema i ugrađuje sigurnosnu zakrpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Višeprozorno">
<feature>Sada se mogu pohranjivati kombinacije aplikacija u načinu rada s podijeljenim ekranom. Dok ste u načinu rada s podijeljenim ekranom dodirnite dugme na sredini razdjelnika da sačuvate kombinaciju kao ikonu na početnom ekranu. Dodirom na ikonu možete brzo pristupiti sačuvanoj kombinaciji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Vodeni žigovi se sada mogu dodavati i uklanjati po želji. Isprobajte odlaskom u opciju Snimite fotografiju > Otvorite fotografiju > Uredi > Vodeni žig > Opcije vodenog žiga: Original, Vodeni žig s tekstom, Vodeni žig s okvirom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Praćenje oka">
<feature>Uključeno je Praćenje oka, što omogućava brzi pristup obavještenjima i detaljnom sadržaju bez ručnog upravljanja kada gledate pravo u ekran na udaljenosti od 20–50 cm. Isprobajte odlaskom u Postavke > Pomoćnik > Praćenje oka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panel za obavještenja">
<feature>Optimiziran je raspored panela za obavještenja, što interfejs čini jasnijim i vizuelno privlačnijim.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efekat kretanja">
<feature>Optimizira dosljednost efekta kretanja na početnom ekranu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Rješava problem neuobičajene potrošnje energije u određenim scenama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Poboljšava stabilnost sistema kako bi se omogućio stabilniji rad uređaja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Ugrađena je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (aug 2024) radi sigurnosti sistema. Više informacija o HONOR sigurnosnim ažuriranjima potražite na našoj web lokaciji https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja se neće izbrisati lični podaci, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització recomanada us permet desar combinacions d'aplicacions en mode de pantalla dividida. Aquesta actualització també introdueix la funció Seguiment ocular i permet editar les filigranes. A més, aquesta versió optimitza l'efecte del disseny del tauler de notificacions i l'efecte de moviment a la pantalla inicial, soluciona el problema del consum anormal d'energia en determinades situacions, millora l'estabilitat del sistema i incorpora un pedaç de seguretat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Diverses finestres">
<feature>Ara, les combinacions en el mode de pantalla dividida es poden desar. En el mode de pantalla dividida, toqueu el botó situat al centre del separador per desar la combinació com una icona a la pantalla inicial. Toqueu la icona per habilitar l'accés ràpid a la combinació.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>Ara, les filigranes es poden afegir i eliminar quan vulgueu. Per utilitzar aquestes funcions, aneu a Fer una foto > Obrir la foto > Editar > Filigrana > Opcions de filigrana: Original, Filigrana de text, Filigrana de marc.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguiment ocular">
<feature>Inclou el Seguiment ocular, que permet accedir ràpidament a les notificacions i al contingut detallat sense operació manual quan els ulls estan mirant directament la pantalla a una distància de 20-50 cm. Per utilitzar aquesta funció, aneu a Configuració > Assistent > Seguiment ocular.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tauler de notificacions">
<feature>El disseny del tauler de notificacions s'ha optimitzat, la qual cosa fa que la interfície sigui més àgil i visualment atractiva.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efecte de moviment">
<feature>Optimitza la coherència de l'efecte de moviment a la pantalla inicial.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consum d'energia">
<feature>Soluciona el problema del consum d'energia anormal en determinades situacions.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Millora l'estabilitat del sistema, la qual cosa permet que el funcionament del dispositiu sigui més estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguretat">
<feature>S'ha incorporat el pedaç de seguretat d'Android (agost del 2024) per a la seguretat del sistema. Per obtenir més informació sobre les actualitzacions de seguretat d'HONOR, consulteu el nostre lloc web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Si instal·leu aquesta actualització, les dades personals no s'esborraran, però us recomanem que en feu una còpia de seguretat.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o aneu al centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR per demanar assistència.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený uživateli, s touto doporučenou aktualizací můžete ukládat kombinace aplikací v režimu rozdělené obrazovky. Tato aktualizace také uvádí Sledování očí a umožňuje upravovat vodoznaky. Tato verze navíc optimalizuje efekt zobrazení v oznamovacím panelu a efekt pohybu na domovské obrazovce, opravuje problém neobvyklé spotřeby energie v některých situacích, zlepšuje stabilitu systému a instaluje opravu zabezpečení.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Více oken">
<feature>Kombinace aplikací v režimu rozdělené obrazovky lze nyní uložit. V režimu rozdělené obrazovky klepnutím na tlačítko uprostřed oddělovače uložte kombinaci jako ikonu na domovské obrazovce. Klepnutím na ikonu zapnete rychlý přístup ke kombinaci.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Vodoznaky lze nyní přidávat a odstraňovat podle potřeby. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce: Pořídit fotografii > Otevřít fotografii > Upravit > Vodoznak > Možnosti vodoznaku: Originál, Textový vodoznak, Rámečkový vodoznak.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sledování očí">
<feature>Součástí je funkce Sledování očí, která umožňuje rychlý přístup k upozorněním a podrobnému obsahu bez ručního ovládání, když jsou vaše oči přímo obráceny k obrazovce ve vzdálenosti 20-50 cm. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce: Nastavení > Asistent > Sledování očí.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oznamovací panel">
<feature>Rozložení oznamovacího panelu je optimalizováno, díky čemuž je rozhraní efektivnější a vizuálně přitažlivější.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pohybový efekt">
<feature>Optimalizuje konzistenci pohybového efektu na domovské obrazovce.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Spotřeba energie">
<feature>Opravuje problém neobvyklé spotřeby energie v některých situacích.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Vylepšuje stabilitu systému, aby zařízení pracovalo stabilněji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bezpečnost">
<feature>Do systému byla začleněna bezpečnostní oprava (srpen 2024) pro systém Android zajišťující bezpečnost systému. Více informací o bezpečnostních aktualizacích HONOR najdete na našem webu https://www.honor.com/cz/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalací této aktualizace nebudou vymazány vaše osobní údaje, ale přesto se doporučuje je předem zálohovat.
2. Pokud se během aktualizace setkáte s nějakými problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo si vyžádejte podporu v Centru služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger, med denne anbefalede opdatering kan du gemme appkombinationer i tilstanden med opdelt skærm. Denne opdatering introducerer også Øjensporing og tillader redigering af vandmærker. Derudover optimerer denne version visningseffekten for Meddelelsespanelet og bevægelseseffekten på startskærmen, løser problemet med unormalt strømforbrug i nogle scenarier, forbedrer systemstabiliteten og integrerer en sikkerhedsrettelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-vindue">
<feature>Appkombinationer i tilstanden Opdelt skærm kan nu gemmes. I tilstanden Opdelt skærm skal du trykke på knappen midt på deleren for at gemme kombinationerne som et ikon på startskærmen. Ved at trykke på ikonet aktiverer du hurtig adgang til kombinationen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleri">
<feature>Vandmærker kan nu tilføjes og fjernes efter ønske. Oplev det ved at gå til: Tag et foto > Åbn fotoet > Rediger > Vandmærke > Vandmærkeindstillinger: Original, Tekstvandmærke, Rammevandmærke.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Øjensporing">
<feature>Øjensporing er inkluderet, hvilket tillader hurtig adgang til meddelelserne og det detaljerede indhold uden manuel betjening, når dine øjne er vendt direkte mod skærmen på en afstand af 20-50 cm. Oplev det ved at gå til: Indstillinger > Assistent > Øjensporing.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Meddelelsespanel">
<feature>Meddelelsespanelets layout er blevet optimeret, hvilket gør grænsefladen mere strømlinet og visuelt tiltrækkende.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bevægelseseffekt">
<feature>Optimerer bevægelseseffektens gennemførthed på startskærmen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Strømforbrug">
<feature>Løser problemet med unormalt strømforbrug i visse scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Forbedrer systemstabiliteten, så din enhed kører mere stabilt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhed">
<feature>Android sikkerhedsrettelse (aug 2024) er blevet integreret for systemsikkerhed. Du kan få flere oplysninger om HONOR-sikkerhedsopdateringer på vores websted https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering vil ikke slette dine personlige data, men det anbefales dog stadig at tage en sikkerhedskopi på forhånd.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du ringe til HONORs service-hotline eller gå til HONORs kundeservicecenter for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Lieber Nutzer, mit dieser empfohlenen Aktualisierung können Sie App-Kombinationen im Modus Geteilter Bildschirm speichern. Diese Aktualisierung führt außerdem Eye-Tracking ein und ermöglicht die Bearbeitung von Wasserzeichen. Darüber hinaus optimiert diese Version den Anzeigeeffekt des Benachrichtigungsfelds und den Bewegungseffekt auf dem Startbildschirm, behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenarien, verbessert die Systemstabilität und umfasst einen Sicherheitspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>App-Kombinationen im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus können jetzt gespeichert werden. Tippen Sie im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus auf die Schaltfläche in der Mitte des Teilers, um die Kombination als Symbol auf dem Startbildschirm zu speichern. Durch Tippen auf das Symbol können Sie schnell auf die Kombination zugreifen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Wasserzeichen können nun nach Bedarf hinzugefügt und entfernt werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Foto aufnehmen > Foto öffnen > Bearbeiten > Wasserzeichen > Wasserzeichenoptionen: Original, Textwasserzeichen, Rahmen-Wasserzeichen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eye-Tracking">
<feature>Eye-Tracking ist enthalten und ermöglicht einen schnellen Zugriff auf Benachrichtigungen und detaillierte Inhalte ohne manuelle Bedienung, wenn Ihre Augen in einem Abstand von 20 bis 50 cm direkt auf den Bildschirm gerichtet sind. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Einstellungen > Assistent > Eye-Tracking.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Benachrichtigungsfeld">
<feature>Das Layout des Benachrichtigungsfelds wurde optimiert, wodurch die Benutzeroberfläche schlanker und optisch ansprechender wird.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bewegungseffekt">
<feature>Optimiert die Konsistenz der Bewegungseffekte auf dem Startbildschirm.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stromverbrauch">
<feature>Behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Verbessert die Systemstabilität, damit Ihr Gerät stabiler läuft.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Aug. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Durch die Installation dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch trotzdem empfohlen, im Vorfeld eine Datensicherung vorzunehmen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Lieber Nutzer, mit dieser empfohlenen Aktualisierung können Sie App-Kombinationen im Modus Geteilter Bildschirm speichern. Diese Aktualisierung führt außerdem Eye-Tracking ein und ermöglicht die Bearbeitung von Wasserzeichen. Darüber hinaus optimiert diese Version den Anzeigeeffekt des Benachrichtigungsfelds und den Bewegungseffekt auf dem Startbildschirm, behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenarien, verbessert die Systemstabilität und umfasst einen Sicherheitspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>App-Kombinationen im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus können jetzt gespeichert werden. Tippen Sie im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus auf die Schaltfläche in der Mitte des Teilers, um die Kombination als Symbol auf dem Startbildschirm zu speichern. Durch Tippen auf das Symbol können Sie schnell auf die Kombination zugreifen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Wasserzeichen können nun nach Bedarf hinzugefügt und entfernt werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Foto aufnehmen > Foto öffnen > Bearbeiten > Wasserzeichen > Wasserzeichenoptionen: Original, Textwasserzeichen, Rahmen-Wasserzeichen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eye-Tracking">
<feature>Eye-Tracking ist enthalten und ermöglicht einen schnellen Zugriff auf Benachrichtigungen und detaillierte Inhalte ohne manuelle Bedienung, wenn Ihre Augen in einem Abstand von 20 bis 50 cm direkt auf den Bildschirm gerichtet sind. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Einstellungen > Assistent > Eye-Tracking.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Benachrichtigungsfeld">
<feature>Das Layout des Benachrichtigungsfelds wurde optimiert, wodurch die Benutzeroberfläche schlanker und optisch ansprechender wird.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bewegungseffekt">
<feature>Optimiert die Konsistenz der Bewegungseffekte auf dem Startbildschirm.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stromverbrauch">
<feature>Behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Verbessert die Systemstabilität, damit Ihr Gerät stabiler läuft.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Aug. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Durch die Installation dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch trotzdem empfohlen, im Vorfeld eine Datensicherung vorzunehmen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Lieber Nutzer, mit dieser empfohlenen Aktualisierung können Sie App-Kombinationen im Modus Geteilter Bildschirm speichern. Diese Aktualisierung führt außerdem Eye-Tracking ein und ermöglicht die Bearbeitung von Wasserzeichen. Darüber hinaus optimiert diese Version den Anzeigeeffekt des Benachrichtigungsfelds und den Bewegungseffekt auf dem Startbildschirm, behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenarien, verbessert die Systemstabilität und umfasst einen Sicherheitspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>App-Kombinationen im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus können jetzt gespeichert werden. Tippen Sie im geteilten Bildschirm-Modus auf die Schaltfläche in der Mitte des Teilers, um die Kombination als Symbol auf dem Startbildschirm zu speichern. Durch Tippen auf das Symbol können Sie schnell auf die Kombination zugreifen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Wasserzeichen können nun nach Bedarf hinzugefügt und entfernt werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Foto aufnehmen > Foto öffnen > Bearbeiten > Wasserzeichen > Wasserzeichenoptionen: Original, Textwasserzeichen, Rahmen-Wasserzeichen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eye-Tracking">
<feature>Eye-Tracking ist enthalten und ermöglicht einen schnellen Zugriff auf Benachrichtigungen und detaillierte Inhalte ohne manuelle Bedienung, wenn Ihre Augen in einem Abstand von 20 bis 50 cm direkt auf den Bildschirm gerichtet sind. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Einstellungen > Assistent > Eye-Tracking.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Benachrichtigungsfeld">
<feature>Das Layout des Benachrichtigungsfelds wurde optimiert, wodurch die Benutzeroberfläche schlanker und optisch ansprechender wird.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bewegungseffekt">
<feature>Optimiert die Konsistenz der Bewegungseffekte auf dem Startbildschirm.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stromverbrauch">
<feature>Behebt das Problem des unnormalen Stromverbrauchs in einigen Szenarien.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Verbessert die Systemstabilität, damit Ihr Gerät stabiler läuft.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicherheit">
<feature>Der Android Sicherheitspatch (Aug. 2024) für Systemsicherheit wurde integriert. Weitere Informationen über die HONOR Sicherheitsaktualisierungen finden Sie auf unserer Website: https://www.honor.com/de/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Durch die Installation dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch trotzdem empfohlen, im Vorfeld eine Datensicherung vorzunehmen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, με αυτή την προτεινόμενη ενημέρωση, μπορείτε να αποθηκεύσετε συνδυασμούς εφαρμογών στη λειτουργία διαιρεμένης οθόνης. Αυτή η ενημέρωση εισάγει επίσης την Ιχνηλάτηση βλέμματος και επιτρέπει την επεξεργασία υδατογραφημάτων. Επιπλέον, αυτή η έκδοση βελτιστοποιεί την ποιότητα απεικόνισης του πίνακα ειδοποιήσεων και το εφέ κίνησης στην αρχική οθόνη, διορθώνει το πρόβλημα της μη φυσιολογικής κατανάλωσης ενέργειας σε ορισμένα σενάρια, βελτιώνει τη σταθερότητα του συστήματος και ενσωματώνει μια ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Πολλαπλά παράθυρα">
<feature>Οι συνδυασμοί εφαρμογών σε λειτουργία διαιρεμένης οθόνης μπορούν πλέον να αποθηκευτούν. Στη λειτουργία διαιρεμένης οθόνης, πατήστε το κουμπί στη μέση του διαχωριστικού για να αποθηκεύσετε τον συνδυασμό ως εικονίδιο στην αρχική οθόνη. Πατήστε το εικονίδιο για γρήγορη πρόσβαση στον συνδυασμό.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Συλλογή">
<feature>Τα υδατογραφήματα μπορούν πλέον να προστεθούν και να αφαιρεθούν, όπως επιθυμείτε. Δοκιμάστε το μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Λήψη φωτογραφίας > Άνοιγμα της φωτογραφίας > Επεξεργασία > Υδατογράφημα > Επιλογές υδατογραφήματος: Αρχικό, Υδατογράφημα κειμένου, Υδατογράφημα πλαισίου.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ιχνηλάτηση βλέμματος">
<feature>Περιλαμβάνεται η Ιχνηλάτηση βλέμματος, επιτρέποντας τη γρήγορη πρόσβαση στις ειδοποιήσεις και στο λεπτομερές περιεχόμενο χωρίς χειροκίνητη λειτουργία όταν τα μάτια σας κοιτάζουν απευθείας την οθόνη σε απόσταση 20-50 cm. Δοκιμάστε την μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις > Βοηθός > Ιχνηλάτηση βλέμματος.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Πίνακας ειδοποιήσεων">
<feature>Η διάταξη του πίνακα ειδοποιήσεων βελτιστοποιήθηκε, κάνοντας έτσι το περιβάλλον εργασίας πιο απλοποιημένο και όμορφο.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Εφέ κίνησης">
<feature>Βελτιστοποιεί τη συνοχή του εφέ κίνησης στην αρχική οθόνη.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Κατανάλωση ενέργειας">
<feature>Διορθώνει το πρόβλημα της μη φυσιολογικής κατανάλωσης ενέργειας σε ορισμένα σενάρια.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σύστημα">
<feature>Βελτιώνει τη σταθερότητα του συστήματος για να λειτουργεί η συσκευή σας πιο σταθερά.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ασφάλεια">
<feature>Η ενημέρωση κώδικα ασφαλείας Android (Αύγουστος 2024) ενσωματώθηκε για την ασφάλεια του συστήματος. Για περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις ενημερώσεις της Ασφάλειας HONOR, επισκεφθείτε τον ιστότοπό μας https://www.honor.com/gr/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα διαγράψει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, ωστόσο συνιστάται προηγουμένως η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας.
2. Εάν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, καλέστε την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή της HONOR ή μεταβείτε στο κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR για υποστήριξη.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, with this recommended update, you can save app combinations in split-screen mode. This update also introduces Eye Tracking, and allows watermarks to be edited. Additionally, this release optimises the display effect of notification panel and the motion effect on home screen, fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenarios, improves the system stability, and incorporates a security patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>App combinations in split-screen mode can now be saved. In split-screen mode, tap the button in the middle of the divider to save the combination as an icon on the home screen. Tap the icon enables quick access to the combination.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Watermarks can now be added and removed as desired. Experience it by going to: Take a photo > Open the photo > Edit > Watermark > Watermark options: Original, Text watermark, Frame watermark.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eye Tracking">
<feature>Eye Tracking is included, allowing a quick access to the notifications and the detailed content without manual operation when your eyes are directly facing the screen at a distance of 20-50 cm. Experience it by going to: Settings > Assistant > Eye Tracking.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notification panel">
<feature>The layout of notification panel is optimised, making the interface more streamlined and visually appealing.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Motion effect">
<feature>Optimises the motion effect consistency on the home screen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Power consumption">
<feature>Fixes the issue of abnormal power consumption in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Improves the system stability to make your device run more stably.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>Android security patch (Aug 2024) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/uk/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service centre for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, con esta actualización recomendada, podrá guardar combinaciones de aplicaciones en modo de pantalla dividida. Esta actualización también implemente Seguimiento ocular y permite editar marcas de agua. Además, esta versión optimiza el efecto de visualización del panel de notificaciones y el efecto de movimiento en la pantalla principal, corrige el problema del consumo de energía anormal en algunos escenarios, mejora la estabilidad del sistema e incorpora un parche de seguridad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ventanas múltiples">
<feature>Ahora se pueden guardar combinaciones de aplicaciones en modo de pantalla dividida. En el modo de pantalla dividida, toque el botón en el medio del divisor para guardar la combinación como un icono en la pantalla principal. Al pulsar el icono se habilita el acceso rápido a la combinación.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galería">
<feature>Ahora se pueden agregar y eliminar marcas de agua según se desee. Puede activar esta opción si va a: Tomar una foto > Abrir la foto > Editar > Marca de agua > Opciones de marca de agua: Original, Marca de agua de texto, Marca de agua de marco.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguimiento ocular">
<feature>Se incluye Seguimiento ocular, lo que permite un acceso rápido a las notificaciones y al contenido detallado sin necesidad de hacer operaciones manuales cuando los ojos están directamente orientados hacia la pantalla a una distancia de entre 20 y 50 cm. Para activar esta opción, acceda a: Ajustes > Asistente > Seguimiento ocular.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panel de notificaciones">
<feature>Se ha optimizado el diseño del panel de notificaciones, lo que hace que la interfaz sea más sencilla y visualmente atractiva.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efecto de movimiento">
<feature>Optimiza la consistencia del efecto de movimiento en la pantalla principal.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de energía">
<feature>Soluciona el problema del consumo de energía anormal en algunos escenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Mejora la estabilidad del sistema para que el dispositivo funcione de manera más estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se ha incorporado el parche de seguridad de Android (agosto de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/es/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Aunque la instalación de esta actualización no eliminará sus datos personales, se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad antes.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para obtener ayuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, con esta actualización recomendada, podrá guardar combinaciones de aplicaciones en modo de pantalla dividida. Esta actualización también incorpora el Seguimiento ocular y permite editar marcas de agua. Además, esta versión optimiza el efecto de visualización del panel de notificaciones y el efecto de movimiento en la pantalla principal, corrige el problema del consumo de energía anormal en algunas situaciones, mejora la estabilidad del sistema e incorpora un parche de seguridad.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ventanas múltiples">
<feature>Ahora se pueden guardar combinaciones de aplicaciones en modo de pantalla dividida. En el modo de pantalla dividida, presione el botón en el medio del divisor para guardar la combinación como un ícono en la pantalla principal. Al presionar el ícono se habilita el acceso rápido a la combinación.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galería">
<feature>Ahora se pueden agregar y eliminar marcas de agua según se desee. Puede activar esta opción si va a: Tomar una foto > Abrir la foto > Editar > Marca de agua > Opciones de marca de agua: Original, Marca de agua de texto, Marca de agua del marco.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguimiento ocular">
<feature>Se incluye Seguimiento ocular, lo que permite un acceso rápido a las notificaciones y al contenido detallado sin necesidad de hacer operaciones manuales cuando los ojos están directamente orientados hacia la pantalla a una distancia de entre 20 y 50 cm. Para activar esta opción, acceda a: Ajustes > Asistente > Seguimiento ocular.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panel de notificaciones">
<feature>Se optimizó el diseño del panel de notificaciones, lo que hace que la interfaz sea más sencilla y visualmente atractiva.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efecto de movimiento">
<feature>Optimiza la consistencia del efecto de movimiento en la pantalla principal.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de energía">
<feature>Soluciona el problema del consumo de energía anormal en algunas situaciones.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Mejora la estabilidad del sistema para que el dispositivo funcione de manera más estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Se incorporó un parche de seguridad de Android (agosto de 2024) para la seguridad del sistema. Para obtener más información sobre las actualizaciones de seguridad de HONOR, visite nuestro sitio web: https://www.honor.com/latam/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Esta actualización no eliminará sus datos personales; sin embargo, le recomendamos hacer una copia de respaldo de los datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visite el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja! Selle soovitatava värskendusega saate rakenduste kombinatsioonid salvestada jagatud ekraani režiimis. Lisaks hõlmab see värskendus silmade jälgimise funktsiooni ja võimaldab vesimärkide muutmist. Peale selle optimeerib värskendus teavituspaneeli kuvaefekti ja avakuva liikumisefekti, lahendab mõnes olukorras ebanormaalse energiakulu probleemi, parandab süsteemi stabiilsust ja sisaldab turvapaika.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mitu akent">
<feature>Jagatud ekraani režiimis saab nüüd rakenduste kombinatsioone salvestada. Puudutage jagatud ekraani režiimis eraldusjoone keskel olevat nuppu, et kombinatsioon ikoonina avakuvale salvestada. Ikooni puudutamisel avaneb kohe sama kombinatsioon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerii">
<feature>Nüüd saab vesimärke vabalt lisada ja eemaldada. Selleks tehke foto > avage foto > valige Redigeeri > Vesimärk > Vesimärgi suvandid: Algne, Tekstiline vesimärk või Raamiga vesimärk.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Silmade jälgimine">
<feature>Nüüd on olemas silmade jälgimine, mis võimaldab kiirpääsu märguannete ja üksikasjaliku sisu juurde käsi kasutamata, kui hoiate ekraani otse silmade ees 20–50 cm kaugusel. Kasutamiseks valige Sätted > Assistent > Silmade jälgimine.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Teavituspaneel">
<feature>Teavituspaneeli paigutust optimeeriti, et liides oleks hoomatavam ja ilusam.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Liikumisefekt">
<feature>Optimeerib liikumisefekti järjepidevust avakuval.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energiakulu">
<feature>Lahendab mõnes olukorras ebanormaalse energiakulu probleemi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Süsteem">
<feature>Parandab süsteemi stabiilsust, et teie seade töötaks ühtlasemalt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvalisus">
<feature>Lisati süsteemi turvalisemaks muutev Androidi turvapaik (august 2024). Lisateavet HONORi turvavärskenduste kohta leiate meie veebisaidilt https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei kustuta teie isikuandmeid, kuid eelnev varundamine on siiski soovitatav.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, helistage HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või minge toe saamiseks HONORi klienditeeninduskeskusesse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile hori: gomendatutako eguneratze honekin, zatitutako pantailako aplikazio-konbinazioak gorde ditzakezu. Halaber, eguneratzeak Begien jarraipena aurkezten du eta ur-markak editatzeko aukera ematen dizu. Gainera, bertsio honek jakinarazpen-panelaren bistaratze-efektua eta hasierako pantailako mugimendu-efektua optimizatzen ditu, ezohiko energia-kontsumoarekin izandako arazoa konpontzen du zenbait egoeratan, sistemaren egonkortasuna hobetzen du eta segurtasun-adabaki bat du barne.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Leiho anitz">
<feature>Orain, aplikazioen konbinazioak zatitutako pantaila moduan gorde daitezke. Zatitutako pantaila moduan, zatitzailearen erdian dagoen botoia ukitu, hasierako pantailan konbinazioa ikono gisa gordetzeko. Ikonoa ukitzeak konbinaziorako sarbide azkarra izateko aukera ematen du.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>Orain, ur-markak nahierara gehitu eta ezaba daitezke. Horretarako, joan hona: Atera argazkia > Ireki argazkia > Editatu > Ur-marka > Ur-markaren aukerak: Jatorrizkoa, Testu-uraren marka, Markaren ura-marka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Begien jarraipena">
<feature>Barne hartzen da Begien jarraipena, jakinarazpenetarako eta eduki xehekaturako sarbide azkarra ahalbidetzen duena eskuzko eragiketarik gabe zure begiak zuzenean pantailaren aurrean daudenean 20-50 cm-ko distantzian. Esperimentatu honako honetara joanez: Ezarpenak > Laguntzailea > Begien jarraipena.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Jakinarazpen-panela">
<feature>Jakinarazpenen panelaren diseinua optimizatu egin da, eta, ondorioz, interfazea arinagoa eta bisualki erakargarriagoa da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mugimendu-efektua">
<feature>Hasierako pantailan mugimendu-efektuaren trinkotasuna optimizatzen du.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bateriaren kontsumoa">
<feature>Egoera batzuetan bateriaren kontsumo anormalaren arazoa konpontzen du.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Sistemaren egonkortasuna hobetzen du, gailuak hobeto funtziona dezan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurtasuna">
<feature>Android-en segurtasun-adabakia (2024ko abu.) gehitu da sistema seguru egoteko. HONOR Segurtasun-eguneratzeei buruzko informazio gehiago nahi izanez gero, joan gure webgunera: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzen baduzu ere, zure datu pertsonalak ez dira ezabatuko, baina, hala ere, instalatu aurretik haien babeskopia bat egitea gomendatzen da.
2. Eguneratze-prozesuan arazoren bat izanez gero, deitu HONOR zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara edo joan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora laguntza jasotzeko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>کاربر گرامی، با انجام این به‌روزرسانی پیشنهادی، می‌توانید ترکیبات برنامه‌ها را در حالت تقسیم صفحه ذخیره کنید. ین به‌روزرسانی همچنین «ردیابی چشم» را ارائه می‌دهد و امکان ویرایش واترمارک‌ها را فراهم می‌کند. علاوه‌براین، این نسخه جلوه نمایش پانل اعلانات و جلوه حرکت را در صفحۀ اصلی بهینه می‌سازد، مشکل مصرف غیرعادی نیرو را در برخی سناریوها برطرف می‌کند، ثبات سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد و حاوی یک وصله امنیتی است.</feature>
</features>
<features module="پنجره‌ها">
<feature>اکنون ترکیب برنامه‌ها در حالت تقسیم صفحه را می‌توان ذخیره کرد. در حالت تقسیم صفحه، روی دکمه وسط تقسیم‌کننده ضربه بزنید تا آن ترکیب به‌صورت آیکونی در صفحۀ اصلی ذخیره شود. با ضربه زدن روی آیکون، امکان دسترسی سریع به ترکیب فراهم می‌شود.</feature>
</features>
<features module="گالری">
<feature>اکنون می‌توانید واترمارک‌ها را به‌دلخواه اضافه و حذف کنید. آن را با رفتن به این قسمت تجربه کنید: «گرفتن عکس > باز کردن عکس > ویرایش > واترمارک > گزینه‌های واترمارک: اصلی، واترمارک متنی، واترمارک قاب».</feature>
</features>
<features module="ردیابی چشم">
<feature>‏«ردیابی چشم» گنجانده شده است، که امکان می‌دهد زمانی که چشمان شما مستقیماً رو به صفحۀ نمایش در فاصله ‎۲۰-۵۰ سانتی‌متری هستند، بدون عملیات دستی دسترسی سریعی به اعلان‌ها و محتوای دقیق داشته باشید. آن را با رفتن به این قسمت تجربه کنید: «تنظيمات > دستیار > ردیابی چشم».</feature>
</features>
<features module="پانل اعلانات">
<feature>چیدمان پانل اعلانات بهینه می‌شود که رابط کاربری را ساده‌تر و از نظر بصری جذاب‌تر می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="جلوه حرکت">
<feature>یکپارچگی جلوه حرکت در صفحۀ اصلی را بهینه می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="مصرف نیرو">
<feature>مشکل مصرف غیرعادی نیرو در برخی شرایط را برطرف می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="سیستم">
<feature>پایداری سیستم را بهبود می‌بخشد تا دستگاه شما عملکرد پایدارتری داشته باشد.</feature>
</features>
<features module="امنیت">
<feature>برای حفظ امنیت سیستم، وصلۀ امنیتی Android (اوت ۲۰۲۴) گنجانده شده است. برای کسب اطلاعات بیشتر دربارۀ به‌روزرسانی‌های امنیتی HONOR، لطفاً به وب‌سایت ما به این نشانی مراجعه کنید: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="نکات مهم:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏۱. با نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما پاک نخواهد شد، اما همچنان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام این به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.
‏‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، لطفاً جهت دریافت پشتیبانی با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämän suositellun päivityksen ansiosta jaetun näytön tilassa käytetyt sovellusyhdistelmät voidaan tallentaa. Tämä päivitys lisää myös Silmien seuranta -ominaisuuden ja mahdollistaa vesileimojen muokkaamisen. Lisäksi tämä päivitys optimoi ilmoituspaneelin näyttötehosteen ja aloitusnäytön liiketehosteen, korjaa epätavallisen virrankulutuksen ongelman joissakin tilanteissa, parantaa järjestelmän vakautta ja sisältää turvallisuuskorjauksen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Moni-ikkuna">
<feature>Jaetun näytön tilassa käytetyt sovellusyhdistelmät voidaan nyt tallentaa. Tallenna yhdistelmä kuvakkeena aloitusnäytölle napauttamalla jakajan keskellä olevaa painiketta. Kuvaketta napauttamalla voit käyttää yhdistelmää nopeasti.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleria">
<feature>Vesileimoja voidaan nyt lisätä ja poistaa tarpeen mukaan. Kokeile sitä: Ota valokuva > Avaa valokuva > Muokkaa > Vesileima > Vesileimavaihtoehdot: Alkuperäinen, Tekstivesileima, Kehyksen vesileima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Silmien seuranta">
<feature>Lisätyn Silmien seuranta -toiminnon avulla näet ilmoitukset ja niiden yksityiskohtaisen sisällön nopeasti käsiäsi käyttämättä, kun katsot suoraan näyttöön 20–50 cm:n päästä. Kokeile sitä menemällä kohtaan Asetukset > Avustaja > Silmien seuranta.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ilmoituspaneeli">
<feature>Ilmoituspaneelin asettelu on optimoitu, ja käyttöliittymä on nyt virtaviivaisempi ja visuaalisesti miellyttävämpi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Liiketehoste">
<feature>Optimoi liiketehosteen yhtenäisyyden aloitusnäytöllä.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Virrankulutus">
<feature>Korjaa epätavallisen virrankulutuksen ongelman joissakin tilanteissa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Järjestelmä">
<feature>Parantaa järjestelmän vakautta, jolloin laite toimii vakaammin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Turvallisuus">
<feature>Android-turvallisuuskorjaus (elokuu 2024) on lisätty järjestelmän turvallisuutta varten. Lisätietoja HONORin turvallisuuspäivityksistä on saatavilla verkkosivustollamme osoitteessa https://www.honor.com/fi/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei pyyhi henkilökohtaisia tietojasi, mutta niiden varmuuskopiointi ennen asennusta on kuitenkin suositeltavaa.
2. Soita HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käy HONORin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa, jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia ja tarvitset apua.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, avec cette mise à jour recommandée, vous pouvez enregistrer des combinaisons d'applications en mode partition d'écran. Cette mise à jour comprend le Suivi des yeux et permet également de modifier les filigranes. De plus, cette version optimise l'effet d'affichage du panneau de notifications et l'effet de mouvement sur l'écran d'accueil, corrige le problème de consommation d'énergie anormale dans certains scénarios, améliore la stabilité du système et intègre un correctif de sécurité.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-fenêtres">
<feature>Les combinaisons d'applications en mode partition d'écran peuvent désormais être enregistrées. En mode partition d'écran, appuyez sur le bouton au milieu du séparateur pour enregistrer la combinaison sous forme d'icône sur l'écran d'accueil. Appuyez sur l'icône pour accéder rapidement à la combinaison.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Les filigranes peuvent désormais être ajoutés et supprimés à volonté. Faites-en l'expérience en accédant à : Prendre une photo > Ouvrir la photo > Retoucher > Filigrane > Options de filigrane : Original, Filigrane de texte, Filigrane du cadre.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Suivi des yeux">
<feature>Le Suivi des yeux est inclus, permettant un accès rapide aux notifications et au contenu détaillé sans opération manuelle lorsque vos yeux sont directement face à l'écran à une distance de 20 à 50 cm. Découvrez-le en accédant à : Paramètres > Assistant > Suivi des yeux.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panneau de notifications">
<feature>La disposition du panneau de notifications est optimisée, rendant l'interface plus simple et visuellement attrayante.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Effet de mouvement">
<feature>Optimise la cohérence de l'effet de mouvement sur l'écran d'accueil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consommation d'énergie">
<feature>Corrige le problème de consommation d'énergie anormale dans certains scénarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>Améliore la stabilité du système de votre appareil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Un correctif de sécurité Android (août 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'effacera pas vos données personnelles, mais une sauvegarde préalable est tout de même recommandée.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, avec cette mise à jour recommandée, vous pouvez enregistrer des combinaisons d'applications en mode partition d'écran. Cette mise à jour comprend le Suivi des yeux et permet également de modifier les filigranes. De plus, cette version optimise l'effet d'affichage du panneau de notifications et l'effet de mouvement sur l'écran d'accueil, corrige le problème de consommation d'énergie anormale dans certains scénarios, améliore la stabilité du système et intègre un correctif de sécurité.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-fenêtres">
<feature>Les combinaisons d'applications en mode partition d'écran peuvent désormais être enregistrées. En mode partition d'écran, appuyez sur le bouton au milieu du séparateur pour enregistrer la combinaison sous forme d'icône sur l'écran d'accueil. Appuyez sur l'icône pour accéder rapidement à la combinaison.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Les filigranes peuvent désormais être ajoutés et supprimés à volonté. Faites-en l'expérience en accédant à : Prendre une photo > Ouvrir la photo > Retoucher > Filigrane > Options de filigrane : Original, Filigrane de texte, Filigrane du cadre.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Suivi des yeux">
<feature>Le Suivi des yeux est inclus, permettant un accès rapide aux notifications et au contenu détaillé sans opération manuelle lorsque vos yeux sont directement face à l'écran à une distance de 20 à 50 cm. Découvrez-le en accédant à : Paramètres > Assistant > Suivi des yeux.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panneau de notifications">
<feature>La disposition du panneau de notifications est optimisée, rendant l'interface plus simple et visuellement attrayante.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Effet de mouvement">
<feature>Optimise la cohérence de l'effet de mouvement sur l'écran d'accueil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consommation d'énergie">
<feature>Corrige le problème de consommation d'énergie anormale dans certains scénarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>Améliore la stabilité du système de votre appareil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sécurité">
<feature>Un correctif de sécurité Android (août 2024) a été intégré pour la sécurité du système. Pour plus d'informations sur les mises à jour de sécurité HONOR, veuillez consulter notre site Web https://www.honor.com/fr/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'effacera pas vos données personnelles, mais une sauvegarde préalable est tout de même recommandée.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Con esta actualización recomendada, pode gardar combinacións de aplicación no modo pantalla dividida. A actualización tamén incorpora Seguimento da mirada e permite editar as marcas de auga. Ademais, esta versión optimiza o efecto de visualización do panel de notificacións e o efecto de movemento na pantalla de inicio, soluciona o problema do consumo anormal de enerxía nalgunhas situacións, mellora a estabilidade do sistema e incorpora un parche de seguranza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Múltiples ventás">
<feature>As combinacións de aplicacións no modo pantalla dividida agora poden gardarse. No modo pantalla dividida, toque o botón no medio do divisor para gardar a combinación como unha icona na Pantalla de inicio. Ao tocar a icona terase acceso rápido á combinación.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galería">
<feature>Agora poden engadirse e eliminarse marcase de auga segundo o desexe. Pode experimentalo seguindo estes paso: Tome unha foto > Abra a foto > Editar > Marca de auga > Opcións de marca de auga: Orixinal, De texto, De marco.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguimento da mirada">
<feature>Inclúese o Seguimento da mirada, o que permite acceso rápido ás notificacións e o contido detallado sen o control manual cando os seus ollos miran directamente á pantalla a unha distancia de entre 20 e 50 cm. Pode experimentalo indo a: Configuración > Asistente > Seguimento da mirada.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panel de notificación">
<feature>Optimizouse o deseño do Panel de notificación, simplificando a interface e volvéndoa máis atractiva.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efecto de movemento">
<feature>Optimizouse a consistencia do efecto de movemento na Pantalla de inicio.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de enerxía">
<feature>Soluciona o problema do consumo de enerxía anómalo nalgúns casos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Mellora a estabilidade do sistema para que o dispositivo funcione dun xeito máis estable.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguranza">
<feature>Incorporouse o parche de seguranza de Android (agosto de 2024) para a seguranza do sistema. Para obter máis información acerca das actualizacións de seguranza de HONOR, visite o noso sitio web https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ao instalar esta actualización non se eliminarán os seus datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar antes unha copia de seguranza.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou visite un centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ ભલામણ કરેલ અપડેટ સાથે, તમે વિભાજીત-સ્ક્રીન મોડમાં એપ્લિકેશન સંયોજનોને સાચવી શકો છો. આ અપડેટ આંખ ટ્રૅકિંગ પણ રજૂ કરે છે, અને વૉટરમાર્ક્સને સંપાદિત કરવાની અનુમતિ આપે છે. વધુમાં, આ પ્રકાશન સૂચના પેનલના ડિસ્પ્લે પ્રભાવ અને હોમ સ્ક્રીન પર ગતિ પ્રભાવને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે, અસામાન્ય સમસ્યાને ઠીક કરે છે. કેટલાક સંજોગોમાં પાવર વપરાશ, સિસ્ટમની સ્થિરતા સુધારે છે અને સુરક્ષા પેચનો સમાવેશ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="મલ્ટિ-વિન્ડો">
<feature>વિભાજીત-સ્ક્રીન મોડમાં એપ્લિકેશન સંયોજનો હવે સાચવી શકાય છે. વિભાજીત-સ્ક્રીન મોડમાં, હોમ સ્ક્રીન પર સંયોજનને ચિહ્ન તરીકે સાચવવા માટે વિભાજકની મધ્યમાં આવેલ બટનને ટૅપ કરો. ચિહ્ન પર ટૅપ કરવાથી સંયોજનનો ઝડપી ઍક્સેસ સક્ષમ બને છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ગૅલેરી">
<feature>વૉટરમાર્ક હવે ઇચ્છિત તરીકે ઉમેરી અને દૂર કરી શકાય છે. અહીં જઈને તેનો અનુભવ કરો: ફોટો લો > ફોટો ખોલો > સંપાદિત કરો > વૉટરમાર્ક > વૉટરમાર્કના વિકલ્પો: મૂળભૂત, ટેક્સ્ટ વૉટરમાર્ક, ફ્રેમ વૉટરમાર્ક.</feature>
</features>
<features module="આંખ ટ્રૅકિંગ">
<feature>જ્યારે તમારી આંખો 20-50 સે.મી.ના અંતરે સીધી સ્ક્રીનની સામે હોય ત્યારે મેન્યુઅલ ઑપરેશન વિના સૂચનાઓ અને વિગતવાર સામગ્રીના ઝડપી ઍક્સેસની અનુમતિ આપતાં આંખ ટ્રૅકિંગનો સમાવેશ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. અહીં જઈને અનુભવ કરો: સેટિંગ્સ > સહાયક > આંખ ટ્રૅકિંગ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સૂચના પેનલ">
<feature>સૂચના પેનલનું લેઆઉટ ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરવામાં આવ્યું છે, જે ઇન્ટરફેસને વધુ સુવ્યવસ્થિત અને જોવામાં આકર્ષક બનાવે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ગતિનો પ્રભાવ">
<feature>હોમ સ્ક્રીન પર ગતિના પ્રભાવની સુસંગતતાને ઓપ્ટિમાઇઝ કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="પાવર વપરાશ">
<feature>કેટલીક પરિસ્થિતિઓમાં અસામાન્ય પાવર વપરાશની સમસ્યાને ઠીક કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સિસ્ટમ">
<feature>તમારાં ઉપકરણને વધુ સ્થિર રીતે ચલાવવા સિસ્ટમની સ્થિરતામાં સુધારો કરે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સુરક્ષા">
<feature>Android સુરક્ષા પેચ (ઑગસ્ટ 2024) સિસ્ટમ સુરક્ષા માટે સામેલ કરવામાં આવ્યો છે. HONOR સુરક્ષા અપડેટ્સ વિશે વધુ માહિતી માટે, કૃપા કરીને અમારી વેબસાઇટ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8 ની મુલાકાત લો</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારો વ્યક્તિગત ડેટા ભૂંસાઈ જશે નહીં, પરંતુ અગાઉથી બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો કૃપા કરીને HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરો અથવા સમર્થન માટે HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્ર પર જાઓ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, इस अनुशंसित अपडेट के साथ, आप ऐप संयोजनों को स्प्लिट-स्क्रीन मोड में सहेज सकते हैं। यह अपडेट नेत्र ट्रैकिंग भी पेश करता है, और वॉटरमार्क को संपादित करने की अनुमति देता है। इसके अतिरिक्त, यह रिलीज़ अधिसूचना पैनल के प्रदर्शन प्रभाव और होम स्क्रीन पर गति प्रभाव को अनुकूलित करता है, कुछ परिदृश्यों में असामान्य पॉवर उपभोग की समस्या को ठीक करता है, सिस्टम स्थिरता में सुधार करता है, और एक सुरक्षा पैच शामिल करता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="मल्टी-विंडो">
<feature>स्क्रीन-विभाजक मोड में ऐप संयोजन अब सहेजे जा सकते हैं। स्क्रीन-विभाजक मोड में, संयोजन को होम स्क्रीन पर आइकन के रूप में सहेजने के लिए विभाजक के बीच में बटन पर टैप करें। आइकन पर टैप करने से संयोजन तक त्वरित पहुँच सक्षम हो जाती है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गैलरी">
<feature>वाटरमार्क अब मनमुताबिक जोड़े और निकाले जा सकते हैं। यहाँ जाकर इसका अनुभव पाएँ: फ़ोटो लें > फ़ोटो खोलें > संपादित करें > वाटरमार्क > वाटरमार्क के विकल्प: मूल, पाठ वाटरमार्क, फ़्रेम वाटरमार्क।</feature>
</features>
<features module="नेत्र ट्रैकिंग">
<feature>नेत्र ट्रैकिंग शामिल है जिसमें आपकी आँखें 20-50 सेमी की दूरी पर सीधे स्क्रीन की ओर होने पर बिना किसी मैन्युअल संचालन के अधिसूचनाओं और विस्तृत सामग्री तक त्वरित पहुँच की अनुमति मिलती है। यहाँ जाकर इसका अनुभव पाएँ: सेटिंग्स > सहायक > नेत्र ट्रैकिंग।</feature>
</features>
<features module="अधिसूचना पैनल">
<feature>अधिसूचना पैनल का लेआउट अनुकूलित किया गया है जिससे इंटरफ़ेस को अधिक व्यवस्थित बनाया जा सके और देखने में आकर्षक लगे।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गति प्रभाव">
<feature>होम स्क्रीन पर गति प्रभाव की स्थिरता को अनुकूलित किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="पॉवर उपभोग">
<feature>कुछ परिदृश्यों में असामान्य पॉवर उपभोग की समस्या को ठीक किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>आपके डिवाइस को अधिक स्थिर रूप से चलाने के लिए सिस्टम स्थिरता में सुधार किया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>सिस्टम की सुरक्षा के लिए Android सुरक्षा पैच (अगस्त, 2024) शामिल किया गया है। HONOR सुरक्षा अद्यतनों के बारे में अधिक जानकारी के लिए, हमारी वेबसाइट: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8 पर जाएँ</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो सहायता के लिए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करें या सहायता के लिए HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाएँ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, zahvaljujući ovom preporučenom ažuriranju možete spremati kombinacije aplikacija u načinu podijeljenog zaslona. Ovim se ažuriranjem omogućuje uređivanje vodenih žigova, a uključena je i značajka Praćenje očiju. Osim toga, ovim se izdanjem optimizira efekt prikaza na ploči za obavijesti i efekt pokreta na početnom zaslonu, rješava se problem neuobičajene potrošnje energije u nekim scenarijima, poboljšava se stabilnost sustava, a implementirana je i sigurnosna zakrpa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Prikaz u više prozora">
<feature>Kombinacije aplikacija u načinu podijeljenog zaslona sada se mogu spremiti. U načinu podijeljenog zaslona dodirnite gumb na sredini razdjelnika kako biste kombinaciju spremili kao ikonu na početnom zaslonu. Dodirnite ikonu za brzi pristup kombinaciji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Vodeni žigovi sada se mogu dodavati i uklanjati po želji. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Snimi fotografiju > Otvori fotografiju > Uredi > Vodeni žig > Opcije vodenog žiga: Izvornik, Tekst vodenog žiga, Okvirni vodeni žig.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Praćenje očiju">
<feature>Uključena je značajka Praćenje očiju, što omogućuje brzi pristup obavijestima i detaljnom sadržaju bez ručnog upravljanja kada su oči izravno okrenute prema zaslonu na udaljenosti od 20–50 cm. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke > Pomoćnik > Praćenje očiju.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ploča za obavijesti">
<feature>Izgled ploče za obavijesti je optimiziran, pa je sučelje jednostavnije i vizualno privlačnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efekt pokreta">
<feature>Optimizira dosljednost efekta pokreta na početnom zaslonu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Potrošnja energije">
<feature>Rješava se problem neuobičajeno velike potrošnje energije u nekim scenarijima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sustav">
<feature>Poboljšava se stabilnost sustava pa uređaj radi stabilnije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sigurnost">
<feature>Implementirana je sigurnosna zakrpa za Android (kolovoz 2024.) za sigurnost sustava. Za više informacija o ažuriranjima značajke HONOR Sigurnost posjetite naše web-mjesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalacijom ovog ažuriranja neće se izbrisati vaši osobni podaci, ali preporučujemo da ipak prije ažuriranja izradite sigurnosnu kopiju.
2. Ako tijekom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za pomoć nazovite telefonsku korisničku službu tvrtke HONOR ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku tvrtke HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez az ajánlott frissítés bevezeti az osztott képernyős alkalmazáskombinációk mentésének lehetőségét. Ez a frissítés ezenfelül bevezeti a Tekintetkövetés funkciót, valamint támogatja a vízjelek szerkesztését is. Ezenfelül ez a verzió optimalizálja az értesítési sáv megjelenési hatását és a főképernyő mozgási effektusát, kijavítja a bizonyos helyzetekben jelentkező rendellenes energiafogyasztás problémáját, fokozza a rendszer stabilitását, és egy biztonsági javítást is tartalmaz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Többablakos">
<feature>Mostantól mentheti az alkalmazáskombinációkat osztott képernyős módban. Osztott képernyős módban koppintson az elválasztó közepén található gombra, így a főképernyőn elhelyezett ikon formájában mentheti az adott kombinációt. Ha az ikonra koppint, gyorsan megnyithatja az adott kombinációt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galéria">
<feature>Mostantól tetszés szerint hozzáadhat és eltávolíthat vízjeleket. Próbálja ki: készítsen egy fényképet > nyissa meg a fényképet > Szerkesztés > Vízjel > a vízjelekhez elérhető opciók: Eredeti, Szöveges vízjel, Keretes vízjel.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tekintetkövetés">
<feature>Elérhetővé vált a Tekintetkövetés funkció, amellyel a kezei használata nélkül is gyorsan megtekintheti az értesítéseket és azok részletes tartalmát, amikor 20–50 centiméteres távolságból közvetlenül a képernyőre néz. Próbálja ki: Beállítások > Asszisztens > Tekintetkövetés.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Értesítési sáv">
<feature>Optimalizáltuk az értesítési sáv elrendezését, letisztultabbá és kellemesebbé tettük a megjelenését.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mozgási hatás">
<feature>Optimalizáltuk a főképernyő mozgási hatását.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energiafogyasztás">
<feature>Kijavítottuk a nem megfelelő energiafogyasztással kapcsolatos problémát, amely bizonyos helyzetekben merült fel.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendszer">
<feature>Javítottuk a rendszer stabilitását, így a készülék zökkenőmentesebben működik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biztonság">
<feature>Tartalmazza a rendszer biztonságát fokozó Android biztonsági javítást (2024. augusztus). A HONOR biztonsági javításaival kapcsolatos további információkért keresse fel weboldalunkat: https://www.honor.com/hu/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. E frissítés telepítése nem törli a személyes adatokat, de javasoljuk, hogy készítsen előtte biztonsági mentést.
2. Ha problémába ütközik a frissítés során, hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, dengan pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini, Anda dapat menyimpan kombinasi aplikasi dalam mode layar terbagi. Pembaruan ini juga memperkenalkan Pelacakan Mata, serta memungkinkan tanda air diedit. Selain itu, rilis ini mengoptimalkan efek tampilan panel notifikasi dan efek gerakan di layar beranda, memperbaiki masalah konsumsi daya abnormal di beberapa skenario, meningkatkan stabilitas sistem, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multijendela">
<feature>Kombinasi aplikasi di mode layar terbagi kini dapat disimpan. Di mode layar terbagi, ketuk tombol di tengah pembagi untuk menyimpan kombinasi sebagai ikon di layar beranda. Ketuk ikon untuk mengaktifkan akses cepat ke kombinasi tersebut.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Tanda air kini dapat ditambahkan dan dihapus sesuai keinginan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Ambil foto > Buka foto > Edit > Tanda air > Opsi tanda air: Asli, Tanda air teks, Tanda air bingkai.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pelacakan Mata">
<feature>Pelacakan Mata disertakan, memungkinkan akses cepat ke notifikasi dan perincian isinya tanpa pengoperasian manual saat mata Anda menatap langsung layar pada jarak 20-50 cm. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Asisten > Pelacakan Mata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panel notifikasi">
<feature>Tata letak panel notifikasi dioptimalkan, menjadikan antarmuka lebih rapi dan menarik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efek gerakan">
<feature>Mengoptimalkan konsistensi efek gerakan di layar beranda.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Konsumsi daya">
<feature>Memperbaiki masalah konsumsi daya abnormal di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Meningkatkan stabilitas sistem sehingga perangkat Anda berjalan dengan lebih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Penambal keamanan Android (Ags 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Memasang pembaruan ini tidak akan menghapus data pribadi Anda, tetapi pencadangan sebelumnya tetap direkomendasikan.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, dengan pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini, Anda dapat menyimpan kombinasi aplikasi dalam mode layar terbagi. Pembaruan ini juga memperkenalkan Pelacakan Mata, serta memungkinkan tanda air diedit. Selain itu, rilis ini mengoptimalkan efek tampilan panel notifikasi dan efek gerakan di layar beranda, memperbaiki masalah konsumsi daya abnormal di beberapa skenario, meningkatkan stabilitas sistem, dan menyertakan penambal keamanan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multijendela">
<feature>Kombinasi aplikasi di mode layar terbagi kini dapat disimpan. Di mode layar terbagi, ketuk tombol di tengah pembagi untuk menyimpan kombinasi sebagai ikon di layar beranda. Ketuk ikon untuk mengaktifkan akses cepat ke kombinasi tersebut.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Tanda air kini dapat ditambahkan dan dihapus sesuai keinginan. Cobalah dengan membuka: Ambil foto > Buka foto > Edit > Tanda air > Opsi tanda air: Asli, Tanda air teks, Tanda air bingkai.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pelacakan Mata">
<feature>Pelacakan Mata disertakan, memungkinkan akses cepat ke notifikasi dan perincian isinya tanpa pengoperasian manual saat mata Anda menatap langsung layar pada jarak 20-50 cm. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan > Asisten > Pelacakan Mata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panel notifikasi">
<feature>Tata letak panel notifikasi dioptimalkan, menjadikan antarmuka lebih rapi dan menarik.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efek gerakan">
<feature>Mengoptimalkan konsistensi efek gerakan di layar beranda.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Konsumsi daya">
<feature>Memperbaiki masalah konsumsi daya abnormal di beberapa skenario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Meningkatkan stabilitas sistem sehingga perangkat Anda berjalan dengan lebih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keamanan">
<feature>Penambal keamanan Android (Ags 2024) telah disertakan untuk keamanan sistem. Untuk informasi selengkapnya tentang pembaruan Keamanan HONOR, kunjungi situs web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Memasang pembaruan ini tidak akan menghapus data pribadi Anda, tetapi pencadangan sebelumnya tetap direkomendasikan.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato consente di salvare le combinazioni di app in modalità schermo diviso. Questo aggiornamento introduce inoltre la funzione Rilevamento occhi e consente la modifica delle filigrane. Inoltre, questa versione ottimizza l'effetto di visualizzazione dell'area notifiche e l'effetto di movimento nella schermata Home, risolve il problema del consumo anomalo di energia in alcuni scenari, migliora la stabilità del sistema e incorpora una patch di sicurezza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-finestra">
<feature>È ora possibile salvare le combinazioni di app in modalità schermo diviso. In modalità schermo diviso, tocca il pulsante al centro del divisore per salvare la combinazione come icona nella schermata Home. Toccando l'icona accedi rapidamente alla combinazione.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleria">
<feature>Ora è possibile aggiungere e rimuovere le filigrane come desiderato. Per provare questa funzione, vai in: Scatta una foto > Apri la foto > Modifica > Filigrana > Opzioni filigrana: Originale, Filigrana di testo, Filigrana cornice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rilevamento occhi">
<feature>È stato incluso Rilevamento occhi, che ti consente di accedere rapidamente alle notifiche e ai contenuti dettagliati senza operazioni manuali quando il tuo sguardo è rivolto verso lo schermo a una distanza di 20-50 cm. Per provare questa funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Assistente > Rilevamento occhi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Area notifiche">
<feature>Il layout del'area notifiche è stato ottimizzato, rendendo l'interfaccia più snella e visivamente accattivante.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Effetto di movimento">
<feature>La coerenza dell'effetto di movimento nella schermata Home è stata ottimizzata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo di energia">
<feature>Viene risolto il problema del consumo di energia anomalo in alcuni scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Viene migliorata la stabilità del sistema, per garantire un funzionamento più stabile del dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (agosto 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non comporta l'eliminazione delle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato consente di salvare le combinazioni di app in modalità schermo diviso. Questo aggiornamento introduce inoltre la funzione Rilevamento occhi e consente la modifica delle filigrane. Inoltre, questa versione ottimizza l'effetto di visualizzazione dell'area notifiche e l'effetto di movimento nella schermata Home, risolve il problema del consumo anomalo di energia in alcuni scenari, migliora la stabilità del sistema e incorpora una patch di sicurezza.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-finestra">
<feature>È ora possibile salvare le combinazioni di app in modalità schermo diviso. In modalità schermo diviso, tocca il pulsante al centro del divisore per salvare la combinazione come icona nella schermata Home. Toccando l'icona accedi rapidamente alla combinazione.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleria">
<feature>Ora è possibile aggiungere e rimuovere le filigrane come desiderato. Per provare questa funzione, vai in: Scatta una foto > Apri la foto > Modifica > Filigrana > Opzioni filigrana: Originale, Filigrana di testo, Filigrana cornice.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rilevamento occhi">
<feature>È stato incluso Rilevamento occhi, che ti consente di accedere rapidamente alle notifiche e ai contenuti dettagliati senza operazioni manuali quando il tuo sguardo è rivolto verso lo schermo a una distanza di 20-50 cm. Per provare questa funzione, vai in: Impostazioni > Assistente > Rilevamento occhi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Area notifiche">
<feature>Il layout del'area notifiche è stato ottimizzato, rendendo l'interfaccia più snella e visivamente accattivante.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Effetto di movimento">
<feature>La coerenza dell'effetto di movimento nella schermata Home è stata ottimizzata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo di energia">
<feature>Viene risolto il problema del consumo di energia anomalo in alcuni scenari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Viene migliorata la stabilità del sistema, per garantire un funzionamento più stabile del dispositivo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sicurezza">
<feature>È stata incorporata la patch di sicurezza di Android (agosto 2024) per garantire la sicurezza del sistema. Per ulteriori informazioni sugli aggiornamenti di sicurezza HONOR, visita il sito Web all'indirizzo https://www.honor.com/it/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non comporta l'eliminazione delle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עם עדכון מומלץ זה ניתן לשמור שילובי יישומים במצב מסך מפוצל. כמו כן, עדכון זה מוסיף לראשונה 'מעקב אחר העיניים', ומאפשר לערוך סימני מים. בנוסף, שחרור זה ממטב את אפקט התצוגה של לוח התראות ואת אפקט התנועה במסך הבית, מתקן את הבעיה של צריכת חשמל חריגה בתרחישים מסוימים, משפר את יציבות המערכת ומשלב תיקון אבטחה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ריבוי חלונות">
<feature>כעת ניתן לשמור שילובי יישומים במצב מסך מפוצל. במצב מסך מפוצל, הקש על הלחצן באמצע המחלק כדי לשמור את השילוב כסמל במסך הבית. הקשה על הסמל מאפשרת גישה מהירה לשילוב.</feature>
</features>
<features module="גלריה">
<feature>כעת ניתן להוסיף ולהסיר סימני מים לפי הצורך. חווה זאת על-ידי מעבר אל 'צלם תמונה' > 'פתח את התמונה' > 'ערוך' > 'סימן מים' > אפשרויות 'סימן מים': מקור, סימן מים של טקסט, סימן מים של מסגרת.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מעקב אחר העיניים">
<feature>‏'מעקב אחר העיניים' כלול, כדי לאפשר גישה מהירה להתראות ולתוכן מפורט ללא הפעלה ידנית כאשר העיניים מביטות ישירות במסך ממרחק של 20‏-50 ס"מ. חווה זאת על-ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' > 'מסייע' > 'מעקב אחר העיניים'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="לוח התראות">
<feature>הפריסה של לוח התראות ממוטבת, מה שהופך את הממשק ליותר יעיל ומושך מבחינה ויזואלית.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אפקט תנועה">
<feature>ממטב את עקביות אפקט התנועה במסך הבית.</feature>
</features>
<features module="צריכת חשמל">
<feature>פותר את הבעיה של צריכת חשמל חריגה בתרחישים מסוימים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מערכת">
<feature>משפר את יציבות המערכת כדי לגרום להתקן שלך לפעול בצורה יציבה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוג' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תמחק את הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לבצע גיבוי מראש.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עם עדכון מומלץ זה ניתן לשמור שילובי יישומים במצב מסך מפוצל. כמו כן, עדכון זה מוסיף לראשונה 'מעקב אחר העיניים', ומאפשר לערוך סימני מים. בנוסף, שחרור זה ממטב את אפקט התצוגה של לוח התראות ואת אפקט התנועה במסך הבית, מתקן את הבעיה של צריכת חשמל חריגה בתרחישים מסוימים, משפר את יציבות המערכת ומשלב תיקון אבטחה.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ריבוי חלונות">
<feature>כעת ניתן לשמור שילובי יישומים במצב מסך מפוצל. במצב מסך מפוצל, הקש על הלחצן באמצע המחלק כדי לשמור את השילוב כסמל במסך הבית. הקשה על הסמל מאפשרת גישה מהירה לשילוב.</feature>
</features>
<features module="גלריה">
<feature>כעת ניתן להוסיף ולהסיר סימני מים לפי הצורך. חווה זאת על-ידי מעבר אל 'צלם תמונה' > 'פתח את התמונה' > 'ערוך' > 'סימן מים' > אפשרויות 'סימן מים': מקור, סימן מים של טקסט, סימן מים של מסגרת.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מעקב אחר העיניים">
<feature>‏'מעקב אחר העיניים' כלול, כדי לאפשר גישה מהירה להתראות ולתוכן מפורט ללא הפעלה ידנית כאשר העיניים מביטות ישירות במסך ממרחק של 20‏-50 ס"מ. חווה זאת על-ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' > 'מסייע' > 'מעקב אחר העיניים'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="לוח התראות">
<feature>הפריסה של לוח התראות ממוטבת, מה שהופך את הממשק ליותר יעיל ומושך מבחינה ויזואלית.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אפקט תנועה">
<feature>ממטב את עקביות אפקט התנועה במסך הבית.</feature>
</features>
<features module="צריכת חשמל">
<feature>פותר את הבעיה של צריכת חשמל חריגה בתרחישים מסוימים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מערכת">
<feature>משפר את יציבות המערכת כדי לגרום להתקן שלך לפעול בצורה יציבה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="אבטחה">
<feature>‏'תיקון אבטחה של Android' (מאוג' 2024) שולב למען אבטחת המערכת. למידע נוסף על עדכוני 'אבטחה של HONOR', אפשר לבקר באתר האינטרנט שלנו בכתובת: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תמחק את הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לבצע גיבוי מראש.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様。今回の推奨更新によって、画面分割モードでアプリの組み合わせを保存できるようになります。また、今回の更新では、アイトラッキングも導入され、ウォーターマークを編集できるようになります。さらに、今回のリリースでは、ホーム画面での通知パネルの表示とモーション効果が最適化され、一部の状況での異常な消費電力の問題が解決され、システムの安定性が改善され、セキュリティパッチが組み込まれます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="マルチウィンドウ">
<feature>画面分割モードでアプリの組み合わせを保存できるようになりました。画面分割モードで分割線の中央にあるボタンをタップすると、組み合わせをホーム画面のアイコンとして保存できます。アイコンをタップすると、その組み合わせにすばやくアクセスできます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="ギャラリー">
<feature>ウォーターマークを自由に追加および削除できるようになりました。この機能を体験するには、写真を撮影 > 写真を開く > [編集] > [ウォーターマーク] > ウォーターマークの選択肢（オリジナル、テキストウォーターマーク、フレームウォーターマーク）にアクセスします。</feature>
</features>
<features module="アイトラッキング">
<feature>アイトラッキングが含まれたことで、ユーザーの目が20～50 cmの距離で画面をまっすぐ見ている場合に、手動の操作をせずに通知と詳細内容にすぐにアクセスできるようになりました。この機能を体験するには、[設定] > [アシスタント] > [アイトラッキング]に移動してください。</feature>
</features>
<features module="通知パネル">
<feature>通知パネルのレイアウトが最適化され、インターフェースがさらに見やすく、魅力的になりました。</feature>
</features>
<features module="モーション効果">
<feature>ホーム画面のモーション効果の一貫性が改善されました。</feature>
</features>
<features module="消費電力">
<feature>一部の状況における異常な消費電力の問題が修正されました。</feature>
</features>
<features module="システム">
<feature>システムの安定性が改善され、デバイスがより安定して動作するようになりました。</feature>
</features>
<features module="セキュリティ">
<feature>システムセキュリティのためにAndroidセキュリティパッチ（2024年8月）が組み込まれました。HONORのセキュリティ更新の詳細については、当社のWebサイトをご覧ください： https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報が消去されることはありませんが、事前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターでサポートを受けてください。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ამ რეკომენდებული განახლებით თქვენ შეინახავთ აპების კომბინაციებს გაყოფილი ეკრანის რეჟიმში. ამ განახლებაში წარმოდგენილია თვალებზე მიდევნება და დაშვებულია წყლის ნიშნების რედაქტირება. ამასთან, ამ გამოშვებაში ოპტიმიზებულია შეტყობინებათა პანელის ჩვენების ეფექტები და საწყის ეკრანზე მოძრაობის ეფექტი, გასწორებულია ზოგიერთ შემთხვევებში ენერგიის არანორმალური მოხმარების პრობლემები, გაუმჯობესებულია სისტემის სტაბილურობა და უზრუნველყოფილია უსაფრთხოების შესწორება.</feature>
</features>
<features module="მულტიფანჯარა">
<feature>ახლა შესაძლებელია აპების კომბინაციების შენახვა გაყოფილი ეკრანის რეჟიმში. გაყოფილი ეკრანის რეჟიმში შეეხეთ ღილაკს გამყოფის შუაში, რომ კომბინაცია საწყის ეკრანზე პიქტოგრამად შეინახოთ. პიქტოგრამაზე შეხება გაძლევთ კომბინაციაზე სწრაფ წვდომას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="გალერეა">
<feature>წყლის ნიშნები ახლა სურვილისამებრ შეგიძლიათ დაამატოთ და ამოშალოთ. ამის გამოცდა შეგიძლიათ შემდეგი გზით: ფოტოს გადაღება > ფოტოს გახსნა > რედაქტირ. > წყლის ნიშანი > წყლის ნიშნის ოფციები: ორიგინალი, ტექსტური წყლის ნიშანი, ჩარჩო-წყლის ნიშანი.</feature>
</features>
<features module="თვალებზე მიდევნება">
<feature>მოიცავს თვალებზე მიდევნების ფუნქციას, რაც შეტყობინებებსა და დეტალურ შიგთავსზე სწრაფ წვდომას გაძლევთ მექანიკური ოპერაციის გარეშე, როცა თვალები პირდაპირ მიმართული გაქვთ ეკრანზე 20-50 სმ-ის მანძილიდან. ამის გამოცდა შეგიძლიათ მენიუდან: პარამეტრები > ასისტენტი > თვალებზე მიდევნება.</feature>
</features>
<features module="შეტყობინებათა პანელი">
<feature>შეტყობინებათა პანელის განლაგება ოპტიმიზებულია, რაც ინტერფეისს უფრო გამარტივებულს და ვიზუალურად მიმზიდველს ხდის.</feature>
</features>
<features module="მოძრაობის ეფექტი">
<feature>ახდენს საწყის ეკრანზე მოძრაობის ეფექტის თანმიმდევრულობის ოპტიმიზებას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ენერგიის მოხმარება">
<feature>აღმოფხვრის ზოგიერთ სცენარში ენერგიის არანორმალურ მოხმარებასთან დაკავშირებულ პრობლემას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="სისტემა">
<feature>აუმჯობესებს სისტემის სტაბილურობას, რის შედეგადაც მოწყობილობა უფრო სტაბილურად მუშაობს.</feature>
</features>
<features module="უსაფრთხოება">
<feature>სისტემის უსაფრთხოებისთვის ჩაირთო Android უსაფრთხოების შესწორება (2024 წლის აგვისტო). HONOR-ის უსაფრთხოების განახლებების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაციისთვის ეწვიეთ ჩვენს ვებსაიტს: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ გამოიწვევს თქვენი პერსონალური მონაცემების წაშლას, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. განახლების დროს პრობლემების წარმოქმნის შემთხვევაში, მხარდაჭერისთვის დარეკეთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან მიმართეთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл ұсынылған жаңартумен бөлінген экран режиміндегі қолданба тіркесімдерін сақтауға болады. Сондай-ақ бұл жаңарту «Көзді бақылау» мүмкіндігін ұсынады және су таңбаларын өңдеуге мүмкіндік береді. Сондай-ақ бұл шығарылым хабарландырулар тақтасының дисплей әсерін және негізгі экрандағы қозғалыс әсерін оңтайландырады, кейбір сценарийлердегі қалыпсыз қуат тұтыну мәселесін шешеді, жүйе тұрақтылығын жақсартады және қауіпсіздік патчын біріктіреді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бірнеше терезе">
<feature>Енді бөлінген экран режиміндегі қолданба тіркесімдерін сақтауға болады. Бөлінген экран режимінде тіркесімді негізгі экранда белгіше ретінде сақтау үшін бөлгіштің ортасындағы түймені түртіңіз. Белгішені түртсеңіз, тіркесімге жылдам қатынасуға мүмкіндік беріледі.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерея">
<feature>Енді су таңбаларын қалауыңызша қосуға және жоюға болады. Мынаған өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз: «Фотосурет түсіру» > «Фотосуретті ашу» > «Өңдеу» > «Су таңбасы» > «Су таңбасы опциялары: Түпнұсқа, Мәтіннің су таңбасы, Жақтаудың су таңбасы».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Көзді бақылау">
<feature>Көздеріңіз экранға тікелей 20-50 см қашықтықта қараған кезде қолмен реттелетін жұмыссыз хабарландырулар мен толық мазмұнға жылдам қатынасуға мүмкіндік беретін «Көзді бақылау» мүмкіндігі қосылған. Мынаған өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз: «Параметрлер» > «Көмекші» > «Көзді бақылау».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хабарландырулар тақтасы">
<feature>Хабарландырулар тақтасының орналасуы оңтайландырылған, бұл интерфейсті ыңғайлырақ және визуалды тартымдырақ етеді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қозғалыс әсері">
<feature>Негізгі экрандағы қозғалыс әсерінің тұрақтылығын оңтайландырады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қуат тұтыну">
<feature>Кейбір сценарийлерде қалыпсыз қуат тұтыну мәселесін шешеді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Жүйе">
<feature>Құрылғының тұрақты жұмыс істеуі үшін жүйенің тұрақтылығын жақсартады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қауіпсіздік">
<feature>Android қауіпсіздік патчы (тамыз, 2024) жүйе қауіпсіздігі үшін біріктірілген. HONOR қауіпсіздік жаңартулары туралы қосымша ақпарат алу үшін біздің веб-сайтқа кіріңіз: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнатсаңыз, жеке деректер өшпейді, бірақ бұрынғы сақтық көшірме әлі де ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту барысында мәселелер орын алса, қолдау алу үшін HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне хабарласыңыз немесе HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына барыңыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើប្រាស់ជាទីគោរព ជាមួយនឹងបច្ចុប្បន្នភាពដែលបានណែនាំនេះ អ្នកអាចរក្សាទុកបន្សំកម្មវិធីនៅក្នុងរបៀបបំបែកអេក្រង់។ បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះក៏ណែនាំមុខងារតាមដានភ្នែកផងដែរ និងអនុញ្ញាតឱ្យមានការកែសម្រួលស្នាមទឹកផងដែរ។ លើសពីនេះ ការចេញផ្សាយនេះបង្កើនប្រសិទ្ធភាពការបង្ហាញនៃផ្ទាំងជូនដំណឹង និងឥទ្ធិពលចលនានៅលើអេក្រង់ដើម ដោះស្រាយបញ្ហានៃការប្រើប្រាស់ថាមពលមិនប្រក្រតីនៅក្នុងសេណារីយ៉ូមួយចំនួន ធ្វើអោយប្រសើរឡើងនូវស្ថេរភាពប្រព័ន្ធ និងរួមបញ្ចូលនូវបំណះសុវត្ថិភាព។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ពហុវិនដូ">
<feature>ឥឡូវ បន្សំកម្មវិធីក្នុងម៉ូដអេក្រង់បំបែកអាចត្រូវបានរក្សាទុក។ ក្នុងម៉ូដអេក្រង់បំបែក ប៉ះប៊ូតុងនៅផ្នែកកណ្ដាលនៃបន្ទាត់ខណ្ឌចែក ដើម្បីរក្សាទុកបន្សំជារូបតំណាងនៅលើអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម។ ប៉ះរូបតំណាង បើកការចូលប្រើរហ័សទៅកាន់បន្សំ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="វិចិត្រសាល">
<feature>ឥឡូវ អាចបញ្ចូល និងយករូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាតចេញតាមការចង់បាន។ ទទួលបទពិសោធប្រើប្រាស់វាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ថតរូប > បើករូបថត > កែ > រូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាត > ជម្រើសរូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាត៖ ដើម, រូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាតជាអក្សរ, រូបភាពព្រាលលើផ្ទៃបាតជាស៊ុម។</feature>
</features>
<features module="មុខងារតាមដានភ្នែក">
<feature>មុខងារតាមដានភ្នែកត្រូវបានរួមបញ្ចូល ដែលអនុញ្ញាតឱ្យធ្វើការចូលប្រើរហ័សទៅកាន់ការជូនដំណឹង និងខ្លឹមសារលម្អិតដោយគ្មានប្រតិបត្តិការដោយផ្ទាល់ដៃ នៅពេលភ្នែករបស់អ្នកបែរចំអេក្រង់នៅចម្ងាយ 20-50 cm។ ទទួលបទពិសោធប្រើប្រាស់វាដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ > ជំនួយការ > មុខងារតាមដានភ្នែក។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ផ្ទាំងជូនដំណឹង">
<feature>ប្លង់នៃផ្ទាំងជូនដំណឹងត្រូវបានធ្វើឱ្យប្រសើរឡើង ដែលធ្វើឱ្យផ្ទៃកាន់តែស្រួលប្រើ និងទាក់ទាញភ្នែក។</feature>
</features>
<features module="បែបផែនចលនា">
<feature>ធ្វើឱ្យភាពស៊ីសង្វាក់នៃបែបផែនចលនាប្រសើរឡើងនៅលើអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ការប្រើប្រាស់​ថាមពល">
<feature>ដោះស្រាយបញ្ហានៃការប្រើប្រាស់​ថាមពលខុសប្រក្រតីនៅក្នុងសេណារីយោមួយចំនួន។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ប្រព័ន្ធ">
<feature>កែលម្អស្ថិរភាពប្រព័ន្ធ ដើម្បីធ្វើឱ្យឧបករណ៍របស់អ្នកដំណើរការបានកាន់តែមានស្ថិរភាព។</feature>
</features>
<features module="សន្តិសុខ">
<feature>បំណះសន្តិសុខ Android (សីហា 2024) ត្រូវបាន​រួមបញ្ចូល​សម្រាប់​សន្តិសុខ​ប្រព័ន្ធ។ សម្រាប់​ព័ត៌មាន​បន្ថែម​អំពី​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​សន្តិសុខ HONOR សូមចូលទៅ​គេហទំព័រ​របស់យើង៖ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​លុបទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ចេញទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបបញ្ហាណាមួយក្នុងអំឡុងពេល​ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព សូមហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សផ្នែកសេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​សេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR ដើម្បី​ទទួលបាន​ជំនួយ។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಿದ ನವೀಕರಣದೊಂದಿಗೆ, ನೀವು ಸ್ಪ್ಲಿಟ್-ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮೋಡ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಸಂಯೋಜನೆಗಳನ್ನು ಉಳಿಸಬಹುದು. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಕಣ್ಣನ್ನು ಟ್ರ್ಯಾಕ್ ಮಾಡುವಿಕೆಯನ್ನು ಸಹ ಪರಿಚಯಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಎಡಿಟ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಅನುಮತಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಹೆಚ್ಚುವರಿಯಾಗಿ, ಈ ಬಿಡುಗಡೆಯು ಅಧಿಸೂಚನೆ ಪ್ಯಾನಲ್‌ನ ಡಿಸ್‌ಪ್ಲೇ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಮತ್ತು ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಮೋಷನ್ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್ ಅನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ, ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಅಸಹಜ ಪವರ್ ಬಳಕೆಯ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಯನ್ನು ಪರಿಹರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಸ್ಥಿರತೆಯನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ ಮತ್ತು ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಮಲ್ಟಿ-ವಿಂಡೋ">
<feature>ಸ್ಪ್ಲಿಟ್-ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮೋಡ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಸಂಯೋಜನೆಗಳನ್ನು ಈಗ ಉಳಿಸಬಹುದು. ಸ್ಪ್ಲಿಟ್-ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮೋಡ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ, ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಸಂಯೋಜನೆಯನ್ನು ಐಕಾನ್ ಆಗಿ ಉಳಿಸಲು ವಿಭಾಜಕದ ಮಧ್ಯದಲ್ಲಿರುವ ಬಟನ್ ಮೇಲೆ ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ. ಐಕಾನ್ ಅನ್ನು ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮಾಡುವುದರಿಂದ ಸಂಯೋಜನೆಗೆ ತ್ವರಿತ ಆ್ಯಕ್ಸೆಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ನೀಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಗ್ಯಾಲರಿ">
<feature>ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ಈಗ ನೀವು ಬಯಸಿದಂತೆ ಸೇರಿಸಬಹುದು ಮತ್ತು ತೆಗೆದುಹಾಕಬಹುದು. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಅದರ ಅನುಭವ ಪಡೆಯಿರಿ: ಫೋಟೋ ತೆಗೆದುಕೊಳ್ಳಿ > ಫೋಟೋ ತೆರೆಯಿರಿ > ಎಡಿಟ್ ಮಾಡಿ > ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್ > ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್ ಆಯ್ಕೆಗಳು: ಮೂಲ, ಪಠ್ಯ ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್, ಫ್ರೇಮ್ ವಾಟರ್‌ಮಾರ್ಕ್.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಕಣ್ಣನ್ನು ಟ್ರ್ಯಾಕ್ ಮಾಡುವಿಕೆ">
<feature>ಕಣ್ಣನ್ನು ಟ್ರ್ಯಾಕ್ ಮಾಡುವಿಕೆ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯವನ್ನು ಸೇರಿಸಲಾಗಿದ್ದು, ಇದು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಕಣ್ಣುಗಳು 20-50 ಸೆಂ.ಮೀ. ದೂರದಲ್ಲಿ ನೇರವಾಗಿ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಕಡೆಗೆ ನೋಡುತ್ತಿರುವಾಗ ಹಸ್ತಚಾಲಿತ ಕಾರ್ಯಾಚರಣೆಯಿಲ್ಲದೆ ಅಧಿಸೂಚನೆಗಳು ಮತ್ತು ವಿವರವಾದ ವಿಷಯಕ್ಕೆ ತ್ವರಿತ ಆ್ಯಕ್ಸೆಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ಅನುಮತಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಇಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದರ ಅನುಭವ ಪಡೆಯಿರಿ: ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು > ಸಹಾಯಕ > ಕಣ್ಣನ್ನು ಟ್ರ್ಯಾಕ್ ಮಾಡುವಿಕೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಅಧಿಸೂಚನೆ ಪ್ಯಾನಲ್">
<feature>ಅಧಿಸೂಚನೆ ಪ್ಯಾನಲ್‌ನ ವಿನ್ಯಾಸವನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ, ಇಂಟರ್ಫೇಸ್ ಅನ್ನು ಹೆಚ್ಚು ಸುವ್ಯವಸ್ಥಿತವಾಗಿ ಮತ್ತು ನೋಡಲು ಆಕರ್ಷಕವಾಗಿರುವಂತೆ ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಚಲನೆಯ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್">
<feature>ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಚಲನೆಯ ಎಫೆಕ್ಟ್‌ನ ಸ್ಥಿರತೆಯನ್ನು ಆಪ್ಟಿಮೈಸ್ ಮಾಡುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಪವರ್ ಬಳಕೆ">
<feature>ಕೆಲವು ಸನ್ನಿವೇಶಗಳಲ್ಲಿ ಅಸಹಜ ಪವರ್ ಬಳಕೆಯ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಯನ್ನು ಪರಿಹರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ">
<feature>ನಿಮ್ಮ ಸಾಧನವು ಹೆಚ್ಚು ಸ್ಥಿರವಾಗಿ ಕಾರ್ಯನಿರ್ವಹಿಸಲು ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಸ್ಥಿರತೆಯನ್ನು ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಭದ್ರತೆ">
<feature>ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ ಭದ್ರತೆಗಾಗಿ Android ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ಯಾಚ್ (ಆಗಸ್ಟ್ 2024) ಅನ್ನು ಅಳವಡಿಸಲಾಗಿದೆ. HONOR ಭದ್ರತಾ ನವೀಕರಣಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಗಾಗಿ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು ನಮ್ಮ ವೆಬ್‌ಸೈಟ್‌ಗೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡಿ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸಿದರೆ ಇದು ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಅಳಿಸುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ಮುಂಚಿತವಾಗಿ ಬ್ಯಾಕ್‍ಅಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ ಇಡಬೇಕೆಂದು ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ಅಥವಾ ಬೆಂಬಲಕ್ಕಾಗಿ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಹೋಗಿ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이 권장 업데이트를 통해 화면 분할 모드에서 앱 조합을 저장할 수 있습니다. 이번 업데이트에서는 시선 추적 기능도 도입되었으며 워터마크 편집이 가능해졌습니다. 또한 이번 릴리스에서는 알림 패널의 디스플레이 효과와 홈 화면의 모션 효과를 최적화하고 일부 시나리오에서 비정상적인 소비 전력 문제를 수정하며 시스템 안정성을 개선하고 보안 패치를 통합했습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="멀티 윈도우">
<feature>이제 화면 분할 모드에서 앱 조합을 저장할 수 있습니다. 화면 분할 모드에서 분할기 가운데에 있는 버튼을 탭하여 조합을 홈 화면에 아이콘으로 저장합니다. 아이콘을 탭하면 조합에 빠르게 액세스할 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="갤러리">
<feature>이제 워터마크를 원하는 대로 추가하고 제거할 수 있습니다. 사진 촬영 > 사진 열기 > 편집 > 워터마크 > 워터마크 옵션: 원본, 텍스트 워터마크, 프레임 워터마크로 이동하여 직접 체험해 보십시오.</feature>
</features>
<features module="시선 추적">
<feature>시선 추적 기능이 포함되어 있어 20~50cm 거리에서 화면을 직접 바라보고 있을 때 수동 조작 없이도 알림 및 상세정보에 빠르게 액세스할 수 있습니다. 설정 > 어시스턴트 > 시선 추적으로 이동하여 직접 체헙해 보십시오.</feature>
</features>
<features module="알림 패널">
<feature>알림 패널의 레이아웃이 최적화되어 인터페이스가 더욱 간소화되고 시각적으로 매력적입니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="모션 효과">
<feature>홈 화면에서 모션 효과의 일관성을 최적화합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="소비 전력">
<feature>일부 시나리오에서 비정상적인 소비 전력 문제를 해결합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="시스템">
<feature>시스템 안정성을 개선하여 장치를 더욱 안정적으로 실행할 수 있도록 합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="보안">
<feature>시스템 보안을 위해 Android 보안 패치(2024년 8월)가 통합되었습니다. HONOR 보안 업데이트에 대해 자세히 알아보려면 다음에 있는 당사 웹사이트를 방문하세요. https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터는 삭제되지 않지만, 사전에 백업하시기를 권장합니다.
2. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터로 가서 지원을 받으십시오.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ດ້ວຍ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ທີ່​ແນະ​ນຳ​ນີ້, ທ່ານ​ສາ​ມາດ​ບັນ​ທຶກ​ການ​ລວມ​ແອັບ​ໃນ​ໂໝດ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ແຍກ​ໄດ້. ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້ຍັງ​ແນະ​ນຳການຕິດຕາມການເຄື່ອນໄຫວຂອງຕາ ແລະ ອະ​ນຸ​ຍາດ​ໃຫ້​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ລາຍ​ນ້ຳ. ນອກ​ຈາກ​ນີ້, ການ​ເປີດ​ຕົວ​ນີ້​​ຍັງ​ປັບ​ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ການ​ສ​ະ​ແດງ​ຜົນ​ຂອງ​ແຜງ​ການ​ແຈ້ງ​ເຕືອນ ແລະ ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ການ​ເຄື່ອນ​ໄຫວ​ໃນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ, ແກ້​ໄຂ​ບັນ​ຫາ​ຂອງ​ການ​ໃຊ້​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານ​ຜິດ​ປົກ​ກະ​ຕິ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ການ, ປັບ​ປຸງ​ຄວາມ​ສະ​ຖຽນ​ຂອງ​ລະ​ບົບ ແລະ ລວມ​ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ເຂົ້າ​ກັນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຫຼາຍ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ">
<feature>ຕອນ​ນີ້ສາ​ມາດ​ບັນ​ທຶກການ​ລວມ​ແອັບ​ໃນ​ໂໝດ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ແຍກ​ໄ​ດ້​ແລ້ວ. ໃນ​ໂໝດ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ແຍກ, ແຕະ​ປຸ່ມ​ຢູ່​ກາງ​ຕົວ​ແບ່ງ ເພື່ອ​ບັນ​ທຶກ​ການ​ລວມ​ເປັນ​ໄອ​ຄອນ​ໃນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ. ແຕະ​ໄອ​ຄອນ​​ເປີດ​ໃຊ້​ງານການ​ເຂົ້າ​ເຖິງ​ດ່ວນຫາ​ການ​ລວມ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ແກ​ເລີ​ຣີ">
<feature>ຕອນ​ນີ້​ສາ​ມາດ​ເພີ່ມ​ລາຍ​ນ້ຳ ແລະ ເອົາ​ອອກໄດ້​ຕາມ​ຕ້ອງ​ການ. ສຳ​ຜັດ​ປະ​ສົບ​ການມັນ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ຖ່າຍ​ຮູບ > ເປີດ​ຮູບ​ຖ່າຍ > ແກ້​ໄຂ > ລາຍ​​ນ້ຳ > ຕົວ​ເລືອກ​ລາຍ​ນ້ຳ: ຕົ້ນ​ສະ​ບັບ, ລາຍ​ນ້ຳ​ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ, ​ລາຍ​ນ້ຳ​ກອບ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ການຕິດຕາມການເຄື່ອນໄຫວຂອງຕາ">
<feature>ການຕິດຕາມການເຄື່ອນໄຫວຂອງຕາ, ເຊິ່ງ​ອະ​ນຸ​ຍາດ​ການ​ເຂົ້າ​ເຖິງ​ດ່ວນ​ຫາ​ການ​ແຈ້ງ​ເຕືອນ ແລະ ເນື້ອ​ຫາ​ລາຍ​ລະ​ອຽດ​ໂດຍ​ບໍ່​ຕ້ອງ​ດຳ​ເນີນ​ການ​ດ້ວຍ​ຕົນ​ເອງ ເມື່ອ​ດວງຕາ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ຈ້ອງ​ແນມ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ໂດຍ​ກົງ​ໃນ​ໄລ​ຍະ 20-50 cm. ສຳ​ຜັດ​ປະ​ສົບ​ການມັນ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່​າ > ຜູ້​ຊ່ວຍ > ການຕິດຕາມການເຄື່ອນໄຫວຂອງຕາ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ແຜງການແຈ້ງເຕືອນ">
<feature>ແຜນ​ຜັງ​ຂອງແຜງການແຈ້ງເຕືອນ​ຖືກ​ປັບ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ, ເຊິ່ງ​ເຮັດ​ໃຫ້​ໜ້າ​ປະ​ສານດຳ​ເນີນ​ການ​ໄດ້​ສະ​ດວກ​ຍິ່ງ​ຂຶ້ນ ແລະ ດຶງ​ດູດ​ສາຍ​ຕາຍິ່ງ​ຂຶ້ນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ການ​ເຄື່ອນ​ໄຫວ">
<feature>ປັບຄວາມ​ສອດ​ຄ່ອງ​ຂອງ​ເອັບ​ເຝັກ​ການ​ເຄື່ອນ​ໄຫວໃນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ​.</feature>
</features>
<features module="​ການ​ໃຊ້​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານ">
<feature>ແກ້​ໄຂ​ບັນ​ຫາ​​ການ​ໃຊ້​ພະ​ລັງ​ງານ​​ຜິດ​ປົກ​ກະ​ຕິ​ໃນ​ບາງ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ການ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ລະບົບ">
<feature>ປັບປຸງຄວາມສະຖຽນຂອງລະບົບ ເພື່ອເຮັດໃຫ້ອຸປະກອນຂອງທ່ານເຮັດວຽກໄດ້ສະຖຽນຍິ່ງຂຶ້ນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ">
<feature>ໂປ​ຣ​ແກ​ຣມ​ແກ້​ໄຂ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ຂອງ Android (ສິງ​ຫາ 2024) ​ໄດ້ຖືກລວມ​​ເຂົ້າ​ເປັນ​ການ​ຮັກ​ສາ​ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ​ລະ​ບົບ. ສຳລັບຂໍ້ມູນເພີ່ມເຕີມກ່ຽວກັບການອັບເດດດ້ານຄວາມປອດໄພຂອງ HONOR, ກະລຸນາເຂົ້າໄປ​ທີ່ເວັບໄຊຂອງພວກເຮົາ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການຕິດຕັ້ງການອັບເດດນີ້ຈະບໍ່ລຶບຂໍ້ມູນສ່ວນຕົວຂອງທ່ານ, ແຕ່ຍັງ​ຄົງຂໍແນະນຳໃຫ້ມີ​ການສຳຮອງຂໍ້ມູນໄວ້ລ່ວງໜ້າ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ກະລຸນາໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR ເພື່ອຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šiuo rekomenduojamu naujiniu galite įrašyti programėlių derinius padalintojo ekrano režimu. Juo taip pat pristatomas akių sekimas ir leidžiama redaguoti vandens ženklus. Be to, šioje laidoje optimizuojamas pranešimų skydelio rodymo efektas ir judesio efektas pradžios ekrane, ištaisoma nenormalių energijos sąnaudų (kai kuriais atvejais) problema, pagerinamas sistemos stabilumas ir įtraukiama saugumo pataisa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Daugialangis">
<feature>Nuo šiol galima įrašyti padalintojo ekrano režimu sukurtus programėlių derinius. Įjungę padalintojo ekrano režimą, palieskite skyriklio viduryje esantį mygtuką ir galėsite įrašyti derinį kaip piktogramą pradžios ekrane. Palietę piktogramą, galėsite greitai pasiekti derinį.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Nuo šiol galima pagal pageidavimą įtraukti ir šalinti vandens ženklus. Išbandykite tai: padarykite nuotrauką > atverkite nuotrauką > „Redaguoti > Vandens ženklas > Vandens ženklo parinktys“ („Originalas“, „Tekstinis vandens ženklas“, „Vandens ženklas rėmelyje“).</feature>
</features>
<features module="Akių sekimas">
<feature>Įtraukta akių sekimo funkcija, leidžianti greitai pasiekti pranešimus ir išsamų turinį be rankinio valdymo, kai jūsų akys nukreiptos tiesiai į ekraną 20–50 cm atstumu. Išbandykite tai nuėję į „Nustatymai > Pagelbiklis > Akių sekimas“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pranešimų skydelis">
<feature>Optimizuotas pranešimų skydelio išdėstymas: sąsaja tapo paprastesnė ir vizualiai patrauklesnė.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Judesio efektas">
<feature>Pradžios ekrane optimizuojamas judesio efekto nuoseklumas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energijos sąnaudos">
<feature>Kai kuriais atvejais išsprendžiama neįprastų energijos sąnaudų problema.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Pagerintas sistemos stabilumas, todėl įrenginys veikia stabiliau.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Saugumas">
<feature>Siekiant užtikrinti sistemos saugumą, įtraukta „Android“ saugumo pataisa (2024 m. rugpjūčio mėn.). Jei reikia daugiau informacijos apie HONOR saugumo naujinius, apsilankykite mūsų svetainėje https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį naujinį, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys ištrinti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama iš anksto padaryti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Jei naujinimo metu kyla problemų, skambinkite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba kreipkitės pagalbos į HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centrą.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Izmantojot šo ieteicamo atjauninājumu, varat saglabāt lietotņu kombinācijas dalītā ekrāna režīmā. Ar šo atjauninājumu ir ieviesta funkcija Acu izsekošana, kā arī ar to var rediģēt ūdenszīmes. Turklāt šis laidiens optimizē paziņojumu paneļa displeja efektu un kustības efektu sākuma ekrānā, novērš neparastu enerģijas patēriņu dažos scenārijos, uzlabo sistēmas stabilitāti un ietver drošības ielāpu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Vairāki logi">
<feature>Lietotņu kombinācijas dalītā ekrāna režīmā var tagad saglabāt. Dalītā ekrāna režīmā pieskarieties pogai sadalītāja vidū, lai saglabātu kombināciju kā ikonu sākuma ekrānā. Pieskarieties ikonai, lai ātri piekļūtu kombinācijai.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Tagad ūdenszīmes var pievienot un noņemt pēc vēlēšanās. Izbaudiet to, atverot: Uzņemt fotoattēlu > Atvērt fotoattēlu > Rediģēt > Ūdenszīme > Ūdenszīmes opcijas: Sākotnējais, Teksta ūdenszīme, Rāmja ūdenszīme.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Acu izsekošana">
<feature>Ir iekļauta acu izsekošanas funkcija, kas ļauj ātri piekļūt paziņojumiem un detalizētam saturam bez manuālas darbības, kad jūsu acis ir tieši vērstas pret ekrānu 20–50 cm attālumā. Izbaudiet to, atverot: Iestatījumi > Palīgs > Acu izsekošana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Paziņojumu panelis">
<feature>Paziņojumu paneļa izkārtojums ir optimizēts, padarot interfeisu racionālāku un vizuāli pievilcīgāku.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kustības efekts">
<feature>Optimizē kustības efekta konsekvenci sākuma ekrānā.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Enerģijas patēriņš">
<feature>Novērš neparastu enerģijas patēriņa problēmu dažos scenārijos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistēma">
<feature>Uzlabo sistēmas stabilitāti, padarot jūsu ierīci stabilāku.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Drošība">
<feature>Sistēmas drošībai iekļauts Android drošības ielāps (2024. gada augusts). Lai iegūtu papildinformāciju par HONOR drošības atjauninājumiem, lūdzu, apmeklējiet mūsu vietni https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Instalējot šo atjauninājumu, jūsu personas dati netiks dzēsti, taču joprojām ir ieteicams iepriekš izveidot dublējumu.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, lūdzu, zvaniet HONOR uzziņu dienestam vai dodieties uz HONOR klientu servisa centru, lai saņemtu atbalstu.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, एहि अनुशंसित अपडेट केर संग अहाँ विभाजित-स्क्रीन मोड मे एप संयोजन संरक्षित कए सकैत छी। एहि अपडेट मे आँखि केँ ट्रैक करब सेहो देल गेल अछि आओर वाटरमार्क केँ संपादित करबाक अनुमति दैत अछि। एकर अतिरिक्त, ई रिलीज अधिसूचना पैनल केर डिस्प्ले प्रभाव आ होम स्क्रीन पर मोशन प्रभाव केँ अनुकूलित करैत अछि, किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे असामान्य पावर खपत केर समस्याक समाधान करैत अछि, सिस्टम स्थिरता मे सुधार करैत अछि आओर एकटा सुरक्षा पैच समाविष्ट करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="मल्टी-विंडो">
<feature>विभाजित-स्क्रीन मोड मे आब एप संयोजन संरक्षित कयल जा सकैत अछि। विभाजित-स्क्रीन मोड मे, संयोजन केँ होम स्क्रीन पर आइकनक रूप मे संरक्षित करबाक लेल विभाजक केर बीच मे बटन टैप करू। आइकन टैप कयला सँ संयोजन धरि त्वरित एक्सेस सक्षम भए जाइत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गैलरी">
<feature>वाटरमार्क सभ केँ आब सुविधानुसार जोड़ल आ हटाओल जा सकैत अछि। एहि मे जा कए एकरा अनुभव करू: एकटा फोटो लिअ > फोटो खोलू > संपादित करू > वाटरमार्क > वाटरमार्क विकल्प सभ: मूल, टेक्स्ट वाटरमार्क, फ्रेम वाटरमार्क।</feature>
</features>
<features module="आँखि केँ ट्रैक करब">
<feature>आँखि केँ ट्रैक करब सम्मिलित अछि, जे अहाँक आँखि 20-50 सेमी केर दूरी पर सोझे स्क्रीनक सामना करैत काल बिना कोनो मैनुअल प्रचालन केँ अधिसूचना आ विस्तृत कंटेंट धरि त्वरित एक्सेस केर अनुमति दैत अछि। एकरा अनुभव करबाक लेल: सेटिंग्स > सहायक > आँखि केँ ट्रैक करब पर जाउ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="अधिसूचना पैनल">
<feature>अधिसूचना पैनल केर लेआउट अनुकूलित अछि, जाहि सँ इंटरफेस बेसी सुव्यवस्थित आ देखए मे आकर्षक भए गेल अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="मोशन प्रभाव">
<feature>होम स्क्रीन पर मोशन प्रभाव केर स्थिरता अनुकूलित करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="पावर खपत">
<feature>किछु परिदृश्य सभ मे असामान्य पावर खपत केर समस्याक समाधान करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>सिस्टमक स्थिरता मे सुधार करैत अछि, जाहि सँ अहाँक डिवाइस बेसी स्थिर रूप सँ चलि सकए।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>सिस्टमक सुरक्षाक लेल Android सुरक्षा पैच (अगस्त 2024) समाविष्ट कयल गेल अछि। HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेट सभक विषय मे आओर जानकारीक लेल, कृपाकए हमरासभक वेबसाइट केँ देखू: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणी:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहि मेटायत मुदा पहिने सँ एकटा बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' सहायताक लेल कृपाकए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन केँ कॉल करू वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाउ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E te kaiwhakamahi, mā tēnei whakahōutanga tūtohu, ka taea e koe te tiaki i ngā pahekotanga taupānga ki te aratau mata-wehe. Ka whakamōhiotia hoki e tēnei whakahōu te Whaiwhai Karu, ā, ka whakaae kia whakatikaina ngā tohuwai. Tērā anō, mā tēnei putanga e arotau ai te pānga whakaatu o te paewhiri whakamōhiotanga me te pānga nekeneke i te mata kāinga, ka whakatika i te take o te whakapetonga hiko rerekē i ētahi tauari, ka whakapai ake i te taimautanga pūnaha, ā, ka komokomo i tētahi āpure haumarutanga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Matapihi-Maha">
<feature>Ināianei ka taea te tiaki i ngā pahekotanga taupānga i te aratau mata-wehe. I roto i te aratau mata-wehe, patohia te pātene i waenganui o te whakawehe hei tiaki i te pahekotanga hei ata i te mata kāinga. Patohia te ata ka whakahohe te uru wawe ki te pahekotanga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Taiwhanga">
<feature>Ināianei ka taea te tāpiri me te tango i ngā tohuwai e hiahiatia ana. Wheako mā te haere: Tangohia tētahi whakaahua > Whakatuwheratia te whakaahua > Te Whakatika > Te Tohuwai > Kōwhiringa tohuwai: Tūturu, Tohuwai kuputuhi, Tohuwai tāpare.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Whaiwhai Karu">
<feature>Kei roto i te Whaiwhai Karu, e whakaae ana i tētahi uru wawe ki ngā whakamōhiotanga me ngā ihirangi taipitopito me te kore mahi ā-ringa ina anga hāngai atu ō whatu ki te mata i te tawhiti o te 20-50 cm. Wheako mā te haere: Ngā tautuhinga > Kaiāwhina > Whaiwhai Karu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Paewhiri whakamōhiotanga">
<feature>Kua arotautia te tahora o te paewhiri whakamōhiotanga, kia māmā ētahi anō ai te atanga me pīra ana ā-ari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pānga nekenga">
<feature>Ka arotautia ai te ōritetanga o te pānga nekenga ki te mata kāinga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Whakapetonga hiko">
<feature>Whakatika ai i te take o te whakapetonga hiko rerekē i ētahi tauari.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pūnaha">
<feature>Ka whakapai ake i te taimautanga pūnaha kia pai ake ai te haere o tō pūrere.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Haumarutanga">
<feature>Kua whakaurua te āpure haumarutanga Android (Akuhata 2024) mō te haumarutanga pūnaha. Mō ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā whakahōutanga Haumarutanga HONOR, haere koa ki tā mātou paetukutuku https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore te tāuta i tēnei whakahōu e muku i ō ngā raraunga whaiaro, engari e manakohia tonutia ana tētahi pūrua i mua.
2. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōutanga, waeawera atu koa ki te raina ratonga HONOR, ka haere rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki HONOR hei tautoko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитуван кориснику, со ова препорачано ажурирање, може да зачувате комбинации на апликации во режим на поделен екран. Ова ажурирање воведува и Следење на очите и овозможува уредување на водените знаци. Дополнително, ажурирањето ги оптимизира ефектот на приказ на таблата за известувања и ефектот на движење на почетниот екран, го поправа проблемот со невообичаена потрошувачка на енергија во некои сценарија, ја подобрува стабилноста на системот и воведува безбедносна крпеница.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Повеќе прозорци">
<feature>Сега може да се зачувуваат комбинации на апликации во режим на поделен екран. Во режим на поделен екран, допрете го копчето во средината од разделникот за да ја зачувате комбинацијата како икона на почетниот екран. Допирањето на иконата овозможува брз пристап до комбинацијата.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерија">
<feature>Водените знаци сега може да се додаваат и отстрануваат како што се посакува. Искусете преку одење во Направете фотографија > Отворете ја фотографијата > Уреди > Воден знак > Опции за воден знак: Оригинал, Воден знак со текст, Воден знак со рамка.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Следење на очите">
<feature>Вклучено е Следење на очите, со што се овозможува брз пристап до известувањата и деталната содржина без рачно работење кога очите се директно насочени кон екранот на растојание од 20-50 cm. Искусете преку одење во: Нагодување > Помошник > Следење на очите.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Табла за известувања">
<feature>Оптимизиран е распоредот на таблата за известувања, со што интерфејсот е повеќе рационализиран и визуелно попривлечен.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ефект на движење">
<feature>Ја оптимизира постојаноста на ефектот на движење на почетниот екран.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Потрошувачка на енергија">
<feature>Го поправа проблемот со абнормална потрошувачка на енергија во некои сценарија.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>Ја подобрува стабилноста на системот за уредот да работи постабилно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безбедност">
<feature>Вградена е безбедносна крпеница за Android (август 2024) за безбедност на системот. За повеќе информации за ажурирања на безбедноста од HONOR, посетете ја нашата веб-локација https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да ги избрише вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува однапред да направите резервна копија.
2. Ако наидете на проблеми при ажурирањето, повикајте го телефонскиот број на службата на HONOR или одете во сервисен центар за корисници од HONOR за поддршка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്ന അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിൽ, സ്പ്ലിറ്റ്-സ്ക്രീൻ മോഡിലെ ആപ്പ് കോംബിനേഷനുകൾ സംരക്ഷിക്കാൻ കഴിയും. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് 'ഐ ട്രാക്കിംഗ്' അവതരിപ്പിക്കുകയും വാട്ടർമാർക്കുകൾ എഡിറ്റ് ചെയ്യാൻ അനുവദിക്കുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു. അതിനുപുറമേ, ഈ റിലീസ് നോട്ടിഫിക്കേഷൻ പാനലിന്റെ ഡിസ്‌പ്ലേ ഇഫക്റ്റും ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനിലെ ചലന ഇഫക്റ്റും ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുകയും ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ അസ്വാഭാവിക വൈദ്യുതി ഉപഭോഗത്തിന്റെ പ്രശ്‌നം പരിഹരിക്കുകയും സിസ്റ്റം സ്ഥിരത മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ഒരു സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തുകയും ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="മൾട്ടി-വിൻഡോ">
<feature>സ്പ്ലിറ്റ്-സ്ക്രീൻ മോഡിലെ ആപ്പ് കോംബിനേഷനുകൾ ഇപ്പോൾ സംരക്ഷിക്കാൻ കഴിയും. സ്പ്ലിറ്റ്-സ്ക്രീൻ മോഡിൽ, ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനിൽ ഒരു ഐക്കണായി കോംബിനേഷൻ സംരക്ഷിക്കാൻ ഡിവൈഡറിന്റെ മധ്യത്തിലെ ബട്ടണിൽ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുക. ഐക്കണിൽ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുന്നത്, കോംബിനേഷനിലേക്കുള്ള ദ്രുത ആക്‌സസ് പ്രവർത്തനസജ്ജമാക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ഗാലറി">
<feature>ഇപ്പോൾ വാട്ടർമാർക്കുകൾ ഇഷ്‌ടാനുസൃതം ചേർക്കാനും നീക്കംചെയ്യാനും കഴിയും. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് അനുഭവിച്ചറിയുക: ഒരു ഫോട്ടോ എടുക്കുക > ഫോട്ടോ തുറക്കുക > എഡിറ്റ് ചെയ്യുക > വാട്ടർമാർക്ക് > വാട്ടർമാർക്ക് ഓപ്‌ഷനുകൾ: ഒറിജിനൽ, ടെക്‌സ്‌റ്റ് വാട്ടർമാർക്ക്, ഫ്രെയിം വാട്ടർമാർക്ക്.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ഐ ട്രാക്കിംഗ്">
<feature>നിങ്ങളുടെ കണ്ണുകൾ 20-50 സെ.മീ. അകലത്തിൽ സ്‌ക്രീനിന് നേരെ അഭിമുഖമായിരിക്കുമ്പോൾ മാനുവൽ പ്രവർത്തനമില്ലാതെ നോട്ടിഫിക്കേഷനുകളിലേക്കും വിശദമായ ഉള്ളടക്കത്തിലേക്കും ഒരു ദ്രുത ആക്‌സസ് അനുവദിക്കുന്ന 'ഐ ട്രാക്കിംഗ്' ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് അനുഭവിച്ചറിയുക: ക്രമീകരണം > അസിസ്റ്റന്റ് > ഐ ട്രാക്കിംഗ്.</feature>
</features>
<features module="നോട്ടിഫിക്കേഷൻ പാനൽ">
<feature>ഇന്റർഫേസ് കൂടുതൽ എളുപ്പവും ആകർഷകവുമാക്കുന്ന വിധത്തിൽ നോട്ടിഫിക്കേഷൻ പാനലിന്റെ ലേഔട്ട് ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്‌തിരിക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ചലന ഇഫക്റ്റ്">
<feature>ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനിലെ ചലന ഇഫക്റ്റ് സ്ഥിരത ഒപ്‌റ്റിമൈസ് ചെയ്യുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="വൈദ്യുതി ഉപഭോഗം">
<feature>ചില സാഹചര്യങ്ങളിലെ അസ്വാഭാവിക വൈദ്യുതി ഉപഭോഗത്തിന്റെ പ്രശ്‌നം പരിഹരിക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സിസ്റ്റം">
<feature>നിങ്ങളുടെ ഉപകരണം കൂടുതൽ സ്ഥിരതയോടെ പ്രവർത്തിക്കാൻ സിസ്റ്റം സ്ഥിരത മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സുരക്ഷ">
<feature>സിസ്റ്റം സുരക്ഷയ്‌ക്കായി Android സുരക്ഷാ പാച്ച് (ഓഗസ്റ്റ് 2024) ഉൾപ്പെടുത്തിയിരിക്കുന്നു. HONOR സുരക്ഷാ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റുകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾക്ക്, ഞങ്ങളുടെ വെബ്‌സൈറ്റ് സന്ദർശിക്കുക: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ മായ്‌ക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും മുൻകൂട്ടി ഒരു ബാക്കപ്പ് എടുത്തുവയ്‌ക്കാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കായി HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү санал болгож буй шинэчлэлтийн тусламжтай та нийлүүлсэн аппуудыг хуваасан дэлгэцийн горимд хадгалах боломжтой. Энэ шинэчлэлт нь Нүд дагагчийг нэвтрүүлснээс гадна усан тэмдэглэгээг засварлах боломж олгодог. Түүнчлэн, энэ хувилбар нь мэдэгдлийн самбарын эффект, үндсэн дэлгэц дээрх хөдөлгөөний эффектийг харуулахыг оновчлохын сацуу хэвийн бус эрчим хүчний хэрэглээ зарим тохиолдолд гарч байсан асуудлыг засаж, системийн тогтвортой байдлыг сайжруулж, хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг багтаасан.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Олон цонх">
<feature>Хуваасан дэлгэцийн горим дахь апликэйшний хослолыг одоо хадгалах боломжтой боллоо. Хуваасан дэлгэц горимд хуваагчийн голд байгаа товчлуур дээр товшиж хослолыг үндсэн дэлгэц дээр шигтгээ зураг болгон хадгална. Шигтгээ зураг дээр товшиж хослол руу шуурхай хандах боломжтой.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерей">
<feature>Усны тэмдгийг одоо хүссэнээрээ нэмж, арилгаж болно. Үүнийг Зураг авах > Зургийг нээх > Засах > Усан тэмдэг > Усан тэмдгийн сонголт руу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү: Эх хувилбар, Бичвэрийн усан тэмдэг, Хүрээний усан тэмдэг.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Нүд дагагч">
<feature>Нүд дагагч нь таны нүд дэлгэц рүү 20-50 см зайнаас шууд харсан үед гар ажиллагаагүйгээр мэдэгдэл, дэлгэрэнгүй агуулга руу шуурхай хандах боломжийг олгодог. Үүнийг Тохиргоо > Туслах > Нүд дагагч руу очиж туршиж үзнэ үү.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Мэдэгдлийн хэсэг">
<feature>Мэдэгдлийн хэсгийн зохион байгуулалтыг оновчтой болгож, интерфейсийг илүү хялбар, үзэмжтэй болгосон.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хөдөлгөөний эффект">
<feature>Үндсэн дэлгэц дээрх хөдөлгөөний эффектийн жигд байдлыг оновчилсон.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Эрчим хүчний хэрэглээ">
<feature>Зарим тохиолдол дахь хэвийн бус эрчим хүчний хэрэглээний асуудлыг зассан.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>Таны төхөөрөмжийг илүү тогтвортой ажиллуулахын тулд системийн тогтвортой байдлыг нэмэгдүүлсэн.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хамгаалалт">
<feature>Системийн хамгаалалтад зориулж Андройд хамгаалалтын нөхөөсийг (2024 оны наймдугаар сар) багтаав. HONOR-н хамгаалалтын шинэчлэлтийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээлэл авах бол манай дараах вебсайтад зочилно уу: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгахад таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч урьдчилан нөөцлөхийг зөвлөж байна.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад аливаа асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төвд зочилж тусламж авна уу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, या शिफारस केलेल्या अद्यतनासह, आपण त्वरित ॲक्सेससाठी विभाजित स्क्रीन मोडमध्ये ॲप कॉम्बिनेशन्स जतन करू शकता. या अद्यतनामध्ये डोळ्यांचे ट्रॅकिंग देखील समाविष्ट आहे आणि वॉटरमार्क संपादित करण्याची अनुमती देते. याव्यतिरिक्त, हे रिलीझ सूचना पॅनेलचा डिस्प्ले प्रभाव आणि मुख्य स्क्रीनवरील मोशन प्रभावाला ऑप्टिमाइझ करते, काही परिस्थितींमध्ये असामान्य पॉवर वापराच्या समस्येचे निराकरण करते, सिस्टम स्थिरता सुधारते आणि सुरक्षितता पॅच समाविष्ट करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="मल्टी-विंडो">
<feature>विभाजित स्क्रीन मोडमधील ॲप संयोजने आता जतन केले जाऊ शकतात. विभाजित स्क्रीन मोडमध्ये, मुख्य स्क्रीनवर संयोजन जतन करण्यासाठी विभाजक मध्ये असलेल्या बटणावर टॅप करा. चिन्हावर टॅप केल्याने संयोजनात जलद अ‍ॅक्‍सेस सक्षम करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="गॅलरी">
<feature>वॉटरमार्क्स आता जोडले जाऊ शकतात आणि हवे तसे काढले जाऊ शकतात. येथे जाऊन त्याचा अनुभव घ्या: फोटो घ्या > फोटो उघडा > संपादित करा > वॉटरमार्क > वॉटरमार्क पर्याय: मूळ, मजकूर वॉटरमार्क, फ्रेम वॉटरमार्क.</feature>
</features>
<features module="डोळ्यांचे ट्रॅकिंग">
<feature>आपले डोळे 20-50 सेमी अंतरावर थेट स्क्रीनच्या समोर असताना, व्यक्तिचलित ऑपरेशनशिवाय सूचना आणि तपशीलवार सामग्रीमध्ये जलद अ‍ॅक्‍सेसला अनुमती देऊन डोळ्यांचे ट्रॅकिंग समाविष्ट केले आहे. येथे जाऊन याचा अनुभव घ्या: सेटिंग्ज > सहाय्यक > डोळ्यांचे ट्रॅकिंग.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सूचना पॅनेल">
<feature>सूचना पॅनेलचे लेआउट ऑप्टिमाइझ केले आहे, ज्यामुळे इंटरफेस अधिक सुव्यवस्थित आणि दृष्यदृष्ट्या आकर्षक बनतो.</feature>
</features>
<features module="मोशन प्रभाव">
<feature>मुख्य स्क्रीनवर मोशन प्रभाव सातत्य ऑप्टिमाइझ करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="पॉवर वापर">
<feature>काही परिस्थितींमध्ये असामान्य वीज वापराच्या समस्येचे निराकरण करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>आपले उपकरण अधिक स्थिरपणे चालण्‍यासाठी सिस्‍टम स्‍थिरता सुधारते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षितता">
<feature>सिस्टम सुरक्षिततेसाठी Android सुरक्षितता पॅच (ऑगस्ट 2024) समाविष्ट करण्यात आला आहे. HONOR सुरक्षितता अद्यतनांबद्दल अधिक माहितीसाठी, कृपया आमच्या वेबसाइट https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8 वर जा</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्थापित केल्याने आपला वैयक्तिक डेटा मिटणार नाही, परंतु आधीच बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करा किंवा समर्थनासाठी HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जा.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, dengan kemas kini yang disyorkan ini, anda boleh menyimpan gabungan aplikasi dalam mod skrin pisah. Kemas kini ini juga memperkenalkan Penjejakan Mata dan membenarkan tera air diedit. Selain itu, keluaran ini mengoptimumkan kesan paparan panel pemberitahuan dan kesan gerakan pada skrin utama, membetulkan isu penggunaan kuasa yang tidak normal dalam beberapa senario, meningkatkan kestabilan sistem serta memasukkan tampalan keselamatan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multitetingkap">
<feature>Gabungan aplikasi dalam mod skrin pisah kini boleh disimpan. Dalam mod skrin pisah, ketik butang di tengah pembahagi untuk menyimpan gabungan sebagai ikon pada skrin utama. Ketik ikon membolehkan akses pantas kepada gabungan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Tera air kini boleh ditambahkan dan dikeluarkan seperti yang dikehendaki. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Ambil foto > Buka foto > Edit > Tera air > Pilihan tera air: Asal, Tera air teks, Tera air bingkai.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Penjejakan Mata">
<feature>Penjejakan Mata disertakan, membolehkan akses pantas kepada pemberitahuan dan kandungan terperinci tanpa operasi manual apabila mata anda menghadap terus ke skrin pada jarak 20-50 cm. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan > Pembantu > Penjejakan Mata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panel pemberitahuan">
<feature>Tataletak panel pemberitahuan dioptimumkan, menjadikan antara muka lebih diperkemas dan menarik secara visual.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kesan gerakan">
<feature>Optimumkan ketekalan kesan gerakan pada skrin utama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Penggunaan kuasa">
<feature>Betulkan isu penggunaan kuasa yang tidak normal dalam beberapa senario.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Tingkatkan kestabilan sistem untuk membolehkan peranti anda berjalan dengan lebih stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Keselamatan">
<feature>Tampalan keselamatan Android (Ogos 2024) telah dimasukkan untuk keselamatan sistem. Untuk mendapatkan maklumat lanjut tentang kemas kini Keselamatan HONOR, sila lawati laman web kami https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Pemasangan kemas kini ini tidak akan memadamkan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda disyorkan agar masih membuat sandaran terlebih dahulu.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, sila hubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau pergi ke pusat khidmat pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan sokongan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ အကြံပြုထားသော ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ဖြင့် သင်သည် မျက်နှာပြင် ပိုင်းခြားမှုစနစ်တွင်သုံးမည့် အက်ပ်အတွဲများကို သိမ်းဆည်းနိုင်သည်။ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် မျက်လုံးအကြည့်ကို ခြေရာခံမှုနှင့်လည်း မိတ်ဆက်ပေးထားပြီး ရေစာများကို တည်းဖြတ်ခွင့်ပေးသည်။ ထို့အပြင် ဤအသစ်ထွက်အပ်ဒိတ်သည် အသိပေးချက် မျက်နှာပြင်၏ ပြသမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်နှင့် ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်ရှိ လှုပ်ရှားမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်၊ အချို့အခြေအနေများတွင် ပါဝါ သုံးစွဲမှု မူမမှန်သည့် ပြဿနာကို ဖြေရှင်းပေးပြီး စနစ် တည်ငြိမ်မှုကို မြှင့်တင်ပေးကာ လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>ယခုအခါ မျက်နှာပြင် ပိုင်းခြားမှုစနစ်ဖြင့် သုံးမည့် အက်ပ်အတွဲများကို သိမ်းဆည်းနိုင်ပါပြီ။ မျက်နှာပြင် ပိုင်းခြားမှုစနစ်တွင် အက်ပ်အတွဲကို ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်ပေါ်တွင် အိုင်ကွန်အဖြစ် သိမ်းဆည်းရန် ပိုင်းခြားမျဉ်း၏အလယ်ရှိ ခလုတ်ကို နှိပ်ပါ။ အိုင်ကွန်ကို နှိပ်ခြင်းဖြင့် အက်ပ်အတွဲကို အမြန် ရယူသုံးစွဲခွင့်ရစေသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပုံပြခန်း">
<feature>ယခုအခါ ရေစာများကို ဆန္ဒရှိသလို ထည့်နိုင် ဖယ်ရှားနိုင်သည်။ ဖော်ပြထားသည့်အတိုင်းသွား၍ ၎င်းကို သုံးစွဲပါ- ဓာတ်ပုံရိုက်မည် > ဓာတ်ပုံ ဖွင့်မည် > တည်းဖြတ်မည် > ရေစာ > ရေစာ ရွေးချယ်မှုများ- မူရင်း၊ စာသားရေစာ၊ ဖရိန် ရေစာ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="မျက်လုံးအကြည့်ကို ခြေရာခံမှု">
<feature>မျက်လုံးအကြည့်ကို ခြေရာခံမှု ပါဝင်ပြီး သင့်မျက်လုံးများက မျက်နှာပြင်နှင့် 20-50 cm ခွာ၍ တိုက်ရိုက်မျက်နှာမူသောအခါ အသိပေး အချက်ပြမှုများနှင့် အသေးစိတ် အကြောင်းအရာကို ကိုယ်တိုင်လုပ်ဆောင်ရန်မလိုဘဲ အမြန် ရယူသုံးစွဲနိုင်သည်။ ဖော်ပြပါအတိုင်းသွား၍ ၎င်းကို သုံးစွဲပါ- ဆက်တင် > အကူ > မျက်လုံးအကြည့်ကို ခြေရာခံမှု။</feature>
</features>
<features module="အသိပေးချက် မျက်နှာပြင်">
<feature>အသိပေးချက် မျက်နှာပြင်ပုံစံကို အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိထား၍ ကြားခံစနစ်ကို ပိုမိုအဆင်ပြေချောမွေ့စေပြီး မျက်စိပသာဒဖြစ်စေသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လှုပ်ရှားမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်">
<feature>ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်တွင် လှုပ်ရှားမှု အထူးပြုလုပ်ချက်ကို တစ်သမတ်တည်းဖြစ်စေရန် အကောင်းဆုံး ချိန်ညှိပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပါဝါ သုံးစွဲမှု">
<feature>အချို့ဖြစ်ရပ်များတွင် ပါဝါ သုံးစွဲမှု မူမမှန်သည့် ပြဿနာကို ဖြေရှင်းပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ်">
<feature>သင့်စက်ကို ပိုမိုတည်ငြိမ်စွာ လုပ်ဆောင်နိုင်စေရန် စနစ် တည်ငြိမ်မှုကို တိုးမြှင့်ပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံခြုံရေး">
<feature>စနစ်လုံခြုံရေးအတွက် Android လုံခြုံရေး အဆင့်မြှင့်ဆော့ဖ်ဝဲ (ဩဂုတ် 2024) ကို ပေါင်းစပ်ထည့်သွင်းပေးထားသည်။ HONOR လုံခြုံရေး အပ်ဒိတ်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို သိရှိရန် ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ ဝက်ဘ်ဆိုဒ်သို့ သွားရောက်ကြည့်ရှုပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းသည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာကို ဖျက်မည် မဟုတ်သော်လည်း ကြိုတင်၍ ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်နေစဉ် ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခု ကြုံတွေ့ပါက အကူအညီရယူရန် HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆိုပါ သို့မဟုတ် HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ အႀကံျပဳထားေသာ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ျဖင့္ သင္သည္ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ ပိုင္းျခားမႈစနစ္တြင္သုံးမည့္ အက္ပ္အတြဲမ်ားကို သိမ္းဆည္းႏိုင္သည္။ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ မ်က္လုံးအၾကည့္ကို ေျခရာခံမႈႏွင့္လည္း မိတ္ဆက္ေပးထားၿပီး ေရစာမ်ားကို တည္းျဖတ္ခြင့္ေပးသည္။ ထို႔အျပင္ ဤအသစ္ထြက္အပ္ဒိတ္သည္ အသိေပးခ်က္ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္၏ ျပသမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ႏွင့္ ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ရွိ လႈပ္ရွားမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္၊ အခ်ိဳ႕အေျခအေနမ်ားတြင္ ပါဝါ သုံးစြဲမႈ မူမမွန္သည့္ ျပႆနာကို ေျဖရွင္းေပးၿပီး စနစ္ တည္ၿငိမ္မႈကို ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးကာ လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>ယခုအခါ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ ပိုင္းျခားမႈစနစ္ျဖင့္ သုံးမည့္ အက္ပ္အတြဲမ်ားကို သိမ္းဆည္းႏိုင္ပါၿပီ။ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ ပိုင္းျခားမႈစနစ္တြင္ အက္ပ္အတြဲကို ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ေပၚတြင္ အိုင္ကြန္အျဖစ္ သိမ္းဆည္းရန္ ပိုင္းျခားမ်ဥ္း၏အလယ္ရွိ ခလုတ္ကို ႏွိပ္ပါ။ အိုင္ကြန္ကို ႏွိပ္ျခင္းျဖင့္ အက္ပ္အတြဲကို အျမန္ ရယူသုံးစြဲခြင့္ရေစသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပုံျပခန္း">
<feature>ယခုအခါ ေရစာမ်ားကို ဆႏၵရွိသလို ထည့္ႏိုင္ ဖယ္ရွားႏိုင္သည္။ ေဖာ္ျပထားသည့္အတိုင္းသြား၍ ၎ကို သုံးစြဲပါ- ဓာတ္ပုံ႐ိုက္မည္ > ဓာတ္ပုံ ဖြင့္မည္ > ျပင္ဆင္မည္ > ေရစာ > ေရစာ ေ႐ြးခ်ယ္မႈမ်ား- မူရင္း၊ စာသားေရစာ၊ ဖရိန္ ေရစာ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="မ်က္လုံးအၾကည့္ကို ေျခရာခံမႈ">
<feature>မ်က္လုံးအၾကည့္ကို ေျခရာခံမႈ ပါဝင္ၿပီး သင့္မ်က္လုံးမ်ားက မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ႏွင့္ 20-50 cm ခြာ၍ တိုက္႐ိုက္မ်က္ႏွာမူေသာအခါ အသိေပး အခ်က္ျပမႈမ်ားႏွင့္ အေသးစိတ္ အေၾကာင္းအရာကို ကိုယ္တိုင္လုပ္ေဆာင္ရန္မလိုဘဲ အျမန္ ရယူသုံးစြဲႏိုင္သည္။ ေဖာ္ျပပါအတိုင္းသြား၍ ၎ကို သုံးစြဲပါ- ဆက္တင္ > အကူ > မ်က္လုံးအၾကည့္ကို ေျခရာခံမႈ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="အသိေပးခ်က္ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္">
<feature>အသိေပးခ်က္ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ပုံစံကို အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိထား၍ ၾကားခံစနစ္ကို ပိုမိုအဆင္ေျပေခ်ာေမြ႕ေစၿပီး မ်က္စိပသာဒျဖစ္ေစသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လႈပ္ရွားမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္">
<feature>ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္တြင္ လႈပ္ရွားမႈ အထူးျပဳလုပ္ခ်က္ကို တစ္သမတ္တည္းျဖစ္ေစရန္ အေကာင္းဆုံး ခ်ိန္ညႇိေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပါဝါ သုံးစြဲမႈ">
<feature>အခ်ိဳ႕ျဖစ္ရပ္မ်ားတြင္ ပါဝါ သုံးစြဲမႈ မူမမွန္သည့္ ျပႆနာကို ေျဖရွင္းေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ္">
<feature>သင့္စက္ကို ပိုမိုတည္ၿငိမ္စြာ လုပ္ေဆာင္ႏိုင္ေစရန္ စနစ္ တည္ၿငိမ္မႈကို တိုးျမႇင့္ေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="လုံျခံဳေရး">
<feature>စနစ္လုံၿခဳံေရးအတြက္ Android လုံၿခဳံေရး အဆင့္ျမႇင့္ေဆာ့ဖ္ဝဲ (ဩဂုတ္ 2024) ကို ေပါင္းစပ္ထည့္သြင္းေပးထားသည္။ HONOR လုံၿခဳံေရး အပ္ဒိတ္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို သိရွိရန္ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ ဝက္ဘ္ဆိုဒ္သို႔ သြားေရာက္ၾကည့္ရႈပါ- https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းသည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာကို ဖ်က္မည္ မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း ႀကိဳတင္၍ ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္ေနစဥ္ ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခု ႀကဳံေတြ႕ပါက အကူအညီရယူရန္ HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆိုပါ သို႔မဟုတ္ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, med denne anbefalte oppdateringen kan du lagre appkombinasjoner i delt-skjermmodus. Denne oppdateringen introduserer også Øyesporing, og gjør at vannmerker kan redigeres. I tillegg optimaliserer denne utgaven visningseffekten til varslingspanelet og bevegelseseffekten på startskjermen, fikser problemet med unormalt strømforbruk i noen scenarioer, forbedrer systemstabiliteten og innlemmer en sikkerhetsoppdatering.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Flere vinduer">
<feature>App-kombinasjoner i delt-skjerm-modus kan nå lagres. I delt-skjerm-modus trykk på knappen i midten av deleren for å lagre kombinasjonen som et ikon på startskjermen. Trykk på ikonet gjør det mulig med hurtigtilgang til kombinasjonen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleri">
<feature>Vannmerker kan nå legges til og fjernes etter ønske. Opplev det ved å gå til: Ta et bilde > Åpne bildet > Rediger > Vannmerke > Vannmerke-alternativer: Original, Tekstvannmerke, Vannmerkestripe.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Øyesporing">
<feature>Øyesporing er inkludert, noe som gjør det mulig med hurtigtilgang til varslingene og det detaljerte innholdet uten manuell drift når øynene direkte vender mot skjermen ved en avstand på 20-50 cm. Opplev det ved å gå til: Innstillinger > Assistent > Øyesporing.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varslingspanel">
<feature>Layout på varslingspanelet er optimalisert, noe som gjør grensesnittet mer strømlinjeformet og visuelt tiltalende.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bevegelseseffekt">
<feature>Optimaliserer bevegelseseffektkonsistensen på startskjermen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Batteribruk">
<feature>Fikser problemet med unormal batteribruk i enkelte scenarioer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Forbedrer systemstabiliteten, slik at enheten kjører mer stabilt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sikkerhet">
<feature>Android-sikkerhetsoppdatering (august 2024) er innlemmet for systemsikkerhet. For mer informasjon om sikkerhetsoppdateringer fra HONOR, se nettstedet vårt: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke slette personopplysningene dine, men det anbefales likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer på forhånd.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, ring HONOR-kundeservice eller gå til HONOR-kundeservicesenteret for assistanse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, तपाईं सिफारिस गरिएको यो अपडेट गरेर स्प्लिट-स्क्रिन मोडमा एपका संयोजनहरू बचत गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ । यो अपडेटले आँखाको ट्र्याकिङ गर्ने सुविधा पनि ल्याएको छ र वाटरमार्क सम्पादन गर्न मिल्ने बनाएको छ । साथै, यो रिलिजले सूचना प्यानलको डिस्प्ले प्रभाव र गृह स्क्रिनको मोसन प्रभाव अप्टिमाइज गरेको छ, केही परिदृश्यमा सामान्य पावर खपत हुने समस्या समाधान गरेको छ, प्रणालीको स्थिरता सुधार गरेको छ र सुरक्षा प्याच समावेश गरेको छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="बहु-विन्डो">
<feature>अब स्प्लिट-स्क्रिन मोडमा एपको संयोजन बचत गर्न सकिन्छ । एपको संयोजनलाई गृह स्क्रिनको आइकनका रूपमा बचत गर्न स्प्लिट-स्क्रिन मोडमा डिभाइडरको मध्य भागमा भएको बटनमा ट्याप गर्नुहोस् । आइकनहरूमा ट्याप गर्नाले तपाईं एपको संयोजनलाई द्रुत पहुँच गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ग्यालरी">
<feature>अबदेखि आफ्नो इच्छाअनुसार वाटरमार्क हाल्न र हटाउन सकिन्छ । यसको अनुभव लिन यहाँ जानुहोस्: फोटो खिच्नुहोस् > फोटो खोल्नुहोस् > सम्पादन गर्नुहोस् > वाटरमार्क > वाटरमार्कसम्बन्धी विकल्पहरू: मौलिक, पाठको वाटरमार्क, फ्रेमको वाटरमार्क ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="आँखाको ट्र्याकिङ">
<feature>आँखाको ट्र्याकिङ समावेश गरिएको छ । तपाईं आफ्नो आँखा 20-50 सेन्टिमिटरको दूरीमा सीधै स्क्रिनतर्फ फर्केका बेला यो सुविधा प्रयोग गरी म्यानुअल तरिका प्रयोग नगरिकनै सूचनाहरू र विस्तृत सामग्रीको द्रुत पहुँच गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ । यहाँ गई यसको अनुभव लिनुहोस्: सेटिङहरू > सहायक >आँखाको ट्र्याकिङ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सूचना प्यानल">
<feature>सूचना प्यानलको लेआउट अप्टिमाइज गरिएको छ र यसले गर्दा इन्टरफेस अझ व्यवस्थित र आकर्षक भएको छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="मोसन प्रभाव">
<feature>यसले गृह स्क्रिनमा मोसन प्रभावको एकरूपता अप्टिमाइज गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="पावर खपत">
<feature>केही दृश्यमा असामान्य पावर खपतको समस्या समाधान गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्रणाली">
<feature>तपाईंको यन्त्रलाई थप स्थिर रूपमा चल्ने बनाउन प्रणालीको स्थिरतामा सुधार ल्याउँछ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सुरक्षा">
<feature>एन्ड्रोइड सुरक्षा प्याच (अगस्ट 2024) प्रणाली सुरक्षाका लागि समावेश गरिएको छ । HONOR सुरक्षा अपडेटबारे थप जानकारीका लागि, कृपया हाम्रो वेबसाइटमा जानुहोस् https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. यो अपडेट स्थापना गर्नाले तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटा मेटिने छैन तर अझै पनि पहिले नै ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. अपडेटको समयमा तपाईंले कुनै पनि समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने, कृपया HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गर्नुहोस् वा सहायताका लागि HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा जानुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruiker, met deze aanbevolen update kunt u app-combinaties opslaan in de modus gesplitst-scherm. Deze update introduceert ook Oogtracking en maakt het mogelijk om watermerken te bewerken. Bovendien optimaliseert deze release het weergave-effect van het meldingenpaneel en het bewegingseffect op het startscherm, lost deze release het probleem van abnormaal energieverbruik in bepaalde scenario's op, verbetert het de stabiliteit van het systeem en bevat het een beveiligingspatch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multivenster">
<feature>App-combinaties in de modus gesplitst-scherm kunnen nu worden opgeslagen. Tik in de modus gesplitst-scherm op de knop in het midden van de verdeler om de combinatie op te slaan als een pictogram op het startscherm. Tik op het pictogram om snel toegang te krijgen tot de combinatie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Foto's">
<feature>Watermerken kunnen nu naar wens worden toegevoegd en verwijderd. Ervaar het via: Een foto maken > De foto openen > Bewerken > Watermerk > Watermerkopties: Origineel, Tekstwatermerk, Framewatermerk.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oogtracking">
<feature>Oogtracking is inbegrepen, waardoor u snel toegang hebt tot de meldingen en de gedetailleerde inhoud zonder handmatige bediening wanneer uw ogen direct naar het scherm gericht zijn op een afstand van 20-50 cm. Ervaar het via: Instellingen > Assistent > Oogtracking.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Meldingenpaneel">
<feature>De lay-out van het meldingenpaneel is geoptimaliseerd, waardoor de interface gestroomlijnder en visueel aantrekkelijker is.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bewegingseffect">
<feature>Optimaliseert de consistentie van het bewegingseffect op het startscherm.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energieverbruik">
<feature>Lost het probleem van abnormaal energieverbruik in bepaalde scenario's op.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systeem">
<feature>Verbetert de systeemstabiliteit om uw apparaat stabieler te laten werken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Beveiliging">
<feature>Android-beveiligingspatch (augustus 2024) is opgenomen voor systeembeveiliging. Voor meer informatie over HONOR-beveiligingsupdates kunt u terecht op onze website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Als u deze update installeert, worden uw persoonlijke gegevens niet gewist, maar een back-up vooraf wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, bel dan de HONOR-servicehotline of ga naar een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum voor ondersteuning.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଥିବା ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ରେ, ଆପଣ ସ୍ପ୍ଲିଟ୍‌-ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ମୋଡ୍‌ର ଆପ୍‌ ମିଶ୍ରଣ ସଞ୍ଚୟ କରିପାରିବେ। ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ଚକ୍ଷୁର ଟ୍ରାକିଂ ମଧ୍ୟ ପ୍ରଦାନ କରେ, ଏବଂ ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ‌କୁ ସମ୍ପାଦନ କରିବାକୁ ଅନୁମତି ଦିଏ। ଅତିରିକ୍ତ ଭାବେ, ଏହି ରିଲିଜ୍ ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ରେ ବିଜ୍ଞପ୍ତି ପ୍ୟାନେଲ୍‌ର ପ୍ରଭାବ ଏବଂ ମୋସନ୍‌ ପ୍ରଭାବର ପ୍ରଦର୍ଶନକୁ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ, କିଛି ପରିଦୃଶ୍ୟରେ ଅସାମାନ୍ୟ ପାୱାର୍ ଖର୍ଚ୍ଚର ସମସ୍ୟାକୁ ସୁଧାର କରେ, ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସ୍ଥିରତାରେ ବିକାଶ କରେ, ଏବଂ ଏକ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ମଲ୍ଟି-ୱିଣ୍ଡୋ">
<feature>ସ୍ପ୍ଲିଟ୍‌-ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ମୋଡ୍‌ରେ ସମସ୍ତ ମିଶ୍ରଣ ବର୍ତ୍ତମାନ ସଞ୍ଚୟ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ। ସ୍ପ୍ଲିଟ୍‌-ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ମୋଡ୍‌ରେ, ମିଶ୍ରଣକୁ ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ରେ ଏକ ଆଇକନ୍ ପରି ସଞ୍ଚୟ କରିବାକୁ ଡିଭାଇଡର୍‌ର ମଧ୍ୟରେ ଥିବା ବଟନ୍‌ରେ ଟ୍ୟାପ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ। ଆଇକନ୍‌ ଉପରେ ଟ୍ୟାପ୍‌ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ମିଶ୍ରଣର ଦ୍ରୁତ ଆକସେସ୍ ସକ୍ଷମ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଗ୍ୟାଲେରୀ">
<feature>ନିଜ ମନ ଅନୁସାରେ ବର୍ତ୍ତମାନ ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ ଯୋଡ଼ାଯାଇ ପାରିବ କିମ୍ବା ଅପସାରଣ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାର ଅନୁଭୂତି ନିଅନ୍ତୁ: ଏକ ଫଟୋ ଉଠାନ୍ତୁ > ଫଟୋ ଖୋଲନ୍ତୁ > ସମ୍ପାଦନ କରନ୍ତୁ > ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ > ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ ବିକଳ୍ପସମୂହ: ମୂଳ, ଟେକ୍ସଟ୍ ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ, ଫ୍ରେମ ୱାଟର୍‌ମାର୍କ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଚକ୍ଷୁର ଟ୍ରାକିଂ">
<feature>ଚକ୍ଷୁର ଟ୍ରାକିଂ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି, ଯାହା 20-50 ସେଣ୍ଟିମିଟର ଦୂରତାରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଚକ୍ଷୁ ସିଧାସଳଖ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଆଡକୁ ମୁହାଁଇଥିବା ବେଳେ ବିନା ମାନୁଆଲ ସଞ୍ଚାଳନାରେ ବିଜ୍ଞପ୍ତିଗୁଡ଼ିକୁ ଏବଂ ସବିଶେଷ ବିଷୟବସ୍ତୁକୁ ଏକ ଦ୍ରୁତ ଆକସେସ୍ ଅନୁମତି ଦିଏ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାର ଅନୁଭୂତି ନିଅନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ > ସହାୟକ > ଚକ୍ଷୁର ଟ୍ରାକିଂ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ବିଜ୍ଞପ୍ତି ପ୍ୟାନେଲ୍‌">
<feature>ବିଜ୍ଞପ୍ତି ପ୍ୟାନେଲ୍‌‌ର ଲେଆଉଟ୍ ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍ କରାଯାଇଛି ଯାହା ଇଣ୍ଟରଫେସ୍‌କୁ ଅଧିକ ସୁଚାରୁ ତଥା ଦେଖିବାରେ ସୁନ୍ଦର କରିଥାଏ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ମୋସନ୍ ପ୍ରଭାବ">
<feature>ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌‌ରେ ମୋସନ୍ ପ୍ରଭାବକୁ ନିରନ୍ତର ଅପ୍ଟିମାଇଜ୍‌ କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ପାୱାର୍ ଖର୍ଚ୍ଚ">
<feature>କେତେକ ପରିଦୃଶ୍ୟ ଅସାମାନ୍ୟ ପାୱାର୍‌ ଖର୍ଚ୍ଚ ସମସ୍ୟାକୁ ସୁଧାର କରେ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌">
<feature>ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡିଭାଇସ୍‌ ଅଧିକ ସ୍ଥିର ଭାବେ ଚଲାଇବାକୁ, ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌ ସ୍ଥିରତାକୁ ବଢ଼ାଇଥାଏ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସୁରକ୍ଷା">
<feature>Android ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ୟାଚ୍‌ (ଅଗଷ୍ଟ 2024) ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍ ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପାଇଁ ଅନ୍ତର୍ଭୁକ୍ତ କରାଯାଇଛି। HONOR ସୁରକ୍ଷା ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ବିଷୟରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି ଆମ ୱେବସାଇଟ୍‌ https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ଲିଭାଇବ ନାହିଁ, କିନ୍ତୁ ଏହା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଏକ ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରାଯିବା ବେଳେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ସମର୍ଥନ ପାଇଁ, ଦୟାକରି HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੇ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨਾਲ, ਤੁਸੀਂ ਐਪ ਸੁਮੇਲਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਸਪਲਿਟ-ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਮੋਡ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ। ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਅੱਖਾਂ ਟ੍ਰੈਕ ਕਰਨਾ ਨੂੰ ਵੀ ਪੇਸ਼ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੋਧ ਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਇਜਾਜ਼ਤ ਦਿੱਤੀ ਗਈ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਤੋਂ ਇਲਾਵਾ, ਇਸ ਰਿਲੀਜ਼ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੂਚਨਾ ਪੈਨਲ ਦੇ ਡਿਸਪਲੇ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਅਤੇ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ 'ਤੇ ਮੋਸ਼ਨ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਅਸਧਾਰਨ ਪਾਵਰ ਖਪਤ ਦੀ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਨੂੰ ਠੀਕ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਮਲਟੀ-ਵਿੰਡੋ">
<feature>ਸਪਲਿਟ-ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਮੋਡ ਵਿੱਚ ਐਪ ਸੁਮੇਲਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਹੁਣ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਸਪਲਿਟ-ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਮੋਡ ਵਿੱਚ, ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ 'ਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਆਈਕੋਨ ਵਜੋਂ ਸੁਮੇਲ ਨੂੰ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਕਰਨ ਲਈ ਡਿਵਾਈਡਰ ਦੇ ਵਿਚਕਾਰ ਬਟਨ ਨੂੰ ਟੈਪ ਕਰੋ। ਆਈਕੋਨ 'ਤੇ ਟੈਪ ਕਰਨਾ ਸੁਮੇਲ ਤੱਕ ਤੇਜ਼ ਐਕਸੈਸ ਨੂੰ ਸਮਰੱਥ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਗੈਲਰੀ">
<feature>ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ ਨੂੰ ਹੁਣ ਲੋੜ ਅਨੁਸਾਰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਅਤੇ ਹਟਾਇਆ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸਦਾ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਕਰੋ: ਇੱਕ ਫ਼ੋਟੋ ਖਿੱਚੋ > ਫ਼ੋਟੋ ਖੋਲ੍ਹੋ > ਸੋਧੋ > ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ > ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ ਵਿਕਲਪ: ਮੂਲ, ਟੈਕਸਟ ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ, ਫ੍ਰੇਮ ਵਾਟਰਮਾਰਕ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਅੱਖਾਂ ਟ੍ਰੈਕ ਕਰਨਾ">
<feature>ਅੱਖਾਂ ਟ੍ਰੈਕ ਕਰਨਾ ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਸੂਚਨਾਵਾਂ ਅਤੇ ਵਿਸਥਾਰਤ ਸਮੱਗਰੀ ਤੱਕ ਬਿਨਾਂ ਮੈਨੁਅਲੀ ਕਾਰਵਾਈ ਦੇ ਤੇਜ਼ ਐਕਸੈਸ ਦੀ ਆਗਿਆ ਮਿਲਦੀ ਹੈ ਜਦੋਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੀਆਂ ਅੱਖਾਂ 20-50 ਸੈਂਟੀਮੀਟਰ ਦੀ ਦੂਰੀ 'ਤੇ ਸਿੱਧੇ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਵੱਲ ਦੇਖ ਰਹੀਆਂ ਹੁੰਦੀਆਂ ਹਨ। ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ > ਸਹਾਇਕ > ਅੱਖਾਂ ਟ੍ਰੈਕ ਕਰਨਾ 'ਤੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਇਸ ਦਾ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਕਰੋ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸੂਚਨਾ ਪੈਨਲ">
<feature>ਸੂਚਨਾ ਪੈਨਲ ਦੇ ਲੇਆਉਟ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਇੰਟਰਫੇਸ ਵਧੇਰੇ ਸਹਿਜ ਅਤੇ ਦਿਖਣ ਵਿੱਚ ਵਧੀਆ ਲੱਗਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਮੋਸ਼ਨ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ">
<feature>ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ 'ਤੇ ਮੋਸ਼ਨ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵ ਦੀ ਇਕਸਾਰਤਾ ਨੂੰ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਇਆ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਪਾਵਰ ਖਪਤ">
<feature>ਕੁਝ ਸਥਿਤੀਆਂ ਵਿੱਚ ਅਸਧਾਰਨ ਪਾਵਰ ਖਪਤ ਸੰਬੰਧੀ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਨੂੰ ਠੀਕ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸਿਸਟਮ">
<feature>ਸਿਸਟਮ ਦੀ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਵਿੱਚ ਸੁਧਾਰ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਡਿਵਾਈਸ ਜ਼ਿਆਦਾ ਸਥਿਰਤਾ ਨਾਲ ਕੰਮ ਕਰੇਗਾ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ">
<feature>ਸਿਸਟਮ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਲਈ Android ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪੈਚ (ਅਗਸਤ 2024) ਨੂੰ ਸ਼ਾਮਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। HONOR ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਅੱਪਡੇਟਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਲਈ, ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਵੈੱਬਸਾਈਟ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਮਿਟਾਇਆ ਨਹੀਂ ਜਾਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ ਸਹਾਇਤਾ ਲਈ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta zalecana aktualizacja umożliwia zapisywanie kombinacji aplikacji w trybie podzielonego ekranu. Ta aktualizacja wprowadza również Śledzenie wzroku i umożliwia edycję znaków wodnych. Ponadto ta wersja optymalizuje efekt wyświetlania panelu powiadomień i efekt ruchu na ekranie głównym, rozwiązuje problem nieprawidłowego zużycia energii w niektórych sytuacjach, poprawia stabilność systemu i zawiera poprawkę bezpieczeństwa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Wiele okien">
<feature>Można już zapisywać kombinacje aplikacji w trybie podzielonego ekranu. W trybie podzielonego ekranu dotknij przycisku pośrodku separatora, aby zapisać kombinację jako ikonę na ekranie głównym. Dotknięcie ikony umożliwia szybki dostęp do kombinacji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>Można już swobodnie dodawać i usuwać znaki wodne. W tym celu: zrób zdjęcie > otwórz zdjęcie > Edytuj > Znak wodny > Opcje znaku wodnego: Oryginalny, Tekstowy znak wodny, Znak wodny ramki.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Śledzenie wzroku">
<feature>Aktualizacja obejmuje Śledzenie wzroku, które umożliwia szybki dostęp do powiadomień i szczegółowych treści bez używania rąk, gdy wzrok jest skierowany bezpośrednio na ekran z odległości 20–50 cm. Aby użyć tej funkcji, wybierz Ustawienia > Asystent > Śledzenie wzroku.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panel powiadomień">
<feature>Zoptymalizowano układ panelu powiadomień, dzięki czemu interfejs jest bardziej uporządkowany i atrakcyjny wizualnie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efekt ruchu">
<feature>Zoptymalizowano spójność efektu ruchu na ekranie głównym.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zużycie energii">
<feature>Rozwiązano problem nieprawidłowego zużycia energii w niektórych sytuacjach.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Poprawiono stabilność systemu, dzięki czemu urządzenie działa bardziej niezawodnie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpieczenia">
<feature>Aktualizacja zawiera Poprawkę zabezpieczeń systemu Android (sierpień 2024 r.). Więcej informacji o aktualizacjach zabezpieczeń urządzeń HONOR można znaleźć w naszej witrynie internetowej: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie powoduje wymazania danych użytkownika, jednak zalecamy uprzednie wykonanie kopii zapasowej.
2. Jeśli podczas procesu aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, zadzwoń na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR, gdzie uzyskasz pomoc.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Prezado usuário, com esta atualização recomendada, você pode salvar combinações de aplicativos no modo tela dividida para um acesso mais rápido. Ela também apresenta o Rastreamento ocular e permite que marcas d'água sejam editadas. Além disso, esta versão otimiza o efeito de exibição do painel de notificações e o efeito de movimento da Tela inicial, corrige o problema de consumo anormal de energia em alguns cenários, aumenta a estabilidade do sistema e incorpora um patch de segurança.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Várias janelas">
<feature>As combinações de aplicativos no modo de tela dividida agora podem ser salvas. No modo de tela dividida, toque no botão no meio do divisor para salvar a combinação como um ícone na tela inicial. Tocar no ícone permite o acesso rápido à combinação.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>As marcas d'água agora podem ser adicionadas e removidas conforme desejado. Experimente-as acessando: Tirar uma foto > Abrir a foto > Editar > Marca d'água > Opções de marca d'água: Original, Marca d'água de texto, Marca d'água do quadro.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rastreamento ocular">
<feature>O Rastreamento ocular está incluído, permitindo um acesso rápido às notificações e ao conteúdo detalhado sem operação manual quando seus olhos estão diretamente voltados para a tela a uma distância de 20 a 50 cm. Experimente-o acessando: Configurações > Assistente > Rastreamento ocular.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Painel de notificações">
<feature>O layout do painel de notificações foi otimizado, tornando a interface mais simplificada e visualmente atraente.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efeito de movimento">
<feature>Otimiza a consistência do efeito de movimento na tela inicial.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de energia">
<feature>Corrige o problema de consumo anormal de energia em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Melhora a estabilidade do sistema para que seu dispositivo funcione de forma mais estável.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Patch de segurança do Android (agosto de 2024) incorporado para a segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite nosso site: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não apagará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, ligue para a linha de atendimento ao cliente da HONOR ou vá à central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro utilizador, com esta atualização recomendada, pode guardar combinações de aplicações no modo de ecrã dividido. Esta atualização também introduz o Rastreamento ocular e permite que as marcas de água sejam editadas. Adicionalmente, esta versão otimiza o efeito de exibição do painel de notificações e o efeito de movimento no ecrã inicial, corrige o problema do anormal consumo de energia em alguns cenários, melhora a estabilidade do sistema e integra uma correção de segurança.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multijanela">
<feature>As combinações de aplicações no modo de ecrã dividido podem agora ser guardadas. No modo de ecrã dividido, toque no botão no meio da divisória para guardar a combinação como um ícone no ecrã inicial. Tocar no ícone permite um acesso rápido à combinação.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeria">
<feature>As marcas de água podem agora ser adicionadas e removidas conforme pretendido. Experimente, acedendo a: Tirar uma fotografia > Abrir a fotografia > Editar > marca de água > Opções da marca de água: Original, Marca de água de texto, Marca de água na moldura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rastreamento ocular">
<feature>O Rastreamento ocular está incluído, permitindo um acesso rápido às notificações e ao conteúdo detalhado sem operação manual quando os seus olhos estão diretamente virados para o ecrã a uma distância de 20-50 cm. Experimente, acedendo a: Definições > Assistente > Rastreamento ocular.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Painel de notificações">
<feature>A disposição do painel de notificações está otimizada, tornando a interface mais simplificada e visualmente apelativa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efeito de movimento">
<feature>Otimiza a consistência do efeito de movimento no ecrã inicial.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consumo de energia">
<feature>Corrige o problema do consumo anormal de energia em alguns cenários.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Melhora a estabilidade do sistema para que o seu dispositivo funcione de forma mais estável.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Segurança">
<feature>Foi incorporada uma correção de segurança Android (agosto de 2024) para segurança do sistema. Para obter mais informações sobre as atualizações de segurança da HONOR, visite o nosso website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não apaga os seus dados pessoais, mas continua a recomendar-se a realização prévia de uma cópia de segurança.
2. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, ligue para a linha direta de assistência da HONOR ou dirija-se ao centro de apoio ao cliente HONOR para suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimate utilizator, cu această actualizare recomandată puteți salva combinații de aplicații în modul Ecran divizat. Această actualizare introduce, de asemenea, funcția Urmărire ochi și permite editarea inscripționărilor. În plus, această versiune optimizează efectul de afișare al panoului de notificări și efectul de mișcare pe ecranul de pornire, rezolvă problema consumului anormal de energie în anumite scenarii, îmbunătățește stabilitatea sistemului și încorporează o corecție de securitate.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ferestre multiple">
<feature>Combinațiile de aplicații în modul Ecran divizat pot fi acum salvate. În modul Ecran divizat, atingeți butonul din mijlocul separatorului pentru a salva combinația ca pictogramă pe ecranul de pornire. Atingerea pictogramei permite accesul rapid la combinație.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerie">
<feature>Inscripționările pot fi acum adăugate și eliminate după cum doriți. Puteți încerca această funcție în următorul mod: Faceți o fotografie > Deschideți fotografia > Editare > Inscripționare > Opțiuni inscripționare: Original, Inscripționare text, Inscripționare cadru.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Urmărire ochi">
<feature>Funcția Urmărire ochi este inclusă și permite accesul rapid la notificări și la conținutul detaliat fără operare manuală atunci când ochii dvs. sunt direct îndreptați spre ecran, la o distanță de 20-50 cm. O puteți încerca accesând: Setări > Asistent > Urmărire ochi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panou de notificări">
<feature>Aspectul panoului de notificări a fost optimizat, iar interfața este acum mai simplă și mai atractivă din punct de vedere vizual.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efect de mișcare">
<feature>Optimizează fluiditatea efectului de mișcare pe ecranul de start.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Consum de energie">
<feature>Rezolvă problema consumului anormal de energie în anumite scenarii.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Îmbunătățește stabilitatea sistemului pentru ca dispozitivul să funcționeze mai stabil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Securitate">
<feature>Corecția de securitate Android (august 2024) a fost inclusă pentru securitatea sistemului. Pentru mai multe informații despre actualizările de securitate HONOR, vizitați site-ul nostru web: https://www.honor.com/ro/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea actualizării nu va cauza ștergerea datelor dvs. personale, dar vă recomandăm totuși să realizați în prealabil o copie de rezervă.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, apelați linia de asistență HONOR sau vizitați centrul de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь, после установки этого рекомендуемого обновления вы сможете сохранять комбинации приложений в режиме нескольких окон. Это обновление также добавляет функцию «Отслеживание взгляда» и возможность редактировать водяные знаки. Кроме того, этот выпуск оптимизирует эффекты отображения панели уведомлений и эффект движения на рабочем экране, исправляет проблему нехарактерного энергопотребления в некоторых сценариях, повышает стабильность системы и включает исправление безопасности.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Мультиоконный режим">
<feature>Теперь можно сохранять комбинации приложений в режиме нескольких окон. В режиме нескольких окон нажмите кнопку в середине разделителя, чтобы сохранить комбинацию в виде значка на рабочем экране. Нажатие на значок предоставит быстрый доступ к комбинации.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерея">
<feature>Водяные знаки теперь можно добавлять и удалять по желанию. Чтобы попробовать, перейдите в раздел «Сделать снимок > Открыть фото > Изменить > Водяной знак > Параметры водяного знака»: «Оригинал», «Водяной знак с текстом», «Водяной знак в кадре».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Отслеживание взгляда">
<feature>Добавлена функция «Отслеживание взгляда», которая обеспечивает быстрый доступ к уведомлениям и подробному контенту без ручного управления, когда ваши глаза смотрят прямо на экран на расстоянии 20–50 см. Чтобы попробовать, перейдите в раздел «Настройки > Ассистент > Отслеживание взгляда».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Панель уведомлений">
<feature>Оптимизировано расположение панели уведомлений, что делает интерфейс более удобным и визуально привлекательным.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Эффект движения">
<feature>Оптимизирована согласованность эффекта движения на рабочем экране.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Энергопотребление">
<feature>Устранена проблема, связанная с некорректным энергопотреблением в некоторых сценариях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>Улучшена стабильность системы и, соответственно, работа вашего устройства.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безопасность">
<feature>В обновление включено исправление безопасности для Android (август 2024 г.). Чтобы получить подробную информацию об обновлениях безопасности HONOR, посетите наш сайт: https://www.honor.com/ru/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не приведет к удалению ваших персональных данных, но мы рекомендуем сделать резервную копию всех важных данных, прежде чем приступить к установке.
2. При возникновении проблем во время обновления обратитесь за помощью на горячую линию службы поддержки HONOR или в сервисный центр для клиентов HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම නිර්දේශිත යාවත්කාලය මගින්, ඔබට බෙදුම් තිර ප්‍රකාරයේ යෙදුම් සංයෝජන සුරකින්නට හැකි වේ. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ඇස ලුහුබැඳීම ද හඳුන්වාදෙන අතර, දිය සලකුණු සංස්කරණය කිරීමට ඉඩ දෙයි. අමතරව, මෙම නිකුතුව දැනුම්දීම් පැනලයේ සංදර්ශක ප්‍රයෝගය සහ මුල් තිරයේ චලන ප්‍රයෝගය ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි, සමහර අවස්ථාවල දී අසාමාන්‍ය බල පරිභෝජන ගැටළුව නිරාකරණය කරයි, පද්ධතියේ ස්ථායීතාව වැඩි දියුණු කරයි, සහ ආරක්ෂක පැච් එකක් ඇතුළත් කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="බහු කවුළුව">
<feature>බෙදුම් තිර ප්‍රකාරයේ යෙදුම් ඒකාබද්ධ දැන් සුරැකිය හැකිවනු ඇත. බෙදුම් තිරය ප්‍රකාරයේ දී, ඒකාබද්ධය මුල් තිරයේ අයිකනයක් ලෙස සුරැකීමට බෙදනයේ මැද ඇති බොත්තම තට්ටු කරන්න. අයිකනය තට්ටු කිරීම ඒකාබද්ධයට ඉක්මන් පිවිසීම සක්‍රිය කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ගැලරිය">
<feature>දැන් දිය සලකුණු අවශ්‍ය පරිදි එක් කිරීමට සහ ඉවත් කිරීමට හැකිවනු ඇත. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය අත්විඳින්න: ඡායාරූපයක් ගන්න > ඡායාරූපය විවෘත කරන්න > සංස්කරණය කරන්න > දිය සලකුණ > දිය සලකුණු විකල්ප: මුල්, පෙළ දිය සලකුණ, රාමු දිය සලකුණ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ඇස ලුහුබැඳීම">
<feature>ඔබේ ඇස් සෙ.මී. 20-50 දුරකින් තිරයට සෘජුව මුහුණ ලා ඇති විට හස්තීයව ක්‍රියා කිරීමෙන් තොරව දැනුම්දීම් සහ සවිස්තරාත්මක අන්තර්ගතය වෙත ඉක්මන් පිවිසීම ලබා දෙන ඇස ලුහුබැඳීම ඇතුළත් වේ. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය අත්විඳින්න: සැකසුම් > සහායක > ඇස ලුහුබැඳීම.</feature>
</features>
<features module="දැනුම්දීම් පැනලය">
<feature>අතුරු මුහුණත වඩා විධිමත් සහ දෘශ්‍යමය වශයෙන් සිත්ගන්නා සුළු කරමින් දැනුම්දීම් පැනලයේ පිරිසැලසුම ප්‍රශස්ත කර ඇත.</feature>
</features>
<features module="චලන ප්‍රයෝගය">
<feature>මුල් තිරයේ චලන ප්‍රයෝගයේ අනුකූලතාවය ප්‍රශස්ත කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="බල පරිභෝජනය">
<feature>සමහර අවස්ථාවල දී අසාමාන්‍ය බල පරිභෝජන ගැටළුව නිරාකරණය කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="පද්ධතිය">
<feature>ඔබගේ උපාංගය වඩා ස්ථායීව ධාවනය කරවීමට පද්ධතියේ ස්ථායිතාවය වැඩිදියුණු කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ආරක්ෂාව">
<feature>පද්ධති ආරක්ෂාව සඳහා Android ආරක්ෂක පැච් එක (2024 අගෝ) යොදාගෙන ඇත. HONOR ආරක්ෂක යාවත්කාල පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු සඳහා, කරුණාකර අපගේ වෙබ් අඩවිය වෙත යන්න https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්ත නොමකනු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් ඊට පෙර උපස්ථ කිරීමක් නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේ දී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, කරුණාකර HONOR සේවා ක්ෂණික ඇමතුම් අමතන්න නැතහොත් සහය සඳහා HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට යන්න.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený používateľ, s touto odporúčanou aktualizáciou môžete ukladať kombinácie aplikácií v režime rozdelenej obrazovky. Táto aktualizácia tiež zavádza funkciu Sledovanie očí a umožňuje úpravu vodotlače. Toto vydanie navyše optimalizuje efekt zobrazenia panela upozornení a efekt pohybu na domovskej obrazovke, rieši problém neobvyklej spotreby energie v niektorých scenároch, zlepšuje stabilitu systému a obsahuje bezpečnostnú opravu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Viacero okien">
<feature>Kombinácie aplikácií v režime rozdelenej obrazovky možno teraz uložiť. V režime rozdelenej obrazovky ťuknite na tlačidlo v strede oddeľovača, čím kombináciu uložíte ako ikonu na domovskej obrazovke. Ťuknutím na ikonu získate rýchly prístup ku kombinácii.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galéria">
<feature>Vodotlače možno pridávať a odstraňovať podľa potreby. Vyskúšajte to podľa tohto postupu: nasnímajte fotografiu > otvorte fotografiu > Upraviť > Vodotlač > Možnosti vodotlače: Originál, Textová vodotlač, Rámová vodotlač.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sledovanie očí">
<feature>Súčasťou je funkcia Sledovanie očí, ktorá umožňuje rýchly prístup k upozorneniam a podrobnému obsahu bez manuálneho ovládania, keď sú vaše oči otočené priamo k obrazovke vo vzdialenosti 20 až 50 cm. Vyskúšajte ju v časti: Nastavenia > Asistent > Sledovanie očí.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Panel upozornení">
<feature>Rozloženie panela upozornení je optimalizované, vďaka čomu je rozhranie efektívnejšie a vizuálne príťažlivejšie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Efekt pohybu">
<feature>Optimalizuje konzistenciu efektu pohybu na domovskej obrazovke.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Spotreba energie">
<feature>Rieši problém neobvyklej spotreby energie v niektorých scenároch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Zlepšuje stabilitu systému, vďaka čomu zariadenie funguje stabilnejšie.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zabezpečenie">
<feature>Súčasťou zabezpečenia systému je bezpečnostná oprava systému Android (z augusta 2024). Ak potrebujete viac informácií o bezpečnostných aktualizáciách spoločnosti HONOR, navštívte webovú stránku https://www.honor.com/sk/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštaláciou tejto aktualizácie nevymažete svoje osobné údaje, ale napriek tomu sa odporúča ich vopred zálohovať.
2. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytnú problémy, podporu môžete získať zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo návštevou Centra služieb zákazníkom HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, s to priporočeno posodobitvijo lahko shranite kombinacije aplikacij v načinu razdeljenega zaslona. Ta posodobitev uvaja tudi funkcijo Sledenje očem in omogoča urejanje vodnih žigov. V tej izdaji sta optimizirana tudi učinek prikaza podokna z obvestili in učinek gibanja na začetnem zaslonu, odpravljena je težava neobičajne porabe energije v nekaterih situacijah, izboljšana je stabilnost sistema in vključen je varnostni popravek.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Več oken">
<feature>Kombinacijo aplikacij v načinu razdeljenega zaslona je zdaj mogoče shraniti. V načinu razdeljenega zaslona se dotaknite gumba na sredini separatorja, da shranite kombinacijo kot ikono na začetnem zaslonu. Z dotikom ikone lahko hitro dostopate do kombinacije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galerija">
<feature>Vodne žige je zdaj mogoče po želji dodati in odstraniti. Izkusite jih na naslednji način: zajemite fotografijo > odprite fotografijo > Uredi > Vodni žig > Možnosti vodnega žiga so: Izvirna slika, Besedilni vodni žig, Vodni žig z okvirjem.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sledenje očem">
<feature>Vključena je funkcija Sledenje očem, ki omogoča hiter dostop do obvestil in podrobne vsebine brez ročnega upravljanja, ko vaše oči gledajo neposredno v zaslon z razdalje 20–50 cm. Izkusite jo tako, da odprete: Nastavitve > Pomočnik > Sledenje očem.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Podokno z obvestili">
<feature>Postavitev podokna z obvestili je optimizirana, zaradi česar je vmesnik učinkovitejši in vizualno privlačnejši.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Učinek gibanja">
<feature>Optimizirana je doslednost učinka gibanja na začetnem zaslonu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poraba energije">
<feature>Odpravljena je težava neobičajne porabe energije v nekaterih situacijah.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Izboljšana je stabilnost sistema za stabilnejše delovanje naprave.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Varnost">
<feature>Varnostni popravki za Android (avgust 2024) so vključeni za varnost sistema. Za več informacij o varnostnih posodobitvah HONOR obiščite spletno mesto https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Z namestitvijo te posodobitve vaši osebni podatki ne bodo izbrisani, vendar vseeno priporočamo, da jih predhodno varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodabljanjem naletite na težave, lahko pokličete odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom družbe HONOR ali obiščete središče za storitve družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, med den här rekommenderade uppdateringen kan du spara appkombinationer i delat skärmläge. Den här uppdateringen introducerar också Ögonspårning och tillåter att vattenstämplar redigeras. I den här utgåvan optimeras dessutom aviseringspanelens visningseffekt och startsidans rörelseeffekt, problemet med onormal energiförbrukning i vissa scenarier åtgärdas, systemets stabilitet förbättras och en säkerhetskorrigering implementeras.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Flera fönster">
<feature>Appkombinationer i delat skärmläge kan nu sparas. Tryck på knappen i mitten av delaren i det delade skärmläget för att spara kombinationen som en ikon på startsidan. Ett tryck på ikonen ger snabbåtkomst till kombinationen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galleri">
<feature>Vattenstämplar kan nu läggas till och tas bort efter önskemål. Prova genom att gå till: Ta ett foto > Öppna fotot > Redigera > Vattenstämpel > Vattenstämpelalternativ: Original, Textvattenstämpel, Vattenstämpel med ram.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ögonspårning">
<feature>Ögonspårning ingår, vilket ger snabbåtkomst till aviseringarna och det detaljerade innehållet utan manuell åtgärd om dina ögon är vända direkt mot skärmen på 20–50 cm avstånd. Prova genom att gå till: Inställningar > Assistent > Ögonspårning.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aviseringspanelen">
<feature>Layouten i aviseringspanelen är optimerad, vilket gör gränssnittet mer rationellt och visuellt tilltalande.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rörelseeffekt">
<feature>Optimerar rörelseeffektens enhetlighet på startsidan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Energiförbrukning">
<feature>Åtgärdar problemet med onormal energiförbrukning i vissa scenarier.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Förbättrar systemets stabilitet så att enheten körs stabilare.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Säkerhet">
<feature>Android-säkerhetskorrigeringen (augusti 2024) har implementerats för systemsäkerhet. Vill du ha mer information om säkerhetsuppdateringar för HONOR går du till vår webbplats https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Den här uppdateringen raderar inga personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du gör en säkerhetskopia innan du installerar den.
2. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs servicecenter och få support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, kwa sasisho hili linalopendekezwa, unaweza kuhifadhi mikusanyiko ya programu katika hali ya ugawaji skrini. Sasisho hili pia linaleta Ufuatiliaji wa Macho na linawezesha alama fifi kuharirirwa. Pia, toleo hili linaboresha athari ya onyesho la paneli ya taarifa na athari ya mwendo kwenye skrini ya mwanzo, linarekebisha tatizo la utumiaji nishati usio wa kawaida katika baadhi ya miktadha, linaboresha uthabiti wa mfumo na linajumuisha rekebisho la usalama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madirisha Kadhaa">
<feature>Mikusanyiko ya programu katika hali ya ugawaji skrini sasa inaweza kuhifadhiwa. Katika hali ya ugawaji skrini, gusa kitufe kilicho katikati ya kitenganishi ili kuhifadhi mkusanyiko kama aikoni kwenye skrini ya mwanzo. Kugusa aikoni huwezesha ufikiaji wa haraka wa mkusanyiko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Matunzio">
<feature>Alama fifi sasa zinaweza kuongezwa na kuondolewa kama upendavyo. Furahia kwa kwenda kwenye: Piga picha > Fungua picha > Hariri > Alama fifi > Machaguo ya alama fifi: Asilia, Alama fifi ya maandishi, Alama fifi ya fremu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ufuatiliaji wa Macho">
<feature>Ufuatiliaji wa Macho umejumuishwa, hivyo basi kuwezesha ufikiaji wa haraka wa taarifa na maudhui ya kina bila mchakato wa kimkono wakati macho yako yanaangalia skrini moja kwa moja katika umbali wa sentimita 20-50. Ufurahie kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio > Kisaidizi > Ufuatiliaji wa Macho.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Paneli ya taarifa">
<feature>Ruwaza ya paneli ya taarifa imeboreshwa, hivyo basi kufanya kiolesura kuboreshwa na kupendeza zaidi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Athari ya mwendo">
<feature>Huboresha uthabiti wa athari ya mwendo kwenye skrini ya mwanzo.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Utumiaji nishati">
<feature>Linarekebisha tatizo la utumiaji nishati usio wa kawaida katika baadhi ya miktadha.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mfumo">
<feature>Linaboresa uthabiti wa mfumo ili kufanya kifaa chako kiendeshwe kwa uthabiti zaidi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Usalama">
<feature>Rekebisho la usalama wa Android (Ago 2024) limejumuishwa kwa ajili ya usalama wa mfumo. Ili kupata maelezo zaidi kuhusu masasisho ya Usalama wa HONOR, tafadhali tembelea tovuti yetu: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutafuta data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini hifadhi rudufu kabla ya kusakinisha bado inapendekezwa.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, tafadhali piga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au nenda kwenye kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha HONOR ili upate usaidizi.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்பார்ந்த பயனரே, இந்தப் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படும் புதுப்பிப்பு மூலம் நீங்கள் திரைப் பிரிப்புப் பயன்முறையில் செயலிக் கலவைகளைச் சேமிக்கலாம். இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு பார்வைத் தடமறிதலை அறிமுகப்படுத்துகிறது, வாட்டர்மார்க்குகளைத் திருத்த அனுமதிக்கிறது. கூடுதலாக, இந்த வெளியீடு முகப்புத் திரையில் அறிவிப்பு பேனலில் காட்சி விளைவு மற்றும் இயக்க விளைவை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது, சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் ஏற்படும் அசாதாரண மின் நுகர்வுச் சிக்கலைச் சரிசெய்கிறது, சிஸ்டம் செயல்திறனை மேம்படுத்துகிறது மற்றும் பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பைக் கொண்டுள்ளது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பல சாளரம்">
<feature>திரைப் பிரிப்புப் பயன்முறையில் செயலிக் கலவைகளை இப்போது சேமிக்கலாம். திரைப் பிரிப்புப் பயன்முறையில், முகப்புத் திரையில் கலவையை ஓர் ஐகானாகச் சேமிக்க டிவைடரின் நடுப்பகுதியில் உள்ள பொத்தானைத் தட்டவும். ஐகானைத் தட்டுவது கலவைக்கான விரைவு அணுகலைச் செயல்படுத்துகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="கேலரி">
<feature>வாட்டர்மார்க்குகளை இப்போது விரும்பியபடி சேர்க்கலாம் மற்றும் அகற்றலாம். இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதைப் பயன்படுத்தவும்: புகைப்படத்தை எடுக்கவும் > புகைப்படத்தைத் திறக்கவும் > திருத்து > வாட்டர்மார்க் > வாட்டர்மார்க் விருப்பங்கள்: அசல், உரை வாட்டர்மார்க், ஃபிரேம் வாட்டர்மார்க்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பார்வைத் தடமறிதல்">
<feature>பார்வைத் தடமறிதல் சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது, இது உங்கள் கண்கள் 20-50 cm தொலைவில் திரையை நேரடியாகப் பார்க்கும்போது கைமுறைச் செயல்பாடு இல்லாமல் அறிவிப்புகள் மற்றும் விரிவான உள்ளடக்கத்திற்கான விரைவு அணுகலை அனுமதிக்கிறது. இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் அதைப் பயன்படுத்தவும்: அமைப்புகள் > உதவியாளர் > பார்வைத் தடமறிதல்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="அறிவிப்பு பேனல்">
<feature>அறிவிப்பு பேனலின் தளவமைப்பு உகந்ததாக்கப்பட்டுள்ளது, இது இடைமுகத்தை மிகவும் நெறிப்படுத்தியும், பார்வைக்குச் சிறப்பாகத் தோன்றும்படியும் செய்கிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="இயக்க விளைவு">
<feature>முகப்புத் திரையில் இயக்க விளைவின் நிலைத்தன்மையை உகந்ததாக்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="மின் நுகர்வு">
<feature>சில சூழ்நிலைகளில் அசாதாரண மின் நுகர்வுச் சிக்கலைச் சரிசெய்கிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="சிஸ்டம்">
<feature>உங்கள் சாதனத்தை மேலும் நிலையாக இயங்கச் செய்ய, சிஸ்டம் நிலைத்தன்மையை மேம்படுத்துகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="பாதுகாப்பு">
<feature>சிஸ்டம் பாதுகாப்பிற்காக Android பாதுகாப்புத் தொகுப்பு (ஆக 2024) சேர்க்கப்பட்டுள்ளது. HONOR பாதுகாப்புப் புதுப்பிப்புகளைப் பற்றிய மேலும் தகவல்களுக்கு, எங்கள் வலைத்தளத்தைப் பார்க்கவும்: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவை அழிக்காது, எனினும் தொடர்வதற்கு முன் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுக்குமாறு பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், உதவிக்காக HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைக்கவும் அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்லவும்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారు, ఈ సిఫార్సు చేసిన అప్‌డేట్‌తో, మీరు స్ప్లిట్-స్క్రీన్ మోడ్‌లో అప్లికేషన్‌ కాంబినేషన్‌లను సేవ్ చేయవచ్చు. ఈ అప్డేట్ కళ్ల ట్రాకింగ్ను కూడా పరిచయం చేస్తుంది మరియు వాటర్‌మార్క్‌లను సవరించడానికి అనుమతిస్తుంది. అదనంగా, ఈ విడుదల నోటిఫికేషన్ ప్యానెల్ యొక్క ప్రదర్శన ప్రభావాన్ని మరియు హోమ్ స్క్రీన్‌పై చలన ప్రభావాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది, కొన్ని దృశ్యాలలో అసాధారణ విద్యుత్ వినియోగం సమస్యను పరిష్కరిస్తుంది, సిస్టమ్ స్థిరత్వాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది మరియు భద్రతా ప్యాచ్‌ను కలిగి ఉంటుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="బహుళ-విండో">
<feature>స్ప్లిట్-స్క్రీన్ మోడ్‌లో అప్లికేషన్ కలయికలను ఇప్పుడు సేవ్ చేయవచ్చు. స్ప్లిట్-స్క్రీన్ మోడ్‌లో, హోమ్ స్క్రీన్‌పై కలయికను ఒక చిహ్నం వలె సేవ్ చేయడానికి డివైడర్ మధ్యలోని బటన్‌ను ట్యాప్ చేయండి. ఐకాన్‌ను ట్యాప్ చేయడం వలన కలయికకు త్వరిత యాక్సెస్ లభిస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="గ్యాలరీ">
<feature>వాటర్‌మార్క్‌లను ఇప్పుడు కావల్సిన విధంగా జోడించవచ్చు మరియు తీసివేయవచ్చు. దీనిని ఇక్కడ ప్రయత్నించండి: ఫోటో తీయండి > ఫోటోను తెరవండి > సవరించు > వాటర్‌మార్క్ > వాటర్‌మార్క్ ఎంపికలు: అసలు, టెక్స్ట్ వాటర్‌మార్క్, ఫ్రేమ్ వాటర్‌మార్క్.</feature>
</features>
<features module="కళ్ల ట్రాకింగ్">
<feature>కళ్ల ట్రాకింగ్ అందుబాటులో ఉంది, ఇది మీరు 20-50 సెమీ దూరంలో స్క్రీన్‌ను మీ కళ్లతో నేరుగా చూస్తున్నప్పుడు మాన్యువల్ ఆపరేషన్ లేకుండానే నోటిఫికేషన్‌లు మరియు వివరణాత్మక కంటెంట్‌కు త్వరిత యాక్సెస్ అందిస్తుంది. దీనిని ఇక్కడ ప్రయత్నించండి: సెట్టింగ్‌లు > సహాయకం > కళ్ల ట్రాకింగ్.</feature>
</features>
<features module="నోటిఫికేషన్ ప్యానెల్">
<feature>నోటిఫికేషన్ ప్యానెల్ లేఅవుట్ ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేయబడింది, దీని వలన ఇంటర్‌ఫేస్ మరింత సరళంగా మరియు చూడటానికి అందంగా కనిపిస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="చలన ప్రభావం">
<feature>హోమ్ స్క్రీన్‌పై చలన ప్రభావాన్ని స్థిరత్వాన్ని ఆప్టిమైజ్ చేస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="పవర్ వాడకం">
<feature>కొన్ని సందర్భాల్లో అసాధారణ పవర్ వినియోగం సమస్యను పరిష్కరిస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="సిస్టమ్">
<feature>మీ పరికరం మరింత స్థిరంగా అమలు అయ్యేలా చేయడానికి సిస్టమ్ స్థిరత్వాన్ని మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="భద్రత">
<feature>సిస్టమ్ భద్రత కోసం Android భద్రతా ప్యాచ్ (ఆగష్టు 2024) చేర్చబడింది. HONOR భద్రత అప్‌డేట్‌ల గురించి మరింత సమాచారం కోసం, దయచేసి మా వెబ్‌సైట్‌ సందర్శించండి https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వలన మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటా ఎరేజ్ చేయబడదు, కాని ముందుగా ఒక బ్యాకప్ తీసుకోవాలని సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీరు ఏవైనా సమస్యలను ఎదుర్కొంటే, దయచేసి మద్దతు కోసం HONOR సర్వీసు హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయండి లేదా HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి వెళ్ళండి.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ ด้วยการอัปเดตที่แนะนำนี้ คุณจะสามารถบันทึกชุดของแอปในโหมดการแบ่งหน้าจอได้ การอัปเดตนี้ยังได้เพิ่มการติดตามสายตาเข้ามา และอนุญาตให้แก้ไขลายน้ำได้ด้วย นอกจากนี้ รีลีสนี้ยังเพิ่มประสิทธิภาพเอฟเฟ็กต์การแสดงผลของแผงการแจ้งเตือนและเอฟเฟ็กต์การเคลื่อนไหวบนหน้าจอหลัก แก้ไขปัญหาการใช้พลังงานที่ผิดปกติในบางสถานการณ์ ปรับปรุงความเสถียรของระบบ และรวมแพตช์ความปลอดภัย</feature>
</features>
<features module="หลายหน้าต่าง">
<feature>บันทึกชุดของแอปในโหมดการแบ่งหน้าจอได้แล้วในตอนนี้ ในโหมดการแบ่งหน้าจอ แตะปุ่มที่ตรงกลางของตัวแบ่งเพื่อบันทึกชุดเป็นไอคอนบนหน้าจอหลัก แตะไอคอนเพื่อเปิดใช้งานการเข้าถึงด่วนถึงชุด</feature>
</features>
<features module="แกลเลอรี">
<feature>เพิ่มและลบลายน้ำออกได้ตามต้องการ สัมผัสได้โดยไปที่: ถ่ายภาพถ่าย > เปิดภาพถ่าย > แก้ไข > ลายน้ำ > ตัวเลือกลายน้ำ: ต้นฉบับ, ลายน้ำข้อความ, ลายน้ำที่เป็นกรอบรูป</feature>
</features>
<features module="การติดตามสายตา">
<feature>รวมการติดตามสายตา ช่วยให้การเข้าถึงด่วนถึงการแจ้งเตือนและเนื้อหาอย่างละเอียดโดยไม่ต้องดำเนินการด้วยตนเองเมื่อดวงตาของคุณมองหน้าจอโดยตรงในระยะ 20-50 ซม. สัมผัสได้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า > ผู้ช่วย > การติดตามสายตา</feature>
</features>
<features module="แผงการแจ้งเตือน">
<feature>ปรับปรุงเลย์เอาต์ของแผงการแจ้งเตือนแล้ว ทำให้อินเทอร์เฟซใช้ง่ายขึ้นและสวยสะดุดตายิ่งขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="เอฟเฟ็กต์การเคลื่อนไหว">
<feature>ปรับปรุงความสอดคล้องของเอฟเฟ็กต์การเคลื่อนไหวบนหน้าจอหลัก</feature>
</features>
<features module="การใช้พลังงาน">
<feature>แก้ไขปัญหาการใช้พลังงานผิดปกติในบางสถานการณ์</feature>
</features>
<features module="ระบบ">
<feature>ปรับปรุงความเสถียรของระบบเพื่อให้อุปกรณ์ของคุณใช้งานได้อย่างเสถียรมากขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="ความปลอดภัย">
<feature>มีการรวมแพตช์การรักษาความปลอดภัยของ Android (ส.ค. 2024) เพื่อการรักษาความปลอดภัยของระบบ ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับการอัปเดตการรักษาความปลอดภัยของ HONOR ได้ในเว็บไซต์ของเรา https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="โปรดทราบ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่ลบข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เรายังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลล่วงหน้า
2. หากคุณพบปัญหาใด ๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต โปรดโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการของ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ HONOR เพื่อขอการสนับสนุน</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, sa inirerekomendang update na ito, puwede kang mag-save ng mga kumbinasyon ng app sa split-screen mode. Ipinapakilala rin ng update na ito ang Pagsubaybay sa Mata, at nagbibigay-daang ma-edit ang mga watermark. Bukod pa rito, ino-optimize ng release na ito ang effect sa display ng notification panel at effect sa paggalaw sa home screen, inaayos ang isyu ng hindi normal na pagkonsumo ng baterya sa ilang sitwasyon, pinapahusay ang stability ng system, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Puwede nang i-save ang mga kumbinasyon ng app sa split-screen mode. Sa split-screen mode, i-tap ang button sa gitna ng divider para i-save ang kumbinasyon bilang isang icon sa home screen. Nagbibigay-daan sa mabilisang pag-access sa kumbinasyon kapag na-tap ang icon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Puwede nang idagdag at alisin ang mga watermark kung kailangan. Maranasan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Kumuha ng larawan > Buksan ang larawan > I-edit > Watermark > Mga opsyon ng watermark: Orihinal, Watermark na text, Watermark na frame.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pagsubaybay sa Mata">
<feature>Kasama ang Pagsubaybay sa Mata, na nagbibigay ng mabilisang pag-access sa mga notification at detalyadong content nang walang manual na pagpapatakbo kapag direktang nakaharap ang iyong mga mata sa screen sa distansyang 20-50 cm. Maranasan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Assistant > Pagsubaybay sa Mata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notification panel">
<feature>Naka-optimize ang layout ng notification panel, na ginagawang mas simple at maganda sa paningin ang interface.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Effect sa paggalaw">
<feature>Ino-optimize ang pagiging consistent ng effect sa paggalaw sa home screen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pagkonsumo ng baterya">
<feature>Inaayos ang isyu ng hindi normal na pagkonsumo ng baterya sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Pinapahusay ang stability ng system para magawang tumakbo nang mas stable ang iyong device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Ago 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi mabubura ang iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa rin ang isang pag-back up bago gawin ito.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, sa inirerekomendang update na ito, puwede kang mag-save ng mga kumbinasyon ng app sa split-screen mode. Ipinapakilala rin ng update na ito ang Pagsubaybay sa Mata, at nagbibigay-daang ma-edit ang mga watermark. Bukod pa rito, ino-optimize ng release na ito ang effect sa display ng notification panel at effect sa paggalaw sa home screen, inaayos ang isyu ng hindi normal na pagkonsumo ng baterya sa ilang sitwasyon, pinapahusay ang stability ng system, at isinasama ang isang panseguridad na patch.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Multi-Window">
<feature>Puwede nang i-save ang mga kumbinasyon ng app sa split-screen mode. Sa split-screen mode, i-tap ang button sa gitna ng divider para i-save ang kumbinasyon bilang isang icon sa home screen. Nagbibigay-daan sa mabilisang pag-access sa kumbinasyon kapag na-tap ang icon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Gallery">
<feature>Puwede nang idagdag at alisin ang mga watermark kung kailangan. Maranasan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Kumuha ng larawan > Buksan ang larawan > I-edit > Watermark > Mga opsyon ng watermark: Orihinal, Watermark na text, Watermark na frame.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pagsubaybay sa Mata">
<feature>Kasama ang Pagsubaybay sa Mata, na nagbibigay ng mabilisang pag-access sa mga notification at detalyadong content nang walang manual na pagpapatakbo kapag direktang nakaharap ang iyong mga mata sa screen sa distansyang 20-50 cm. Maranasan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Assistant > Pagsubaybay sa Mata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notification panel">
<feature>Naka-optimize ang layout ng notification panel, na ginagawang mas simple at maganda sa paningin ang interface.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Effect sa paggalaw">
<feature>Ino-optimize ang pagiging consistent ng effect sa paggalaw sa home screen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pagkonsumo ng baterya">
<feature>Inaayos ang isyu ng hindi normal na pagkonsumo ng baterya sa ilang sitwasyon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Pinapahusay ang stability ng system para magawang tumakbo nang mas stable ang iyong device.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Seguridad">
<feature>Isinama ang panseguridad na patch ng Android (Ago 2024) para sa seguridad ng system. Para sa higit pang impormasyon tungkol sa Mga panseguridad na update ng HONOR, pakibisita ang aming website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi mabubura ang iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa rin ang isang pag-back up bago gawin ito.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sayın kullanıcı, bu önerilen güncelleme ile çeşitli uygulama kombinasyonlarını bölünmüş ekran modunda kaydedebilirsiniz. Güncelleme ayrıca Göz Takibi özelliğini getiriyor ve filigranların düzenlenmesine olanak tanıyor. Bu sürüm, bildirim panelinin görüntü efektlerini ve ana ekrandaki hareket efektlerini optimize eder, bazı senaryolarda yaşanan anormal güç tüketimi sorununu düzeltir, sistem kararlılığını iyileştirir ve bir güvenlik yaması içerir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Çoklu Pencere">
<feature>Bölünmüş ekran modundaki uygulama kombinasyonları artık kaydedilebilir. Bölünmüş ekran modunda, kombinasyonu başlangıç ekranında bir simge olarak kaydetmek için ayırıcının ortasındaki düğmeye dokunun. Simgeye dokunarak kombinasyona hızlı erişim sağlayabilirsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galeri">
<feature>Filigranlar artık istenildiği gibi eklenebilir ve kaldırılabilir. Bu işlevi şuraya giderek deneyimleyebilirsiniz: Fotoğraf çek > Fotoğrafı aç > Düzenle > Filigran > Filigran seçenekleri: Orijinal, Metin filigranı, Çerçeve filigranı.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Göz Takibi">
<feature>Göz Takibi özelliği, gözleriniz 20-50 cm mesafede doğrudan ekrana bakarken manuel işlem yapmadan bildirimlere ve ayrıntılı içeriğe hızlı bir şekilde erişmenizi sağlar. Bu işlevi şuraya giderek deneyimleyebilirsiniz: Ayarlar > Asistan > Göz Takibi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bildirim paneli">
<feature>Bildirim panelinin düzeni optimize edilerek arayüz daha akıcı ve görsel olarak çekici hale getirilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hareket efekti">
<feature>Başlangıç ekranındaki hareket efekti tutarlılığı optimize edildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güç tüketimi">
<feature>Bazı durumlarda anormal güç tüketimi sorunu düzeltildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Sistem kararlılığı iyileştirilerek cihazınız daha kararlı hale getirilmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Güvenlik">
<feature>Sistem güvenliği için Android güvenlik yamasını (Ağustos 2024) içermektedir. HONOR Güvenlik güncellemeleri ile ilgili daha fazla bilgi için lütfen web sitemizi ziyaret edin: https://www.honor.com/tr/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi silmeyecektir, fakat yine de öncesinde yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşmanız durumunda destek için lütfen HONOR servisi yardım hattını arayın veya HONOR müşteri hizmetleri merkezlerinden birine gidin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>‏ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا ئېكران بۆلۈشنى ساقلاش، كامېرانىڭ سۇباسمىسىنى تەھرىرلەش ۋە كۆز ئىزلاش يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ئۇقتۇرۇش بالدىقىنىڭ كۆرسىتىش ئۈنۈمى ۋە ئۈستەليۈزىنىڭ ھەرىكەت ئۈنۈمى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلۇپ، بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى بىنورمال توك خوراش مەسىلىسى ئوڭشالدى، سىستېمىنىڭ مۇقىملىقى ئۆستۈرۈلۈپ، بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«كۆپ كۆزنەك»">
<feature>‏ئېكران بۆلۈشنى ساقلاش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ئېكران بۆلۈش ھالىتىدە ئېكران بۆلۈش سىزىقىنىڭ ئوتتۇرىدىكى كۇنۇپكىنى چەكسىڭىز، ئېكران بۆلۈش بىرىكمىسى سىنبەلگە شەكلىدە ئۈستەليۈزىگە ساقلىنىدۇ، كېيىن بۇ سىنبەلگىنى چېكىش ئارقىلىق بۇ ئېكران بۆلۈش بىرىكمىسىنى تېزلىكتە ئاچسىڭىز بولىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«ئامبار»">
<feature>‏كامېرا سۇباسمىسىنى تەھرىرلەش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، سۇ باسمىنى ئۆزىڭىز قوشسىڭىز ۋە ئەسلىگە كەلتۈرسىڭىز بولىدۇ، سىناش يولى: رەسىمگە تارتىش > رەسىمنى ئېچىش > تەھرىرلەش > سۇباسما > سۇباسما دېگەن ئورۇندىن تۆۋەندىكىلەرنى تاللاڭ: ئەسلى رەسىم، تېكىست سۇباسما، رامكا سۇباسما.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«كۆز ئىزلاش»">
<feature>‏كۆز ئىزلاش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، كۆز بىلەن ئېكراننىڭ ئارىلىقى 20~50 سانتىمېتىر بولغاندا ئېكرانغا تىكىلىپ قارىسىڭىز، ھېچقانداق قول مەشغۇلاتى ئىشلەتمەيلا، تىكىلىپ قاراش ئارقىلىق مۇناسىۋەتلىك پىلاكات ئۇقتۇرۇشىنى تېزلىكتە ئاچالايسىز ياكى تەپسىلىي مەزمۇنىنى كۆرەلەيسىز، سىناش يولى: تەڭشەك > ئاڭلىق ياردەمچى > كۆز ئىزلاش.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«ئۇقتۇرۇش بالدىقى»">
<feature>‏ئۇقتۇرۇش بالدىقىنىڭ ئورۇنلاشتۇرۇلۇشى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى، ئارايۈز تېخىمۇ رەتلىك ۋە چىرايلىق كۆرۈنىدىغان بولدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«ھەرىكەت ئۈنۈمى»">
<feature>‏ئۈستەليۈزى ھەرىكەت ئۈنۈمىنىڭ بىردەكلىكى ئەلالاشتۇرۇلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«توك سەرپىياتى»">
<feature>‏بىر قىسىم كۆرۈنۈشلەردىكى بىنورمال توك خوراش مەسىلىسى ئوڭشالدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«سىستېما»">
<feature>‏سىستېمىنىڭ مۇقىملىقى ئۆستۈرۈلۈپ، يانفونىڭىزنىڭ ئىجرا قىلىنىشى تېخىمۇ مۇقىملاشتۇرۇلدى.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«بىخەتەرلىك»">
<feature>‏ئاندرويدنىڭ 2024-يىل 8-ئايلىق بىخەتەرلىك يامىقى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، سىستېما بىخەتەرلىكى كۈچەيتىلدى. روڭياۋ يۇمشاق دېتالىنىڭ بىخەتەرلىك يېڭىلاش مەزمۇنىغا ئالاقىدار ئۇچۇرلار ئۈچۈن روڭياۋ ئورگان تەرەپ تور بېكىتىنى زىيارەت قىلىڭ https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановний користувачу! Це рекомендоване оновлення дає змогу зберігати сполучення додатків у режимі розділення екрана. Це оновлення також упроваджує функцію "Відстеження руху очей" і дає змогу змінювати водяні знаки. Крім того, у цьому випуску оптимізовано ефект відображення панелі сповіщень і ефект руху на головному екрані, усунуто проблему з аномальним споживанням енергії в деяких ситуаціях, покращено стабільність системи й упроваджено виправлення для системи безпеки.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Багатовіконний режим">
<feature>Тепер можна зберігати комбінації додатків у режимі розділення екрана. Щоб зберегти комбінацію як піктограму на головному екрані, у режимі розділеного екрана торкніться кнопки посередині роздільника. Щоб отримати швидкий доступ до комбінації, торкніться піктограми.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Галерея">
<feature>Водяні знаки тепер можна додавати й видаляти за бажанням. Щоб спробувати, перейдіть до меню "Зробити фото" > "Відкрити фотографію" > "Змінити" > "Водяний знак" > "Параметри водяного знака": "Оригінал", "Текстовий водяний знак", "Водяний знак із рамкою".</feature>
</features>
<features module="Відстеження руху очей">
<feature>Додано функцію відстеження руху очей, яка дає змогу швидко отримувати доступ до повідомлень і докладного вмісту без ручного керування, коли ви дивитеся прямо на екран на відстані 20-50 см. Щоб спробувати, перейдіть до меню "Налаштування" > "Помічник" > "Відстеження руху очей".</feature>
</features>
<features module="Панель сповіщень">
<feature>Оптимізовано макет панелі сповіщень, завдяки чому інтерфейс став зручнішим і візуально привабливішим.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ефект руху">
<feature>Оптимізовано узгодженість ефекту руху на головному екрані.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Споживання енергії">
<feature>Усунуто проблему аномального енергоспоживання в деяких сценаріях.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>Підвищено стабільність функціонування системи для надійнішої роботи пристрою.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Безпека">
<feature>Виправлення для системи безпеки Android від серпня 2024 року впроваджено для посилення безпеки системи. Додаткову інформацію про оновлення для системи безпеки HONOR див. на нашому вебсайті https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примітки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ваші особисті дані не буде видалено внаслідок установлення цього оновлення, але все ж радимо створити резервну копію заздалегідь.
2. Якщо під час оновлення у вас виникнуть будь-які проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію обслуговування користувачів HONOR або зверніться в сервісний центр HONOR по допомогу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>محترم صارف، اس تجویز کردہ اپ ڈیٹ کے ساتھ، آپ تیز رسائی کے لیے ایپ کے امتزاج کو منقسم اسکرین موڈ میں محفوظ کر سکتے ہیں۔ یہ اپ ڈیٹ آنکھ کی ٹریکنگ کو بھی متعارف کرواتی ہے، اور واٹر مارکس میں ترمیم کرنے کی اجازت دیتی ہے۔ مزید برآں، یہ ریلیز اطلاعی پینل کے ڈسپلے کے اثر اور ہوم اسکرین پر حرکت کے اثر کو بہتر بناتی ہے، کچھ منظرناموں میں بجلی کی غیر معمولی کھپت کے مسئلے کو حل کرتی ہے، سسٹم کے استحکام کو بہتر بناتی ہے، اور سکیورٹی پیچ شامل کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="ملٹی ونڈو">
<feature>منقسم اسکرین موڈ میں ایپ کے امتزاج کو اب محفوظ کیا جا سکتا ہے۔ منقسم سکرین موڈ میں، ہوم اسکرین پر امتزاج کو بطور آئیکن محفوظ کرنے کے لیے ڈیوائیڈر کے وسط میں بٹن پر ٹیپ کریں۔ آئیکن پر ٹیپ کرنے سے امتزاج تک جلدی رسائی حاصل ہوتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="گیلری">
<feature>واٹر مارکس کو اب حسب ضرورت شامل کیا جا سکتا اور ہٹایا جا سکتا ہے۔ اس پر جا کر تجربہ کریں: تصویر لیں > تصویر کھولیں > ترمیم کریں > واٹر مارک > واٹر مارک کے اختیارات: اصل، متنی واٹر مارک، فریم واٹر مارک۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="آنکھ کی ٹریکنگ">
<feature>آنکھ کی ٹریکنگ شامل ہے، جب آپ کی آنکھیں 20-50 سینٹی میٹر کے فاصلے پر براہ راست اسکرین کا سامنا کر رہی ہوں تو دستی آپریشن کے بغیر اطلاعات اور تفصیلی مواد تک جلدی رسائی کی اجازت دیتی ہے۔ اس پر جا کر تجربہ کریں: ترتیبات > اسِسٹنٹ > آنکھ کی ٹریکنگ۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="اطلاعی پینل">
<feature>اطلاعی پینل کی لے آؤٹ کو بہتر بنا یا گیا ہے، جو انٹرفیس کو مزید ہموار اور بصری طور پر دلکش بناتا ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="حرکت کا اثر">
<feature>ہوم اسکرین پر حرکت کے اثر کے مستقل پن کو بہتر بناتا ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="بجلی کی کھپت">
<feature>کچھ مناظر میں بجلی کی غیر معمولی کھپت کے مسئلے کو حل کرتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سسٹم">
<feature>آپ کی ڈیوائس کو زیادہ مستحکم طریقے سے چلانے کے لیے سسٹم کے استحکام کو بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="سکیورٹی">
<feature>‏‏Android سکیورٹی پیچ (اگست 2024) شامل کر دیا گیا ہے۔ HONOR سکیورٹی اپ ڈیٹس کے بارے میں مزید معلومات کے لیے، براہ کرم ہماری ویب سائٹ ملاحظہ کریں: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں مٹے گا، لیکن پھر بھی پہلے سے بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2۔ اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو تعاون کے لیے براہ کرم HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کریں یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جائیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu tavsiya etiladigan yangilanish sizga ajratilgan ekran rejimida ilovalar kombinatsiyalarini saqlash imkonini beradi. Bu yangilanishda Koʻz kuzatuvi funksiyasi va shaffof belgilarni tahrirlash imkoniyati ham taqdim etildi. Bundan tashqari, ushbu yangilanishda bildirishnomalar panelini koʻrsatish effekti va bosh ekrandagi harakat effekti optimallandi, ayrim holatlardagi noodatiy quvvat sarfi muammosi hal etildi, tizim barqarorligi oshirildi hamda xavfsizlik tuzatmasi taqdim etildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bir nechta oyna">
<feature>Ajratilgan ekran rejimida endi ilovalar kombinatsiyasi saqlanishi mumkin. Kombinatsiyani bosh ekranga belgi sifatida saqlash uchun Ajratilgan ekran rejimida ajratkich markazidagi tugmani bosing. Bu belgini bosish kombinatsiyaga tezkor kirish imkonini beradi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Galereya">
<feature>Endi shaffof belgilarni xohlagancha qoʻshish yoki olib tashlash mumkin. Uni sinash uchun kiring: Surat oling > Suratni oching > Tahrirlash > Shaffof belgi > Shaffof belgi parametrlari: Original, Matnli shaffof belgi, Hoshiyali shaffof belgi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Koʻz kuzatuvi">
<feature>Ekranga 20-50 sm masofadan bevosita qarab turilganda bildirishnomalar va batafsil kontentga oddiy usulda amal bajarmasdan tezkor kirish imkonini beradigan Koʻz kuzatuvi funksiyasi kiritildi. Uni sinash uchun kiring: Sozlamalar > Assistent > Koʻz kuzatuvi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bildirishnomalar paneli">
<feature>Bildirishnomalar panelining sxemasi optimallandi, bu interfeysni yanada soddalashtiradi va unga chiroyli tus beradi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Harakat effekti">
<feature>Bosh ekrandagi harakat effektining bir xilligi optimallandi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Quvvat sarfi">
<feature>Ayrim holatlardagi noodatiy quvvat sarfi muammosi tuzatildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tizim">
<feature>Qurilmangiz yanada barqaror ishlashi uchun tizim barqarorligi oshirildi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Xavfsizlik">
<feature>Tizim xavfsizligi uchun Android xavfsizlik tuzatmasi (2024-yil, avgust) kiritildi. HONOR Xavfsizlik yangilanishlari haqida batafsil axborot olish uchun veb-saytimizga tashrif buyuring: https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanish oʻrnatilsa shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringiz oʻchib ketmaydi, lekin ularni oldindan zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, yordam uchun HONOR xizmat markazi tezkor raqamiga murojaat qiling yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyuring.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, với bản cập nhật đề xuất này, bạn có thể lưu các kiểu kết hợp ứng dụng ở chế độ màn hình chia. Bản cập nhật này cũng giới thiệu tính năng Theo dõi chuyển động mắt và cho phép sửa hình chìm mờ. Ngoài ra, bản phát hành này tối ưu hóa hiệu ứng hiển thị của bảng thông báo và hiệu ứng chuyển động trên màn hình chính, khắc phục sự cố tiêu thụ pin bất thường trong một số trường hợp, cải thiện độ ổn định của hệ thống và tích hợp một bản vá bảo mật.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Đa cửa sổ">
<feature>Giờ đây, bạn có thể lưu các kiểu kết hợp ứng dụng ở chế độ màn hình chia. Ở chế độ màn hình chia, hãy chạm vào nút ở giữa đường phân cách để lưu kiểu kết hợp đó làm biểu tượng trên màn hình chính. Chạm vào biểu tượng để bật quyền truy cập nhanh vào kiểu kết hợp.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bộ sưu tập">
<feature>Giờ đây, bạn có thể thêm và xóa hình chìm mờ theo ý muốn. Trải nghiệm bằng cách vào: Chụp ảnh > Mở ảnh > Sửa > Hình chìm mờ > Tùy chọn hình chìm mờ: Ảnh gốc, Hình chìm mờ dạng văn bản, Hình chìm mờ dạng khung.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Theo dõi chuyển động mắt">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này bao gồm tính năng Theo dõi chuyển động mắt, giúp truy cập nhanh vào các thông báo và nội dung chi tiết mà không cần thao tác thủ công khi mắt bạn nhìn thẳng vào màn hình ở khoảng cách 20 – 50 cm. Hãy trải nghiệm tính năng này bằng cách vào: Cài đặt > Trợ lý > Theo dõi chuyển động mắt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bảng thông báo">
<feature>Tối ưu hóa bố cục, giúp giao diện được sắp xếp hợp lý và trực quan hấp dẫn hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hiệu ứng chuyển động">
<feature>Tối ưu hóa tính nhất quán của hiệu ứng chuyển động trên màn hình chính.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tiêu thụ pin">
<feature>Khắc phục sự cố tiêu thụ pin bất thường trong một số trường hợp.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hệ thống">
<feature>Cải thiện độ ổn định của hệ thống để giúp thiết bị của bạn chạy ổn định hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bảo mật">
<feature>Bản cập nhật này tích hợp Bản vá bảo mật Android (tháng 8 năm 2024) để bảo mật hệ thống. Để biết thêm thông tin về các Bản cập nhật bảo mật của HONOR, vui lòng truy cập trang web của chúng tôi https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ghi chú:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị xóa. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu trước.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新新增了分割屏幕儲存、相機浮水印編輯和眼動追蹤功能，優化了通知欄顯示效果和主屏幕動畫效果，修復了部分場景異常耗電問題，提升系統穩定性，整合安全性修補程式，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【智能多窗】">
<feature>新增分割屏幕儲存功能。在分割屏幕狀態下輕觸分割屏幕線中間按鈕，可將分割屏幕組合以圖標形式儲存在主屏幕，之後可透過輕觸該圖標即可快速開啟此分割屏幕組合。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【圖片庫】">
<feature>新增相機浮水印編輯功能，可自行新增和還原浮水印，體驗路徑：拍攝 > 開啟相片 > 編輯 > 浮水印 > 浮水印選擇：原圖、文字浮水印、相框浮水印。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【眼動追蹤】">
<feature>新增眼動追蹤功能，在距離屏幕 20-50 厘米處，眼睛正對屏幕時，無需手動操作，透過注視即可快捷展開相關橫幅通知或檢視詳細內容，體驗路徑：設定 > 智能助手 > 眼動追蹤。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【通知欄】">
<feature>優化了通知欄佈局顯示，介面呈現更加簡潔美觀。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【動畫效果】">
<feature>優化主屏幕動畫效果的一致性。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【功耗】">
<feature>修復了部分場景異常耗電的問題。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>提升系統穩定性，讓您的手機運行更穩定。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>整合 Android 2024年8月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟件安全更新內容的資訊，請瀏覽榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線，或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新新增螢幕分割儲存、相機浮水印編輯以及眼動追蹤功能，最佳化通知列顯示效果和桌面動效，修復在部分場景下的異常耗電問題，提升系統穩定性，並整合安全性修補程式，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【智慧多窗】">
<feature>新增螢幕分割儲存功能，螢幕分割狀態下輕觸螢幕分割線中間按鈕，可將螢幕分割組合，以圖示形式儲存在桌面，後續透過輕觸該圖示即可快捷開啟此螢幕分割組合。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【圖片庫】">
<feature>新增相機浮水印編輯功能，可自行新增和還原浮水印，體驗路徑：拍照 > 開啟相片 > 編輯 > 浮水印 > 浮水印選取：原始版本、文字浮水印、相框浮水印。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【眼動追蹤】">
<feature>新增眼動追蹤功能，在距離螢幕 20~50 公分處眼睛正對螢幕，無需手動操作，透過注視即可快捷展開相關橫幅通知或查看詳細內容，體驗路徑：設定 > 智慧助手 > 眼動追蹤。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【通知列】">
<feature>最佳化通知列版面配置顯示，介面呈現更加簡潔美觀。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【動畫】">
<feature>最佳化桌面動畫一致性。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【電力消耗】">
<feature>修復在部分場景下的異常耗電問題。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>提升系統穩定性，讓您的手機執行更穩定。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【安全】">
<feature>整合 Android 2024 年 8 月的安全性修補程式，增強系統安全性。如需有關榮耀軟體安全更新內容的資訊，請造訪榮耀官方網站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2024/8</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
