<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新新增桌面图标大小调节和一步手势分屏功能，提升悬浮窗使用体验，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【桌面图标】">
<feature>支持桌面图标大小调节，满足用户对图标大小的不同显示需求，体验路径：“设置->桌面和个性化->桌面设置->图标大小”。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【分屏】">
<feature>新增一步手势分屏功能，应用全屏下拖动底部至左上角，点击其他支持分屏应用，即可实现应用分屏。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【悬浮窗】">
<feature>迷你窗支持移动和悬停到手机桌面任意位置。</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更多精彩功能介绍，请访问“玩机技巧”应用。
3. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update introduces new functions, allowing you to adjust the size of Home screen icons and activate App Extender with a single swipe. This update also improves the user experience of floating window.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Home screen icons">
<feature>The size of Home screen icons can be adjusted to suit individual needs. Experience it by going to: Settings -> Home screen and style -> Home screen settings -> Icon size.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Extender">
<feature>App Extender can be invoked with just one swipe. Drag the bottom to the upper left corner, then tap another app that supports App Extender to enable dual-window display.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Floating window">
<feature>Mini window can be moved and hovered to any position on the home screen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. Check out more information on product features in the Tips app.
3. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling HONOR service hotline or visiting HONOR Customer Service Center.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ የሚመከር ዝማኔ አዳዲስ ተግባራትን ያስተዋውቃል፣ ይህም የመነሻ ገጽ አዶዎችን መጠን እንዲያስተካክሉ እና መተግበሪያ ማራዘሚያን በአንድ መጥረግ ገቢር እንዲያረጉ ያስችልዎታል። ይህ ዝማኔ በተጨማሪም የተንሳፋፊ መስኮት የተጠቃሚ ተሞክሮን ያሻሽላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የመነሻ ገጽ አዶዎች">
<feature>ግለሰባዊ ፍላጎቶች ለማሟላት የመነሻ ገጽ አዶዎች መጠን ሊስተካከል ይችላል። ወደ ቅንብሮች -> መነሻ ገጽ እና ቅጥ -> የመነሻ ማያ ቅንብሮች -> የአዶ መጠን በመሄድ ይሞክሩት።</feature>
</features>
<features module="የመተግበሪያ ማራዘሚያ">
<feature>መተግበሪያ ማራዘሚያን በአንድ መጥረግ ብቻ መጥራት ይችላል። ባለሁለት-መስኮት ማሳያን ስራ ለማስጀመር ታቹን ወደ ላይኛው ግራ ጥግ ይጎትቱት፣ ከዚያ መተግበሪያ ማራዘሚያን የሚደግፍ ሌላ መተግበሪያ ይንኩ።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ተንሳፋፊ መስኮት">
<feature>ትንሽ መስኮት በመነሻ ገጽ ላይ ወደ ማንኛውም ቦታ ማንቀሳቀስ እና ማንዣበብ ይችላል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ዝማኔ መጫን የእርስዎን የግል ውሂብ አይሰርዝም፣ ነገር ግን አስቀድሞ መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ አሁንም ይመከራል።
2. በምርቱ ባህሪያት ላይ ተጨማሪ መረጃን ለማየት ወደ ጠቃሚ ምክሮች መተግበሪያው ይሂዱ።
3. በዝማኔው ወቅት ማንኛቸውም ጉዳዮች ካጋጠሙዎት የHONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር ላይ በመደወል ወይም የHONOR የደንበኛ አገልግሎት ማዕከልን በመጎብኘት የእኛን እርዳታ ማግኘት ይችላሉ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزي المستخدم، يقدم هذا التحديث الموصى به وظائف جديدة، مما يسمح لك بتعديل حجم أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية وتنشيط مُوسِع التطبيقات بعملية سحب واحدة. يحسّن هذا التحديث أيضًا تجربة المستخدم في استخدام النافذة العائمة.</feature>
</features>
<features module="أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية">
<feature>يمكن تعديل حجم أيقونات الشاشة الرئيسية لتناسب احتياجاتك الفردية. يمكنك تجربة ذلك بالانتقال إلى: الإعدادات -> الشاشة الرئيسية والنمط -> إعدادات الشاشة الرئيسية -> حجم الأيقونة.</feature>
</features>
<features module="مُوسِع التطبيقات">
<feature>يمكن استدعاء مُوسِع التطبيقات بعملية سحب واحدة فقط. اسحب الجزء السفلي إلى الزاوية العلوية اليسرى، ثم اضغط على تطبيق آخر يدعم مُوسِع التطبيقات لتمكين العرض في نوافذ مزدوجة.</feature>
</features>
<features module="نافذة عائمة">
<feature>يمكن تحريك النافذة الصغيرة ووضعها في أي موضع على الشاشة الرئيسية.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>1. لن يؤدي تثبيت هذا التحديث إلى مسح بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن من المستحسن إجراء عملية نسخ احتياطي مسبقًا.
2. اطلع على المزيد من المعلومات حول ميزات المنتج في التطبيق "تلميحات".
3. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيمكنك الحصول على مساعدتنا عن طريق الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة عملاء HONOR أو زيارة مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR.‬</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই অনুমোদিত আপডেটে নতুন ফাংচনসমূহৰ পৰিচয় কৰায়, যিয়ে আপোনাক এবাৰ ছোৱাইপ কৰি হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্নসমূহৰ আকাৰ মিলাবলৈ আৰু এপ্প্‌ এক্সটেণ্ডাৰ সক্রিয় কৰিবলৈ অনুমতি দিয়ে। এই আপডেটটোৱে ফ্ল'টিং উইণ্ড'ৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ অভিজ্ঞতা উন্নত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্নসমূহ">
<feature>ব্যক্তিগত প্ৰয়োজনীয়তাসমূহৰ লগত খাপ খাবলৈ হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ চিহ্নসমূহৰ আকাৰ মিলাব পাৰি। ইয়ালৈ গৈ ইয়াৰ অভিজ্ঞতা লওক: ছেটিংছ -> হোম স্ক্ৰীণ আৰু শৈলী -> হোম স্ক্ৰীণৰ ছেটিংছ -> চিহ্নৰ আকাৰ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="এপ্প্‌ এক্সটেণ্ডাৰ">
<feature>মাত্ৰ এবাৰ ছোৱাইপ কৰি এপ্প্‌ এক্সটেণ্ডাৰ কাৰ্যকৰী কৰিব পাৰি। তলটো ওপৰৰ বাওঁ কোণলৈ টানক, তাৰপিছত দুখন-উইণ্ড'ৰ ডিচপ্লে সক্ষম কৰিবলৈ এপ্প্‌ এক্সটেণ্ডাৰ সমৰ্থন কৰা অন্য এপ্প্‌ টিপক।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ফ্ল'টিং উইণ্ড'">
<feature>হোম স্ক্ৰীণখনত যিকোনো ঠাইলৈ মিনি উইণ্ড' লৈ যাব আৰু হোভাৰ কৰিব পাৰি।</feature>
</features>
<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটা মোহৰা নহ'ব, কিন্তু তথাপিও তাৰ আগতে বেকআপ ল'বলৈ অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আভাস এপ্প্‌টোত প্ৰ'ডাক্টৰ ফিচাৰসমূহৰ ওপৰত অধিক তথ্য চাওক।
3. আপুনি আপডেটৰ সময়ত কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হ'লে, আপুনি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত কল কৰি বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ গৈ সহায় লাভ কৰিব পাৰে।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, tövsiyə edilən bu yeniləmə yeni funksiyalar təqdim edir, sizə əsas ekran nişanlarının ölçüsünü tənzimləməyə və bir çəkmə əməliyyatı ilə Proqram Genişləndiricisini aktivləşdirməyə imkan verir. Bu yeniləmə həm də sürüşdürülən pəncərənin istifadəçi təcrübəsini yaxşılaşdırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Əsas ekran nişanları">
<feature>Əsas ekran nişanlarının ölçüsü fərdi tələbləri ödəmək üçün tənzimlənə bilər. Bunu aşağıdakı bölmələrə keçməklə təcrübədən keçirə bilərsiniz: Parametrlər -> Əsas ekran və üslub -> Əsas ekran parametrləri -> Nişan ölçüsü.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Proqram Genişləndiricisi">
<feature>Proqram Genişləndiricisi yalnız bir çəkmə əməliyyatı ilə işə salına bilər. Aşağı tərəfi yuxarı sol küncə çəkin, sonra ikili pəncərə ekranını aktivləşdirmək üçün Proqram Genişləndiricisini dəstəkləyən başqa proqrama toxunun.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sürüşdürülən pəncərə">
<feature>Kiçik pəncərə əsas ekranda istənilən mövqeyə köçürülə və aparıla bilər.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınızı silməyəcək, lakin yenə də əvvəlcədən ehtiyat nüsxənin yaradılması tövsiyə olunur.
2. İpucları proqramında məhsul xüsusiyyətləri haqqında daha çox məlumata nəzər salın.
3. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlə üzləşsəniz, HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng etməklə və ya HONOR Müştəri Xidməti Mərkəzinə getməklə bizdən kömək əldə edə bilərsiniz.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran sing disaranake iki nglebokake fungsi anyar, sing ngidini sampeyan kanggo ngatur ukuran ikon Layar ngarep lan ngaktifake Pangulur Apl kanthi sak usapan. Panganyaran iki uga ngapikake pangalaman pangguna babagan jendhela nglayang.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikon layar ngarep">
<feature>Ukuran ikon Layar ngarep bisa diatur supaya cocog karo saben-saben kabutuhan. Gunakake fungsi iki kanthi mbukak: Setelan -> Layar ngarep lan gaya -> Setelan layar ngarep -> Ukuran ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pangulur Apl">
<feature>Pangulur Apl bisa dipicu kanthi mung sak usapan. Seret saka ngisor dewe menyang pojok kiwa ndhuwur, banjur tutul apl liya sing ndhukung Pangulur Apl kanggo ngaktifake tampilan rong jendhela.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Jendhela nglayang">
<feature>Jendhela mini bisa dipindhahake lan diarahake menyang sembarang posisi ing layar ngarep.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mbusak data pribadi sampeyan, nanging nggawe serep dhisik tetep disaranake.
2. Informasi sing luwih jangkep babagan fitur prodhuk bisa dideleng ing apl Tips.
3. Yen sampeyan ngalami masalah sajrone panganyaran, sampeyan bisa njaluk bantuan kita kanthi nelpon hotline layanan HONOR utawa nekani Pusat Layanan Pelanggan HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem uvode se nove funkcije koje vam omogućavaju da podesite veličinu ikona na početnom ekranu i da jednim prevlačenjem aktivirate Proširivač aplikacije. Ovim ažuriranjem takođe se unapređuje korisničko iskustvo korišćenja plutajućeg prozora.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikone na početnom ekranu">
<feature>Korisnik može u skladu sa svojim potrebama prilagoditi veličinu ikona na početnom ekranu. Putem sledeće putanje možete da probate novu funkciju: Podešavanja -> Početni ekran i stil -> Podešavanja početnog ekrana -> Veličina ikone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Proširivač aplikacije">
<feature>Proširivač aplikacije je sada moguće aktivirati jednim prevlačenjem. Prevucite sa dna do gornjeg levog ugla, a zatim dodirnite drugu aplikaciju koja podržava Proširivač aplikacije da biste omogućili prikaz u dva prozora.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Plutajući prozor">
<feature>Možete pomerati mini-prozor i zadržati ga u bilo kom položaju na početnom ekranu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. U aplikaciji Saveti pročitajte detaljnije informacije o funkcijama proizvoda.
3. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, možete da dobijete našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili tako što ćete posetiti korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem uvode se nove funkcije koje vam omogućavaju da podesite veličinu ikona na početnom ekranu i da jednim prevlačenjem aktivirate Proširivač aplikacije. Ovim ažuriranjem takođe se unapređuje korisničko iskustvo korišćenja plutajućeg prozora.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikone na početnom ekranu">
<feature>Korisnik može u skladu sa svojim potrebama prilagoditi veličinu ikona na početnom ekranu. Putem sledeće putanje možete da probate novu funkciju: Podešavanja -> Početni ekran i stil -> Podešavanja početnog ekrana -> Veličina ikone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Proširivač aplikacije">
<feature>Proširivač aplikacije je sada moguće aktivirati jednim prevlačenjem. Prevucite sa dna do gornjeg levog ugla, a zatim dodirnite drugu aplikaciju koja podržava Proširivač aplikacije da biste omogućili prikaz u dva prozora.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Plutajući prozor">
<feature>Možete pomerati mini-prozor i zadržati ga u bilo kom položaju na početnom ekranu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. U aplikaciji Saveti pročitajte detaljnije informacije o funkcijama proizvoda.
3. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, možete da dobijete našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili tako što ćete posetiti korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem uvode se nove funkcije koje vam omogućavaju da podesite veličinu ikona na početnom ekranu i da jednim prevlačenjem aktivirate Proširivač aplikacije. Ovim ažuriranjem takođe se unapređuje korisničko iskustvo korišćenja plutajućeg prozora.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikone na početnom ekranu">
<feature>Korisnik može u skladu sa svojim potrebama prilagoditi veličinu ikona na početnom ekranu. Putem sledeće putanje možete da probate novu funkciju: Podešavanja -> Početni ekran i stil -> Podešavanja početnog ekrana -> Veličina ikone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Proširivač aplikacije">
<feature>Proširivač aplikacije je sada moguće aktivirati jednim prevlačenjem. Prevucite sa dna do gornjeg levog ugla, a zatim dodirnite drugu aplikaciju koja podržava Proširivač aplikacije da biste omogućili prikaz u dva prozora.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Plutajući prozor">
<feature>Možete pomerati mini-prozor i zadržati ga u bilo kom položaju na početnom ekranu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja neće biti obrisani vaši lični podaci, ali se preporučuje da prethodno napravite rezervnu kopiju.
2. U aplikaciji Saveti pročitajte detaljnije informacije o funkcijama proizvoda.
3. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, možete da dobijete našu pomoć tako što ćete pozvati dežurnu liniju korisničke službe kompanije HONOR ili tako što ćete posetiti korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта рэкамендаванае абнаўленне ўводзіць новыя функцыі, якія дазваляюць рэгуляваць памер значкоў галоўнага экрана і актываваць Пашыральнік праграм адным рухам пальца. Таксама гэта абнаўленне паляпшае выкарыстанне плаваючых вокнаў.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Значкі галоўнага экрана">
<feature>Памер значкоў галоўнага экрана можна рэгуляваць у адпаведнасці з індывідуальнымі патрэбамі. Каб паспрабаваць гэту функцыю, прайдзіце ў меню «Налады -> Галоўны экран і стыль -> Налады галоўнага экрана -> Памер значка».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Пашыральнік праграм">
<feature>Каб актываваць Пашыральнік праграм, дастаткова адзін раз правесці пальцам. Правядзіце пальцам ад нізу экрана ў верхні левы вугал, а потым краніце іншую праграму, якая падтрымлівае Пашыральнік праграм, каб уключыць адлюстраванне двух вокнаў.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Плаваючае акно">
<feature>Цяпер міні-акно можна перамясціць і зафіксаваць у любым месцы галоўнага экрана.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не сатрэ вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем загадзя зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію.
2. Больш інфармацыі аб функцыях прадукту можна знайсці ў праграме «Падказкі».
3. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, вы можаце патэлефанаваць на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або наведаць сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, с тази препоръчителна актуализация се въвеждат нови функции, които ви позволяват да регулирате размера на иконите на началния екран и да активирате „Разширител на приложения“ с едно плъзване. Тази актуализация също така подобрява потребителското изживяване с плаващия прозорец.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Икони на началния екран">
<feature>Размерът на иконите на началния екран може да бъде регулиран така, че да отговаря на индивидуалните нужди. Можете да го изпробвате, като отидете на: „Настройки -> Начален екран и стил -> Настройки на началния екран -> Размер на икони“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Разширител на приложения">
<feature>„Разширител на приложения“ може да бъде извикан само с едно плъзване. Плъзнете долната част до горния ляв ъгъл, след което докоснете друго приложение, което поддържа „Разширител на приложения“, за да активирате показването в два прозореца.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Плаващ прозорец">
<feature>Мини прозорецът може да бъде преместен и поставен с мишката на всяко място на началния екран.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да доведе до изтриване на личните ви данни, но все пак е препоръчително да направите архивиране преди това.
2. Вижте още информация за характеристиките на продукта в приложението „Съвети“.
3. Ако по време на актуализацията срещнете някакви проблеми, можете да получите нашата помощ, като се обадите на горещата линия за обслужване на HONOR или посетите Сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই সুপারিশকৃত আপডেটটি নতুন ফাংশনগুলি চালু করে, যা আপনাকে হোম স্ক্রিনের আইকনগুলির আকার সামঞ্জস্য করতে দেয় এবং একবার সোয়াইপ করে অ্যাপ এক্সটেন্ডার সক্রিয় করতে দেয়। এই আপডেটটি ভাসমান উইন্ডোর ব্যবহারকারীর অভিজ্ঞতাও উন্নত করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="হোম স্ক্রিন আইকন">
<feature>ব্যক্তিগত প্রয়োজন অনুসারে উপযুক্ত হওয়ার জন্য হোম স্ক্রিন আইকনগুলির আকার সামঞ্জস্য করা যেতে পারে। এখানে গিয়ে এটি ব্যবহার করে দেখুন: সেটিংস -> হোম স্ক্রিন এবং স্টাইল -> হোম স্ক্রিন সেটিংস -> আইকনের আকার।</feature>
</features>
<features module="অ্যাপ এক্সটেন্ডার">
<feature>মাত্র একবার সোয়াইপ করে অ্যাপ এক্সটেন্ডার চালু করা যায়। নিচের অংশটিকে উপরের বাঁদিকের কোণায় টানুন, তারপরে ডুয়াল-উইন্ডো ডিসপ্লে সক্রিয় করতে এমন অন্য একটি অ্যাপে ট্যাপ করুন যা অ্যাপ এক্সটেন্ডারকে সমর্থন করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ভাসমান উইন্ডো">
<feature>মিনি উইন্ডোটি হোম স্ক্রিনের যেকোনো অবস্থানে সরানো এবং হোভার করা যেতে পারে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটা মুছে যাবে না, তবে তা সত্ত্বেও আগে থেকে ব্যাকআপ নেওয়ার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. পরামর্শ অ্যাপে প্রোডাক্টের বৈশিষ্ট্যগুলি সম্পর্কে আরও তথ্য দেখুন।
3. আপডেট হওয়ার সময় আপনি কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে HONOR সেবা হটলাইনে কল করে বা HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে গিয়ে আমাদের সহায়তা পেতে পারেন।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་དུ་ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས་ཆེ་ཆུང་སྙོམ་སྒྲིག་དང་གོམ་གང་ལག་བརྡས་ཡོལ་བགོ་བའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། གཡེང་སྒྲོམ་བེད་སྤྱོད་པའི་ཉམས་ལེན་མཐོར་འདེགས་བཏང་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུར་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས།】">
<feature>ཅོག་ངོས་རིས་རྟགས་ཆེ་ཆུང་སྙོམ་སྒྲིག་བྱེད་པར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད། སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་རིས་རྟགས་ཆེ་ཆུང་མི་འདྲ་བའི་མངོན་སྟོན་དགོས་མཁོ་སོང་། ཉམས་ལེན་བརྒྱུད་ལམ། སྒྲིག་འགོད་ནས་ཅོག་ངོས་དང་སྒེར་གཤིས་ཅན། ཅོག་ངོས་སྒྲིག་འགོད། དེ་ནས་རིས་རྟགས་ཆེ་ཆུང་།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【ཡོལ་བགོ】">
<feature>གོམ་གཅིག་གི་ལག་བརྡས་ཡོལ་བགོ་བའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཧྲིལ་ཡོལ་འོག་ཏུ་འོག་ཁུལ་གཡོན་གོང་ཟུར་དུ་འགུལ་འདྲུད་བྱས་ནས། ཡོལ་བགོ་ལ་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད་པའི་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་གཞན་པར་བརྡབས་ན་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ཡོལ་བགོ་མངོན་འགྱུར་བྱ་ཆོག</feature>
</features>
<features module="【གཡེང་སྒྲོམ།】">
<feature>སྒྲོམ་ཆུང་ལག་ཁྱེར་ཁ་པར་གྱི་ཅོག་ངོས་ཀྱི་གནས་ཡུལ་གང་རུང་དུ་སྤོ་འགུལ་དང་སྡོད་པར་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་ཉམས་འཇོག་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་ཁྱེད་ཀྱིས་སྔར་བཞིན་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་སྔོན་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ལེགས་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. དེ་ལས་མང་བའི་ངོ་མཚར་བའི་རྩོལ་ནུས་ངོ་སྤྲོད། ཁ་པར་རྩེ་བའི་ལག་རྩལ་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་ལ་ལྟ་སྤྱོད་བྱེད་རོགས།
3. གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱེད་པའི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད་དུ། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ། ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་མཁོ་མཁན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་ཕེབས་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་འཚོལ་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje uvodi nove funkcije koje vam omogućavaju da prilagodite veličinu ikona na početnom ekranu i aktivirate Proširivač aplikacija jednim prevlačenjem. Ovo ažuriranje također poboljšava korisničko iskustvo s plutajućim prozorom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikone na početnom ekranu">
<feature>Veličina ikona na početnom ekranu se može prilagoditi potrebama svakog korisnika. Isprobajte tu funkciju odlaskom u Postavke -> Početni ekran i stil -> Postavke početnog ekrana -> Veličina ikona.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Proširivač aplikacija">
<feature>Proširivač aplikacija se može aktivirati samo jednim prevlačenjem. Povucite sa dna u gornji lijevo ugao ekrana, a zatim dodirnite drugu aplikaciju koja podržava Proširivač aplikacija da omogućite prikaz u dva prozora.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Plutajući prozor">
<feature>Mini prozor se može premještati i postaviti da pluta na bilo koji položaj na početnom ekranu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranjem ovog ažuriranja se neće izbrisati lični podaci, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju prije ažuriranja.
2. Više informacija o funkcijama proizvoda možete pogledati u aplikaciji Savjeti.
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització recomanada introdueix noves funcions, que us permeten ajustar la mida de les icones de la pantalla inicial i activar l'Extensor d'aplicacions amb un sol cop. Aquesta actualització també millora l'experiència d'usuari de la finestra flotant.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Icones de la pantalla inicial">
<feature>La mida de les Icones de la pantalla inicial es pot ajustar per adaptar-se a les necessitats individuals. Per provar-ho, aneu a: Configuració -> Pantalla inicial i estil -> Configuració de la pantalla inicial -> Mida de la icona.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Extensor d'aplicacions">
<feature>L'Extensor d'aplicacions es pot activar amb un sol cop. Arrossegueu la part inferior cap a l'extrem superior esquerre i, a continuació, toqueu una altra aplicació que admeti l'Extensor d'aplicacions per habilitar la visualització de doble finestra.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Finestra flotant">
<feature>La minifinestra es pot moure i desplaçar a qualsevol posició de la pantalla inicial.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Si instal·leu aquesta actualització, les dades personals no s'esborraran, però us recomanem que en feu una còpia de seguretat.
2. Si voleu més informació sobre les funcions del producte, aneu a l'aplicació Suggeriments.
3. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o visiteu el Centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR per rebre ajuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený uživateli, tato doporučená aktualizace přináší nové funkce, které vám umožňují upravit velikost ikon na domovské obrazovce a aktivovat Rozšíření aplikace jediným přejetím prstu. Tato aktualizace také zlepšuje uživatelský zážitek z plovoucího okna.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikony domovské obrazovky">
<feature>Velikost ikon na domovské obrazovce lze upravit podle individuálních potřeb. Vyzkoušejte to v nabídce: Nastavení -> Domovská obrazovka a styl -> Nastavení domovské obrazovky -> Velikost ikony.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rozšíření aplikace">
<feature>Rozšíření aplikace lze vyvolat jediným přejetím prstu. Přetáhněte spodní část do levého horního rohu a potom klepněte na jinou aplikaci, která podporuje funkci Rozšíření aplikace, a povolte zobrazení dvou oken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Plovoucí okno">
<feature>Mini okno lze přesunout a umístit na libovolnou pozici na domovské obrazovce.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalací této aktualizace nebudou vymazány vaše osobní údaje, ale přesto se doporučuje je předem zálohovat.
2. Další informace o funkcích produktu naleznete v aplikaci Tipy.
3. Pokud během aktualizace narazíte na nějaké problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo navštivte Centrum služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger, denne anbefalede opdatering introducerer nye funktioner, der lader dig justere størrelsen på ikoner på startskærmen og aktivere App Extender med et enkelt strøg. Denne opdatering forbedrer også brugeroplevelsen med flydende vindue.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikoner på startskærmen">
<feature>Størrelsen på ikoner på startskærmen kan justeres, så de passer til individuelle behov. Oplev det ved at gå til: Indstillinger -> Startskærm og stil -> Indstillinger for startskærm -> Ikonstørrelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Extender">
<feature>App Extender kan hentes med et enkelt strøg. Træk knappen til øverste venstre hjørne, og tryk så på en anden app, der understøtter App Extender for at aktivere visning i dobbelte vinduer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Flydende vindue">
<feature>Minivindue kan flyttes og svæves til enhver position på startskærmen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering vil ikke slette dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadig at tage en sikkerhedskopi på forhånd.
2. Se yderligere oplysninger om produktfunktioner i appen Tips.
3. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du få hjælp ved at ringe til HONORs servicehotline eller besøge HONORs kundeservicecenter.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Lieber Nutzer, dieses empfohlene Update führt neue Funktionen ein, mit denen Sie die Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm anpassen und App-Extender mit einem einzigen Streichen aktivieren können. Dieses Update verbessert auch das Benutzererlebnis mit unverankerten Fenstern.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm">
<feature>Die Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm kann an individuelle Bedürfnisse angepasst werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Einstellungen -> Startbildschirm und Stil -> Startbildschirmeinstellungen -> Symbolgröße.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App-Extender">
<feature>App-Extender kann mit nur einem Streichen aufgerufen werden. Ziehen Sie den unteren Rand in die obere linke Ecke und tippen Sie dann auf eine andere App, die App-Extender unterstützt, um die Anzeige in zwei Fenstern zu aktivieren.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Unverankertes Fenster">
<feature>Das Minifenster kann verschoben und an einer beliebige Position auf dem Startbildschirm platziert werden.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Durch die Installation dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch trotzdem empfohlen, im Vorfeld eine Datensicherung vorzunehmen.
2. Weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen finden Sie in der Tipps-App.
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die HONOR-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein HONOR Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Lieber Nutzer, dieses empfohlene Update führt neue Funktionen ein, mit denen Sie die Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm anpassen und App-Extender mit einem einzigen Streichen aktivieren können. Dieses Update verbessert auch das Benutzererlebnis mit unverankerten Fenstern.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm">
<feature>Die Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm kann an individuelle Bedürfnisse angepasst werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Einstellungen -> Startbildschirm und Stil -> Startbildschirmeinstellungen -> Symbolgröße.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App-Extender">
<feature>App-Extender kann mit nur einem Streichen aufgerufen werden. Ziehen Sie den unteren Rand in die obere linke Ecke und tippen Sie dann auf eine andere App, die App-Extender unterstützt, um die Anzeige in zwei Fenstern zu aktivieren.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Unverankertes Fenster">
<feature>Das Minifenster kann verschoben und an einer beliebige Position auf dem Startbildschirm platziert werden.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Durch die Installation dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch trotzdem empfohlen, im Vorfeld eine Datensicherung vorzunehmen.
2. Weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen finden Sie in der Tipps-App.
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die HONOR-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein HONOR Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Lieber Nutzer, dieses empfohlene Update führt neue Funktionen ein, mit denen Sie die Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm anpassen und App-Extender mit einem einzigen Streichen aktivieren können. Dieses Update verbessert auch das Benutzererlebnis mit unverankerten Fenstern.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm">
<feature>Die Größe der Symbole auf dem Startbildschirm kann an individuelle Bedürfnisse angepasst werden. Wechseln Sie hierfür zu: Einstellungen -> Startbildschirm und Stil -> Startbildschirmeinstellungen -> Symbolgröße.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App-Extender">
<feature>App-Extender kann mit nur einem Streichen aufgerufen werden. Ziehen Sie den unteren Rand in die obere linke Ecke und tippen Sie dann auf eine andere App, die App-Extender unterstützt, um die Anzeige in zwei Fenstern zu aktivieren.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Unverankertes Fenster">
<feature>Das Minifenster kann verschoben und an einer beliebige Position auf dem Startbildschirm platziert werden.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Durch die Installation dieser Aktualisierung werden Ihre persönlichen Daten nicht gelöscht. Es wird jedoch trotzdem empfohlen, im Vorfeld eine Datensicherung vorzunehmen.
2. Weitere Informationen zu den Produktfunktionen finden Sie in der Tipps-App.
3. Wenn bei der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, rufen Sie die HONOR-Service-Hotline an oder besuchen Sie ein HONOR Kunden-Service-Center, um Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η συνιστώμενη ενημέρωση εισάγει νέες λειτουργίες, που σας επιτρέπουν να προσαρμόσετε το μέγεθος των εικονιδίων της Αρχικής οθόνης και να ενεργοποιήσετε την Επέκταση εφαρμογών με ένα μόνο σύρσιμο. Αυτή η ενημέρωση βελτιώνει επίσης την εμπειρία χρήστη του αιωρούμενου παραθύρου.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Εικονίδια αρχικής οθόνης">
<feature>Είναι δυνατή η προσαρμογή του μεγέθους των εικονιδίων της Αρχικής οθόνης για να ταιριάζει με τις ατομικές ανάγκες. Δοκιμάστε αυτή τη λειτουργία μεταβαίνοντας στις εξής επιλογές: Ρυθμίσεις -> Αρχική οθόνη και στυλ -> Ρυθμίσεις αρχικής οθόνης -> Μέγεθος εικονιδίου.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Επέκταση εφαρμογών">
<feature>Είναι δυνατή η κλήση της Επέκτασης εφαρμογών με ένα μόνο σύρσιμο. Σύρετε το κάτω μέρος στην επάνω αριστερή γωνία και, στη συνέχεια, πατήστε μια άλλη εφαρμογή που υποστηρίζει την Επέκταση εφαρμογών για να ενεργοποιήσετε την εμφάνιση σε δύο παράθυρα.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Αιωρούμενο παράθυρο">
<feature>Το μικρό παράθυρο μπορεί να μετακινηθεί και να τοποθετηθεί σε οποιαδήποτε θέση στην αρχική οθόνη.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα διαγράψει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, ωστόσο συνιστάται προηγουμένως η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας.
2. Δείτε περισσότερες πληροφορίες σχετικά με τις δυνατότητες του προϊόντος στην εφαρμογή Συμβουλές.
3. Αν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, μπορείτε να λάβετε τη βοήθειά μας καλώντας την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή εξυπηρέτησης της HONOR ή με επίσκεψη σε ένα Κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update introduces new functions, allowing you to adjust the size of Home screen icons and activate App Extender with a single swipe. This update also improves the user experience of floating window.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Home screen icons">
<feature>The size of Home screen icons can be adjusted to suit individual needs. Experience it by going to: Settings -> Home screen and style -> Home screen settings -> Icon size.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Extender">
<feature>App Extender can be invoked with just one swipe. Drag the bottom to the upper left corner, then tap another app that supports App Extender to enable dual-window display.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Floating window">
<feature>Mini window can be moved and hovered to any position on the home screen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not erase your personal data, but a backup beforehand is still recommended.
2. Check out more information on product features in the Tips app.
3. If you encounter any issues during the update, you can get our help by calling HONOR service hotline or visiting HONOR Customer Service Centre.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada introduce nuevas funciones, que le permiten ajustar el tamaño de los iconos de la pantalla de inicio y activar Extensor de aplicaciones con un solo deslizamiento. Esta actualización también mejora la experiencia de usuario de la ventana flotante.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iconos de la pantalla principal">
<feature>El tamaño de los iconos de la pantalla de inicio puede ajustarse a las necesidades individuales. Experiméntelo en a: Ajustes -> Pantalla principal y estilo -> Ajustes pantalla principal -> Tamaño de icono.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Extensor de aplicaciones">
<feature>Se puede invocar Extensor de aplicaciones con solo deslizar el dedo. Arrastre la parte inferior hacia la esquina superior izquierda y luego toque otra aplicación que admita Extensor de aplicaciones para habilitar la visualización en doble ventana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ventana flotante">
<feature>La miniventana se puede mover y colocar sobre cualquier posición en la pantalla principal.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Aunque la instalación de esta actualización no eliminará sus datos personales, se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad antes.
2. Consulte más información sobre las características del producto en la aplicación Sugerencias.
3. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, puede obtener nuestra ayuda si llama a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o si visita el Centro de servicios de atención al cliente de HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada introduce nuevas funciones, que le permiten ajustar el tamaño de los íconos de la pantalla principal y activar Extensor de aplicaciones con un solo deslizamiento. Esta actualización también mejora la experiencia de usuario de la ventana flotante.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Íconos de la pantalla principal">
<feature>El tamaño de los íconos de la pantalla principal puede ajustarse a las necesidades individuales. Para realizar este cambio, vaya a Ajustes -> Pantalla principal y estilo -> Ajustes de pantalla principal -> Tamaño de ícono.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Extensor de aplicaciones">
<feature>Se puede invocar Extensor de aplicaciones con solo deslizar el dedo. Arrastre la parte inferior hacia la esquina superior izquierda y, luego, toque otra aplicación que admita Extensor de aplicaciones para habilitar la visualización en doble ventana.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ventana flotante">
<feature>La miniventana se puede mover y colocar sobre cualquier posición en la pantalla principal.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Esta actualización no eliminará sus datos personales; sin embargo, le recomendamos hacer una copia de respaldo de los datos antes de actualizar.
2. Consulte más información sobre las funcionalidades del producto en la aplicación Sugerencias.
3. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, puede llamar a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visitar el centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja, see soovitatav värskendus lisab uued funktsioonid avakuva ikoonide suuruse muutmiseks ja rakendusekordisti aktiveerimiseks ühe nipsuga. Ühtlasi parendab see värskendus ujuva akna kasutajakogemust.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Avakuva ikoonid">
<feature>Avakuva ikoonide suurust saab vastavalt vajadusele muuta. Proovimiseks valige Sätted -> Avakuva ja stiil -> Avakuva sätted -> Ikooni suurus.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rakendusekordisti">
<feature>Rakendusekordisti saab avada ühe nipsuga. Lohistage alumisest ülemisse vaskusse nurka ja puudutage teist rakendust, mis toetab rakendusekordistit, misjärel aktiveerub kaheaknaline kuva.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ujuv aken">
<feature>Miniakent saab liigutada ja hõljutada avakuva mis tahes osas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei kustuta teie isikuandmeid, kuid eelnev varundamine on siiski soovitatav.
2. Vaadake toote funktsioonide kohta lisateavet rakendusest Tips.
3. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, saate meilt abi, helistades HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või külastades HONORi klienditeeninduskeskust.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile hori, gomendatutako eguneratze honetan funtzio berriak gehitu dira, eta aukera izango duzu hatza irristatze hutsarekin hasierako pantailako ikonoen tamaina egokitzeko eta Aplikazio-hedatzailea aktibatzeko. Eguneratze honetan, gainera, leiho flotatzailearen erabiltzaile-esperientzia ere hobetu da.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hasierako pantailako ikonoak">
<feature>Norberaren beharretara egokitzeko, hasierako pantailako ikonoen tamaina egokitu daiteke. Probatzeko, joan Ezarpenak -> Hasierako pantaila eta estiloa -> Hasierako pantailako ezarpenak -> Ikonoen tamaina atalera.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aplikazio-hedatzailea">
<feature>Aplikazio-hedatzailea hatza behin irristatuta abiaraz daiteke. Arrastatu behealdea goi-ezkerreko izkinara eta, gero, sakatu Aplikazio-hedatzailea onartzen duen beste aplikazio bat, pantaila bikoitzeko bistaratzea gaitzeko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Leiho flotatzailea">
<feature>Leiho txikia hasierako pantailako edozein posiziotara mugitu eta haren gainetik pasa daiteke.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratzea instalatzen baduzu, ez dira ezabatuko datu pertsonalak; hala ere, gomendagarria da datuen babeskopia bat egitea.
2. Ikusi produktuen eginbideei buruzko informazio gehiago Aholkuak aplikazioan.
3. Arazoren bat baduzu eguneratzea instalatzean, deitu HONOR-en telefonozko arreta-lineara edo jarri harremanetan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentroarekin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>‏کاربر گرامی، عملکردهای جدیدی در این به‌روزرسانی پیشنهادی عرضه می‌شود که به شما امکان می‌دهد اندازه آیکون‌های «صفحۀ اصلی» را تنظیم کنید و «برنامه‌گستر» را با یک بار کشیدن انگشت فعال کنید. این به‌روزرسانی تجربه کاربر پنجرۀ شناور را نیز بهبود می‌بخشد.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏آیکون‌های صفحۀ اصلی">
<feature>‏اندازه آیکون‌های «صفحۀ اصلی» را می‌توان مطابق نیاز شخصی تنظیم کرد. آن را با رفتن به این قسمت تجربه کنید: تنظیمات -> صفحۀ اصلی و سبک -> تنظیمات صفحۀ اصلی -> اندازۀ آیکون.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏برنامه‌گستر">
<feature>‏‏«برنامه‌گستر» را می‌توان تنها با یک بار کشیدن انگشت فراخوانی کرد. از قسمت پایین به گوشه بالا سمت چپ بکشید، سپس روی برنامه دیگری که از «برنامه‌گستر» پشتیبانی می‌کند ضربه بزنید تا نمایش دوپنجره‌ای فعال شود.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏پنجرۀ شناور">
<feature>‏پنجرۀ کوچک را می‌توان به هر موقعیتی در صفحۀ اصلی منتقل کرد و نگه داشت.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏نکات مهم:" type="end">
<feature>‏۱. با نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما پاک نخواهد شد، اما کماکان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام این به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.‎
‏‏۲. اطلاعات بیشتر در مورد قابلیت‌های محصول را در برنامه «نکات» بررسی کنید.
‏‏۳. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، می‌توانید جهت دریافت کمک با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به «مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR» مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä suositeltu päivitys lisää uusia toimintoja, joiden avulla voit säätää Aloitusnäytön kuvakkeiden kokoa ja ottaa Sovelluksen laajentimen käyttöön yhdellä pyyhkäisyllä. Lisäksi tämä päivitys parantaa kelluvan ikkunan käyttökokemusta.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Aloitusnäytön kuvakkeet">
<feature>Aloitusnäytön kuvakkeiden kokoa voidaan säätää yksilöllisten tarpeiden mukaan. Voit kokeilla sitä menemällä kohtaan Asetukset -> Aloitusnäyttö ja tyyli -> Aloitusnäytön asetukset -> Kuvakkeen koko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sovelluksen laajennin">
<feature>Sovelluksen laajennin voidaan avata yhdellä pyyhkäisyllä. Vedä alaosa vasempaan yläkulmaan ja ota sitten kaksoisikkunanäyttö käyttöön napauttamalla toista Sovelluksen laajenninta tukevaa sovellusta.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kelluva ikkuna">
<feature>Mini-ikkuna voidaan siirtää ja kohdistaa mihin tahansa kohtaan aloitusnäytöllä.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei pyyhi henkilökohtaisia tietojasi, mutta niiden varmuuskopiointi ennen asennusta on kuitenkin suositeltavaa.
2. Lisätietoja tuoteominaisuuksista on Vihjeitä-sovelluksessa.
3. Jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia, saat apua soittamalla HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käymällä HONORin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée ajoute de nouvelles fonctions, qui vous permettent d'ajuster la taille des icônes de l'écran d'accueil et d'activer Extension d'application avec le geste Faire glisser. Cette mise à jour améliore également l'expérience utilisateur de la fenêtre flottante.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Icônes de l'écran d'accueil">
<feature>La taille des icônes de l'écran d'accueil peut être ajustée en fonction des besoins individuels. Faites-en l'expérience en accédant à Paramètres -> Écran d'accueil et style -> Paramètres de l'écran d'accueil -> Taille de l'icône.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Extension d'application">
<feature>Extension d'application peut être lancée avec le geste Faire glisser. Faites glisser le bas vers le coin supérieur gauche, puis appuyez sur une autre application qui prend en charge Extension d'application pour activer l'affichage dans deux fenêtres.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fenêtre flottante">
<feature>La mini-fenêtre peut être déplacée et survolée vers n'importe quelle position sur l'écran d'accueil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'effacera pas vos données personnelles, mais une sauvegarde préalable est tout de même recommandée.
2. Consultez plus d'informations sur les fonctionnalités du produit dans l'application Astuces.
3. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes pendant la mise à jour, vous pouvez obtenir de l'aide en contactant la hotline de service HONOR ou en vous rendant dans un centre de services clients HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée ajoute de nouvelles fonctions, qui vous permettent d'ajuster la taille des icônes de l'écran d'accueil et d'activer Extension d'application avec le geste Faire glisser. Cette mise à jour améliore également l'expérience utilisateur de la fenêtre flottante.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Icônes de l'écran d'accueil">
<feature>La taille des icônes de l'écran d'accueil peut être ajustée en fonction des besoins individuels. Faites-en l'expérience en accédant à Paramètres -> Écran d'accueil et style -> Paramètres de l'écran d'accueil -> Taille de l'icône.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Extension d'application">
<feature>Extension d'application peut être lancée avec le geste Faire glisser. Faites glisser le bas vers le coin supérieur gauche, puis appuyez sur une autre application qui prend en charge Extension d'application pour activer l'affichage dans deux fenêtres.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fenêtre flottante">
<feature>La mini-fenêtre peut être déplacée et survolée vers n'importe quelle position sur l'écran d'accueil.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'effacera pas vos données personnelles, mais une sauvegarde préalable est tout de même recommandée.
2. Consultez plus d'informations sur les fonctionnalités du produit dans l'application Astuces.
3. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes pendant la mise à jour, vous pouvez obtenir de l'aide en contactant la hotline de service HONOR ou en vous rendant dans un centre de services clients HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada introduce novas funcionalidades que permiten axustar o tamaño das iconas da Pantalla de inicio e activar Ampliador de aplicacións só con desprazar o dedo unha vez. Esta actualización tamén mellora a experiencia do usuario da ventá flotante.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Iconas da pantalla de inicio">
<feature>O tamaño das iconas da pantalla de inicio pódese axustar para adaptalo ás diferentes necesidades dos usuarios. Pode probar a facelo indo a Configuración -> Pantalla de inicio e estilo -> Configuración da pantalla de inicio -> Tamaño de iconas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ampliador de aplicacións">
<feature>O Ampliador de aplicacións pode invocarse só con pasar o dedo unha vez. Arrastre desde a parte inferior á esquina inferior esquerda, e logo toque noutra aplicación compatible con Ampliador de aplicacións para activar a visualización en pantalla dobre.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ventá flotante">
<feature>A miniventá pode moverse e pousarse en calquera posición da pantalla de inicio.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ao instalar esta actualización non se eliminarán os seus datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar antes unha copia de seguranza.
2. Pode obter máis información acerca das funcións do produto na aplicación Consellos.
3. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou visite o Centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ ભલામણ કરેલ અપડેટ નવા કાર્યોનો પરિચય આપે છે, જે તમને હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્નોના કદને સમાયોજિત કરવાની અને એક જ સ્વાઇપ સાથે એપ્લિકેશન એક્સ્ટેન્ડરને સક્રિય કરવાની અનુમતિ આપે છે. આ અપડેટ ફ્લોટિંગ વિન્ડોના વપરાશકર્તા અનુભવને પણ સુધારે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્ન">
<feature>હોમ સ્ક્રીન ચિહ્નોનું કદ વ્યક્તિગત જરૂરિયાતોને અનુરૂપ ગોઠવી શકાય છે. અહીં જઈને તેનો અનુભવ કરો: સેટિંગ્સ -> હોમ સ્ક્રીન અને શૈલી -> હોમ સ્ક્રીન સેટિંગ્સ -> ચિહ્નનું કદ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="એપ્લિકેશન એક્સ્ટેન્ડર">
<feature>એપ્લિકેશન એક્સ્ટેન્ડરને માત્ર એક સ્વાઇપ સાથે લાગુ કરી શકાય છે. તળિયાને ઉપરના ડાબા ખૂણા તરફ ખેંચો, પછી ડ્યુઅલ-વિન્ડો ડિસ્પ્લેને સક્ષમ કરવા માટે એપ્લિકેશન એક્સ્ટેન્ડરનું સમર્થન કરતી બીજી એપ્લિકેશનને ટૅપ કરો.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ફ્લોટિંગ વિન્ડો">
<feature>મીની વિન્ડોને હોમ સ્ક્રીન પર કોઈપણ સ્થાન પર ખસેડી અને હોવર કરી શકાય છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારો વ્યક્તિગત ડેટા ભૂંસાશે નહીં, પરંતુ તો પણ અગાઉથી બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. ટિપ્સ એપ્લિકેશનમાં ઉત્પાદન સુવિધાઓ વિશે વધુ માહિતી તપાસો.
3. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો તમે HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરીને અથવા HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્રની મુલાકાત લઈને અમારી મદદ મેળવી શકો છો.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अनुशंसित अद्यतन में नए फ़ंक्शन पेश किए गए हैं जिससे आपको होम स्क्रीन आइकन के आकार को समायोजित करने और सिंगल स्वाइप से ऐप एक्सटेंडर को सक्रिय करने की अनुमति मिलती है। इस अद्यतन से फ़्लोटिंग विंडो के उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव को भी बेहतर बनाया जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="होम स्क्रीन के आइकन">
<feature>होम स्क्रीन के आइकन का आकार व्यक्तिगत आवश्यकताओं को पूरा करने के लिए समायोजित किया जा सकता है। आप यहाँ जाकर इसका अनुभव पा सकते हैं: सेटिंग्स -> होम स्क्रीन और शैली -> होम स्क्रीन सेटिंग्स -> आइकन का आकार।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ऐप एक्सटेंडर">
<feature>ऐप एक्सटेंडर को केवल एक स्वाइप से चालू किया जा सकता है। निचले हिस्से को ऊपरी बाएँ कोने पर खींचें, उसके बाद डुअल-विंडो डिस्प्ले को सक्षम करने के लिए ऐप एक्सटेंडर का समर्थन करने वाले किसी अन्य ऐप पर टैप करें।</feature>
</features>
<features module="फ़्लोटिंग विंडो">
<feature>मिनी विंडो को होम स्क्रीन पर किसी भी स्थिति में ले जाया और होवर किया जा सकता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. युक्तियाँ ऐप में उत्पाद की सुविधाओं के बारे में अधिक जानकारी देखें।
3. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो आप HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करके या HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाकर हमारी सहायता पा सकते हैं।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se preporučenim ažuriranjem uvode nove funkcije koje omogućuju prilagođavanje veličina ikona početnog zaslona i aktivaciju Ekstendera aplikacija jednim prelaskom prstom. Ovo ažuriranje poboljšava i iskustvo korištenja plutajućeg prozora.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikone na početnom zaslonu">
<feature>Veličinu ikona početnog zaslona moguće je prilagoditi individualnim potrebama. Isprobajte odlaskom na: Postavke -> Početni zaslon i stil -> Postavke početnog zaslona -> Veličina ikone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ekstender aplikacija">
<feature>Značajku Ekstender aplikacija moguće je pokrenuti samo jednim prelaskom prstom. Povucite donji dio u gornji lijevi kut, a zatim dodirnite drugu aplikaciju koja podržava Ekstender aplikacija za omogućivanje prikaza u dvostrukim prozorima.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Plutajući prozor">
<feature>Mini prozor može se pomicati i lebdjeti na bilo kojem položaju na početnom zaslonu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalacijom ovog ažuriranja neće se izbrisati vaši osobni podaci, ali preporučujemo da ipak prije ažuriranja izradite sigurnosnu kopiju.
2. Idite u aplikaciju Savjeti kako biste provjerili više informacija o značajkama proizvoda.
3. Ako naiđete na bilo kakve probleme tijekom ažuriranja, našu pomoć možete dobiti tako da nazovete HONOR servisnu korisničku službu ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez az ajánlott frissítés új funkciókat vezet be, amelyekkel beállíthatja a főképernyő ikonjainak a méretét, valamint egyetlen mozdulattal aktiválhatja az Alkalmazáskiterjesztőt. Ez a frissítés emellett a lebegő ablakok felhasználói élményét is javítja.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Főképernyő ikonok">
<feature>Mostantól az egyéni igényeinek megfelelően állíthatja be az ikonok méretét a főképernyőn. Próbálja ki: Beállítások -> Főképernyő és stílus -> Főképernyőbeállítások -> Ikon mérete.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Alkalmazáskiterjesztő">
<feature>Egyetlen elhúzással aktiválhatja az Alkalmazáskiterjesztőt. Húzza el az alját a bal felső sarokba, majd a kétablakos megjelenítés engedélyezéséhez koppintson egy másik alkalmazásra, amely támogatja az Alkalmazáskiterjesztőt.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lebegő ablak">
<feature>A miniablakot tetszőleges pozícióba húzhatja a főképernyőn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. E frissítés telepítése nem törli a személyes adatait, de javasoljuk, hogy készítsen előtte biztonsági mentést.
2. A termékjellemzőkről bővebben a Tippek alkalmazásban olvashat.
3. Ha bármilyen problémába ütközik a frissítés során, kérjen tőlünk segítséget: hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati vonalát, vagy keresse fel a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati központját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini memperkenalkan fungsi-fungsi baru, memungkinkan Anda untuk menyesuaikan ukuran ikon Layar beranda dan mengaktifkan Penambah Aplikasi dengan sekali gesek. Pembaruan ini juga meningkatkan pengalaman pengguna jendela melayang.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikon layar beranda">
<feature>Ukuran ikon layar Beranda dapat disesuaikan untuk memenuhi kebutuhan setiap individu. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan -> Layar beranda dan gaya -> Pengaturan layar beranda -> Ukuran ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Penambah Aplikasi">
<feature>Penambah Aplikasi dapat dipicu dengan sekali gesek. Seret bagian bawah ke sudut kiri atas, lalu ketuk aplikasi lain yang mendukung Penambah Aplikasi untuk mengaktifkan tampilan jendela ganda.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Jendela melayang">
<feature>Jendela mini dapat dipindahkan dan diarahkan ke posisi mana pun di layar beranda.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan menghapus data pribadi Anda, tetapi pencadangan sebelumnya tetap direkomendasikan.
2. Periksa informasi selengkapnya terkait fitur produk di aplikasi Kiat.
3. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau mengunjungi Pusat Layanan Pelanggan HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini memperkenalkan fungsi-fungsi baru, memungkinkan Anda untuk menyesuaikan ukuran ikon Layar beranda dan mengaktifkan Penambah Aplikasi dengan sekali gesek. Pembaruan ini juga meningkatkan pengalaman pengguna jendela melayang.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikon layar beranda">
<feature>Ukuran ikon layar Beranda dapat disesuaikan untuk memenuhi kebutuhan setiap individu. Cobalah dengan membuka: Pengaturan -> Layar beranda dan gaya -> Pengaturan layar beranda -> Ukuran ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Penambah Aplikasi">
<feature>Penambah Aplikasi dapat dipicu dengan sekali gesek. Seret bagian bawah ke sudut kiri atas, lalu ketuk aplikasi lain yang mendukung Penambah Aplikasi untuk mengaktifkan tampilan jendela ganda.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Jendela melayang">
<feature>Jendela mini dapat dipindahkan dan diarahkan ke posisi mana pun di layar beranda.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan menghapus data pribadi Anda, tetapi pencadangan sebelumnya tetap direkomendasikan.
2. Periksa informasi selengkapnya terkait fitur produk di aplikasi Kiat.
3. Jika Anda mengalami masalah selama pembaruan, Anda bisa mendapatkan bantuan kami dengan menghubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau mengunjungi Pusat Layanan Pelanggan HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato introduce nuove funzioni che consentono di modificare le dimensioni delle icone della schermata Home e di attivare App Extender con un semplice scorrimento. Inoltre, migliora l'esperienza utente della finestra mobile.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Icone schermata Home">
<feature>È possibile modificare le dimensioni delle icone della schermata Home in base alle proprie esigenze. Per provare questa funzione, vai in: Impostazioni -> Schermata Home e stile -> Impostazioni schermata Home -> Dimensioni delle icone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Extender">
<feature>È possibile avviare App Extender con un semplice scorrimento. Trascina la parte inferiore nell'angolo in alto a sinistra, quindi tocca un'altra app che supporti App Extender per attivare la visualizzazione a finestra doppia.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Finestra mobile">
<feature>La mini finestra può essere spostata e posizionata in qualsiasi posizione della schermata Home.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non comporta l'eliminazione delle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Per ulteriori informazioni sulle funzioni del prodotto, vai in Suggerimenti.
3. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center HONOR o visitando un Centro servizio clienti HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato introduce nuove funzioni che consentono di modificare le dimensioni delle icone della schermata Home e di attivare App Extender con un semplice scorrimento. Inoltre, migliora l'esperienza utente della finestra mobile.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Icone schermata Home">
<feature>È possibile modificare le dimensioni delle icone della schermata Home in base alle proprie esigenze. Per provare questa funzione, vai in: Impostazioni -> Schermata Home e stile -> Impostazioni schermata Home -> Dimensioni delle icone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Extender">
<feature>È possibile avviare App Extender con un semplice scorrimento. Trascina la parte inferiore nell'angolo in alto a sinistra, quindi tocca un'altra app che supporti App Extender per attivare la visualizzazione a finestra doppia.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Finestra mobile">
<feature>La mini finestra può essere spostata e posizionata in qualsiasi posizione della schermata Home.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non comporta l'eliminazione delle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Per ulteriori informazioni sulle funzioni del prodotto, vai in Suggerimenti.
3. In caso di problemi durante l'aggiornamento, puoi richiedere assistenza chiamando il servizio call center HONOR o visitando un Centro servizio clienti HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה מוסיף לראשונה פונקציות חדשות, כדי לאפשר לך להתאים את גודל הסמלים של מסך הבית ולהפעיל את 'מרחיב היישומים' בהחלקה אחת. כמו כן, עדכון זה משפר את חוויית המשתמש של חלון צף.</feature>
</features>
<features module="סמלי מסך הבית">
<feature>ניתן להתאים את גודל הסמלים של מסך הבית כך שיתאימו לצרכים האישיים. ניתן להתנסות בכך על-ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' -> 'מסך הבית וסגנון' -> 'הגדרות מסך הבית' -> 'גודל סמל'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מרחיב היישומים">
<feature>ניתן להפעיל את 'מרחיב היישומים' בהחלקה אחת בלבד. גרור את החלק התחתון לפינה השמאלית העליונה, ולאחר מכן הקש על יישום אחר שתומך ב'מרחיב היישומים' כדי להפעיל תצוגה בשני חלונות.</feature>
</features>
<features module="חלון צף">
<feature>ניתן להזיז ולרחף מיני-חלון לכל מיקום במסך הבית.</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תמחק את הנתונים האישיים שלך. אך עדיין מומלץ לבצע גיבוי קודם לכן.
‏‏2. אפשר למצוא מידע נוסף על תכונות המוצר ביישום 'טיפים'.
‏‏3. אם נתקלת בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, אפשר לקבל עזרה מאיתנו על-ידי התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה מוסיף לראשונה פונקציות חדשות, כדי לאפשר לך להתאים את גודל הסמלים של מסך הבית ולהפעיל את 'מרחיב היישומים' בהחלקה אחת. כמו כן, עדכון זה משפר את חוויית המשתמש של חלון צף.</feature>
</features>
<features module="סמלי מסך הבית">
<feature>ניתן להתאים את גודל הסמלים של מסך הבית כך שיתאימו לצרכים האישיים. ניתן להתנסות בכך על-ידי מעבר אל 'הגדרות' -> 'מסך הבית וסגנון' -> 'הגדרות מסך הבית' -> 'גודל סמל'.</feature>
</features>
<features module="מרחיב היישומים">
<feature>ניתן להפעיל את 'מרחיב היישומים' בהחלקה אחת בלבד. גרור את החלק התחתון לפינה השמאלית העליונה, ולאחר מכן הקש על יישום אחר שתומך ב'מרחיב היישומים' כדי להפעיל תצוגה בשני חלונות.</feature>
</features>
<features module="חלון צף">
<feature>ניתן להזיז ולרחף מיני-חלון לכל מיקום במסך הבית.</feature>
</features>
<features module="הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תמחק את הנתונים האישיים שלך. אך עדיין מומלץ לבצע גיבוי קודם לכן.
‏‏2. אפשר למצוא מידע נוסף על תכונות המוצר ביישום 'טיפים'.
‏‏3. אם נתקלת בבעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, אפשר לקבל עזרה מאיתנו על-ידי התקשרות לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ביקור במרכז שירות לקוחות של HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様。今回の推奨更新では新機能が導入され、ホーム画面のアイコンのサイズを調整したり、1回のスワイプでApp Extenderを起動できるようになります。また、今回の更新でフローティングウィンドウのユーザー体験も向上します。</feature>
</features>
<features module="ホーム画面のアイコン">
<feature>ホーム画面のアイコンのサイズは、個々のニーズに応じて調整できます。この機能は[設定] -> [ホーム画面とスタイル] -> [ホーム画面設定] -> [アイコンのサイズ]に移動して利用できます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Extender">
<feature>App Extenderはたった1回のスワイプで起動できます。下部を左上隅までドラッグしてから、App Extenderをサポートする別のアプリをタップすると、デュアルウィンドウ表示が有効になります。</feature>
</features>
<features module="フローティングウィンドウ">
<feature>ミニウィンドウをホーム画面で移動して、任意の位置でホバリングさせることができます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報が消去されることはありませんが、事前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 製品の機能の詳細については、ヒントアプリで確認してください。
3. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターまでご来店ください。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ამ რეკომენდებულ განახლებას შემოაქვს ახალი ფუნქციები, რაც საშუალებას გაძლევთ, თითის ერთი გადასმით დაარეგულიროთ საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამების ზომა და გაააქტიუროთ აპის გამაფართოებელი. ეს განახლება ასევე აუმჯობესებს მცურავი ფანჯრის მომხმარებლის გამოცდილებას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამები">
<feature>საწყისი ეკრანის პიქტოგრამების ზომა შეიძლება დარეგულირდეს ინდივიდუალური საჭიროებების შესაბამისად. ამის გაკეთება შეგიძლიათ მენიუში: პარამეტრები -> საწყისი ეკრანი და სტილი -> საწყისი ეკრანის პარამეტრები -> პიქტოგრამის ზომა.</feature>
</features>
<features module="აპის გამაფართოებელი">
<feature>აპის გამაფართოებლის გამოძახება შესაძლებელია თითის მხოლოდ ერთი გადასმით. ჩავლებით გადაიტანეთ ქვედა მხარე მარცხენა ზედა კუთხეში, შემდეგ შეეხეთ მეორე აპს, რომელსაც აქვს აპის გამაფართოებლის მხარდაჭერა, რომ ჩართოთ ორმაგი ფანჯრის ჩვენება.</feature>
</features>
<features module="მცურავი ფანჯარა">
<feature>შესაძლებელია მინიფანჯრის გადატანა და დაკიდება საწყისი ეკრანის ნებისმიერ პოზიციაზე.</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ გამოიწვევს თქვენი პერსონალური მონაცემების წაშლას, თუმცა, მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. პროდუქტის ფუნქციების შესახებ დამატებითი ინფორმაცია იხილეთ აპში „რჩევები“.
3. განახლების დროს პრობლემები თუ შეგექმნებათ, ჩვენგან დახმარების მისაღებად შეგიძლიათ დარეკოთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან ეწვიოთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл ұсынылған жаңарту негізгі экран белгішелерінің өлшемін реттеуге және «Қолданбаны кеңейткіш» мүмкіндігін бір рет жанап өту арқылы белсендіруге мүмкіндік беретін жаңа функцияларды ұсынады. Сондай-ақ бұл жаңарту қалқымалы терезенің пайдаланушы тәжірибесін жақсартады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Негізгі экран белгішелері">
<feature>Негізгі экран белгішелерінің өлшемін жеке қажеттіліктерге сай реттеуге болады. Келесіге өту арқылы оны қолданып көріңіз: «Параметрлер» -> «Негізгі экран және стиль» -> «Негізгі экран параметрлері» -> «Белгіше өлшемі».</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қолданбаны кеңейткіш">
<feature>«Қолданбаны кеңейткіш» мүмкіндігін бір ғана жанап өту арқылы шақыруға болады. Төменгі жағын жоғарғы сол жақ бұрышқа сүйреп, қос терезе дисплейін қосу үшін «Қолданбаны кеңейткіш» мүмкіндігін қолдайтын басқа қолданбаны түртіңіз.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Қалқымалы терезе">
<feature>Шағын терезені жылжытуға және негізгі экрандағы кез келген орынға апаруға болады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнатсаңыз, жеке деректер өшпейді, бірақ бұрынғы сақтық көшірме әлі де ұсынылады.
2. «Кеңестер» қолданбасында өнім мүмкіндіктері туралы қосымша ақпаратты тексеріңіз.
3. Жаңарту кезінде қандай да бір мәселе орын алса, HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне қоңырау шалу не HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына бару арқылы көмегімізді ала аласыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពដែលបានណែនាំនេះដាក់ចេញមុខងារថ្មី ដែលអនុញ្ញាតឱ្យអ្នកលៃតម្រូវទំហំរូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម និងដាក់ឲ្យ​ដំណើរការមុខងារពង្រីកបន្ថែមកម្មវិធីដោយគ្រាន់តែវាសម្រាមដៃមួយ។ បច្ចុប្បន្នភាពនេះក៏កែលម្អបទពិសោធអ្នកប្រើវិនដូអណ្ដែតផងដែរ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="រូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម">
<feature>ទំហំរូបតំណាងអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើមអាចត្រូវបានលៃតម្រូវ ដើម្បីបំពេញតាមតម្រូវការខុសៗគ្នា។ ទទួលបទពិសោធប្រើប្រាស់វាបានដោយចូលទៅកាន់៖ ការកំណត់ -> អេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម និងរចនាបថ -> ការកំណត់អេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម -> ទំហំរូបតំណាង។</feature>
</features>
<features module="មុខងារពង្រីកបន្ថែមកម្មវិធី">
<feature>មុខងារពង្រីកបន្ថែមកម្មវិធីអាចត្រូវបានបើកដំណើរការដោយគ្រាន់តែវាសម្រាមដៃមួយ។ ចុចអូសផ្នែកខាងក្រោមទៅជ្រុងខាងឆ្វេងខាងលើ រួចប៉ះកម្មវិធីមួយទៀតដែលអាចប្រើមុខងារពង្រីកបន្ថែមកម្មវិធី ដើម្បីបើកការបង្ហាញវិនដូពីរ។</feature>
</features>
<features module="វិនដូអណ្ដែត">
<feature>វិនដូខ្នាតតូចអាចត្រូវបានផ្លាស់ទី និងដាក់ព្រួញពីលើទៅទីតាំងណាមួយនៅលើអេក្រង់ទំព័រដើម។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​លុបទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ចេញទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ពិនិត្យមើល​ព័ត៌មានបន្ថែមអំពី​លក្ខណៈពិសេសផលិតផលនៅក្នុងកម្មវិធីគន្លឹះ។
3. ប្រសិនបើ​អ្នក​ជួបប្រទះបញ្ហា​ណាមួយ​ក្នុងអំឡុង​ការធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ អ្នកអាច​ទទួល​ជំនួយ​របស់យើង​បាន​ដោយ​ហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័ស​សេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬ​ទៅកាន់​មជ្ឈមណ្ឌលសេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಿದ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಹೊಸ ಕಾರ್ಯಗಳನ್ನು ಪರಿಚಯಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳ ಗಾತ್ರವನ್ನು ಸರಿಹೊಂದಿಸಲು ಮತ್ತು ಒಂದೇ ಸ್ವೈಪ್‌ನ ಮೂಲಕ ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಎಕ್ಸ್‌ಟೆಂಡರ್ ಅನ್ನು ಸಕ್ರಿಯಗೊಳಿಸಲು ನಿಮಗೆ ಅನುಮತಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಫ್ಲೋಟಿಂಗ್ ವಿಂಡೋದ ಬಳಕೆದಾರ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಸಹ ಸುಧಾರಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳು">
<feature>ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಐಕಾನ್‌ಗಳ ಗಾತ್ರವನ್ನು ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಅಗತ್ಯಗಳಿಗೆ ಹೊಂದಿಕೊಳ್ಳುವಂತೆ ಸರಿಹೊಂದಿಸಬಹುದು. ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು -> ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಮತ್ತು ಶೈಲಿ -> ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್ ಸೆಟ್ಟಿಂಗ್‌ಗಳು -> ಐಕಾನ್ ಗಾತ್ರ ಎಂಬಲ್ಲಿಗೆ ಹೋಗುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಇದರ ಅನುಭವವನ್ನು ಪಡೆಯಿರಿ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಎಕ್ಸ್‌ಟೆಂಡರ್">
<feature>ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಎಕ್ಸ್‌ಟೆಂಡರ್ ಅನ್ನು ಕೇವಲ ಒಂದು ಸ್ವೈಪ್‌ನ ಮೂಲಕ ಕರೆಯಬಹುದು. ಡ್ಯುಯಲ್-ವಿಂಡೋ ಡಿಸ್‌ಪ್ಲೇಯನ್ನು ಸಕ್ರಿಯಗೊಳಿಸಲು ಕೆಳಭಾಗವನ್ನು ಮೇಲಿನ ಎಡ ಮೂಲೆಗೆ ಎಳೆಯಿರಿ, ನಂತರ ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಎಕ್ಸ್‌ಟೆಂಡರ್ ಅನ್ನು ಬೆಂಬಲಿಸುವ ಮತ್ತೊಂದು ಆ್ಯಪ್ ಅನ್ನು ಟ್ಯಾಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಫ್ಲೋಟಿಂಗ್ ವಿಂಡೋ">
<feature>ಮಿನಿ ವಿಂಡೋವನ್ನು ಹೋಮ್ ಸ್ಕ್ರೀನ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಯಾವುದೇ ಸ್ಥಾನಕ್ಕೆ ಸರಿಸಬಹುದು ಮತ್ತು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸ್ಥಾನದಲ್ಲಿ ಸುಳಿದಾಡುವಂತೆ ಮಾಡಬಹುದು.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಅಳಿಸುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ಮುಂಚಿತವಾಗಿ ಬ್ಯಾಕ್‌ಅಪ್ ಮಾಡಿ ಇಡಲು ಈಗಲೂ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ಸಲಹೆಗಳು ಆ್ಯಪ್‌ನಲ್ಲಿ ಉತ್ಪನ್ನ ಸೌಲಭ್ಯಗಳ ಕುರಿತು ಹೆಚ್ಚಿನ ಮಾಹಿತಿಯನ್ನು ಪರಿಶೀಲಿಸಿ.
3. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ನೀವು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ಅಥವಾ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಭೇಟಿ ನೀಡುವ ಮೂಲಕ ನಮ್ಮ ಸಹಾಯವನ್ನು ಪಡೆಯಬಹುದು.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 권장 업데이트에서는 홈 화면 아이콘의 크기를 조정하고 스와이프 한 번으로 앱 확장 프로그램을 활성화할 수 있는 새로운 기능이 도입되었습니다. 이 업데이트는 플로팅 윈도우의 사용자 경험도 개선합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="홈 화면 아이콘">
<feature>홈 화면 아이콘의 크기는 개인의 필요에 맞게 조정할 수 있습니다. 설정 -> 홈 화면 및 스타일 -> 홈 화면 설정 -> 아이콘 크기로 이동하면 직접 체험해 볼 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="앱 확장 프로그램">
<feature>앱 확장 프로그램은 스와이프 한 번으로 호출할 수 있습니다. 하단을 왼쪽 상단으로 드래그한 다음 앱 확장 프로그램을 지원하는 다른 앱을 탭하여 이중 창 표시를 실행합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="플로팅 윈도우">
<feature>미니 윈도우는 홈 화면의 원하는 위치로 이동하고 마우스를 가져갈 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터는 삭제되지 않지만, 사전에 백업하시기를 권장합니다.
2. Tips 앱에서 제품 기능에 대한 자세한 정보를 확인하세요.
3. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인으로 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터를 방문하여 도움을 받을 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ທີ່​ແນະ​ນຳນີ້​ແນະ​ນຳ​ຟັງ​ຊັນ​ໃໝ່, ເຊິ່ງ​ອະ​ນຸ​ຍາດ​ໃຫ້​ທ່ານ​ປັບ​ຂະ​ໜາດ​ຂອງ​ໄອ​ຄອນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ ແລະ ເປີດ​ນຳ​ໃຊ້​ຕົວ​ຂະ​ຫຍາຍ​ແອັບ​ດ້ວຍ​ການ​ປັດ​ຄັ້ງ​ດຽວ. ນອກນັ້ນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​​ຍັງປັບ​ປຸງ​ປະ​ສົບ​ການ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້​​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ລອຍ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໄອ​ຄອນໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ">
<feature>​ສາ​ມາດ​ປັບຂະ​ໜາດ​ຂອງໄອ​ຄອນໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ​ໃຫ້​ເໝາະ​ສົມ​ກັບ​ຄວາມ​ຕ້ອງ​ການສ່ວນ​ບຸກ​ຄົນ​ໄດ້. ສຳ​ຜັດ​ປະ​ສົບ​ການມັນ​ໂດຍ​ການ​ໄປ​ທີ່: ການ​ຕັ້ງ​ຄ່າ -> ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ ແລະ ຮູບ​ແບບ -> ການຕັ້ງຄ່າໜ້າຈໍຫຼັກ -> ຂະ​ໜາດ​ໄອ​ຄອນ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ຕົວ​ຂະ​ຫຍາຍ​ແອັບ">
<feature>ສາ​ມາດ​ຮຽກ​ໃຊ້ຕົວ​ຂະ​ຫຍາຍ​ແອັບ​ໄດ້​ດ້ວຍ​ການ​ປັດ​ພຽງ​ຄັ້ງ​ດຽວ. ລາກ​ດ້ານ​ລຸ່ມ​ສຸດ​ໄປ​ຫາ​ມຸມ​ຊ້າຍດ້ານ​ເທິງ, ຈາກນັ້ນ ແຕະ​​ອີກແອັບ​​ທີ່​ຮອງ​ຮັບຕົວ​ຂະ​ຫຍາຍ​ແອັບ ເພື່ອ​ເປີດ​ໃຊ້​ງານ​ການສະ​ແດງ​ຜົນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ຄູ່.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ລອຍ">
<feature>ໜ້າ​ຈໍ​ນ້ອຍສາ​ມາດ​ຍ້າຍ ແລະ ລອຍ​ຕົວ​ໄປ​ຫາ​ຕຳ​ແໜ່ງ​ໃດ​ໜຶ່ງ​ໃນ​ໜ້າ​ຈໍຫຼັກ​ໄດ້.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການຕິດຕັ້ງການອັບເດດນີ້ຈະບໍ່ລຶບຂໍ້ມູນສ່ວນຕົວຂອງທ່ານ, ແຕ່ຍັງ​ຄົງຂໍແນະນຳໃຫ້ມີ​ການສຳຮອງຂໍ້ມູນໄວ້ລ່ວງໜ້າ.
2. ກວດ​ເບິ່ງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ເພີ່ມ​ເຕີມ​ກ່ຽວ​ກັບ​ຄຸນ​ສົມ​ບັດ​ຜະ​ລິດ​ຕະ​ພັນ​ໃນ​ແອັບ​ເຄັດ​ລັບ.
3. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ທ່ານສາມາດຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອຈາກພວກເຮົາໄດ້ ໂດຍການໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນ​ບໍ​ລິ​ການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šiuo rekomenduojamu naujiniu pristatomos naujos funkcijos, leidžiančios reguliuoti pražios ekrano piktogramų dydį ir vienu perbraukimu aktyvuoti programėlių plėstuvą. Šiuo naujiniu taip pat pagerinama slankiojo lango naudotojo patirtis.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pradžios ekrano piktogramos">
<feature>Pradžios ekrano piktogramų dydį galima reguliuoti pagal individualius poreikius. Išbandykite tai nuėję į „Nuostatos -> Pradžios ekranas ir stilius -> Pradžios ekrano nuostatos -> Piktogramos dydis“.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Programėlių plėstuvas">
<feature>Programėlių plėstuvą galima iškviesti vos vienu perbraukimu. Nuvilkite apačią į viršutinį kairįjį kampą, tada palieskite kitą programėlę, kuri dera su programėlių plėstuvo funkcija, kad įjungtumėte dviejų langų rodinį.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Slankusis langas">
<feature>Minilangą galima perkelti ir užkelti į bet kurią pradžios ekrano vietą.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį naujinį, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys ištrinti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama iš anksto padaryti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Daugiau informacijos apie produktų funkcijas rasite Patarimų programėlėje.
3. Jei naujinimo metu kiltų bet kokių problemų, galite kreiptis į mus pagalbos paskambindami HONOR priežiūros karštąja linija arba apsilankydami HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centre.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo ieteicamo atjauninājumu tiek ieviestas jaunas funkcijas, kas ļauj pielāgot sākuma ekrāna ikonu izmēru un aktivizēt funkciju Lietotņu paplašinātājs ar vienu pavilkšanu. Šis atjauninājums arī uzlabo peldošā loga lietošanas iespējas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sākuma ekrāna ikonas">
<feature>Sākuma ekrāna ikonu lielumu var pielāgot atbilstoši individuālajām vajadzībām. Izbaudiet to, atverot: Iestatījumi -> Sākuma ekrāns un stils -> Sākuma ekrāna iestatījumi -> Ikonas izmērs.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lietotņu paplašinātājs">
<feature>Funkciju Lietotņu paplašinātājs var izsaukt tikai ar vienu pavilkšanu. Velciet apakšējo daļu uz augšējo kreiso stūri, pēc tam pieskarieties citai lietotnei, kas atbalsta funkciju Lietotņu paplašinātājs, iespējotu attēlošanu divos logos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Peldošais logs">
<feature>Mini logu var pārvietot un novietot uz jebkuru pozīciju sākuma ekrānā.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Instalējot šo atjauninājumu, jūsu personas dati netiks dzēsti, taču joprojām ir ieteicams iepriekš izveidot dublējumu.
2. Lietotnē Padomi skatiet vairāk par produkta funkcijām.
3. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, varat saņemt mūsu palīdzību, zvanot uz HONOR klientu apkalpošanas dienesta tālruni vai apmeklējot HONOR klientu pakalpojumu centru.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अनुशंसित अपडेट नव फंक्शन सभ प्रस्तुत करैत अछि, जे अहाँ केँ होम स्क्रीन आइकन सभक आकार समायोजित करबाक अनुमति दैत अछि आओर एकल स्वाइप सँ एप एक्सटेंडर सक्रिय करैत अछि। ई अपडेट फ्लोटिंग विंडो केर उपयोगकर्ता अनुभव मे सुधार सेहो करैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="होम स्क्रीन आइकन सभ">
<feature>होम स्क्रीन आइकन केर आकार व्यक्तिगत आवश्यकता सभक अनुरूप समायोजित कयल जा सकैत अछि। एहि मे जा कए एकरा अनुभव करू: सेटिंग्स -> होम स्क्रीन आ शैली -> होम स्क्रीनक सेटिंग्स -> आइकनक आकार।</feature>
</features>
<features module="एप एक्सटेंडर">
<feature>एप एक्सटेंडर केँ मात्र एक स्वाइप सँ चालू कयल जा सकैत अछि। निचला हिस्सा केँ उपरका बामा कोना पर खींचू, तकर बाद ड्यूअल-विंडो डिस्प्ले केँ सक्षम करबाक लेल एप एक्सटेंडर केर सपोर्ट करए वला कोनो दोसर एप पर टैप करू।</feature>
</features>
<features module="फ्लोटिंग विंडो">
<feature>मिनी विंडो केँ होम स्क्रीन पर कोनो स्थिति मे मूव आ हॉवर कयल जा सकैत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणी:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहि मेटायत, मुदा तैयो पहिने सँ एकटा बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. टिप्स एप मे उत्पादक विशेषताक बेसी जानकारी प्राप्त करू।
3. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन केँ कॉल कए वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जा कए अहाँ हमरासभ सँ मदति प्राप्त कए सकैत छी।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E te kaiwhakamahi, ka whakamōhiotia e tēnei whakahōutanga manako ngā taumahi hōu, e āhei ai koe ki te whakarite i te rahi o ngā ata Mata kāinga me te whakahohe i te Pūwhakawhānui Taupānga ki tētahi miri kotahi. Ka whakapai ake hoki tēnei whakahōu i te wheako kaiwhakamahi o te matapihi māu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā ata mata kāinga">
<feature>Ka taea te huri i te rahi o ngā ata mata Kāinga kia hāngai ki ia hiahia. Wheako mā te haere: Ngā tautuhinga -> Mata Kāinga me te kāhua -> Ngā tautuhinga mata kāinga -> Rahi ata.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pūwhakawhānui Taupānga">
<feature>Ka taea te whakatara i te Pūwhakawhānui Taupānga me te miri kotahi noa iho. Tōia whakararo ki te kokonga mauī o runga, ka pato i tētahi atu taupānga e tautoko ana i te Pūwhakawhānui Taupānga hei whakahohe i te whakaaturanga iti-rua.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Matapihi māu">
<feature>Ka taea te nuku i te matapihi iti me te whakaparo ki tētahi tūnga i te mata kāinga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Ki te tāutahia tēnei whakahōu kāore e mukua ō ngā raraunga whaiaro, engari e tūtohua ana kia pūruatia i mua.
2. Tirohia ētahi anō mōhiohio mō ngā āhuahira hua i te taupānga Ngā Aki.
3. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi take i te wā o te whakahōutanga, ka taea e koe te tiki i tā mātou āwhina mā te waea i te raina waeawera ratonga HONOR, te toro rānei i te Pokapū Ratonga Kiritaki HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова препорачано ажурирање воведува нови функции, со што ви се овозможува да ја прилагодите големината на иконите на почетниот екран и да активирате Проширувач на апликации со едно поминување. Ова ажурирање исто така го подобрува корисничкото искуство со лебдечки прозорец.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Икони на почетниот екран">
<feature>Големината на иконите на почетниот екран може да се прилагодува за да се задоволат индивидуалните потреби. Искусете преку одење во: Нагодување -> Почетен екран и стил -> Поставки за почетниот екран -> Големина на икони.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Проширувач на апликации">
<feature>Проширувач на апликации може да се повика со само едно поминување. Повлечете го дното кон горниот лев агол, па допрете друга апликација што поддржува Проширувач на апликации за да овозможите приказ на двоен прозорец.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Лебдечки прозорец">
<feature>Мини прозорец може да се преместува и да лебди во која било позиција во почетниот екран.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да ги избрише вашите лични податоци, но сепак се препорачува претходно правење резервна копија.
2. Проверете за повеќе информации за карактеристиките на производот во Совети.
3. Ако наидете на какви било проблеми при ажурирањето, може да ја добиете нашата помош со повикување на телефонскиот број на службата на HONOR или посета на Центарот за услуги за корисници на HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്ന അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കണുകളുടെ വലുപ്പം ക്രമീകരിക്കാനും ഒരൊറ്റ സ്വൈപ്പിൽ ആപ്പ് എക്സ്റ്റെൻഡർ ആക്‌ടിവേറ്റ് ചെയ്യാനും നിങ്ങളെ അനുവദിക്കുന്ന പുതിയ പ്രവർത്തനങ്ങൾ അവതരിപ്പിക്കുന്നു. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഫ്ലോട്ടിംഗ് വിൻഡോയുടെ ഉപയോക്തൃ അനുഭവവും മെച്ചപ്പെടുത്തുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കണുകൾ">
<feature>വെവ്വേറെ ആവശ്യകതകൾക്ക് ഇണങ്ങുന്ന വിധത്തിൽ ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ഐക്കണുകളുടെ വലുപ്പം ക്രമീകരിക്കാൻ കഴിയും. ഇതിലേക്ക് പോയി അത് അനുഭവിച്ചറിയുക: ക്രമീകരണം -> ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനും ശൈലിയും -> ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീൻ ക്രമീകരണം -> ഐക്കൺ വലുപ്പം.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ആപ്പ് എക്സ്റ്റെൻഡർ">
<feature>വെറുമൊരു സ്വൈപ്പിൽ ആപ്പ് എക്സ്റ്റെൻഡർ സജീവമാക്കാൻ കഴിയും. ഇരട്ട വിൻഡോയിൽ പ്രദർശിപ്പിക്കുന്നത് പ്രവർത്തനസജ്ജമാക്കാൻ, ചുവടുഭാഗം മുകളിൽ ഇടതുകോണിലേക്ക് ഡ്രാഗ് ചെയ്‌ത ശേഷം ആപ്പ് എക്സ്റ്റെൻഡറിനെ പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കുന്ന മറ്റൊരു ആപ്പിൽ ടാപ്പ് ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ഫ്ലോട്ടിംഗ് വിൻഡോ">
<feature>ഹോം സ്‌ക്രീനിൽ ഏതൊരു സ്ഥാനത്തേക്കും മിനി വിൻഡോ നീക്കാനും ഹോവർ ചെയ്യാനും കഴിയും.</feature>
</features>
<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ മായ്‌ക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും മുൻകൂട്ടി ഒരു ബാക്കപ്പ് എടുത്തുവയ്‌ക്കാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. 'നുറുങ്ങുകൾ' ആപ്പിൽ ഉൽപ്പന്ന സവിശേഷതകൾ സംബന്ധിച്ച കൂടുതൽ വിവരങ്ങൾ പരിശോധിക്കുക.
3. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടയിൽ നിങ്ങൾക്ക് എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്‌ത് ഞങ്ങളുടെ സഹായം കരസ്ഥമാക്കാവുന്നതാണ്.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү санал болгож буй шинэчлэлтээр шинэ функцүүд танилцуулж байгаа бөгөөд энэ нь танд нэг зурах үйлдлээр үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зургийн хэмжээг тохируулах, Апликэйшн өргөтгөгчийг идэвхжүүлэх боломжийг олгоно. Энэхүү шинэчлэлтээр хөвөгч цонхны хэрэглэгчийн туршлагыг сайжруулсан.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зураг">
<feature>Үндсэн дэлгэцийн шигтгээ зургийн хэмжээг хувь хүний хэрэгцээнд нийцүүлэн тохируулах боломжтой. Та Тохиргоо -> Үндсэн дэлгэц ба хэв маяг -> Үндсэн дэлгэцийн тохиргоо -> Шигтгээ зургийн хэмжээ рүү очиж үүнийг туршиж үзэж болно.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Апликэйшн өргөтгөгч">
<feature>Апликэйшн өргөтгөгчийг зөвхөн нэг зурах үйлдлээр дуудаж болно. Доод хэсгийг зүүн дээд булан руу чирээд, дараа нь Апликэйшн өргөтгөгчийг дэмждэг өөр апликэйшн дээр дарж хос цонхтой дэлгэцийг идэвхжүүлнэ үү.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Хөвдөг цонх">
<feature>Мини цонхыг үндсэн дэлгэцийн аль ч байрлалд шилжүүлж, зөөвөрлөх боломжтой.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгахад таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч урьдчилан нөөцлөхийг зөвлөж байна.
2. Зөвлөгөө апликэйшн дээрээс бүтээгдэхүүний онцлогийн талаар нэмэлт мэдээллийг харна уу.
3. Шинэчлэх явцад аливаа асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR Хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төвд зочилж тусламж авна уу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे शिफारस केलेले अद्यतन नवीन फंक्शन्स सादर करते, जे तुम्हाला मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्हांचा आकार समायोजित करण्याची आणि एकाच स्वाइपने ॲप एक्सटेंडर सक्रिय करण्याची अनुमती देते. हे अद्यतन फ्लोटिंग विंडोचा वापरकर्ता अनुभव देखील सुधारतो.</feature>
</features>
<features module="मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्हे">
<feature>मुख्य स्क्रीन चिन्हांचा आकार वैयक्तिक गरजांनुसार समायोजित केला जाऊ शकतो. येथे जाऊन त्याचा अनुभव घ्या: सेटिंग्ज -> मुख्य स्क्रीन आणि शैली -> मुख्य स्क्रीन सेटिंग्ज -> चिन्हाचा आकार.</feature>
</features>
<features module="अ‍ॅप एक्सटेंडर">
<feature>अ‍ॅप एक्स्टेंडरला फक्त एका स्वाइपने लागू केले जाऊ शकते. तळाशी असलेला भाग वरच्या डाव्या कोपऱ्यात ओढा, त्यानंतर दुहेरी-विंडो डिस्प्ले सक्षम करण्यासाठी ॲप एक्स्टेंडरला समर्थन देणाऱ्या दुसऱ्या ॲपवर टॅप करा.</feature>
</features>
<features module="फ्लोटिंग विंडो">
<feature>मिनी विंडो हलवता येते आणि मुख्य स्क्रीनवरील कोणत्याही स्थानावर फिरवता येते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्‍थापित केल्याने आपला वैयक्तिक डेटा मिटणार नाही, पण तरीही आधीच बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. Tips अ‍ॅपमध्ये उत्पादन वैशिष्ट्यांबद्दल अधिक माहिती पहा.
3. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, आपण HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करून किंवा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जाऊन आमची मदत मिळवू शकता.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini yang disyorkan ini memperkenalkan fungsi baharu, membenarkan anda melaraskan saiz ikon Skrin utama dan mengaktifkan Pelanjut Aplikasi dengan satu leretan. Kemas kini ini juga meningkatkan pengalaman pengguna tetingkap apungan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikon skrin utama">
<feature>Saiz ikon Skrin utama boleh dilaraskan mengikut keperluan individu. Cuba ciri ini dengan pergi ke: Tetapan -> Skrin utama dan gaya -> Tetapan skrin utama -> Saiz ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pelanjut Aplikasi">
<feature>Pelanjut Aplikasi boleh digunakan dengan hanya satu leretan. Seret bahagian bawah ke penjuru kiri sebelah atas, kemudian ketik aplikasi lain yang menyokong Pelanjut Aplikasi untuk mendayakan paparan dwitetingkap.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tetingkap apungan">
<feature>Tetingkap mini boleh dianjakkan dan dilayangkan ke mana-mana kedudukan pada skrin utama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Pemasangan kemas kini ini tidak akan memadamkan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda disyorkan agar masih membuat sandaran terlebih dahulu.
2. Semak maklumat lanjut tentang ciri produk dalam aplikasi Tip.
3. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang isu semasa pengemaskinian, anda boleh mendapatkan bantuan daripada kami dengan menghubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau melawati Pusat Servis Pelanggan HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ အကြံပြုထားသော ဤအပ်ဒိတ်တွင် လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်အသစ်များနှင့် မိတ်ဆက်ပေးထားပြီး ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် အိုင်ကွန်များ၏ အရွယ်အစားကို ချိန်ညှိနိုင်စေကာ တစ်ချက်ပွတ်ဆွဲရုံဖြင့် အက်ပ်တိုးချဲ့ကို ဖွင့်နိုင်စေသည်။ ဤအပ်ဒိတ်သည် Floating ဝင်းဒိုး သုံးစွဲရသည့် အတွေ့အကြုံကိုလည်း မြှင့်တင်ပေးသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် အိုင်ကွန်များ">
<feature>သုံးစွဲသူတစ်ဦးချင်းစီ၏ လိုအပ်ချက်များကို ဖြည့်ဆည်းပေးရန် ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် အိုင်ကွန်များ၏ အရွယ်အစားကို ချိန်ညှိနိုင်သည်။ သင်သည် ဆက်တင် -> ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်နှင့် စတိုင် -> ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင် ဆက်တင် -> အိုင်ကွန် အရွယ်အစားသို့ သွား၍ ၎င်းကို တွေ့ကြုံသုံးစွဲနိုင်သည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="အက်ပ်တိုးချဲ့">
<feature>တစ်ချက်ပွတ်ဆွဲရုံဖြင့် အက်ပ်တိုးချဲ့ကို ဖွင့်နိုင်သည်။ ဝင်းဒိုးနှစ်ခုဖြင့် ပြသမှုကို ဖွင့်ရန် အောက်ခြေကို အပေါ်ဘယ်ဘက်ထောင့်သို့ ဆွဲရွှေ့ပြီးနောက် အက်ပ်တိုးချဲ့သုံးနိုင်သော အခြားအက်ပ်ကို နှိပ်ပါ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Floating ဝင်းဒိုး">
<feature>ပင်မ မျက်နှာပြင်တွင် မီနီဝင်းဒိုးကို မည်သည့်နေရာသို့မဆို ရွှေ့နိုင်ပြီး ကာဆာဝဲနိုင်သည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းက သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာကို ပျက်စေမည်မဟုတ်သော်လည်း ကြိုတင်၍ ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. ထုတ်ကုန် လုပ်‌ဆောင်ချက်များအကြောင်း နောက်ထပ်အချက်အလက်များကို Tips အက်ပ်တွင် ကြည့်ရှုပါ။
3. အပ်ဒိတ်လုပ်စဉ်အတွင်း ပြဿနာတစ်စုံတစ်ရာ ကြုံရပါက HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းကို ဖုန်းခေါ်ဆို၍ဖြစ်စေ၊ HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွား၍ဖြစ်စေ ကျွန်ုပ်တို့၏ အကူအညီကို ရယူနိုင်ပါသည်။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ အႀကံျပဳထားေသာ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္တြင္ လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္အသစ္မ်ားႏွင့္ မိတ္ဆက္ေပးထားၿပီး ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ား၏ အ႐ြယ္အစားကို ခ်ိန္ညႇိႏိုင္ေစကာ တစ္ခ်က္ပြတ္ဆြဲ႐ုံျဖင့္ အက္ပ္တိုးခ်ဲ႕ကို ဖြင့္ႏိုင္ေစသည္။ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္သည္ Floating ဝင္းဒိုး သုံးစြဲရသည့္ အေတြ႕အႀကဳံကိုလည္း ျမႇင့္တင္ေပးသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ား">
<feature>သုံးစြဲသူတစ္ဦးခ်င္းစီ၏ လိုအပ္ခ်က္မ်ားကို ျဖည့္ဆည္းေပးရန္ ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ အိုင္ကြန္မ်ား၏ အ႐ြယ္အစားကို ခ်ိန္ညႇိႏိုင္သည္။ သင္သည္ ဆက္တင္ -> ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ႏွင့္ စတိုင္ -> ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္ ဆက္တင္ -> အိုင္ကြန္ အ႐ြယ္အစားသို႔ သြား၍ ၎ကို ေတြ႕ႀကဳံသုံးစြဲႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="အက္ပ္တိုးခ်ဲ႕">
<feature>တစ္ခ်က္ပြတ္ဆြဲ႐ုံျဖင့္ အက္ပ္တိုးခ်ဲ႕ကို ဖြင့္ႏိုင္သည္။ ဝင္းဒိုးႏွစ္ခုျဖင့္ ျပသမႈကို ဖြင့္ရန္ ေအာက္ေျခကို အေပၚဘယ္ဘက္ေထာင့္သို႔ ဆြဲေ႐ႊ႕ၿပီးေနာက္ အက္ပ္တိုးခ်ဲ႕သုံးႏိုင္ေသာ အျခားအက္ပ္ကို ႏွိပ္ပါ။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Floating ဝင္းဒိုး">
<feature>ပင္မ မ်က္ႏွာျပင္တြင္ မီနီဝင္းဒိုးကို မည္သည့္ေနရာသို႔မဆို ေ႐ႊ႕ႏိုင္ၿပီး ကာဆာဝဲႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းက သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာကို ပ်က္ေစမည္မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း ႀကိဳတင္၍ ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. ထုတ္ကုန္ လုပ္‌ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ားအေၾကာင္း ေနာက္ထပ္အခ်က္အလက္မ်ားကို Tips အက္ပ္တြင္ ၾကည့္ရႈပါ။
3. အပ္ဒိတ္လုပ္စဥ္အတြင္း ျပႆနာတစ္စုံတစ္ရာ ႀကဳံရပါက HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းကို ဖုန္းေခၚဆို၍ျဖစ္ေစ၊ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြား၍ျဖစ္ေစ ကြၽႏ္ုပ္တို႔၏ အကူအညီကို ရယူႏိုင္ပါသည္။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, denne anbefalte oppdateringen introduserer nye funksjoner, noe som gjør at du kan justere størrelsen på Startskjerm-ikonene og aktivere App-utvidelse med et enkelt sveip. Denne oppdateringen forbedrer også brukeropplevelsen med svevende vindu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Startskjermikoner">
<feature>Størrelsen på startskjermikoner kan justeres for å passe til individuelle behov. Opplev det ved å gå til: Innstillinger -> Startskjerm og stil -> Innstillinger for startskjerm -> Ikonstørrelse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App-utvidelse">
<feature>App-utvidelse kan startes bare med ett sveip. Dra bunnen til øverste venstre hjørne og trykk deretter på den andre appen som støtter App-utvidelse for å vise appene i doble vinduer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Svevende vindu">
<feature>Minivindu kan flyttes og sveves til enhver posisjon på startskjermen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke slette personopplysningene dine, men det anbefales likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer på forhånd.
2. Se mer informasjon om produktfunksjoner i Tips-appen.
3. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, kan du få hjelp av oss ved å ringe til HONOR-kundeservice eller besøke et HONOR-kundeservicesenter.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, सिफारिस गरिएको यो अपडेटले नयाँ सुविधाहरू ल्याएको छ र तपाईं ती सुविधा प्रयोग गरी एक स्वाइप गरेकै भरमा गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरूको आकार बदल्न र एप एक्स्टेन्डर सक्रिय गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ । यो अपडेटले फ्लोटिङ विन्डोको प्रयोगकर्ता अनुभव पनि सुधार गर्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरू">
<feature>प्रयोगकर्ताका व्यक्तिगत आवश्यकताहरू पूरा गर्नका लागि गृह स्क्रिनका आइकनहरूको आकार बदल्न मिल्छ । यसको अनुभव लिन यहाँ जानुहोस्: सेटिङहरू -> गृह स्क्रिन र शैली -> गृह स्क्रिन सेटिङहरू -> आइकनको साइज ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="एप एक्स्टेन्डर">
<feature>एक स्वाइप गरेकै भरमा एप एक्स्टेन्डर सक्रिय गर्न सकिन्छ । पुछारलाई तानेर सिरानको बायाँ कुनामा लैजानुहोस् अनि डुअल विन्डोमा देखाउने सुविधा सक्षम गर्न एप एक्स्टेन्डर प्रयोग गर्न मिल्ने अर्को एपमा ट्याप गर्नुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="फ्लोटिङ विन्डो">
<feature>मिनी विन्डो सार्न सकिन्छ र गृह स्क्रिनमा कुनै पनि स्थानमा होभर गर्न सकिन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. यो अपडेट स्थापना गर्नाले तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटा मेटिने छैन तर अझै पनि पहिले नै ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. सुझावहरू नामक एपमा गई उत्पादनका सुविधाहरूका बारेमा थप जानकारी हेर्नुहोस् ।
3. अपडेटको क्रममा तपाईंले कुनै समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईं HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गरेर वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा गएर हाम्रो मद्दत प्राप्त गर्न सक्नुहुन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruiker, deze aanbevolen update introduceert nieuwe functies, waarmee u de grootte van pictogrammen op het Startscherm kunt aanpassen en App-uitbreider met één veeg kunt activeren. Deze update verbetert ook de gebruikerservaring van zwevend venster.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pictogrammen op startscherm">
<feature>De grootte van de pictogrammen op het Startscherm kan worden aangepast om aan individuele behoeften te voldoen. Ervaar het door te gaan naar: Instellingen -> Startscherm en stijl -> Startscherminstellingen -> Pictogramgrootte.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App-uitbreider">
<feature>App-uitbreider kan met slechts één veeg worden geactiveerd. Sleep de onderkant naar de linkerbovenhoek en tik vervolgens op een andere app die App-uitbreider ondersteunt om weergave op twee vensters mogelijk te maken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Zwevend venster">
<feature>Het minivenster kan worden verplaatst en naar elke positie op het startscherm worden bewogen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Het installeren van deze update zal uw persoonlijke gegevens niet wissen, maar een back-up vooraf wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Bekijk meer informatie over productfuncties in de Tips-app.
3. Als u tijdens de update problemen ondervindt, kunt u onze hulp krijgen door de HONOR-servicehotline te bellen of naar het HONOR-klantenservicecentrum te gaan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଥିବା ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌‌ରେ ନୂତନ ଫଙ୍କସନ୍ ରହିଛି, ଯାହା ଆପଣଙ୍କୁ ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍ ଆଇକନ୍‌ର ଆକାର ଆଡଜଷ୍ଟ କରିବାକୁ ଏବଂ ଗୋଟିଏ ସ୍ୱାଇପ୍‌ରେ ଆପ୍‌ ପରିବର୍ଦ୍ଧକକୁ ସକ୍ରିୟ କରିବାକୁ ଦେଇଥାଏ। ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ଭାସମାନ ୱିଣ୍ଡୋର ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ଅନୁଭୂତିରେ ମଧ୍ୟ ବିକାଶ ଆଣିଥାଏ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍‌">
<feature>ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଆଇକନ୍‌ର ଆକାର ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଆବଶ୍ୟକତା ପୂରଣ କରିବାକୁ ଆଡଜଷ୍ଟ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ। ଏଥିକୁ ଯାଇ ଏହାର ଅନୁଭୂତି ନିଅନ୍ତୁ: ସେଟିଂସ୍ -> ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ଏବଂ ଷ୍ଟାଇଲ୍‌ -> ହୋମ୍‌ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌ ସେଟିଂସ୍ -> ଆଇକନ୍ ଆକାର।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଆପ୍‌ ପରିବର୍ଦ୍ଧକ">
<feature>ଆପ୍‌ ପରିବର୍ଦ୍ଧକ ମାତ୍ର ଗୋଟିଏ ସ୍ୱାଇପ୍‌ରେ ଅପସାରଣ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ। ବାମ କୋଣକୁ ନିମ୍ନଭାଗ ଡ୍ରାଗ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ, ଏବଂ ତାପରେ ଡୁଆଲ୍‌ ୱିଣ୍ଡୋସ୍‌ ପ୍ରଦର୍ଶନ ସକ୍ଷମ କରିବାକୁ ଆପ୍‌ ପରିବର୍ଦ୍ଧକ ସମର୍ଥନ କରୁଥିବା ଅନ୍ୟ ଆପ୍‌କୁ ଟ୍ୟାପ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ଭାସମାନ ୱିଣ୍ଡୋ">
<feature>ଛୋଟ ୱିଣ୍ଡୋ ହୋମ୍ ସ୍କ୍ରିନ୍‌‌ରେ ଯେକୌଣସି ସ୍ଥିତିକୁ ଘୁଞ୍ଚାଯାଇ ପାରିବ ଏବଂ ହୋଭର୍‌ କରାଯାଇ ପାରିବ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ଲିଭାଇବ ନାହିଁ, କିନ୍ତୁ ଏହା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଏକ ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଟିପ୍ସ ଆପ୍‌ରେ ଉତ୍ପାଦ ବିଶେଷତାଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଉପରେ ଅଧିକ ସୂଚନା ଯାଞ୍ଚ କରି ନିଅନ୍ତୁ।
3. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ କରିବା ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଆପଣ HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌କୁ କଲ୍‌ କରି କିମ୍ବା HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଇ, ଆମ ସହାୟତା ପାଇପାରିବେ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਹ ਸਿਫਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੇ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਨਵੇਂ ਫੰਕਸ਼ਨ ਪੇਸ਼ ਕੀਤੇ ਗਏ ਹਨ, ਜਿਨ੍ਹਾਂ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨਾਂ ਦੇ ਆਕਾਰ ਨੂੰ ਵਿਵਸਥਿਤ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ ਅਤੇ ਇੱਕ ਸਵਾਈਪ ਨਾਲ ਐਪ ਐਕਸਟੈਂਡਰ ਨੂੰ ਕਿਰਿਆਸ਼ੀਲ ਕਰ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ। ਇਹ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਫਲੋਟਿੰਗ ਵਿੰਡੋ ਦੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਨੂੰ ਵੀ ਬਿਹਤਰ ਬਣਾਉਂਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨ">
<feature>ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਆਈਕੋਨਾਂ ਦਾ ਆਕਾਰ ਵਿਅਕਤੀਗਤ ਲੋੜਾਂ ਦੇ ਅਨੁਕੂਲ ਬਣਾਉਣ ਲਈ ਵਿਵਸਥਿਤ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ ਇੱਥੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਅਨੁਭਵ ਕਰੋ: ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ -> ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਅਤੇ ਸਟਾਈਲ -> ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ ਸੈਟਿੰਗਾਂ -> ਆਈਕੋਨ ਦਾ ਆਕਾਰ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਐਪ ਐਕਸਟੈਂਡਰ">
<feature>ਐਪ ਐਕਸਟੈਂਡਰ ਨੂੰ ਸਿਰਫ਼ ਇੱਕ ਸਵਾਈਪ ਨਾਲ ਕਿਰਿਆਸ਼ੀਲ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ। ਹੇਠਲੇ ਪਾਸੇ ਨੂੰ ਖਿੱਚ ਕੇ ਉੱਪਰਲੇ ਖੱਬੇ ਕੋਨੇ 'ਤੇ ਲੈ ਜਾਓ, ਉਸਤੋਂ ਬਾਅਦ ਡੂਅਲ-ਵਿੰਡੋ ਡਿਸਪਲੇ ਨੂੰ ਸਮਰੱਥ ਕਰਨ ਵਾਸਤੇ ਐਪ ਐਕਸਟੈਂਡਰ ਦਾ ਸਮਰਥਨ ਕਰਨ ਵਾਲੀ ਕਿਸੇ ਹੋਰ ਐਪ 'ਤੇ ਟੈਪ ਕਰੋ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਫਲੋਟਿੰਗ ਵਿੰਡੋ">
<feature>ਮਿਨੀ ਵਿੰਡੋ ਨੂੰ ਹੋਮ ਸਕ੍ਰੀਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਿਸੇ ਵੀ ਸਥਿਤੀ ਵਿੱਚ ਲਿਜਾਇਆ ਅਤੇ ਘੁਮਾਇਆ ਜਾ ਸਕਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਨਹੀਂ ਮਿਟੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਸੁਝਾਅ ਐਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਉਤਪਾਦ ਦੀਆਂ ਵਿਸ਼ੇਸ਼ਤਾਵਾਂ ਬਾਰੇ ਹੋਰ ਜਾਣਕਾਰੀ ਦੇਖੋ।
3. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰ ਕੇ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾ ਕੇ ਸਾਡੀ ਮਦਦ ਲੈ ਸਕਦੇ ਹੋ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta zalecana aktualizacja wprowadza nowe funkcje, umożliwiające dostosowanie rozmiaru ikon na Ekranie głównym i aktywację Rozszerzonego wyświetlania aplikacji jednym przeciągnięciem. Ta aktualizacja poprawia także komfort użytkowania okna przestawnego.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikony na ekranie głównym">
<feature>Rozmiar ikon na Ekranie głównym można dostosować do indywidualnych potrzeb. W tym celu wybierz Ustawienia -> Ekran główny i styl -> Ustawienia ekranu głównego -> Rozmiar ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rozszerzone wyświetlanie aplikacji">
<feature>Rozszerzone wyświetlanie aplikacji można wywołać jednym przeciągnięciem. Przeciągnij od dołu do lewego górnego rogu, a następnie dotknij innej aplikacji obsługującej Rozszerzone wyświetlanie aplikacji, aby włączyć wyświetlanie w dwóch oknach.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Okno przestawne">
<feature>Małe okno można przenieść i ustawić w dowolnym położeniu na ekranie głównym.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie powoduje wymazania danych użytkownika. Zalecamy jednak uprzednie wykonanie kopii zapasowej.
2. Więcej informacji o funkcjach produktu zawiera aplikacja Porady.
3 Jeśli podczas aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, możesz uzyskać pomoc, dzwoniąc na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedzając punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Prezado(a) usuário(a), esta atualização recomendada apresenta novas funções, permitindo que você ajuste o tamanho dos ícones da Tela inicial e ative o Extensor de aplicativo com apenas um deslizar. Esta atualização também aprimora a experiência de usuário com a janela flutuante.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ícones da tela inicial">
<feature>Os tamanhos dos ícones da Tela inicial podem ser ajustados para atender a necessidades individuais. Experimente acessando: Configurações -> Tela inicial e estilo -> Configurações da tela inicial ->Tamanho do ícone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Extensor de aplicativo">
<feature>O Extensor de aplicativo pode ser ativado com apenas um deslizar. Arraste da parte inferior para o canto superior esquerdo e toque em outro aplicativo compatível com o Extensor de aplicativo para ativar a exibição em janelas duplas.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Janela flutuante">
<feature>A minijanela pode ser movida e posicionada em qualquer lugar na tela inicial.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. A instalação desta atualização não apagará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Confira mais informações sobre as características do produto no aplicativo Dicas.
3. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, poderá obter ajuda ligando para a linha de atendimento da HONOR ou visitando a Central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente da HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização recomendada introduz novas funções, permitindo-lhe ajustar o tamanho dos ícones do Ecrã inicial e ativar e ativar a Extensão de aplicações com um simples toque. Esta atualização também melhora a experiência do utilizador da janela flutuante.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ícones do ecrã inicial">
<feature>O tamanho dos ícones do ecrã inicial pode ser ajustado de acordo com as necessidades individuais. Experimente, acedendo a: Definições -> Ecrã inicial e estilo -> Definições do ecrã inicial -> Tamanho do ícone.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Extensão de aplicações">
<feature>A Extensão de aplicações pode ser ativada com apenas um toque. Arraste a parte inferior para o canto superior esquerdo e, de seguida, toque noutra aplicação que suporte a Extensão de aplicações para ativar o ecrã de janela dupla.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Janela flutuante">
<feature>A mini-janela pode ser movida e colocada em qualquer posição no ecrã inicial.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não elimina os seus dados pessoais, mas continua a recomendar-se a realização prévia de uma cópia de segurança.
2. Obtenha mais informações sobre as funcionalidades dos produtos na aplicação Sugestões.
3. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, pode obter a nossa ajuda ligando para a linha direta de apoio HONOR ou visitando o Centro de Serviços ao Cliente HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare recomandată introduce noi funcții, permițându-vă să ajustați dimensiunea pictogramelor de pe ecranul de pornire și să activați funcția Extindere aplicații cu o singură glisare. Această actualizare îmbunătățește, de asemenea, experiența utilizatorului cu ferestrele flotante.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pictograme pe ecranul de pornire">
<feature>Dimensiunea pictogramelor de pe ecranul de pornire poate fi ajustată pentru a satisface diferitele nevoi ale utilizatorilor. Puteți încerca această funcție din Setări -> Ecran de pornire și stil -> Setări ecran de pornire -> Dimensiunea pictogramei.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Extindere aplicații">
<feature>Funcția Extindere aplicații poate fi apelată cu o singură glisare. Trageți de jos spre colțul din stânga sus, apoi atingeți o altă aplicație care acceptă funcția Extindere aplicații pentru a activa afișarea în două ferestre.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Fereastră flotantă">
<feature>Mini-fereastra poate fi mutată și plasată în orice poziție de pe ecranul de pornire.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu vă va șterge datele personale, dar vă recomandăm totuși să realizați în prealabil o copie de rezervă.
2. Aflați mai multe informații despre caracteristicile produsului din aplicația Sugestii.
3. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, puteți obține ajutorul nostru sunând la linia de asistență telefonică HONOR sau vizitând Centrul de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы разработали это рекомендованное обновление, чтобы внедрить новые функции, настройку размера значков на рабочем экране и возможность активации функции App Extender одним движением пальца, а также улучшить пользовательский интерфейс плавающего окна.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Значки рабочего экрана">
<feature>Чтобы настроить размер значков рабочего стола, перейдите в раздел «Настройки > Рабочий экран и стиль > Настройки экрана > Размер значков».</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Extender">
<feature>Функцию App Extender можно вызвать, проведя пальцем по экрану. Перетащите нижнюю часть в верхний левый угол, а затем нажмите на другое приложение, поддерживающее функцию App Extender, чтобы включить отображение в двух окнах.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Плавающее окно">
<feature>Вы можете перемещать миниокно в любое место на рабочем экране.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не приведет к удалению ваших персональных данных, но мы рекомендуем сделать резервную копию всех важных данных, прежде чем приступить к установке.
2. Вы найдете дополнительную информацию о функциях продукта в приложении «Советы».
3. При возникновении проблем во время обновления обратитесь за помощью на горячую линию службы поддержки HONOR или в сервисный центр для клиентов HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, ඔබට තනි ස්වයිප් කිරීමකින් මුල් තිර අයිකනවල ප්‍රමාණය සීරු මාරු කිරීමට සහ යෙදුම් විස්තාරකය සක්‍රිය කරන්නට ඉඩ දෙමින් මෙම නිර්දේශිත යාවත්කාලය නව ක්‍රියාකාරීත්ව හඳුන්වා දෙයි. මෙම යාවත්කාලය පාවෙන කවුළුවේ පරිශීලක අත්දැකීම ද වැඩි දියුණු කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="මුල් තිර අයිකන">
<feature>පුද්ගලයාගේ අවශ්‍යතාවලට ගැළපෙන පරිදි මුල් තිර අයිකනවල ප්‍රමාණය සීරු මාරු කළ හැකිවනු ඇත. මෙය වෙත යාමෙන් එය අත්විඳින්න: සැකසුම් -> මුල් තිරය සහ විලාසය -> මුල් තිර සැකසුම් -> අයිකනයේ ප්‍රමාණය.</feature>
</features>
<features module="යෙදුම් විස්තාරකය">
<feature>හුදෙක් එක් ස්වයිප් කිරීමකින් යෙදුම් විස්තාරකය කැඳවීමට හැකිවනු ඇත. ද්විත්ව කවුළු සංදර්ශකය සබල කරන්නට පහළ කෙළවර ඉහළ වම් කෙළවරට ඇදගෙන ගොස්, ඉන්පසු යෙදුම් විස්තාරකයට සහය දක්වන වෙනත් යෙදුමක් තට්ටු කරන්න.</feature>
</features>
<features module="පාවෙන කවුළුව">
<feature>කුඩා කවුළුව මුල් තිරයේ ඕනෑම පිහිටීමකට ගෙන යාමට සහ මතින් ගෙන යාමට හැකිවනු ඇත.</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්ත නොමකනු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් ඊට පෙර උපස්ථ කිරීමක් නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. ඉඟි යෙදුම තුළ නිෂ්පාදන විශේෂාංග පිළිබඳ තවත් තොරතුරු පරීක්ෂා කරන්න.
3. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේදී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, ඔබට HONOR සේවා හොට්ලයින් ඇමතීමෙන් හෝ HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට පිවිසීමෙන් අපගේ උපකාර ලබා ගත හැකිය.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený používateľ, táto odporúčaná aktualizácia prináša nové funkcie, ktoré umožňujú upravovať veľkosť ikon na domovskej obrazovke a aktivovať Extender aplikácií jediným potiahnutím prstom. Táto aktualizácia tiež zlepšuje používateľskú skúsenosť s plávajúcim oknom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikony na domovskej obrazovke">
<feature>Veľkosť ikon domovskej obrazovky možno upraviť podľa individuálnych potrieb. Vyskúšajte to v časti: Nastavenia -> Domovská obrazovka a štýl -> Nastavenia domovskej obrazovky -> Veľkosť ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Extender aplikácií">
<feature>Extender aplikácií možno vyvolať jediným potiahnutím prstom. Potiahnite spodnú časť do ľavého horného rohu a ťuknutím na inú aplikáciu podporujúcu Extender aplikácií zapnite zobrazenie v dvoch oknách.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Plávajúce okno">
<feature>Miniokno možno presunúť a umiestniť na ľubovoľnú pozíciu na domovskej obrazovke.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštaláciou tejto aktualizácie sa nevymažú vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča vopred si ich zálohovať.
2. Ďalšie informácie o funkciách produktu nájdete v aplikácii Tipy.
3. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytne problém, pomoc môžete získať na zákazníckej linke HONOR alebo navštívením servisného strediska spoločnosti HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta priporočena posodobitev uvaja nove funkcije, s katerimi lahko prilagodite velikost ikon na začetnem zaslonu in z enim potegom prsta aktivirate razširitev za aplikacije. S to posodobitvijo se izboljša tudi uporabniška izkušnja plavajočega okna.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikone na začetnem zaslonu">
<feature>Velikost ikon na začetnem zaslonu lahko prilagodite individualnim potrebam. To lahko storite tako, da obiščete: Nastavitve -> Domači zaslon in slog -> Nastavitve domačega zaslona -> Velikost ikon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Razširitev za aplikacije">
<feature>Razširitev za aplikacije lahko prikličete z enim samim potegom. Povlecite s spodnjega dela v zgornji levi kot, nato pa se dotaknite druge aplikacije, ki podpira razširitev za aplikacije, da omogočite prikaz dveh oken.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Plavajoče okno">
<feature>Mini okno lahko premaknete in v lebdečem položaju postavite v poljuben položaj na začetnem zaslonu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Z namestitvijo te posodobitve vaši osebni podatki ne bodo izbrisani, vendar priporočamo, da jih predhodno varnostno kopirate.
2. Več informacij o funkcijah izdelkov je na voljo v aplikaciji Nasveti.
3. Če med posodabljanjem naletite na težave, lahko pokličete odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom družbe HONOR ali obiščete servisni center družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, den här rekommenderade uppdateringen introducerar nya funktioner som gör att du kan justera storleken på startsidans ikoner och aktivera Apputökare med ett enda svep. Den här uppdateringen förbättrar också användarupplevelsen av flytande fönster.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikoner på startsidan">
<feature>Storleken på startsidans ikoner kan justeras så de passar individuella behov. Prova själv genom att gå till: Inställningar -> Startsida och stil -> Inställningar för startsidan -> Ikonstorlek.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Apputökare">
<feature>Apputökare kan tas fram med bara ett svep. Dra från nederkanten till det övre vänstra hörnet, tryck sedan på en annan app som stöder Apputökare för att aktivera visning i dubbla fönster.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Flytande fönster">
<feature>Minifönster kan flyttas och hovras till valfri position på startsidan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Den här uppdateringen raderar inga personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du gör en säkerhetskopia innan du installerar den.
2. Se mer information om produktfunktioner i appen Tips.
3. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs kundservicecenter för att få hjälp.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili linalopendekezwa linaleta vipengele vipya, hivyo basi kukuwezesha kurekebisha ukubwa wa ikoni za Skrini ya mwanzo na kuwezesha Kienezi Programu kwa kutelezesha kidole tu. Sasisho hili pia linaboresha uzoefu wa mtumiaji wa dirisha linaloelea.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ikoni za skrini ya mwanzo">
<feature>Ukubwa wa ikoni za skrini ya mwanzo unaweza kurekebishwa ili kukidhi mahitaji yako binafsi. Furahia kipengele hiki kwa kwenda kwenye: Mipangilio -> Skrini ya mwanzo na mtindo -> Mipangilio ya skrini ya mwanzo -> Ukubwa wa ikoni.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kienezi Programu">
<feature>Kienezi Programu kinaweza kuanzishwa kwa kutelezesha kidole tu. Kokota upande wa chini hadi kona ya juu kushoto, kisha gusa programu nyingine inayotumia Kienezi Programu ili kuwezesha onyesho la madirisha mawili.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Dirisha linaloelea">
<feature>Dirisha ndogo linaweza kusogezwa na kuenezwa hadi kwenye eneo lolote kwenye skrini.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutafuta data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado hifadhi rudufu inapendekezwa kabla ya kusakinisha.
2. Angalia maelezo zaidi ya vipengele vya bidhaa kwenye programu ya Vidokezo.
3. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, unaweza kupata msaada wetu kwa kupiga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au kutembelea Kituo cha Huduma kwa Wateja cha HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படும் புதுப்பிப்பு புதிய செயல்பாடுகளை அறிமுகப்படுத்துகிறது, இது முகப்புத் திரை ஐகானின் அளவைச் சரிசெய்யவும் ஒற்றை ஸ்வைப்பில் செயலி நீட்டிப்பியைச் செயல்படுத்தவும் அனுமதிக்கிறது. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பு மிதவைச் சாளரத்தின் பயனர் அனுபவத்தையும் மேம்படுத்துகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான்கள்">
<feature>முகப்புத் திரை ஐகான்களின் அளவைத் தனிநபரின் தேவைக்கு ஏற்ப சரிசெய்யலாம். இதற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலம் நீங்கள் அதைப் பயன்படுத்தலாம்: அமைப்புகள் -> முகப்புத் திரை மற்றும் ஸ்டைல் -> முகப்புத் திரை அமைப்புகள் -> ஐகான் அளவு.</feature>
</features>
<features module="செயலி நீட்டிப்பி">
<feature>செயலி நீட்டிப்பியை ஒரே ஒரு ஸ்வைப் மூலம் செயல்படுத்த முடியும். இரட்டைச் சாளரக் காட்சியைச் செயல்படுத்த, கீழிருந்து மேல் இடது மூலைக்கு இழுத்து, பின்னர் செயலி நீட்டிப்பியை ஆதரிக்கும் மற்றொரு செயலியைத் தட்டவும்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="மிதவைச் சாளரம்">
<feature>முகப்புத் திரையில் எந்த நிலைக்கும் மினி சாளரத்தை நகர்த்தலாம், ஹோவர் செய்யலாம்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவை அழிக்காது, எனினும் தொடர்வதற்கு முன் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுக்குமாறு பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. தயாரிப்பு அம்சங்களைப் பற்றிய கூடுதல் தகவல்களை உதவிக்குறிப்புகள் செயலியில் பார்க்கவும்.
3. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைப்பதன் மூலமோ அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்வதன் மூலமோ எங்கள் உதவியைப் பெறலாம்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ సిఫార్సు చేయబడిన అప్‌డేట్ కొత్త ఫంక్షన్‌లను పరిచయం చేస్తుంది, ఇవి మిమ్మల్ని హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాల పరిమాణాన్ని మార్చడానికి మరియు ఒక స్వైప్‌తో అప్లికేషన్ ఎక్స్‌టెండర్‌ను యాక్టివేట్ చేయడానికి అనుమతిస్తాయి. ఈ అప్‌డేట్ తేలియాడే విండో యొక్క వినియోగదారు అనుభవాన్ని కూడా మెరుగుపరుస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాలు">
<feature>వ్యక్తిగతంగా తగినట్లు హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ చిహ్నాల పరిమాణాన్ని సర్దుబాటు చేయవచ్చు. మీరు ఇక్కడికి వెళ్లి దానిని ఆనందించవచ్చు: సెట్టింగ్‌లు -> హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ మరియు శైలి -> హోమ్ స్క్రీన్ సెట్టింగ్‌లు -> చిహ్నం పరిమాణం.</feature>
</features>
<features module="అప్లికేషన్ ఎక్స్‌టెండర్">
<feature>అప్లికేషన్ ఎక్స్‌టెండర్‌ను ఒక స్వైప్‌తో పొందవచ్చు. దిగువ భాగాన్ని ఎగువ ఎడమ మూలకు లాగండి, ఆపై డ్యూయల్-విండో ప్రదర్శనను ప్రారంభించడానికి అప్లికేషన్ ఎక్స్‌టెండర్‌కు మద్దతు ఇచ్చే మరొక అప్లికేషన్‌ను ట్యాప్ చేయండి.</feature>
</features>
<features module="తేలియాడే విండో">
<feature>మినీ విండోను హోమ్ స్క్రీన్‌లో ఏదైనా స్థానానికి తరలించవచ్చు మరియు ఉంచవచ్చు.</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వలన మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటా ఎరేజ్ చేయబడదు, కాని ముందుగానే బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. చిట్కాలు అప్లికేషన్‌లో ఉత్పత్తి ఫీచర్‌లపై మరింత సమాచారాన్ని తనిఖీ చేయండి.
3. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీకు ఏవైనా సమస్యలు ఎదురైనట్లయితే, మీరు HONOR సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేసి లేదా HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి సందర్శించి మా సహాయాన్ని పొందవచ్చు.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตที่แนะนำครั้งนี้เปิดตัวฟังก์ชันใหม่ซึ่งช่วยให้คุณปรับขนาดไอคอนหน้าจอหลักและเปิดใช้งาน App Extender โดยปัดนิ้วครั้งเดียว การอัปเดตนี้ยังปรับปรุงการใช้งานของผู้ใช้ของหน้าต่างแบบลอยอีกด้วย</feature>
</features>
<features module="ไอคอนหน้าจอหลัก">
<feature>ปรับขนาดไอคอนหน้าจอหลักให้ตรงกับความต้องการที่ต่างกันของผู้ใช้ได้ คุณสามารถลองได้โดยไปที่: การตั้งค่า -> หน้าจอหลักและสไตล์ -> การตั้งค่าหน้าจอหลัก -> ขนาดไอคอน</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Extender">
<feature>สามารถเรียกใช้ App Extender ได้ด้วยการปัดนิ้วเพียงครั้งเดียว ลากด้านล่างขึ้นไปที่มุมบนซ้าย จากนั้นแตะแอปอื่นที่สนับสนุน App Extender เพื่อเปิดใช้งานการแสดงผลสองหน้าต่าง</feature>
</features>
<features module="หน้าต่างแบบลอย">
<feature>สามารถย้ายหน้าต่างขนาดเล็กและวางไว้ที่ตำแหน่งใดก็ได้บนหน้าจอหลัก</feature>
</features>
<features module="โปรดทราบ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่ลบข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เรายังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลล่วงหน้า
2. ดูข้อมูลเพิ่มเติมเกี่ยวกับฟีเจอร์ของผลิตภัณฑ์ได้ในแอปเคล็ดลับ
3. หากคุณพบปัญหาใด ๆ ระหว่างการอัปเดต คุณสามารถรับความช่วยเหลือของเราได้โดยการติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการลูกค้าของ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ HONOR</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, ipinapakilala ng inirerekomendang update na ito ang mga bagong function, na nagbibigay-daan sa iyong i-adjust ang laki ng mga icon ng Home screen at i-activate ang App Extender sa isang pag-swipe. Pinapahusay ng update na ito ang karanasan ng user ng lumulutang na window.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga icon sa home screen">
<feature>Puwedeng i-adjust ang laki ng mga icon ng Home screen para iangkop ang mga indibidwal na pangangailangan. Maranasan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Home screen at estilo -> Mga setting ng home screen -> Laki ng icon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Extender">
<feature>Mapapalabas ang App Extender sa isang swipe lang. I-drag ang ibaba sa kaliwang sulok sa itaas, pagkatapos ay i-tap ang isa pang app na sumusuporta sa App Extender para i-enable ang dual-window na display.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lumulutang na window">
<feature>Puwedeng galawin ang mini window at i-hover sa anumang posisyon sa home screen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi buburahin ng update na ito ang iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa rin ang pag-back up bago gawin ito.
2. Tingnan ang higit pang impormasyon sa mga feature ng produkto sa app na Mga Tip.
3. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, makakakuha ka ng aming tulong sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pagbisita sa Customer Service Center ng HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, ipinapakilala ng inirerekomendang update na ito ang mga bagong function, na nagbibigay-daan sa iyong i-adjust ang laki ng mga icon ng Home screen at i-activate ang App Extender sa isang pag-swipe. Pinapahusay ng update na ito ang karanasan ng user ng lumulutang na window.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga icon sa home screen">
<feature>Puwedeng i-adjust ang laki ng mga icon ng Home screen para iangkop ang mga indibidwal na pangangailangan. Maranasan ito sa pamamagitan ng pagpunta sa: Mga Setting > Home screen at estilo -> Mga setting ng home screen -> Laki ng icon.</feature>
</features>
<features module="App Extender">
<feature>Mapapalabas ang App Extender sa isang swipe lang. I-drag ang ibaba sa kaliwang sulok sa itaas, pagkatapos ay i-tap ang isa pang app na sumusuporta sa App Extender para i-enable ang dual-window na display.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lumulutang na window">
<feature>Puwedeng galawin ang mini window at i-hover sa anumang posisyon sa home screen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi buburahin ng update na ito ang iyong personal na data, pero inirerekomenda pa rin ang pag-back up bago gawin ito.
2. Tingnan ang higit pang impormasyon sa mga feature ng produkto sa app na Mga Tip.
3. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang isyu habang nag-a-update, makakakuha ka ng aming tulong sa pamamagitan ng pagtawag sa hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pagbisita sa Customer Service Center ng HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Sayın kullanıcı; yeni işlevler sağlayan bu önerilen güncelleme ile Başlangıç ekranı simgelerinizin boyutunu ayarlayabilecek ve tek kaydırma hareketiyle Uygulama Genişleticiyi etkinleştirebileceksiniz. Bu güncelleme ayrıca kayar pencere ile ilgili kullanıcı deneyimini iyileştirir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Başlangıç ekranı simgeleri">
<feature>Başlangıç ekranı simgelerinin boyutları kişisel ihtiyaçları karşılamak için ayarlanabilir. Ayarlar -> Başlangıç ekranı ve stil -> Başlangıç ekranı ayarları -> Simge boyutu adımlarını takip ederek bu deneyimi kendiniz yaşayabilirsiniz.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uygulama Genişletici">
<feature>Uygulama Genişletici sadece bir kaydırma hareketiyle çalıştırılabilir. Sol üst köşeden aşağı sürükleyin, ardından ikili pencere görünümünü etkinleştirmek için Uygulama Genişleticiyi destekleyen başka bir uygulama üzerine dokunun.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kayan pencere">
<feature>Mini pencere artık başlangıç ekranındaki herhangi bir konuma taşınabilir ve sürüklenebilir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi silmeyecektir, fakat yine de öncesinde yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. İpuçları uygulamasında ürün özellikleri hakkında daha fazla bilgiye göz atabilirsiniz.
3. Güncelleme sırasında bir sorun yaşamanız durumunda HONOR servis yardım hattını arayarak veya HONOR Müşteri Hizmetleri Merkezini ziyaret ederek yardım alabilirsiniz.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا ئۈستەليۈزىدىكى سىنبەلگە چوڭلۇقىنى تەڭشەش ۋە بىر ئىشارە ئارقىلىق ئېكران بۆلۈش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلۇپ، لەيلىمە كۆزنەك ئىشلىتىش تەسىراتى ياخشىلاندى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«ئۈستەليۈزى سىنبەلگىسى»">
<feature>ئۈستەليۈزىدىكى سىنبەلگە چوڭلۇقىنى تەڭشەشنى قوللاپ، ئىشلەتكۈچىلەرنىڭ سىنبەلگە چوڭلۇقىنى ئوخشىمىغان چوڭلۇقتا كۆرسىتىش ئېھتىياجىنى قاندۇرىدۇ، سىناش يولى: «تەڭشەك > ئۈستەليۈزى ۋە خاسلاشتۇرۇش > ئۈستەليۈزى تەڭشىكى > سىنبەلگە چوڭلۇقى».</feature>
</features>
<features module="«ئېكران بۆلۈش»">
<feature>ئىشارە ئارقىلىق ئېكران بۆلۈش ئىقتىدارى يېڭىدىن قوشۇلدى، ئەپ پۈتۈن ئېكران ھالەتتە ئاستىنى سول تەرەپ ئۈستىگىچە سۆرەپ، ئېكران بۆلۈشنى قوللايدىغان باشقا ئەپنى چەكسىڭىزلا، ئەپ ئېكرانىنى بۆلۈشنى ئەمەلگە ئاشۇرغىلى بولىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="«لەيلىمە كۆزنەك»">
<feature>‏كىچىك كۆزنەكنى يانفون ئۈستەليۈزىنىڭ خالىغان ئورنىغا يۆتكەش ۋە شۇ ھالەتتە لەيلىتىشنى قوللايدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىمقى يېڭىلاشتا سىزنىڭ ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتىڭىز ئۆچۈرۈلمەيدۇ، لېكىن يەنىلا يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن مەلۇمات زاپاسلاشنى تەكلىپ قىلىمىز.
2. تېخىمۇ كۆپ ئىقتىدارلار تونۇشتۇرۇشىنى «ئىشلىتىش كۆرسەتمىسى» ئەپىنى زىيارەت قىلىپ كۆرۈڭ.
3. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا، ھەر قانداق مەسىلىگە ئۇچرىسىڭىز، روڭياۋ ماركىسىنىڭ مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىگە بېرىپ ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановний користувачу! У цьому рекомендованому оновленні додано нові функції, які дозволяють регулювати розмір піктограм головного екрана та активувати Розширення додатка одним рухом. Це оновлення також покращує взаємодію з переміщуваним вікном.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Піктограми на головному екрані">
<feature>Розмір піктограм на головному екрані можна настроювати відповідно до індивідуальних потреб. Щоб зробити це, перейдіть у меню "Налаштування" -> "Головний екран і стиль" -> "Налаштування головного екрана" -> "Розмір піктограми".</feature>
</features>
<features module="Розширення додатка">
<feature>Розширення додатка можна викликати одним рухом. Перетягніть нижню частину у верхній лівий кут, а потім торкніться іншої програми, яка підтримує Розширення додатка, щоб увімкнути відображення двох вікон.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Переміщуване вікно">
<feature>Мінівікно можна переміщувати й перетягувати до будь-якого положення на головному екрані.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примітки" type="end">
<feature>1. Ваші особисті дані не буде видалено внаслідок установлення цього оновлення, але все ж радимо створити резервну копію заздалегідь.
2. Перейдіть до додатка "Підказки", щоб дізнатися більше про функції продукту.
3. У разі виникнення проблем під час оновлення зателефонуйте за номером гарячої лінії HONOR або зверніться в сервісний центр HONOR по допомогу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>پیارے صارف، یہ تجویز کردہ اپ ڈیٹ نئے فنکشنز متعارف کرواتی ہے، جو آپ کو ہوم اسکرین کے آئیکنز کے سائز کو ایڈجسٹ کرنے اور ایک ہی سوائپ کے ساتھ ایپ ایکسٹنڈر کو فعال کرنے کی اجازت دیتا ہے۔ یہ اپ ڈیٹ معلق ونڈو کے صارف کے تجربے کو بھی بہتر بناتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="ہوم اسکرین کے آئیکنز">
<feature>ہوم اسکرین آئیکنز کے سائز کو انفرادی ضروریات کے مطابق ایڈجسٹ کیا جا سکتا ہے۔ ترتیبات -> ہوم اسکرین اور اسٹائل -> ہوم اسکرین کی ترتیبات -> آئیکن کا سائز پر جا کر اس کا تجربہ کریں۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="ایپ ایکسٹنڈر">
<feature>ایپ ایکسٹنڈر کو صرف ایک سوائپ سے ظاہر کیا جا سکتا ہے۔ نچلے حصے سے بالائی بائیں کنارے پر گھسیٹیں، پھر دوہری ونڈو کے ڈسپلے کو فعال کرنے کے لیے ایپ ایکسٹنڈر میں تعاون کرنے والی ایک اور ایپ پر ٹیپ کریں۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="معلق ونڈو">
<feature>منی ونڈو کو ہوم اسکرین پر کسی بھی پوزیشن پر منتقل اور ہوور کیا جا سکتا ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں مٹے گا، لیکن پھر بھی پہلے سے بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2. پروڈکٹ کی خصوصیات کے بارے میں مزید معلومات تجاویز کی ایپ میں دیکھیں۔
‏3. اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو آپ HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کر کے یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جا کر ہماری مدد حاصل کر سکتے ہیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu tavsiya etiladigan yangilanishda yangi funksiyalar taqdim etildi, bu sizga Bosh ekrandagi belgilar hajmini sozlash va Ilovani kengaytirish funksiyasini bir marta surish orqali faollashtirish imkonini beradi. Bu yangilanishda qalqib chiquvchi oyna foydalanuvchi taassuroti yaxshilandi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Bosh ekran belgisi">
<feature>Bosh ekrandagi belgilar hajmi shaxsiy ehtiyojlarga mos ravishda sozlanishi mumkin. Bu yerda uni sinashingiz mumkin: Sozlamalar -> Bosh ekran va uslub -> Bosh ekran sozlamalari -> Belgilar hajmi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ilovani kengaytirish">
<feature>Ilovani kengaytirish funksiyasini bir marta surish orqali ishga tushirish mumkin. Juft oynalarda chiqarish uchun pastdan yuqori chap burchakka ushlab torting va keyin Ilovani kengaytirish funksiyasini dastaklaydigan boshqa ilovani bosing.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qalqib chiquvchi oyna">
<feature>Bosh ekranda mini oynani surish va istalgan joyga olib borish mumkin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanish oʻrnatilsa shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringiz oʻchib ketmaydi, lekin ularni oldindan zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Maslahatlar ilovasida mahsulot xususiyatlari haqida batafsilroq maʼlumot oling.
3. Agar yangilash paytida biror muammoga duch kelsangiz, HONOR xizmatining tezkor raqamiga telefon qilish yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyurish orqali yordam olishingiz mumkin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật đề xuất này giới thiệu các chức năng mới, giúp bạn điều chỉnh kích thước biểu tượng Màn hình chính và kích hoạt tính năng Mở rộng ứng dụng chỉ bằng một thao tác vuốt. Bản cập nhật này cũng cải thiện trải nghiệm người dùng về cửa sổ di động.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Biểu tượng màn hình chính">
<feature>Có thể điều chỉnh kích thước biểu tượng Màn hình chính để đáp ứng các nhu cầu cá nhân. Bạn có thể trải nghiệm tính năng này bằng cách vào: Cài đặt -> Phong cách và màn hình chính -> Cài đặt màn hình chính -> Kích thước biểu tượng.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mở rộng ứng dụng">
<feature>Có thể kích hoạt tính năng Mở rộng ứng dụng chỉ bằng một thao tác vuốt. Kéo góc dưới cùng lên trên bên trái, sau đó chạm vào một ứng dụng khác hỗ trợ Mở rộng ứng dụng để bật chế độ hiển thị hai cửa sổ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cửa sổ di động">
<feature>Có thể di chuyển và chuyển cửa sổ mini sang trạng thái di động đến bất kỳ vị trí nào trên màn hình chính.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Lưu ý:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị xóa. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu trước.
2. Vào ứng dụng Mẹo để xem thêm thông tin về các tính năng của sản phẩm.
3. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến Trung tâm Dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新新增主屏幕圖標大小調節和一步手勢分割屏幕功能，提升浮動視窗使用體驗，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【主屏幕圖標】">
<feature>支援主屏幕圖標大小調節，滿足用戶對圖標大小的不同顯示需求，體驗路徑：「設定 -> 主屏幕和個人化 -> 主屏幕設定 -> 圖標大小」。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【分割屏幕】">
<feature>新增了一步手勢分割屏幕功能，應用程式全屏幕下拖動底部至左上方，輕觸其他支援分割屏幕應用程式，即可啟用應用程式分割屏幕。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【浮動視窗】">
<feature>迷你視窗支援移動和懸停到手機主屏幕任何位置。</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 如需了解更多精彩功能介紹，請存取「玩機技巧」應用程式。
3. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新新增桌面圖示大小調整和一步手勢螢幕分割功能，並提升懸浮視窗的使用體驗，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【桌面圖示】">
<feature>支援桌面圖示大小調整，滿足使用者對圖示大小的不同顯示需求，體驗路徑：「設定 -> 桌面和個人化 -> 桌面設定 -> 圖示大小」。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【螢幕分割】">
<feature>新增一步手勢螢幕分割功能，在應用程式全螢幕下，將底部拖曳至左上角，輕觸其他支援螢幕分割的應用程式，即可實現應用程式螢幕分割。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【懸浮視窗】">
<feature>迷你視窗支援移動和懸停至手機桌面的任意位置。</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 如需更多精彩功能介紹，請查看「玩機技巧」應用程式。
3. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
