<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新新增灵动胶囊，更改 USB 连接方式时增加用户身份验证，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【灵动胶囊】">
<feature>以“胶囊”形态显示，展示进行中的任务，便于查看实时状态、执行快捷操作或快速进入应用，高效服务、准确触达。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系统】">
<feature>更改 USB 连接方式时增加用户身份验证，从“仅充电”切换至“传输文件 / Android Auto”或“传输文件”模式时，弹出验证界面或安全提示，让您的数据传输更安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更新过程中，如果遇到任何问题，请拨打荣耀品牌服务热线或至荣耀品牌客户服务中心寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update introduces Magic Capsule. Additionally, user authentication is required when switching USB connection purposes.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Magic Capsule provides you with accurate and efficient services. Displayed in the form of a "capsule", it presents ongoing tasks, making it easy to view real-time status, perform quick operations, or quickly enter apps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>User authentication is required when switching USB connection purposes. A verification or security prompt appears when you select Transfer photos or Transfer files / Android Auto, instead of Charge only, ensuring safer data transfer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service center for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="am-ET" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ውድ ተጠቃሚ፣ ይህ የሚመከር ዝማኔ አስማታዊ ካፕሱልን ያስተዋውቃል። በተጨማሪም የUSB ግንኙነት ዓላማዎችን ሲቀይሩ የተጠቃሚ ማረጋገጫ ያስፈልጋል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="አስማታዊ ካፕሱል">
<feature>አስማታዊ ካፕሱል ትክክለኛ እና ቀልጣፋ አገልግሎቶችን ያቀርባል። በ"ካፕሱል" መልክ የሚታይ ሲሆን ቀጣይነት ያላቸውን ተግባራት ያቀርባል፣ ይህም ቅጽበታዊ ሁኔታን ለማየት፣ ፈጣን ስራዎችን ለመስራት ወይም መተግበሪያዎችን በፍጥነት ለማስገባት ቀላል ያደርገዋል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ስርዓት">
<feature>የUSB ግንኙነት ዓላማዎችን ሲቀይሩ የተጠቃሚ ማረጋገጫ ያስፈልጋል። ደህንነቱ የተጠበቀ የውሂብ ማስተላለፍን የሚያረጋግጥ ኃይል መሙላት ብቻ የሚለውን አጥፍተው ፎቶዎችን አስተላልፍ ወይም ፋይሎችን አስተላልፍ / Android Autoን ሲመርጡ የማረጋገጫ ወይም የደህንነት ጥያቄ ይመጣል።</feature>
</features>
<features module="ማስታወሻዎች፦" type="end">
<feature>1. ይህን ማሻሻያ መጫን የእርስዎን የግል መረጃዎን አይነካም፣ ነገር ግን አሁንም ከማዘመን በፊት አስቀድሞ መጠባበቂያ ማስቀመጥ ይመከራል።
2. በማሻሻያው ወቅት ማንኛውም አይነት ችግር ካጋጠመዎት እባክዎን ወደ HONOR አገልግሎት የቀጥታ መስመር ይደውሉ ወይም ድጋፍ ለማግኘት ወደ HONOR የደንበኞች የአገልግሎት ማዕከል ይሂዱ።</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ar-eg" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>عزيزنا المستخدم، يقدم هذا التحديث الموصى به ميزة Magic Capsule. علاوةً على ذلك، يجب إجراء مصادقة المستخدم عند تغيير أغراض اتصال USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏Magic Capsule">
<feature>توفر لك ميزة Magic Capsule خدمات دقيقة وفعالة. إنها تظهر على شكل "كبسولة"، وتقدم المهام الجارية، مما يسهّل عرض الحالة في الوقت الفعلي، أو تنفيذ عمليات سريعة، أو الدخول إلى التطبيقات بسرعة.</feature>
</features>
<features module="النظام">
<feature>يجب إجراء مصادقة المستخدم عند تغيير أغراض اتصال USB. تظهر مطالبة التحقق أو الأمان عندما تحدد "نقل الصور" أو "نقل الملفات / أندرويد أوتو"، بدلاً من "الشحن فقط"، مما يضمن نقل البيانات بشكل أكثر أمانًا.</feature>
</features>
<features module="الملاحظات:" type="end">
<feature>1. لن يؤثر تثبيت هذا التحديث على بياناتك الشخصية، ولكن لا يزال من المستحسن إنشاء نسخة احتياطية لبياناتك قبل التحديث.
2. إذا واجهت أي مشاكل أثناء التحديث، فيُرجى الاتصال بالخط الساخن لخدمة HONOR أو الانتقال إلى مركز خدمة عملاء HONOR للحصول على الدعم.‬</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="as-IN" code="3073">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>মৰমৰ ব্যৱহাৰকাৰী, এই অনুমোদিত আপডেটটোৱে মেজিক কেপচুলৰ পৰিচয় কৰায়। অতিৰিক্তভাৱে, USB সংযোগৰ উদ্দেশ্যসমূহ সাল-সলনি কৰাৰ সময়ত ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ প্ৰামাণিকীকৰণৰ আৱশ্যক।</feature>
</features>
<features module="মেজিক কেপচুল">
<feature>মেজিক কেপচুলে আপোনাক সঠিক আৰু দক্ষ সেৱাসমূহ প্ৰদান কৰে। এটা "কেপচুল"ৰ ৰূপত প্ৰদৰ্শন হয়, ই চলিত কাৰ্যসমূহ উপস্থাপন কৰে, যিয়ে প্ৰকৃত-সময়ৰ স্থিতি চোৱাত, দ্ৰুত কাৰ্যসমূহ সম্পাদন কৰাত বা এপ্লিকেশ্বনসমূহত দ্ৰুতভাৱে প্ৰৱেশ কৰাত সহজ কৰি তুলে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ছিষ্টেম">
<feature>USB সংযোগৰ উদ্দেশ্যসমূহ সাল-সলনি কৰাৰ সময়ত ব্যৱহাৰকাৰীৰ প্ৰামাণিকীকৰণৰ আৱশ্যক। আপুনি কেৱল চাৰ্জ কৰকৰ পৰিৱৰ্তে ফটোসমূহ স্থানান্তৰ কৰক বা ফাইলসমূহ স্থানান্তৰ কৰক/Android Auto বাছনি কৰাৰ সময়ত এটা প্ৰমাণীকৰণ বা নিৰাপত্তাৰ সংকেত দেখা পায়, যিয়ে নিৰাপদ ডাটা স্থানান্তৰ নিশ্চিত কৰে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="মনত ৰাখিব:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটো ইনষ্টল কৰিলে আপোনাৰ ব্যক্তিগত ডাটাত প্ৰভাৱ নপৰিব, কিন্তু আপডেট কৰাৰ পূৰ্বে আপোনাৰ ডাটাৰ বেক আপ ল'বলৈ এতিয়াও অনুমোদন জনোৱা হয়।
2. আপডেটৰ সময়ত আপুনি যদি কোনো সমস্যাৰ সন্মুখীন হয়, তেন্তে সমৰ্থনৰ বাবে অনুগ্ৰহ কৰি HONOR সেৱা হটলাইনত ফোন কৰিব বা HONOR গ্ৰাহক সেৱা কেন্দ্ৰলৈ যাব।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="az-az" code="1068">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hörmətli istifadəçi, tövsiyə edilən bu yeniləmə Sehrli Kapsul təqdim edir. Əlavə olaraq USB bağlantı məqsədlərini dəyişdirərkən istifadəçi əsilliyinin yoxlanılması tələb olunur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sehrli Kapsul">
<feature>Sehrli Kapsul sizə dəqiq və səmərəli xidmətlər təqdim edir. "Kapsul" şəklində nümayiş etdirilən xidmət real vaxtda statusa baxmağı, cəld əməliyyatlar yerinə yetirməyi və ya proqramlara cəld daxil olmağı asanlaşdıraraq davam edən tapşırıqlar təqdim edir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>USB bağlantı məqsədlərini dəyişdirərkən istifadəçi əsilliyinin yoxlanılması tələb olunur. Verilənlərin təhlükəsiz ötürülməsini təmin etmək üçün Yalnız doldurma əvəzinə Fotoları ötürün və ya Faylları ötürün/Android Auto seçdiyiniz zaman yoxlama və ya təhlükəsizlik sorğusu görünür.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Qeydlər:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yeniləmənin quraşdırılması şəxsi məlumatlarınıza təsir etməyəcək, lakin yeniləmədən əvvəl verilənlərinizin ehtiyat nüsxəsini çıxarmaq tövsiyə olunur.
2. Yeniləmə zamanı hər hansı problemlərlə qarşılaşsanız, dəstək üçün HONOR xidmətinin qaynar xəttinə zəng edin, yaxud HONOR müştəri xidməti mərkəzinə gedin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="jv-id" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Katur pangguna, panganyaran sing disaranake iki nglebokake Kapsul Ajaib. Saliyane iku, otentikasi pangguna dibutuhake nalika ngalihake tujuan sambungan USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kapsul Ajaib">
<feature>Kapsul Ajaib nyedhiyakake layanan sing akurat lan efisien. Ditampilake ing wujud "kapsul", Kapsul Ajaib nuduhake tugas sing aktif, saengga nggampangake ndeleng status ing wektu saknyatane, nindakake operasi cepet, utawa mlebu menyang apl kanthi cepet.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Otentikasi pangguna dibutuhake nalika ngalihake tujuan sambungan USB. Prentah verifikasi utawa keamanan bakal muncul yen sampeyan milih opsi Transfer foto utawa Nransfer file/Android Auto, tinimbang Mung ngisi daya, saengga njamin transfer data sing luwih aman.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cathetan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nginstal panganyaran iki ora bakal mengaruhi data pribadi sampeyan, nanging sampeyan tetep disaranake nggawe serep data sadurunge nganyarake.
2. Yen ana masalah sajrone panganyaran, ubungi hotline layanan HONOR utawa tekani pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR kanggo njaluk dukungan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-rs" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem uvodi se Magična kapsula. Pored toga, potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika prilikom prebacivanja režima za povezivanje USB vezom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magična kapsula">
<feature>Magična kapsula vam omogućava precizno i efikasno korišćenje usluga. Prikazuje se u obliku kapsule u kojoj su prikazani trenutno aktivni zadaci čime su olakšani prikaz statusa u realnom vremenu, obavljanje brzih radnji i brzo otvaranje aplikacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Kada se menjaju svrhe USB veze potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika. Verifikacija ili bezbednosni upit se pojavljuje kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka/Android auto umesto Samo punjenje, čime se obezbeđuje bezbedniji prenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-ba" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem uvodi se Magična kapsula. Pored toga, potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika prilikom prebacivanja režima za povezivanje USB vezom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magična kapsula">
<feature>Magična kapsula vam omogućava precizno i efikasno korišćenje usluga. Prikazuje se u obliku kapsule u kojoj su prikazani trenutno aktivni zadaci čime su olakšani prikaz statusa u realnom vremenu, obavljanje brzih radnji i brzo otvaranje aplikacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Kada se menjaju svrhe USB veze potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika. Verifikacija ili bezbednosni upit se pojavljuje kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka/Android auto umesto Samo punjenje, čime se obezbeđuje bezbedniji prenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sr-me" code="2074">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim preporučenim ažuriranjem uvodi se Magična kapsula. Pored toga, potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika prilikom prebacivanja režima za povezivanje USB vezom.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magična kapsula">
<feature>Magična kapsula vam omogućava precizno i efikasno korišćenje usluga. Prikazuje se u obliku kapsule u kojoj su prikazani trenutno aktivni zadaci čime su olakšani prikaz statusa u realnom vremenu, obavljanje brzih radnji i brzo otvaranje aplikacija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Kada se menjaju svrhe USB veze potrebna je potvrda identiteta korisnika. Verifikacija ili bezbednosni upit se pojavljuje kada izaberete Prenos fotografija ili Prenos datoteka/Android auto umesto Samo punjenje, čime se obezbeđuje bezbedniji prenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće uticati na vaše lične podatke, ali se i dalje preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju pre ažuriranja.
2. Ako tokom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za podršku pozovite dežurnu liniju za podršku kompanije HONOR ili posetite korisnički servisni centar kompanije HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="be-by" code="1059">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Паважаны карыстальнік, гэта рэкамендаванае абнаўленне ўводзіць функцыю «Чароўная капсула». Акрамя таго, пры змяненні мэты падключэння USB цяпер патрабуецца праверка сапраўднасці карыстальніка.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Чароўная капсула">
<feature>Чароўная капсула забяспечваць дакладныя і эфектыўныя сэрвісы. Яна адлюстроўваецца ў форме капсулы і паказвае бягучыя задачы, што палягчае прагляд статусу ў рэальным часе, выкананне хуткіх дзеянняў і хуткі ўваход у праграмы.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сістэма">
<feature>Пры змяненні мэты падключэння USB патрабуецца праверка сапраўднасці карыстальніка. Калі вы выбераце функцыю «Перадача фота» або «Перадача файлаў / Android Auto» замест функцыі «Зарадкі», з’явіцца падказка наконт праверкі або бяспекі, каб гарантаваць бяспечную перадачу даных.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Заўвагі." type="end">
<feature>1. Устаноўка гэтага абнаўлення не паўплывае на вашы асабістыя даныя, але мы ўсё роўна рэкамендуем зрабіць іх рэзервовую копію перад абнаўленнем.
2. Калі падчас абнаўлення ў вас узнікнуць праблемы, патэлефануйце на гарачую лінію абслугоўвання HONOR або звярніцеся па дапамогу ў сэрвісны цэнтр HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bg-bg" code="1026">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаеми потребители, тази препоръчителна актуализация въвежда „Магическа капсула“. Освен това се изисква удостоверяване на потребителя при превключване на целите на USB връзката.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Магическа капсула">
<feature>„Магическа капсула“ ви осигурява точни и ефикасни услуги. Тя се показва под формата на „капсула“ и представя текущите задачи, като улеснява прегледа на състоянието в реално време, извършването на бързи операции или бързото влизане в приложения.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>При превключване на целите на USB връзката се изисква удостоверяване на потребителя. Когато изберете „Прехвърляне на снимки“ или „Прехвърляне на файлове/Android Auto“, вместо „Само зареждане“, се появява подкана за проверка или за сигурност, което гарантира по-безопасен трансфер на данни.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Бележки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирането на тази актуализация няма да засегне личните ви данни, но е препоръчително архивирането им преди това.
2. Ако срещнете проблеми по време на актуализирането, обадете се на обслужващата гореща линия на HONOR или посетете сервизния център за клиенти на HONOR за поддръжка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bn-bd" code="2117">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>প্রিয় ব্যবহারকারী, এই সুপারিশকৃত আপডেটটি ম্যাজিক ক্যাপসুল চালু করেছে। এছাড়াও, USB সংযোগের উদ্দেশ্যে সুইচ করার সময় ব্যবহারকারীর প্রমাণীকরণ প্রয়োজন।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ম্যাজিক ক্যাপসুল">
<feature>ম্যাজিক ক্যাপসুল আপনাকে সঠিক এবং দক্ষ পরিষেবা প্রদান করে। একটি "ক্যাপসুল" আকারে প্রদর্শিত হয়, এটি চলমান কাজগুলি উপস্থাপন করে, যা রিয়েল-টাইম স্ট্যাটাস দেখা, দ্রুত কাজ করা বা দ্রুত অ্যাপগুলিতে প্রবেশ করাকে সহজ করে তোলে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="সিস্টেম">
<feature>USB সংযোগের উদ্দেশ্যে সুইচ করার সময় ব্যবহারকারীর প্রমাণীকরণ প্রয়োজন। আপনি যখন শুধুমাত্র চার্জ-এর পরিবর্তে ফটোগুলি ট্রান্সফার করুন বা ফাইলগুলি স্থানান্তর করুন / Android অটো নির্বাচন করেন তখন একটি যাচাইকরণ বা নিরাপত্তা প্রম্পট দেখতে পাওয়া যায়, যা নিরাপদ ডেটা স্থানান্তর নিশ্চিত করে।</feature>
</features>
<features module="নোট:" type="end">
<feature>1. এই আপডেটটি ইনস্টল করলে তা আপনার ব্যক্তিগত ডেটাকে প্রভাবিত করবে না, তবুও আপডেট করার আগে আপনার ডেটা ব্যাক আপ করার পরামর্শ দেওয়া হয়।
2. আপনি আপডেটের সময় কোনো সমস্যার সম্মুখীন হলে HONOR সার্ভিস হটলাইনে কল করুন বা সহায়তার জন্য HONOR গ্রাহক সেবা কেন্দ্রে যান।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bo-cn" code="1105">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>སྙིང་ཉེ་བའི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་ལགས། ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་དུ་འགུལ་རྣམ་སྦྱིན་ཐུམ་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། USB འབྲེལ་མཐུད་བྱ་ཐབས་བཟོ་བཅོས་བྱེད་སྐབས་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་ཐོབ་ཐང་ར་སྤྲོད་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། ཁྱེད་ལ་གསར་སྒྱུར་བྱ་རྒྱུའི་འོས་སྦྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【འགུལ་རྣམ་སྦྱིན་ཐུམ།】">
<feature>སྦྱིན་ཐུམ་རྣམ་པས་མངོན་སྟོན་བྱེད། སྒྲུབ་བཞིན་པའི་ལས་འགན་འགྲེམ་སྟོན་བྱེད་དེ། དུས་དངོས་ཀྱི་རྣམ་པ་དང་མྱུར་སྟབས་བཀོལ་སྤྱོད་ལག་བསྟར་བྱེད་པའམ་ཡང་ན་མགྱོགས་མྱུར་གྱིས་ཉེར་སྤྱོད་དུ་འཛུལ། ནུས་ཕྱོད་མཐོ་བའི་ཞབས་ཞུ་ཞིབ་དག་གིས་ཐུག་འབྱོར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="【རྒྱུད་ཁོངས།】">
<feature>USB འབྲེལ་མཐུད་བྱ་ཐབས་བཟོ་བཅོས་བྱེད་སྐབས་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་ཐོབ་ཐང་ར་སྤྲོད་གསར་སྣོན་བྱས་ཡོད། གློག་གསོག་པ་ཁོ་ན་ནས་ཡིག་ཆ་བརྒྱུད་གཏོང་ / Android Auto ཡང་ན་ཡིག་ཆ་བརྒྱུད་གཏོང་རྣམ་པར་བརྗེ་སྐབས། ར་སྤྲོད་མཚམས་ངོས་ཡང་ན་བདེ་འཇགས་དྲན་སྐུལ་འཕར། ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་བརྒྱུད་སྐུར་དེ་བས་བདེ་འཇགས་ཡིན་པར་བྱེད།</feature>
</features>
<features module="གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་དོ་སྣང་དོན་ཚན།" type="end">
<feature>1. ཐེངས་འདིའི་གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱིས་ཁྱེད་ཀྱི་སྤྱོད་མཁན་གྱི་གཞི་གྲངས་གསུབ་མི་སྲིད། འོན་ཀྱང་གསར་སྒྱུར་མ་བྱས་གོང་གཞི་གྲངས་གྲབས་ཉར་ཡག་པོ་བྱས་ན་ལེགས།
2. གསར་སྒྱུར་གྱི་བརྒྱུད་རིམ་ཁྲོད། གལ་ཏེ་གནད་དོན་གང་རུང་ལ་འཕྲད་ཚེ། རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ཁ་པར་ལ་ཁ་པར་གཏོང་བའམ་ཡང་ན་རུང་ཡོའོ་ཚོང་རྟགས་ཀྱི་སྐུ་མགྲོན་ཞབས་ཞུའི་ལྟེ་གནས་སུ་སོང་ནས་རྒྱབ་སྐྱོར་རེ་ཞུ་བྱེད་རོགས།</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="bs-ba" code="5146">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovo preporučeno ažuriranje uvodi Magičnu kapsulu. Osim toga, prilikom promjene svrhe USB veze je obavezna provjera autentičnosti korisnika.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magična kapsula">
<feature>Magična kapsula vam pruža tačne i precizne usluge. Prikazuje se u obliku kapsule i predstavlja tekuće zadatke, što olakšava pregledanje njihovog statusa u stvarnom vremenu, obavljanje brzih radnji i brz ulazak u aplikacije.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Obavezna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika prilikom promjene svrhe USB veze. Kada odaberete opciju Prenošenje fotografija ili Prijenos datoteka/Android automatski umjesto opcije Samo punjenje, prikazuje se upit za potvrdu ili sigurnosni upit, čime se omogućava sigurniji prijenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja ne utiče na lične podatke, ali ipak se preporučuje da napravite rezervnu kopiju podataka.
2. Ako naiđete na bilo kakav problem tokom ažuriranja, pozovite HONOR dežurnu liniju korisničke podrške ili posjetite HONOR servisni centar za korisnike da potražite pomoć.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ca-es" code="1027">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Benvolgut usuari, aquesta actualització recomanada presenta Càpsula màgica. A més, cal l'autenticació de l'usuari quan es canvia la connexió USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Càpsula màgica">
<feature>Càpsula màgica us ofereix serveis precisos i eficients. En forma de "càpsula", presenta tasques en curs, la qual cosa facilita visualitzar l'estat en temps real, fer operacions ràpides i entrar ràpidament a les aplicacions.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Es necessita l'autenticació de l'usuari quan es canvia la connexió USB. Apareix una indicació de verificació o de seguretat quan seleccioneu Transferir fotos o Transferir fitxers/Android Auto, en lloc de Només carregar, per tal que la transferència de dades sigui més segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. El fet d'instal·lar aquesta actualització no afectarà les vostres dades personals, però tot i així us recomanem que feu una còpia de seguretat de les dades abans de l'actualització.
2. Si teniu problemes durant l'actualització, truqueu a la línia directa de servei d'HONOR o visiteu el centre de servei d'atenció al client d'HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="cs-cz" code="1029">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený uživateli, tato doporučená aktualizace uvádí Magickou kapsli. Pro účely přepínání připojení USB je dále vyžadováno ověření uživatele.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magická kapsle">
<feature>Magická kapsle poskytuje přesné a efektivní služby. Zobrazuje se ve formě „kapsle“ a představuje probíhající úkoly, což usnadňuje zobrazení stavu v reálném čase, provádění rychlých operací nebo rychlý přechod do aplikací.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Pro účely přepínání připojení USB je vyžadováno ověření uživatele. Když vyberete možnost Přenos fotografií nebo Přenos souborů / Android Auto namísto možnosti Nabíjení, zobrazí se výzva k ověření nebo výzva zabezpečení, což zajistí bezpečnější přenos dat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalace této aktualizace neovlivní vaše osobní data, ale přesto doporučujeme před aktualizací zálohovat data.
2. Pokud se během aktualizace setkáte s nějakými problémy, zavolejte na informační linku HONOR nebo si vyžádejte podporu v Centru služeb zákazníkům HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="da-dk" code="1030">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kære bruger, denne anbefalede opdatering introducerer Magisk kapsel. Desuden er brugergodkendelse påkrævet under skift af USB-forbindelsesformål.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magisk kapsel">
<feature>Magisk kapsel giver dig nøjagtige og effektive tjenester. Den vises i form af en "kapsel" og præsenterer igangværende opgaver, så det er nemt at se status i realtid, udføre hurtige handlinger eller få hurtig adgang til apps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Brugergodkendelse er påkrævet under skift af USB-forbindelsesformål. En bekræftelses- eller sikkerhedsprompt bliver vist, når du vælger Overfør fotos eller Overfør filer / Android Auto i stedet for Oplad kun, hvilket garanterer sikrere dataoverførsel.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noter:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation af denne opdatering vil ikke påvirke dine personlige data, men det anbefales stadig at sikkerhedskopiere dine data, før du opdaterer.
2. Hvis du støder på problemer under opdateringen, kan du ringe til HONORs service-hotline eller gå til HONORs kundeservicecenter for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-de" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung führt Magic Capsule ein. Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist außerdem eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Magic Capsule bietet Ihnen genaue und effiziente Services. Es wird in Form einer „Kapsel“ angezeigt und stellt laufende Aufgaben dar, sodass der Echtzeitstatus einfacher angezeigt, die Schnellbedienung ausgeführt oder Apps schnell eingegeben werden können.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie „Fotos übertragen“ oder „Dateien übertragen / Android Auto“ anstelle von „Nur laden“ auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-at" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung führt Magic Capsule ein. Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist außerdem eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Magic Capsule bietet Ihnen genaue und effiziente Services. Es wird in Form einer „Kapsel“ angezeigt und stellt laufende Aufgaben dar, sodass der Echtzeitstatus einfacher angezeigt, die Schnellbedienung ausgeführt oder Apps schnell eingegeben werden können.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie „Fotos übertragen“ oder „Dateien übertragen / Android Auto“ anstelle von „Nur laden“ auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="de-ch" code="1031">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Liebe Nutzer, diese empfohlene Aktualisierung führt Magic Capsule ein. Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist außerdem eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Magic Capsule bietet Ihnen genaue und effiziente Services. Es wird in Form einer „Kapsel“ angezeigt und stellt laufende Aufgaben dar, sodass der Echtzeitstatus einfacher angezeigt, die Schnellbedienung ausgeführt oder Apps schnell eingegeben werden können.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Beim Wechseln des USB-Verbindungszwecks ist eine Nutzerauthentifizierung erforderlich. Wenn Sie „Fotos übertragen“ oder „Dateien übertragen / Android Auto“ anstelle von „Nur laden“ auswählen, wird eine Bestätigungs- oder Sicherheitsabfrage angezeigt, um eine sicherere Datenübertragung zu gewährleisten.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hinweise:" type="end">
<feature>1. Die Installation dieser Aktualisierung hat keine Auswirkungen auf Ihre persönlichen Daten, aber es wird dennoch empfohlen, vor der Aktualisierung eine Sicherungskopie Ihrer Daten zu erstellen.
2. Falls während der Aktualisierung Probleme auftreten, wenden Sie sich bitte telefonisch an die HONOR Service-Hotline oder suchen Sie das HONOR Customer Service-Center auf, um weitere Unterstützung zu erhalten.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="el-gr" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Αγαπητέ χρήστη, αυτή η προτεινόμενη ενημέρωση εισάγει τη Μαγική κάψουλα. Επιπλέον, απαιτείται επαλήθευση ταυτότητας χρήστη κατά την αλλαγή των σκοπών σύνδεσης USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Μαγική κάψουλα">
<feature>Η Μαγική κάψουλα σας παρέχει ακριβείς και αποτελεσματικές υπηρεσίες. Εμφανίζεται με τη μορφή κάψουλας και παρουσιάζει εργασίες σε εξέλιξη, κάνοντας εύκολη την προβολή της κατάστασης σε πραγματικό χρόνο, την εκτέλεση γρήγορων λειτουργιών ή τη γρήγορη είσοδο σε εφαρμογές.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σύστημα">
<feature>Απαιτείται επαλήθευση ταυτότητας χρήστη κατά την αλλαγή των σκοπών σύνδεσης USB. Ένα μήνυμα επαλήθευσης ή ασφάλειας εμφανίζεται όταν επιλέγετε «Μεταφορά φωτογραφιών» ή «Μεταφορά αρχείων/Android Auto», αντί για «Μόνο φόρτιση», εξασφαλίζοντας πιο ασφαλή μεταφορά δεδομένων.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Σημειώσεις:" type="end">
<feature>1. Η εγκατάσταση αυτής της ενημέρωσης δεν θα επηρεάσει τα προσωπικά δεδομένα σας, αλλά ακόμη και έτσι συνιστάται η δημιουργία αντιγράφων ασφαλείας των δεδομένων σας πριν από την ενημέρωση.
2. Εάν αντιμετωπίσετε προβλήματα κατά την ενημέρωση, καλέστε την ανοιχτή τηλεφωνική γραμμή της HONOR ή μεταβείτε στο κέντρο εξυπηρέτησης πελατών της HONOR για υποστήριξη.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-GB" code="1032">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this recommended update introduces Magic Capsule. Additionally, user authentication is required when switching USB connection purposes.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Magic Capsule provides you with accurate and efficient services. Displayed in the form of a "capsule", it presents ongoing tasks, making it easy to view real-time status, perform quick operations, or quickly enter apps.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>User authentication is required when switching USB connection purposes. A verification or security prompt appears when you select Transfer photos or Transfer files / Android Auto, instead of Charge only, ensuring safer data transfer.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. If you encounter any problems during the update, please call the HONOR service hotline or go to the HONOR customer service centre for support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-es" code="1034">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado/a usuario/a, esta actualización recomendada introduce Magic Capsule. Además, se requiere autenticación de usuario al cambiar los propósitos de conexión USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Magic Capsule le ofrece servicios precisos y eficientes. Se muestra en forma de “cápsula” y presenta tareas en curso, lo que facilita ver el estado en tiempo real, hacer operaciones rápidas o acceder a aplicaciones rápidamente.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Se requiere autenticación de usuario al cambiar los propósitos de conexión USB. Aparece un mensaje de verificación o seguridad cuando selecciona Transferir fotos o Transferir archivos/Android Auto, en lugar de Solo carga, lo que garantiza una transferencia de datos más segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará a sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene algún problema durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o diríjase al centro de servicios al cliente de HONOR para obtener ayuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="es-us" code="21514">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada introduce Magic Capsule. Además, se requiere autenticación de usuario al cambiar los propósitos de conexión USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Magic Capsule proporciona servicios precisos y eficientes. Se muestra como una cápsula y presenta las tareas en curso, lo que facilita ver el estado en tiempo real, realizar operaciones rápidas o ingresar rápidamente a las aplicaciones.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Se requiere autenticación de usuario al cambiar los propósitos de conexión USB. Aparece un mensaje de verificación o seguridad cuando selecciona Transferir fotos o Transferir archivos/Android Auto, en lugar de Solo carga, lo que garantiza una transferencia de datos más segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. La instalación de esta actualización no afectará sus datos personales, pero se recomienda hacer una copia de seguridad de sus datos antes de actualizar.
2. Si tiene problemas durante la actualización, llame a la línea de atención al cliente de HONOR o visite el centro de atención al cliente de HONOR para recibir asistencia.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="et-ee" code="1061">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hea kasutaja! See soovitatav värskendus lisab Maagilise kapsli. Lisaks on ühelt USB-ühenduselt teisele vahetamisel vajalik kasutaja autentimine.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Maagiline kapsel">
<feature>Maagiline kapsel funktsioon pakub teile täpseid ja tõhusaid teenuseid. See kuvatakse kapsli kujul ja selles näidatakse käimasolevaid ülesandeid, et lihtsustada nende oleku vaatamist reaalajas, kiirtoimingute sooritamist või rakendustesse kiiresti sisenemist.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Süsteem">
<feature>Ühelt USB-ühenduselt teisele vahetamisel on vajalik kasutaja autentimine. Kui valite funktsiooni Ainult laadimine asemel Fotode edastamine või Failide edastamine / Android Auto, kuvatakse kinnitus- või turvaviip, mis tagab turvalisema andmeedastuse.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Märkused:" type="end">
<feature>1. Selle värskenduse installimine ei mõjuta teie isikuandmeid, aga soovitame ikkagi enne värskendamist andmed varundada.
2. Kui teil tekib värskendamise ajal probleeme, helistage HONORi klienditoe infoliinile või minge toe saamiseks HONORi klienditeeninduskeskusesse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="eu-es" code="1069">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Erabiltzaile hori, gomendatutako eguneratze honek Kapsula magikoa du. Gainera, erabiltzaile-autentifikazioa behar da USB bidezko konexiora aldatzeko.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kapsula magikoa">
<feature>Kapsula magikoak zerbitzu zehatzak eta efizienteak ematen ditu. "Kapsula" moduan agertzen da, eta abian diren atazak aurkezten ditu. Horrek erraztu egiten du egoera denbora errealean ikustea, eragiketa azkarrak egitea edo aplikazioetan azkar sartzea.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Erabiltzaile-autentifikazioa beharrezkoa da USB bidezko konexiora aldatzen duzunean. Egiaztapen- edo segurtasun-gonbita bat bistaratuko da Transferitu argazkiak edo Transferitu fitxategiak / Android Auto aukera hautatzen duzunean, Kargatu bakarrik aukeratu beharrean; horri esker datuok segurtasunez transferituko dira.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Oharrak:" type="end">
<feature>1. Eguneratze hau instalatzen baduzu ere, ez diezu eragingo datu pertsonalei, baina gomendagarria da datuen babeskopia bat egitea eguneratzea egin baino lehen.
2. Arazorik baduzu eguneratzea egitean, deitu HONOR zerbitzuaren telefonozko arreta-lineara edo joan HONOR bezeroarentzako zerbitzu-zentrora laguntza lortzeko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fa-ir" code="1065">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>‏کاربر گرامی، این به‌روزرسانی پیشنهادی، «کپسول جادویی» را معرفی می‌کند. به‌علاوه، هنگام تغییر هدف اتصال USB، تأیید هویت کاربر مورد نیاز است.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏کپسول جادویی">
<feature>‏‏‏«کپسول جادویی» سرویس‌های دقیق و کارآمد را به شما ارائه می‌دهد. به‌شکل کپسول نمایش داده می‌شود و وظایف در حال انجام را نشان می‌دهد و مشاهده وضعیت لحظه‌ای، انجام دادن عملیات سریع یا ورود سریع به برنامه‌ها را تسهیل می‌کند.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏سیستم">
<feature>‏هنگام تغییر هدف اتصال USB، تأیید هویت کاربر نیاز است. هنگامی‌که «انتقال تصاویر» یا «انتقال فایل‌ها / Android Auto» را به‌جای «فقط شارژ» انتخاب می‌کنید، یک پیام‌واره تأیید یا امنیتی ظاهر می‌شود تا داده‌های خود را با امنیت بیشتری انتقال دهید.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏نکات مهم:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏‏۱. نصب این به‌روزرسانی، داده‌های شخصی شما را تحت تأثیر قرار نخواهد داد، اما همچنان توصیه می‌شود قبل از انجام به‌روزرسانی از داده‌های خود پشتیبان‌گیری کنید.
‏‏۲. اگر در حین به‌روزرسانی با مشکلی مواجه شدید، لطفاً جهت دریافت پشتیبانی با تلفن مستقیم خدمات HONOR تماس بگیرید یا به مرکز خدمات مشتریان HONOR مراجعه کنید.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fi-fi" code="1035">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hyvä käyttäjä, tämä suositeltu päivitys ottaa käyttöön Magic-kapselin. Lisäksi vaaditaan käyttäjän tunnistus, kun USB-liitäntätarkoituksia vaihdetaan.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic-kapseli">
<feature>Magic-kapseli tarjoaa tarkkoja ja tehokkaita palveluita. Se näkyy kapselinmuotoisena ja näyttää käynnissä olevat tehtävät, jolloin on helppoa katsoa tosiaikainen tila, tehdä pikatoimia tai siirtyä nopeasti sovelluksiin.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Järjestelmä">
<feature>Käyttäjän todentaminen vaaditaan, kun USB-liitännän tarkoitusta vaihdetaan. Kun valitset Siirrä valokuvia tai Siirrä tiedostoja / Android Auto sen sijaan, että valitsisit Vain lataus -vaihtoehdon, tarkastus- tai turvallisuuskehote avautuu, mikä varmistaa turvallisemman tiedonsiirron.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Huomautukset:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tämän päivityksen asentaminen ei vaikuta henkilökohtaisiin tietoihisi, mutta tietojen varmuuskopiointi ennen päivittämistä on kuitenkin suositeltavaa
2. Soita HONORin palvelunumeroon tai käy HONORin asiakaspalvelukeskuksessa, jos päivityksen aikana ilmenee ongelmia ja tarvitset apua.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-fr" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée présente Magic Capsule. De plus, l'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors du changement de connexion USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Magic Capsule vous offre des services précis et efficaces. Affichée sous forme d'une "capsule", elle présente les tâches en cours, ce qui facilite la visualisation de leur statut en temps réel, l'exécution d'opérations rapides ou la saisie rapide d'applications.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors du changement de connexion USB. Une invite de vérification ou de sécurité s'affiche lorsque vous sélectionnez Transférer des photos ou Transférer des fichiers / Android Auto, au lieu de Charger uniquement, garantissant ainsi un transfert de données plus sûr.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fr-ch" code="1036">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cher utilisateur, cette mise à jour recommandée présente Magic Capsule. De plus, l'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors du changement de connexion USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Magic Capsule vous offre des services précis et efficaces. Affichée sous forme d'une "capsule", elle présente les tâches en cours, ce qui facilite la visualisation de leur statut en temps réel, l'exécution d'opérations rapides ou la saisie rapide d'applications.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Système">
<feature>L'authentification de l'utilisateur est requise lors du changement de connexion USB. Une invite de vérification ou de sécurité s'affiche lorsque vous sélectionnez Transférer des photos ou Transférer des fichiers / Android Auto, au lieu de Charger uniquement, garantissant ainsi un transfert de données plus sûr.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Remarques :" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installation de cette mise à jour n'affectera pas vos données personnelles, mais il est tout de même recommandé de sauvegarder vos données avant la mise à jour.
2. Si vous rencontrez des problèmes lors de la mise à jour, veuillez appeler la Hotline du service HONOR ou accéder au centre de service client HONOR pour obtenir de l'aide.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gl-es" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Estimado usuario, esta actualización recomendada incorpora Cápsula máxica. Ademais, requírese a autenticación do usuario para cambiar de conexión USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cápsula máxica">
<feature>Cápsula máxica fornécelle servizos precisos e eficientes. Móstrase en forma de "cápsula" e presenta tarefas en curso, e así fai que sexa sinxelo ver o seu estado en tempo real, realizar operacións rápidas e entrar rapidamente en aplicacións.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Requírese a autenticación do usuario para cambiar de conexión USB. Aparece unha mensaxe de verificación ou seguranza ao seleccionar Transferir fotos ou Transferir ficheiros/Android Auto, en lugar de Só carga, o que garante unha transferencia de datos máis segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta actualización non afectará os seus datos persoais, aínda que se recomenda realizar unha copia de seguranza dos datos antes da actualización.
2. Se ten algún problema durante a actualización, contacte coa liña directa de servizo de HONOR ou vaia ao centro de servizos ao cliente de HONOR para obter axuda.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="gu-IN" code="1110">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>પ્રિય વપરાશકર્તા, આ ભલામણ કરેલ અપડેટ મેજિક કેપ્સ્યુલ રજૂ કરે છે. વધુમાં, USB કનેક્શન હેતુઓ પર સ્વિચ કરતી વખતે વપરાશકર્તા પ્રમાણીકરણ જરૂરી છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="મેજિક કેપ્સ્યુલ">
<feature>મેજિક કેપ્સ્યુલ તમને સચોટ અને કાર્યક્ષમ સેવાઓ પ્રદાન કરે છે. "કેપ્સ્યુલ" ના રૂપમાં પ્રદર્શિત થાય છે, તે ચાલુ કાર્યોને રજૂ કરે છે, જે વાસ્તવિક-સમયમાં સ્થિતિ જોવાનું, ઝડપી કામગીરી કરવાનું અથવા એપ્લિકેશન્સમાં ઝડપથી પ્રવેશવાનું સરળ બનાવે છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="સિસ્ટમ">
<feature>USB કનેક્શન હેતુઓ પર સ્વિચ કરતી વખતે વપરાશકર્તા પ્રમાણીકરણ જરૂરી છે. જ્યારે તમે સુરક્ષિત ડેટા ટ્રાન્સફરને સુનિશ્ચિત કરવા માટે માત્ર ચાર્જ કરોને બદલે, ફોટા ટ્રાન્સફર કરો અથવા ફાઇલો ટ્રાન્સફર કરો / Android Auto પસંદ કરો ત્યારે ચકાસણી અથવા સુરક્ષા પ્રોમ્પ્ટ દેખાય છે.</feature>
</features>
<features module="નોંધો:" type="end">
<feature>1. આ અપડેટ ઇન્સ્ટોલ કરવાથી તમારા વ્યક્તિગત ડેટાને અસર થશે નહીં, પરંતુ અપડેટ કરતા પહેલા તમારા ડેટાનો બૅકઅપ લેવાની ભલામણ કરવામાં આવે છે.
2. જો તમને અપડેટ દરમિયાન કોઈ સમસ્યા આવે, તો કૃપા કરીને HONOR સેવા હોટલાઇન પર કૉલ કરો અથવા સમર્થન માટે HONOR ગ્રાહક સેવા કેન્દ્ર પર જાઓ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hi-in" code="1081">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>नमस्ते उपयोगकर्ता, इस अनुशंसित अद्यतन में मैजिक कैप्सूल पेश किया जाता है। इसके अलावा, USB कनेक्शन उद्देश्यों को स्विच करते समय उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण की आवश्यकता होती है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="मैजिक कैप्सूल">
<feature>मैजिक कैप्सूल से आपको सटीक और कुशल सेवाएँ दी जाती हैं। इसे "कैप्सूल" के रूप में दिखाया जाता है और इससे चल रहे कार्यों का पता चलता है जिससे वास्तविक समय स्थिति देखना, त्वरित संचालन करना या ऐप्स में तेज़ी से जाना आसान हो जाता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>USB कनेक्शन उद्देश्यों को स्विच करते समय उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण की आवश्यकता होती है। जब आप सुरक्षित डेटा स्थानांतरण सुनिश्चित करने के लिए केवल चार्ज के बजाय फ़ोटो स्थानांतरित करें या फ़ाइलें स्थानांतरित करें / Android ऑटो को चुनते हैं, तो सत्यापन या सुरक्षा संकेत दिखाई देता है।</feature>
</features>
<features module="टिप्पणियाँ:" type="end">
<feature>1. इस अद्यतन को स्थापित करने से आपका व्यक्तिगत डेटा नहीं मिटेगा, लेकिन फिर भी पहले से बैकअप लेने की अनुशंसा की जाती है।
2. अगर अद्यतन के दौरान आपको कोई भी समस्या होती है, तो सहायता पाने के लिए, HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करें या HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाएँ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hr-hr" code="1050">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Poštovani korisniče, ovim se preporučenim ažuriranjem uvodi značajka Magična kapsula. Osim toga, potrebna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika prilikom promjene svrhe povezivanja putem USB-a.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magična kapsula">
<feature>Magična kapsula pruža točne i učinkovite usluge. Prikazana u obliku „kapsule“ predstavlja tekuće zadatke, olakšavajući pregled statusa u stvarnom vremenu, izvođenje brzih radnji ili brzi pristup aplikacijama.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sustav">
<feature>Potrebna je provjera autentičnosti korisnika prilikom promjene svrhe povezivanja putem USB-a. Kada odaberete Prijenos fotografija ili Prijenos datoteka / Android Auto, umjesto opcije Samo punjenje, pojavljuje se upit za provjeru ili sigurnost, čime se osigurava sigurniji prijenos podataka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Napomene:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instaliranje ovog ažuriranja neće utjecati na osobne podatke, ali se svejedno preporučuje izraditi sigurnosnu kopiju podataka prije ažuriranja.
2. Ako tijekom ažuriranja naiđete na bilo kakve probleme, za pomoć nazovite telefonsku korisničku službu tvrtke HONOR ili posjetite centar za korisničku podršku tvrtke HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="hu-hu" code="1038">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kedves felhasználó! Ez az ajánlott frissítés bevezeti a Mágikus kapszula szolgáltatást. Ezenfelül az USB-kapcsolat típusának módosításához mostantól felhasználói hitelesítés szükséges.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mágikus kapszula">
<feature>A Mágikus kapszula funkció pontos és hatékony szolgáltatásokat biztosít Önnek. Ez egy „kapszula” formájában jelenik meg, bemutatva a folyamatban lévő feladatokat, és lehetővé téve azok valós idejű állapotának nyomon követését, gyorsműveletek végrehajtását vagy a gyors belépést az alkalmazásokba.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Rendszer">
<feature>Az USB-kapcsolat váltásakor felhasználói hitelesítés szükséges. Ha a Csak töltés opció helyett a Fotók átvitele vagy Fájlok átvitele/Android Auto opciót választja, megjelenik egy hitelesítési vagy biztonsági üzenet, amelynek célja, hogy az adatátvitel garantáltan biztonságos legyen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Megjegyzések:" type="end">
<feature>1. A frissítés telepítése nem érinti az Ön személyes adatait, de a frissítés megkezdése előtt ajánlott biztonsági másolatot készíteni az adatokról.
2. Ha problémába ütközik a frissítés során, hívja a HONOR ügyfélszolgálati forródrótját, vagy keresse fel a HONOR szervizközpontját.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="in-id" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini memperkenalkan Kapsul Ajaib. Selain itu, autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat beralih tujuan koneksi USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kapsul Ajaib">
<feature>Kapsul Ajaib menyediakan layanan akurat dan efisien untuk Anda. Ditampilkan dalam bentuk "kapsul", layanan ini menyajikan tugas yang sedang berlangsung, sehingga memudahkan Anda untuk melihat status dalam waktu nyata, melakukan operasi cepat, atau masuk aplikasi dengan cepat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat beralih tujuan koneksi USB. Verifikasi atau perintah keamanan muncul saat Anda memilih Transfer foto atau Transfer file/Android Auto, bukan Isi daya saja, memastikan transfer data yang lebih aman.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="id-" code="1057">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang terhormat, pembaruan yang direkomendasikan ini memperkenalkan Kapsul Ajaib. Selain itu, autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat beralih tujuan koneksi USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kapsul Ajaib">
<feature>Kapsul Ajaib menyediakan layanan akurat dan efisien untuk Anda. Ditampilkan dalam bentuk "kapsul", layanan ini menyajikan tugas yang sedang berlangsung, sehingga memudahkan Anda untuk melihat status dalam waktu nyata, melakukan operasi cepat, atau masuk aplikasi dengan cepat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Autentikasi pengguna diperlukan saat beralih tujuan koneksi USB. Verifikasi atau perintah keamanan muncul saat Anda memilih Transfer foto atau Transfer file/Android Auto, bukan Isi daya saja, memastikan transfer data yang lebih aman.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Catatan:" type="end">
<feature>1. Menginstal pembaruan ini tidak akan memengaruhi data pribadi Anda, tetapi tetap direkomendasikan mencadangkan data Anda sebelum memperbarui.
2. Jika Anda mengalami masalah apa pun selama pembaruan, hubungi saluran siaga layanan HONOR atau kunjungi pusat layanan pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan bantuan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-it" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato introduce Magic Capsule. Inoltre, introduce l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente quando si cambia la connessione USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Magic Capsule fornisce servizi accurati ed efficienti. Visualizzata sotto forma di pillola, presenta le attività in corso, semplificando la visualizzazione dello stato in tempo reale, l'esecuzione di operazioni rapide o l'accesso rapido alle app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>L'autenticazione utente è richiesta quando si cambia la connessione USB. Quando si seleziona Trasferisci foto o Trasferire file/Android Auto anziché Solo ricarica, viene visualizzato un messaggio di verifica o di sicurezza, per garantire un trasferimento dati più sicuro.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="it-ch" code="1040">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gentile utente, questo aggiornamento consigliato introduce Magic Capsule. Inoltre, introduce l'obbligo dell'autenticazione utente quando si cambia la connessione USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Magic Capsule fornisce servizi accurati ed efficienti. Visualizzata sotto forma di pillola, presenta le attività in corso, semplificando la visualizzazione dello stato in tempo reale, l'esecuzione di operazioni rapide o l'accesso rapido alle app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>L'autenticazione utente è richiesta quando si cambia la connessione USB. Quando si seleziona Trasferisci foto o Trasferire file/Android Auto anziché Solo ricarica, viene visualizzato un messaggio di verifica o di sicurezza, per garantire un trasferimento dati più sicuro.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. L'installazione di questo aggiornamento non avrà effetto sulle informazioni personali, ma si consiglia comunque di effettuare un backup prima di procedere.
2. Se si verificano problemi durante l'aggiornamento, contatta il servizio call center di HONOR oppure recati presso un centro servizio clienti HONOR per ricevere supporto.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="iw-il" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>‏משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה מוסיף לראשונה את 'קפסולת קסם'. בנוסף, אימות משתמש נדרש בעת החלפת מטרת חיבור USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏קפסולת קסם">
<feature>‏‏'קפסולת קסם' מספקת לך שירותים מדויקים ויעילים. היא מוצגת בצורה של "קפסולה" ומציגה משימות בביצוע, כדי להקל על הצגת סטטוסים בזמן אמת, לבצע פעולות מהירות או להיכנס במהירות ליישומים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏מערכת">
<feature>‏אימות משתמש נדרש בעת החלפת מטרת חיבור USB. הודעת אימות או אבטחה תופיע כאשר תבחר העברת תמונות או העברת קבצים/Android Auto, במקום טעינה בלבד, כדי להבטיח העברת נתונים בטוחה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="he-" code="1037">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>‏משתמש יקר, עדכון מומלץ זה מוסיף לראשונה את 'קפסולת קסם'. בנוסף, אימות משתמש נדרש בעת החלפת מטרת חיבור USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏קפסולת קסם">
<feature>‏‏'קפסולת קסם' מספקת לך שירותים מדויקים ויעילים. היא מוצגת בצורה של "קפסולה" ומציגה משימות בביצוע, כדי להקל על הצגת סטטוסים בזמן אמת, לבצע פעולות מהירות או להיכנס במהירות ליישומים.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏מערכת">
<feature>‏אימות משתמש נדרש בעת החלפת מטרת חיבור USB. הודעת אימות או אבטחה תופיע כאשר תבחר העברת תמונות או העברת קבצים/Android Auto, במקום טעינה בלבד, כדי להבטיח העברת נתונים בטוחה יותר.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏הערות:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏‏1. התקנת עדכון זה לא תשפיע על הנתונים האישיים שלך, אך עדיין מומלץ לגבות את הנתונים לפני העדכון.
‏‏2. אם מופיעות בעיות כלשהן במהלך העדכון, יש להתקשר לקו החם של השירות של HONOR או ללכת למרכז שירות הלקוחות של HONOR לקבלת תמיכה.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ja-jp" code="1041">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ユーザーの皆様、今回の推奨更新では、マジックカプセルが導入されました。また、USB接続の目的を切り替える際、ユーザー認証が必要になります。</feature>
</features>
<features module="マジックカプセル">
<feature>マジックカプセルは正確で効率的なサービスを提供します。「カプセル」の形状で表示され、進行中のタスクを表示し、リアルタイムの状況把握、迅速な操作の実行、あるいはアプリへのすばやいアクセスを簡単にします。</feature>
</features>
<features module="システム">
<feature>USB接続の目的を切り替える際、ユーザー認証が必要になります。[充電のみ]ではなく、[写真の転送]または[ファイルの転送/Android Auto]を選択すると、認証またはセキュリティプロンプトが表示され、より安全なデータ転送が保証されます。</feature>
</features>
<features module="注意：" type="end">
<feature>1. この更新をインストールしてもユーザーの個人情報に影響はありませんが、更新前にバックアップを取ることをおすすめします。
2. 更新中に問題が発生した場合は、HONORサービスホットラインにお電話をいただくか、HONORカスタマーサービスセンターでサポートを受けてください。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ka-ge" code="1079">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ძვირფასო მომხმარებელო, ეს რეკომენდებული განახლება წარმოგიდგენთ ჯადოსნურ კაფსულას. ამასთან, მომხმარებლის ავტორიზაციაა საჭირო USB კავშირის გადართვის მიზნით.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ჯადოსნური კაფსულა">
<feature>ჯადოსნური კაფსულა ფუნქცია უზრუნველყოფს ზუსტ და ეფექტიან სერვისებს. ის ნაჩვენებია კაფსულის სახით და წარმოგიდგენთ მიმდინარე ამოცანებს, რაც აადვილებს რეალურ დროში სტატუსის ნახვას, სწრაფი ოპერაციების შესრულებას ან აპლიკაციებში სწრაფად შესვლას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="სისტემა">
<feature>USB კავშირის გადართვის დროს აუცილებელია მომხმარებლის ავტორიზაცია. შემოწმების ან უსაფრთხოების მოთხოვნა გამოჩნდება, როცა აირჩევთ ფოტოების გადაცემას ან ფაილების გადაცემას / Android Auto-ს, მხოლოდ დამუხტვის ნაცვლად, რაც უზრუნველყოფს მონაცემთა უსაფრთხო გადაცემას.</feature>
</features>
<features module="შენიშვნები:" type="end">
<feature>1. ამ განახლების ინსტალირება არ იქონიებს გავლენას თქვენს პერსონალურ მონაცემებზე, თუმცა მაინც გირჩევთ წინასწარ სარეზერვო კოპირებას.
2. განახლების დროს პრობლემების წარმოქმნის შემთხვევაში, მხარდაჭერის მისაღებად დარეკეთ HONOR-ის მომსახურების ცხელ ხაზზე ან მიმართეთ HONOR-ის კლიენტთა სერვისცენტრს.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kk-kz" code="1087">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Құрметті пайдаланушы, бұл ұсынылған жаңарту «Сиқырлы капсула» мүмкіндігін ұсынады. Сондай-ақ USB байланысының мақсаттарын ауыстырған кезде пайдаланушының аутентификациясы қажет.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Сиқырлы капсула">
<feature>«Сиқырлы капсула» сізге дәл және тиімді қызметтерді қамтамасыз етеді. «Капсула» түрінде көрсетіледі, ағымдағы тапсырмаларды ұсынады, бұл нақты уақыттағы күйді көруді, жылдам жұмыстарды орындауды немесе қолданбаларды жылдам енгізуді жеңілдетеді.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Жүйе">
<feature>USB байланысының мақсаттарын ауыстырған кезде пайдаланушының аутентификациясы қажет. Деректерді қауіпсіз тасымалдауды қамтамасыз ететін «Тек зарядтау» орнына «Фотосуреттерді тасымалдау» немесе «Файлдарды тасымалдау/Android Auto» параметрін таңдаған кезде растау немесе қауіпсіздік сұрауы пайда болады.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ескертпелер:" type="end">
<feature>1. Бұл жаңартуды орнату жеке деректеріңізге әсер етпейді, бірақ жаңартпас бұрын деректердің сақтық көшірмесін жасау ұсынылады.
2. Жаңарту барысында мәселелер орын алса, қолдау алу үшін HONOR қызмет көрсету орталығының байланыс желісіне хабарласыңыз немесе HONOR тұтынушыларға қызмет көрсету орталығына барыңыз.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="km-kh" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>អ្នកប្រើជាទីរាប់អាន បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​ដែលបានណែនាំនេះដាក់ចេញខេបស៊ូលវេទមន្ត។ លើសពីនេះ តម្រូវឱ្យមានការផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់អ្នកប្រើ នៅពេលប្តូរគោលបំណងនៃការតភ្ជាប់ USB។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ខេបស៊ូលវេទមន្ត">
<feature>ខេបស៊ូលវេទមន្តផ្ដល់សេវាកម្មដែលត្រឹមត្រូវ និងមានប្រសិទ្ធផលដល់អ្នក។ ដោយបង្ហាញជាទម្រង់ "ខេបស៊ូល" វាបង្ហាញកិច្ចការដែលកំពុងបន្ត ដែលធ្វើឱ្យមានភាពងាយស្រួលក្នុងការមើលស្ថានភាពក្នុងពេលជាក់ស្ដែង ធ្វើប្រតិបត្តិការរហ័ស ឬចូលទៅកម្មវិធីបានរហ័ស។</feature>
</features>
<features module="ប្រព័ន្ធ">
<feature>តម្រូវឱ្យមានការផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់អ្នកប្រើ នៅពេលប្តូរគោលបំណងនៃការតភ្ជាប់ USB។ សារតម្រុយផ្ទៀងផ្ទាត់ ឬសារតម្រុយសន្តិសុខមួយបង្ហាញ នៅពេលអ្នកជ្រើសរើស "ផ្ទេររូបថត" ឬ "ផ្ទេរ​ឯកសារ / Android Auto" ជំនួសឱ្យការសាកថ្មតែប៉ុណ្ណោះ ដែលធានាបាននូវការផ្ទេរទិន្នន័យដែលកាន់តែមានសុវត្ថិភាព។</feature>
</features>
<features module="កំណត់សម្គាល់៖" type="end">
<feature>1. ការដំឡើង​បច្ចុប្បន្នភាព​នេះ​នឹងមិន​ប៉ះពាល់ទិន្នន័យផ្ទាល់ខ្លួន​របស់អ្នក​ទេ ប៉ុន្តែ​នៅតែ​ណែនាំឱ្យ​ធ្វើ​ការបម្រុងទុក​ជាមុន​ដដែល។
2. ប្រសិនបើអ្នកជួបបញ្ហាណាមួយក្នុងអំឡុងពេល​ធ្វើបច្ចុប្បន្នភាព សូមហៅទូរស័ព្ទទៅ​ខ្សែទូរស័ព្ទរហ័សផ្នែកសេវាកម្ម HONOR ឬទៅកាន់មជ្ឈមណ្ឌល​សេវាកម្មអតិថិជន HONOR ដើម្បី​ទទួលបាន​ជំនួយ។</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="kn-IN" code="1107">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ಆತ್ಮೀಯ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರೇ, ಈ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಿದ ನವೀಕರಣವು ಮ್ಯಾಜಿಕ್ ಕ್ಯಾಪ್ಸೂಲ್ ಅನ್ನು ಪರಿಚಯಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಹೆಚ್ಚುವರಿಯಾಗಿ, USB ಕನೆಕ್ಷನ್‌ನ ಉದ್ದೇಶಗಳನ್ನು ಬದಲಾಯಿಸುವಾಗ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ದೃಢೀಕರಣದ ಅಗತ್ಯವಿದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಮ್ಯಾಜಿಕ್ ಕ್ಯಾಪ್ಸೂಲ್">
<feature>ಮ್ಯಾಜಿಕ್ ಕ್ಯಾಪ್ಸೂಲ್ ನಿಮಗೆ ನಿಖರ ಮತ್ತು ಪರಿಣಾಮಕಾರಿ ಸೇವೆಗಳನ್ನು ಒದಗಿಸುತ್ತದೆ. ಇದನ್ನು "ಕ್ಯಾಪ್ಸೂಲ್" ರೂಪದಲ್ಲಿ ಪ್ರದರ್ಶಿಸಲಾಗುತ್ತದೆ, ಇದು ನಡೆಯುತ್ತಿರುವ ಕಾರ್ಯಗಳನ್ನು ಪ್ರಸ್ತುತಪಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ, ಈ ಮೂಲಕ ನೈಜ-ಸಮಯದ ಸ್ಥಿತಿಯನ್ನು ವೀಕ್ಷಿಸುವುದನ್ನು, ತ್ವರಿತ ಕಾರ್ಯಾಚರಣೆಗಳನ್ನು ನಿರ್ವಹಿಸುವುದನ್ನು ಅಥವಾ ಆ್ಯಪ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ತ್ವರಿತವಾಗಿ ಪ್ರವೇಶಿಸುವುದನ್ನು ಸುಲಭಗೊಳಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಸಿಸ್ಟಂ">
<feature>USB ಕನೆಕ್ಷನ್‌ನ ಉದ್ದೇಶಗಳನ್ನು ಬದಲಾಯಿಸುವಾಗ ಬಳಕೆದಾರರ ದೃಢೀಕರಣದ ಅಗತ್ಯವಿರುತ್ತದೆ. ನೀವು ಚಾರ್ಜ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಮಾತ್ರ ಎಂಬುದರ ಬದಲಿಗೆ ಫೋಟೊಗಳನ್ನು ವರ್ಗಾಯಿಸಿ ಅಥವಾ ಫೈಲ್‌ಗಳನ್ನು ವರ್ಗಾಯಿಸಿ/Android Auto ವನ್ನು ಆಯ್ಕೆ ಮಾಡಿದಾಗ ಪರಿಶೀಲನೆ ಅಥವಾ ಭದ್ರತಾ ಪ್ರಾಂಪ್ಟ್ ಕಾಣಿಸಿಕೊಳ್ಳುತ್ತದೆ, ಇದು ಸುರಕ್ಷಿತ ಡೇಟಾ ವರ್ಗಾವಣೆಯನ್ನು ಖಚಿತಪಡಿಸುತ್ತದೆ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ಟಿಪ್ಪಣಿಗಳು:" type="end">
<feature>1. ಈ ನವೀಕರಣವನ್ನು ಸ್ಥಾಪಿಸುವುದರಿಂದ ನಿಮ್ಮ ವೈಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಡೇಟಾದ ಮೇಲೆ ಪರಿಣಾಮ ಬೀರುವುದಿಲ್ಲ, ಆದರೆ ನವೀಕರಿಸುವ ಮೊದಲು ನಿಮ್ಮ ಡೇಟಾವನ್ನು ಬ್ಯಾಕಪ್ ಮಾಡಲು ಈಗಲೂ ಶಿಫಾರಸು ಮಾಡಲಾಗಿದೆ.
2. ನವೀಕರಣದ ಸಮಯದಲ್ಲಿ ನೀವು ಯಾವುದೇ ಸಮಸ್ಯೆಗಳನ್ನು ಎದುರಿಸಿದರೆ, ದಯವಿಟ್ಟು HONOR ಸೇವಾ ಹಾಟ್‌ಲೈನ್‌ಗೆ ಕರೆ ಮಾಡಿ ಅಥವಾ ಬೆಂಬಲಕ್ಕಾಗಿ HONOR ಗ್ರಾಹಕ ಸೇವಾ ಕೇಂದ್ರಕ್ಕೆ ಹೋಗಿ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ko-kr" code="1042">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>사용자 여러분, 이번 권장 업데이트에서는 매직 캡슐을 소개합니다. 또한 USB 연결 용도를 전환할 때는 사용자 인증이 필요합니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="매직 캡슐">
<feature>매직 캡슐은 정확하고 효율적인 서비스를 제공합니다. 진행 중인 작업을 "캡슐" 형태로 표시하여 실시간 상태를 확인하고, 빠른 작업을 수행하거나, 앱에 빠르게 진입할 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="시스템">
<feature>USB 연결 용도를 전환할 때는 사용자 인증이 필요합니다. 충전 전용 대신 사진 전송 또는 파일 전송/Android Auto를 선택하면 인증 또는 보안 메시지가 표시되어 더욱 안전하게 데이터를 전송할 수 있습니다.</feature>
</features>
<features module="참고:" type="end">
<feature>1. 이 업데이트를 설치해도 개인 데이터에는 영향을 미치지 않지만 업데이트하기 전에 데이터를 백업하는 것이 좋습니다.
2. 업데이트 중에 문제가 발생하면 HONOR 서비스 핫라인에 전화하거나 HONOR 고객 서비스 센터로 가서 지원을 받으십시오.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lo-la" code="1108">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ສະ​ບາຍ​ດີ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້, ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ທີ່​ແນະ​ນຳນີ້​ແນະ​ນຳແຄັບ​ຊູ​ລ​ເມ​ຈິກ. ນອກ​ຈາກ​ນີ້, ຍັງຮຽກ​ຮ້ອງ​ການກວດ​ຮັບ​ຮອງ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້​ເມື່ອ​ສັບ​ປ່ຽນ​ຈຸດ​ປະ​ສົງ​ການ​ເຊື່ອມ​ຕໍ່ USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ແຄັບ​ຊູ​ລ​ເມ​ຈິກ">
<feature>ແຄັບ​ຊູ​ລ​ເມ​ຈິກໃຫ້​ການ​ບໍ​ລິ​ການ​ທີ່​ຖືກ​ຕ້ອງ​ ແລະ ມີ​ປະ​ສິດ​ທິ​ພາບ​ແກ່​ທ່ານ. ສະ​ແດງ​ໃນ​ຮູບ​ແບບ​ຂອງ "ແຄັບ​ຊູ​ລ", ມັນນຳ​ສະ​ເໜີ​ໜ້າ​ວ​ຽກ​ທີ່​ດຳ​ເນີນ​ຢູ່, ເຊິ່ງ​ເຮັດ​ໃຫ້​ມັນ​ງ່າຍ​ໃນ​ການ​ເບິ່ງ​ສະ​ຖາ​ນະ​ໃນ​ເວ​ລາ​ຈິງ, ເຮັດ​ການ​ດຳ​ເນີນ​ການ​ດ່ວນ ຫຼື ເຂົ້າ​​ແອັບ​​ຢ່າງ​ໄວ​ວາ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ລະບົບ">
<feature>ຮຽກ​ຮ້ອງ​ການກວດ​ຮັບ​ຮອງ​ຜູ້​ໃຊ້​ເມື່ອ​ສັບ​ປ່ຽນ​ຈຸດ​ປະ​ສົງ​ການ​ເຊື່ອມ​ຕໍ່ USB. ຂໍ້​ຄວາມ​​ແຈ້ງ​ເຕືອນ​ການກວດ​ສອບ ຫຼື ຄວາມ​ປອດ​ໄພ ປະ​ກົດຂຶ້ນ​ເມື່ອ​ທ່ານ​ເລືອກ​ ໂອນ​ຮູບ​ຖ່າຍ ຫຼື ໂອນ​ໄຟ​ລ໌ / Android ອັດ​ຕະ​ໂນ​ມັດ, ແທນ​ການ​ສາກ​ເທົ່າ​ນັ້ນ, ເຊິ່ງ​ຮັບ​ປະ​ກັນ​ການ​ໂອນ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ທີ່​ປອດ​ໄພ​ກວ່າ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="ໝາຍ​ເຫດ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ການ​ຕິດ​ຕັ້ງ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ​ນີ້​ຈະ​ບໍ່​ສົ່ງ​ຜົນ​ຕໍ່​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ສ່ວນ​ຕົວ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ, ແຕ່​ຍັງ​ຄົງ​ຂໍ​ແນະ​ນຳ​ໃຫ້​ສຳ​ຮອງ​ຂໍ້​ມູນ​ຂອງ​ທ່ານ​ໄວ້ກ່ອນ​ການ​ອັບ​ເດດ.
2. ຖ້າທ່ານພົບບັນຫາໃດໆໃນລະຫວ່າງການອັບເດດ, ກະລຸນາໂທຫາສາຍດ່ວນບໍລິການ HONOR ຫຼື ເຂົ້າໄປທີ່ສູນບໍລິການລູກຄ້າ HONOR ເພື່ອຂໍຄວາມຊ່ວຍເຫຼືອ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lt-lt" code="1063">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Gerbiamasis naudotojau, šiuo rekomenduojamu naujiniu pristatoma stebuklingoji kapsulė. Be to, keičiant USB jungties paskirtį, reikia nustatyti naudotojo tapatumą.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Stebuklingoji kapsulė">
<feature>Stebuklingoji kapsulė teikia tikslias ir veiksmingas paslaugas. Kapsulės pavidalo ekrane pateikiamos vykdomos užduotys, todėl lengva peržiūrėti tikralaikę būseną, atlikti greitas operacijas arba greitai įeiti į programėles.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>Keičiant USB jungties paskirtį, reikia nustatyti naudotojo tapatumą. Pasirinkus „Persiųsti nuotraukas“ arba „Persiųsti failus („Android Auto“)“, o ne „Tik įkrauti“, pateikiamas patvirtinimo arba saugumo raginimas, užtikrinantis saugesnį duomenų persiuntimą.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pastabos" type="end">
<feature>1. Įdiegiant šį naujinį, jūsų asmeniniai duomenys paveikti nebus, tačiau vis tiek rekomenduojama prieš naujinant padaryti atsarginę kopiją.
2. Jei naujinimo metu kyla problemų, skambinkite HONOR klientų aptarnavimo karštąja linija arba kreipkitės pagalbos į HONOR klientų aptarnavimo centrą.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="lv-lv" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Cien. lietotāj! Ar šo ieteicamo atjauninājumu ir ieviesta Maģijas kapsula. Turklāt, pārslēdzot uz USB savienojumu, ir nepieciešama lietotāja autentifikācija.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Maģijas kapsula">
<feature>Maģijas kapsula nodrošina precīzus un efektīvus pakalpojumus. Tā, kas parādīta “kapsulas” formā, parāda notiekošos uzdevumus, ļaujot ērti skatīt reāllaika statusu, veikt ātras darbības vai ātri ievadīt lietotnes.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistēma">
<feature>Pārslēdzot uz USB savienojumu, ir nepieciešama lietotāja autentifikācija. Izvēloties Pārsūtīt fotoattēlus vai Pārsūtīt failus/Android Auto, nevis Tikai uzlāde, tiek parādīta verifikācijas vai drošības uzvedne, garantējot drošāku datu pārsūtīšanu.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Piezīmes." type="end">
<feature>1. Šī atjauninājuma instalēšana neietekmēs jūsu personas datus, taču joprojām ir ieteicams pirms atjaunināšanas dublēt datus.
2. Ja atjaunināšanas laikā rodas problēmas, lūdzu, zvaniet HONOR uzziņu dienestam vai dodieties uz HONOR klientu servisa centru, lai saņemtu atbalstu.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mai-IN" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय उपयोगकर्ता, ई अनुशंसित अपडेट मैजिक कैप्सूल प्रस्तुत करैत अछि। एकर अतिरिक्त, USB कनेक्शन उद्देश्य सभ स्विच करैत काल उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="मैजिक कैप्सूल">
<feature>मैजिक कैप्सूल अहाँ केँ सटीक आ कुशल सेवा सभ प्रदान करैत अछि। एकटा "कैप्सूल" केर रूप मे प्रदर्शित, ई चलि रहल टास्क सभ केँ प्रस्तुत करैत अछि, जाहि सँ वास्तविक-समय केर स्थिति देखब, त्वरित संचालन करब वा एप सभ मे त्वरित रूप सँ प्रविष्ट करब आसान भए जाइत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>USB कनेक्शन उद्देश्य सभ स्विच करैत काल उपयोगकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक अछि। जखन अहाँ मात्र चार्ज करबाक बजाय फोटो सभ केँ स्थानांतरित करू वा फाइल सभ ट्रांसफर करू/Android ऑटो चुनैत छी, तखन एकटा सत्यापन वा सुरक्षा संकेत देखाय पड़ैत अछि, जाहि सँ सुरक्षित डेटा ट्रांसफर सुनिश्चित होइत अछि।</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट:" type="end">
<feature>1. एहि अपडेट केँ इंस्टॉल कयला सँ अहाँक व्यक्तिगत डेटा प्रभावित नहि होयत, मुदा तैयो अपडेट करए सँ पहिने अपन डेटाक बैकअप लेबाक अनुशंसा कयल जाइत अछि।
2. यदि अपडेटक दरमियान अहाँ केँ कोनो समस्या अबैत अछि, त' सहायताक लेल कृपाकए HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइन पर कॉल करू वा HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्र पर जाउ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mi-NZ" code="1062">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>E te kaiwhakamahi, ka whakamōhiotia e tēnei whakahōutanga tūtohu te Pūmatua Tūmatarau. Tērā anō, ka hiahiatia he motuhēhēnga kaiwhakamahi ina whakawhiti i ngā take tūhononga USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pūmatua Tūmatarau">
<feature>Mā te Pūmatua Tūmatarau koe e whakarato ki ngā ratonga tika, māia hoki. E whakaaturia ana ki te āhua o tētahi "papa", ka whakaaturia e ia ngā tūmahi haere tonu, kia māmā ai te tiro ki te tūnga wā tūturu, te mahi i ngā mahi tere, te tāuru tere rānei i ngā taupānga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Pūnaha">
<feature>E hiahiatia ana te motuhēhēnga kaiwhakamahi ina whakawhiti i ngā take hononga USB. Ka puta mai tētahi manatokonga, tohuāki haumarutanga rānei ina tīpako koe i Whakawhiti whakaahua, Whakawhitia ngā kōnae / Android Auto rānei, kaua ko te Whakahiko anake, me whakarite kia haumaru ake te whakawhiti raraunga.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ngā Tuhipoka:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kāore e pā te tāuta i tēnei whakahōu ki ō ngā raraunga whaiaro, engari me tārua tonu ō raraunga i mua i te whakahōu.
2. Ki te tūtaki koe i ētahi raruraru i te wā o te whakahōu, waea atu koa ki te raina waewera ratonga HONOR, haere rānei ki te pokapū ratonga kiritaki HONOR hei tautoko.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mk-mk" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Почитуван кориснику, ова препорачано ажурирање ја воведува Магична капсула. Дополнително, потребна е автентикација на корисникот кога се врши промена на намената на поврзувањето преку USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Магична капсула">
<feature>Магична капсула ви обезбедува точни и ефикасни услуги. Се прикажува во форма на „капсула“ и ги претставува задачите во тек, со што го олеснува прегледот на статусот во реално време, вршењето брзи операции или брзо влегување во апликации.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>Потребна е автентикација на корисникот кога се врши промена на намената на поврзувањето преку USB. Се појавува барање за потврдување или безбедносно барање кога ќе изберете Пренесувајте фотографии или Пренос на датотеки / Android Auto наместо Само полнење, за да се осигури безбеден пренос на податоците.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Белешки:" type="end">
<feature>1. Инсталирањето на ова ажурирање нема да влијае врз вашите лични податоци, но, се препорачува да направите резервна копија од податоците пред да ажурирате.
2. Ако се појават проблеми во текот на ажурирањето, јавете се на телефонскиот број на службата за корисници на HONOR или посетете сервисен центар за корисници на HONOR за да добиете поддршка.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ml-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>പ്രിയ ഉപയോക്താവേ, ഈ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്ന അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് മാജിക്ക് ക്യാപ്‌സൂൾ അവതരിപ്പിക്കുന്നു. അതിനുപുറമേ, USB കണക്ഷൻ ആവശ്യകതകൾ മാറുമ്പോൾ ഉപയോക്താവിനെ പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കേണ്ടതും ആവശ്യമാണ്.</feature>
</features>
<features module="മാജിക്ക് ക്യാപ്‌സൂൾ">
<feature>മാജിക്ക് ക്യാപ്‌സൂൾ നിങ്ങൾക്ക് കൃത്യതയാർന്നതും ഫലപ്രദവുമായ സേവനങ്ങൾ നൽകുന്നു. ഒരു "ക്യാപ്‌സൂൾ" രൂപത്തിൽ പ്രദർശിപ്പിക്കപ്പെടുന്ന ഇത് ഇപ്പോൾ നടന്നുകൊണ്ടിരിക്കുന്ന ടാസ്‌ക്കുകളെ പ്രതിനിധാനം ചെയ്യുന്നു, ഇത് തത്സമയ സ്റ്റാറ്റസ് കാണുന്നതോ ദ്രുത പ്രവർത്തനങ്ങൾ നിർവ്വഹിക്കുന്നതോ ആപ്ലിക്കേഷനുകളിൽ അതിവേഗം പ്രവേശിക്കുന്നതോ എളുപ്പമാക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="സിസ്റ്റം">
<feature>USB കണക്ഷൻ ആവശ്യകതകൾ മാറുമ്പോൾ ഉപയോക്താവിനെ പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കൽ ആവശ്യമാണ്. 'ചാർജ് ചെയ്യാൻ മാത്രം' എന്നതിന് പകരം, നിങ്ങൾ 'ഫോട്ടോകൾ കൈമാറുക' അല്ലെങ്കിൽ 'ഫയലുകൾ കൈമാറുക/Android Auto' എന്നത് തിരഞ്ഞെടുക്കുമ്പോൾ ഒരു പരിശോധിച്ചുറപ്പിക്കൽ അല്ലെങ്കിൽ സുരക്ഷാ നിർദ്ദേശം ദൃശ്യമാകുന്നു, ഇത് സുരക്ഷിതമായ ഡാറ്റാ കൈമാറ്റം ഉറപ്പാക്കുന്നു.</feature>
</features>
<features module="കുറിപ്പുകൾ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ഈ അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ഇൻസ്റ്റാൾ ചെയ്യുന്നത് നിങ്ങളുടെ വ്യക്തിഗത ഡാറ്റയെ ബാധിക്കില്ല, എങ്കിൽപ്പോലും അപ്‌ഡേറ്റ് ചെയ്യുന്നതിന് മുമ്പായി നിങ്ങളുടെ ഡാറ്റ ബാക്കപ്പ് ചെയ്യാൻ ശുപാർശ ചെയ്യുന്നു.
2. അപ്‌ഡേറ്റിനിടെ എന്തെങ്കിലും പ്രശ്‌നങ്ങൾ നേരിടുകയാണെങ്കിൽ, പിന്തുണയ്‌ക്കായി HONOR സർവീസ് ഹോട്ട്‌ലൈനിൽ വിളിക്കുകയോ HONOR ഉപഭോക്തൃ സർവീസ് സെന്റർ സന്ദർശിക്കുകയോ ചെയ്യുക.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mn-MN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Хүндэт хэрэглэгч танаа, энэхүү санал болгож буй шинэчлэлтээр Шидэт капсулыг танилцуулж байна. Мөн энэ нь USB холболтын зорилгыг солих үед хэрэглэгчийн баталгаажуулалт шаардана.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Шидэт капсул">
<feature>Шидэт капсул нь оновчтой, үр дүнтэй үйлчилгээг үзүүлдэг. Энэ нь "капсул" хэлбэрээр харагдах бөгөөд одоо үргэлжилж буй даалгаврыг илэрхийлэх тул бодит хугацааны төлөв харах, шуурхай үйлдэл хийх, апликэйшн рүү шуурхай ороход илүү хялбар болсон.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Систем">
<feature>USB холболтын зорилгыг солих үед хэрэглэгчийн баталгаажуулалт шаардан. Зөвхөн цэнэглэхийн оронд, зургуудыг дамжуулах эсвэл файл шилжүүлэх / Андройд автоматыг сонгох үед баталгаажуулах эсвэл хамгаалалтын сануулга гарч ирж, өгөгдөл дамжуулах аюулгүй байдлыг хангана.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Тэмдэглэл:" type="end">
<feature>1. Энэ шинэчлэлтийг суулгах нь таны хувийн мэдээллийг арилгахгүй ч, шинэчлэхийн өмнө өгөгдлөө нөөцөлсөн нь дээр.
2. Шинэчлэх явцад ямар нэг асуудал тулгарсан тохиолдолд HONOR үйлчилгээний дуудлага хүлээн авах утас руу залгаж эсвэл HONOR хэрэглэгчийн үйлчилгээний төв рүү очиж дэмжлэг авна уу.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="mr-IN" code="1071">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>प्रिय वापरकर्ता, हे शिफारस केलेले अद्यतन जादूई कॅप्सूल सादर करते. याव्यतिरिक्त, USB कनेक्शनच्या उद्देशाने स्विच करताना वापरकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक आहे.</feature>
</features>
<features module="जादूई कॅप्सूल">
<feature>जादूई कॅप्सूल आपल्याला अचूक आणि कार्यक्षम सेवा प्रदान करते. जी "कॅप्सूलच्या" स्वरूपात प्रदर्शित केली जाते, चालू कार्ये सादर करते, ज्यामुळे रिअल-टाइम स्थिती पाहणे, जलद ऑपरेशन्स करणे किंवा ॲप्समध्ये जलदरीत्या प्रवेश करणे सोपे होते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="सिस्टम">
<feature>USB कनेक्शनच्या उद्देशांनी स्विच करताना वापरकर्ता प्रमाणीकरण आवश्यक आहे. जेव्हा आपण फोटो स्‍थानांतरित करा किंवा फाइल्स/Android स्वयं स्‍थानांतरित करा निवडता तेव्हा एक सत्यापन किंवा सुरक्षितता सूचना दिसते, केवळ चार्ज करण्याऐवजी, सुरक्षित डेटा स्थानांतरण सुनिश्चित करते.</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोट्स:" type="end">
<feature>1. हे अद्यतन स्थापित केल्याने आपल्या वैयक्तिक डेटावर परिणाम होणार नाही, परंतु तरीही अद्यतनित करण्यापूर्वी आपल्या डेटाचा बॅकअप घेण्याची शिफारस केली जाते.
2. अद्यतनादरम्यान आपल्याला काही समस्या आल्यास, कृपया HONOR सेवा हॉटलाइनवर कॉल करा किंवा समर्थनासाठी HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केंद्रावर जा.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ms-my" code="1086">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Pengguna yang dihormati, kemas kini yang disyorkan ini memperkenalkan Kapsul Magic. Selain itu, pengesahan pengguna diperlukan apabila menukar tujuan sambungan USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kapsul Magic">
<feature>Kapsul Magic menyediakan kepada anda perkhidmatan yang tepat dan cekap. Dipaparkan dalam bentuk "kapsul", ia membentangkan tugas sedang berjalan, memudahkan untuk melihat status masa nyata, melakukan operasi pantas atau memasuki aplikasi dengan cepat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Pengesahan pengguna diperlukan apabila menukar tujuan sambungan USB. Pengesahan atau gesaan keselamatan muncul apabila anda memilih Pindahkan foto atau Pindahkan fail / Android Auto, bukannya Cas sahaja, demi memastikan pemindahan data yang lebih selamat.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Nota:" type="end">
<feature>1. Tindakan memasang kemas kini ini tidak akan menjejaskan data peribadi anda, tetapi anda masih disyorkan untuk membuat sandaran data sebelum mengemas kini.
2. Jika anda menghadapi sebarang masalah semasa kemas kini, sila hubungi talian penting khidmat HONOR atau pergi ke pusat khidmat pelanggan HONOR untuk mendapatkan sokongan.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-mm" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>လေးစားရပါသော သုံးစွဲသူ၊ အကြံပြုထားသော ဤအပ်ဒိတ်တွင် Magic ဆေးတောင့်ရှည်နှင့် မိတ်ဆက်ပေးထားသည်။ ထို့အပြင် USB ပြောင်းလဲချိတ်ဆက်သည့်အခါ သုံးစွဲသူကို စစ်မှန်ကြောင်း အတည်ပြုရန် လိုအပ်သည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic ဆေးတောင့်ရှည်">
<feature>Magic ဆေးတောင့်ရှည်သည် မှန်ကန်တိကျပြီး ထိရောက်သော ဝန်ဆောင်မှုများကို သင့်အား ပံ့ပိုးပေးသည်။ ၎င်းကို "ဆေးတောင့်ရှည်" ပုံစံဖြင့် ပြသပြီး လုပ်ဆောင်နေဆဲ အလုပ်များကို ဖော်ပြသောကြောင့် အချိန်နှင့်တစ်ပြေးညီ ဖြစ်ပေါ်နေသော အခြေအနေကို အလွယ်တကူ ကြည့်ရှုနိုင်ကာ အမြန်လုပ်ဆောင်ချက်များ ပြုလုပ်နိုင်သည် သို့မဟုတ် အက်ပ်များထဲသို့ အမြန်ဝင်ရောက်နိုင်သည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ်">
<feature>USB ချိတ်ဆက်မှု အပြောင်းအလဲလုပ်သည့်အခါ သုံးစွဲသူကို စစ်မှန်ကြောင်း အတည်ပြုရန် လိုအပ်သည်။ "အားသွင်းရန်သာ" အစား ပုံများ လွှဲပြောင်းရန် သို့မဟုတ် ဖိုင်များ လွှဲပြောင်းရန် / Android Auto ကို ရွေးချယ်သည့်အခါ အတည်ပြုမှု သို့မဟုတ် လုံခြုံရေး ညွှန်ကြားချက် ပေါ်လာပြီး ဒေတာ လွှဲပြောင်းမှုကို ပို၍လုံခြုံစေသည်။</feature>
</features>
<features module="မှတ်ချက်-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ်ဒိတ်ကို ထည့်သွင်းခြင်းသည် သင့်ကိုယ်ရေး ဒေတာအပေါ် ထိခိုက်မည် မဟုတ်သော်လည်း အပ်ဒိတ်မလုပ်မီ သင့်ဒေတာကို ဘက်ခ်အပ်လုပ်ရန် အကြံပြုပါသည်။
2. အပ်ဒိတ်အတောအတွင်း ပြဿနာတစ်ခုခု ကြုံတွေ့ပါက အကူအညီအတွက် HONOR ဝန်ဆောင်မှုဌာန ဟော့လိုင်းသို့ ခေါ်ဆိုပါ သို့မဟုတ် HONOR သုံးစွဲသူ ဝန်ဆောင်မှုစင်တာသို့ သွားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="my-zg" code="1109">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ေလးစားရပါေသာ သုံးစြဲသူ၊ အႀကံျပဳထားေသာ ဤအပ္ဒိတ္တြင္ Magic ေဆးေတာင့္ရွည္ႏွင့္ မိတ္ဆက္ေပးထားသည္။ ထို႔အျပင္ USB ေျပာင္းလဲခ်ိတ္ဆက္သည့္အခါ သုံးစြဲသူကို စစ္မွန္ေၾကာင္း အတည္ျပဳရန္ လိုအပ္သည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic ေဆးေတာင့္ရွည္">
<feature>Magic ေဆးေတာင့္ရွည္သည္ မွန္ကန္တိက်ၿပီး ထိေရာက္ေသာ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈမ်ားကို သင့္အား ပံ့ပိုးေပးသည္။ ၎ကို "ေဆးေတာင့္ရွည္" ပုံစံျဖင့္ ျပသၿပီး လုပ္ေဆာင္ေနဆဲ အလုပ္မ်ားကို ေဖာ္ျပေသာေၾကာင့္ အခ်ိန္ႏွင့္တစ္ေျပးညီ ျဖစ္ေပၚေနေသာ အေျခအေနကို အလြယ္တကူ ၾကည့္ရႈႏိုင္ကာ အျမန္လုပ္ေဆာင္ခ်က္မ်ား ျပဳလုပ္ႏိုင္သည္ သို႔မဟုတ္ အက္ပ္မ်ားထဲသို႔ အျမန္ဝင္ေရာက္ႏိုင္သည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="စနစ္">
<feature>USB ခ်ိတ္ဆက္မႈ အေျပာင္းအလဲလုပ္သည့္အခါ သုံးစြဲသူကို စစ္မွန္ေၾကာင္း အတည္ျပဳရန္ လိုအပ္သည္။ "အားသြင္းရန္သာ" အစား ပုံမ်ား လႊဲေျပာင္းရန္ သို႔မဟုတ္ ဖိုင္မ်ား လႊဲေျပာင္းရန္ / Android Auto ကို ေ႐ြးခ်ယ္သည့္အခါ အတည္ျပဳမႈ သို႔မဟုတ္ လုံျခံဳေရး ၫႊန္ၾကားခ်က္ ေပၚလာၿပီး ေဒတာ လႊဲေျပာင္းမႈကို ပို၍လုံၿခဳံေစသည္။</feature>
</features>
<features module="မွတ္ခ်က္-" type="end">
<feature>1. ဤအပ္ဒိတ္ကို ထည့္သြင္းျခင္းသည္ သင့္ကိုယ္ေရး ေဒတာအေပၚ ထိခိုက္မည္ မဟုတ္ေသာ္လည္း အပ္ဒိတ္မလုပ္မီ သင့္ေဒတာကို ဘက္ခ္အပ္လုပ္ရန္ အႀကံျပဳပါသည္။
2. အပ္ဒိတ္အေတာအတြင္း ျပႆနာတစ္ခုခု ႀကဳံေတြ႕ပါက အကူအညီအတြက္ HONOR ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈဌာန ေဟာ့လိုင္းသို႔ ေခၚဆိုပါ သို႔မဟုတ္ HONOR သုံးစြဲသူ ဝန္ေဆာင္မႈစင္တာသို႔ သြားပါ။</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nb-no" code="1044">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Kjære bruker, denne anbefalte oppdateringen introduserer Magisk kapsel. I tillegg kreves brukergodkjenning ved bytte av USB-tilkoblingsformål.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magisk kapsel">
<feature>Magisk kapsel gi deg nøyaktige og effektive tjenester. Den vises i form av en «kapsel», og presenterer pågående oppgaver, slik at det blir lett å se status i sanntid, utføre hurtighandlinger eller raskt åpne apper.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Brukerbekreftelse kreves ved bytting av USB-tilkoblingsformål. En bekreftelse eller sikkerhetsmelding dukker opp når du velger Overfør bilder eller Overfør filer / Android Auto istedenfor Bare opplading, og sikrer dermed tryggere dataoverføring.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Merknader:" type="end">
<feature>1. Å installere denne oppdateringen vil ikke påvirke personopplysningene dine, men vi anbefaler likevel at du sikkerhetskopierer dataene dine før du oppdaterer.
2. Hvis du møter på problemer under oppdateringen, ring HONOR-kundeservice eller gå til HONOR-kundeservicesenteret for assistanse.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ne-np" code="1121">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>आदरणीय प्रयोगकर्ता, सिफारिस गरिएको यो अपडेटले म्याजिक क्याप्सुल सुविधा ल्याएको छ । साथै, USB जडानका प्रयोजनहरू परिवर्तन गर्दा प्रयोगकर्ताले अधिकार-प्रदान गर्नु पर्ने हुन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="म्याजिक क्याप्सुल">
<feature>म्याजिक क्याप्सुलले तपाईंलाई सटीक र प्रभावकारी सेवाहरू प्रदान गर्छ । "क्याप्सुल"का रूपमा देखाइने यसले जारी कार्यहरू देखाउँछ जसले गर्दा वास्तविक समयमा स्थिति हेर्न, द्रुत कारबाहीहरू गर्न वा तुरुन्तै एपमा जान सजिलो हुन्छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="प्रणाली">
<feature>USB जडानका प्रयोजनहरू परिवर्तन गर्दा प्रयोगकर्ताले अधिकार-प्रदान गर्नु पर्ने हुन्छ । तपाईंले चार्ज मात्र गर्नुहोस् विकल्पको साटो फोटोहरू स्थानान्तरण गर्नुहोस् वा फाइल स्थानान्तर गर्नुहोस् / Android Auto चयन गर्नुभयो भने प्रमाणीकरण वा सुरक्षा प्रम्प्ट देखिने छ ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="नोटहरू:" type="end">
<feature>1. तपाईंले यो एप स्थापना गर्नुभयो भने तपाईंको व्यक्तिगत डाटामा कुनै प्रभाव नपर्ने भए पनि तपाईंलाई अपडेट गर्नुअघि आफ्नो डाटा ब्याकअप गर्न सिफारिस गरिन्छ ।
2. अपडेटको समयमा तपाईंले कुनै पनि समस्याको सामना गर्नुभयो भने, कृपया HONOR सेवा हटलाइनमा कल गर्नुहोस् वा सहायताका लागि HONOR ग्राहक सेवा केन्द्रमा जानुहोस् ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="nl-nl" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Beste gebruiker, deze aanbevolen update introduceert Magische capsule. Bovendien is gebruikersauthenticatie vereist bij het wisselen van USB-verbindingsdoeleinden.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magische capsule">
<feature>Magische capsule biedt u nauwkeurige en efficiënte services. Het wordt weergegeven in de vorm van een "capsule" en toont lopende taken, waardoor het gemakkelijk is om de realtime status ervan te bekijken, snelle bewerkingen uit te voeren of snel apps te openen.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systeem">
<feature>Gebruikersauthenticatie is vereist bij het wisselen van USB-verbindingsdoeleinden. Er verschijnt een verificatie- of beveiligingsprompt wanneer u Foto's overdragen of Bestanden overdragen / Android Auto selecteert, in plaats van Alleen opladen, wat zorgt voor een veiligere gegevensoverdracht.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opmerkingen:" type="end">
<feature>1. Als u deze update installeert, worden uw persoonlijke gegevens niet beïnvloed, maar een back-up van uw gegevens maken voordat u bijwerkt wordt nog steeds aanbevolen.
2. Als u problemen ondervindt tijdens de update, bel dan de HONOR-servicehotline of ga naar een HONOR-klantenservicecentrum voor ondersteuning.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="or-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ପ୍ରିୟ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା, ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଥିବା ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ରେ ମ୍ୟାଜିକ୍ କ୍ୟାପସୁଲ୍ ରହିଛି। ଅତିରିକ୍ତ ଭାବେ, USB ସଂଯୋଜନା ଉଦ୍ଦେଶ୍ୟ ସ୍ୱିଚ୍ କରିବା ବେଳେ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ପ୍ରାମାଣିକରଣ ଆବଶ୍ୟକ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ମ୍ୟାଜିକ୍ କ୍ୟାପସୁଲ୍">
<feature>ମ୍ୟାଜିକ୍ କ୍ୟାପସୁଲ୍ ଆପଣଙ୍କୁ ସଠିକ ତଥା ଦକ୍ଷ ସେବାଗୁଡ଼ିକ ପ୍ରଦାନ କରେ। ଏକ "କ୍ୟାପସୁଲ୍‌" ଆକାରରେ ପ୍ରଦର୍ଶିତ କରାଯାଇ, ଏବଂ ଚାଲୁଥିବା ଟାସ୍କ ଦର୍ଶାଏ, ଯାହା ରିଅଲ୍‌-ଟାଇମ୍ ସ୍ଥିତି ଦେଖିବାରେ, ଦ୍ରୁତ ସଞ୍ଚାଳନାଗୁଡ଼ିକ ସମ୍ପାଦନ କରିବାରେ, କିମ୍ବା ଆପସ୍‌ରେ ତୁରନ୍ତ ପ୍ରବେଶ କରିବାରେ ସହଜ କରାଏ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ସିଷ୍ଟମ୍‌">
<feature>USB ସଂଯୋଜନା ଉଦ୍ଦେଶ୍ୟ ସ୍ୱିଚ୍ କରିବା ବେଳେ ଉପଯୋଗକର୍ତ୍ତା ପ୍ରାମାଣିକରଣ ଆବଶ୍ୟକ। ଆପଣ ଫଟୋଗୁଡିକ ସ୍ଥାନାନ୍ତର କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ଫାଇଲ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ ଟ୍ରାନ୍ସଫର୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ/Android Auto ଚୟନ କରିବା ବେଳେ, କେବଳ ଚାର୍ଜ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ ବଦଳରେ ସୁରକ୍ଷିତ ଡାଟା ଟ୍ରାନ୍ସଫର୍‌ ନିଶ୍ଚିତ କରି ଏହା ଯାଞ୍ଚ କିମ୍ବା ସୁରକ୍ଷା ପ୍ରମ୍ପଟ୍‌ ଦେଖାଯଏ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ନୋଟ୍‌ଗୁଡ଼ିକ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ଏହି ଅପଡେଟ୍ ସଂସ୍ଥାପନ କରିବା ଦ୍ୱାରା ଆପଣଙ୍କ ବ୍ୟକ୍ତିଗତ ଡାଟା ପ୍ରଭାବିତ ହେବ ନାହିଁ, ତଥାପି ଅପଡେଟ୍ କରିବା ପୂର୍ବରୁ ଆପଣଙ୍କ ଡାଟାର ବ୍ୟାକଅପ୍‌ ନେବାକୁ ସୁପାରିଶ କରାଯାଇଛି।
2. ଅପଡେଟ୍‌ ସମୟରେ ଯଦି ଆପଣ କୌଣସି ସମସ୍ୟାର ସମ୍ମୁଖୀନ ହୁଅନ୍ତି, ଦୟାକରି HONOR ସେବା ହଟଲାଇନ୍‌ରେ କଲ୍‌ କରନ୍ତୁ କିମ୍ବା ସହାୟତା ପାଇଁ ଏକ HONOR ଗ୍ରାହକ ସେବା କେନ୍ଦ୍ରକୁ ଯାଆନ୍ତୁ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pa-IN" code="1043">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ਪਿਆਰੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ, ਇਸ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੇ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਵਿੱਚ ਮੈਜਿਕ ਕੈਪਸੂਲ ਨੂੰ ਪੇਸ਼ ਕੀਤਾ ਗਿਆ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਤੋਂ ਇਲਾਵਾ, USB ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਦੇ ਉਦੇਸ਼ਾਂ ਦੀ ਅਦਲਾ-ਬਦਲੀ ਕਰਨ ਵੇਲੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਪ੍ਰਮਾਣੀਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਲੋੜ ਹੁੰਦੀ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਮੈਜਿਕ ਕੈਪਸੂਲ">
<feature>ਮੈਜਿਕ ਕੈਪਸੂਲ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਸਟੀਕ ਅਤੇ ਕੁਸ਼ਲ ਸੇਵਾਵਾਂ ਪ੍ਰਦਾਨ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ। ਇਸ ਨੂੰ "ਕੈਪਸੂਲ" ਦੇ ਰੂਪ ਵਿੱਚ ਪ੍ਰਦਰਸ਼ਿਤ ਕੀਤਾ ਜਾਂਦਾ ਹੈ, ਅਤੇ ਇਹ ਚੱਲ ਰਹੇ ਕਾਰਜਾਂ ਨੂੰ ਪੇਸ਼ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ, ਜਿਸ ਨਾਲ ਅਸਲ-ਸਮਾਂ ਸਥਿਤੀ ਨੂੰ ਵੇਖਣਾ, ਤੇਜ਼ ਕਾਰਵਾਈਆਂ ਕਰਨਾ, ਜਾਂ ਐਪਾ ਵਿੱਚ ਤੇਜ਼ੀ ਨਾਲ ਦਾਖਲ ਹੋਣਾ ਆਸਾਨ ਹੋ ਜਾਂਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਸਿਸਟਮ">
<feature>USB ਕਨੈਕਸ਼ਨ ਦੇ ਉਦੇਸ਼ਾਂ ਦੀ ਅਦਲਾ-ਬਦਲੀ ਕਰਨ ਵੇਲੇ ਵਰਤੋਂਕਾਰ ਪ੍ਰਮਾਣੀਕਰਨ ਦੀ ਲੋੜ ਹੁੰਦੀ ਹੈ। ਜਦੋਂ ਤੁਸੀਂ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਅਤ ਡੇਟਾ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਨੂੰ ਯਕੀਨੀ ਬਣਾਉਣ ਲਈ, ਸਿਰਫ਼ ਚਾਰਜ ਕਰੋ ਦੀ ਬਜਾਏ, ਫ਼ੋਟੋਆਂ ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ ਫ਼ਾਈਲਾਂ/Android Auto ਟ੍ਰਾਂਸਫਰ ਕਰੋ ਨੂੰ ਚੁਣਦੇ ਹੋ ਤਾਂ ਤਸਦੀਕ ਜਾਂ ਸੁਰੱਖਿਆ ਪ੍ਰੌਂਪਟ ਦਿਖਾਈ ਦਿੰਦਾ ਹੈ।</feature>
</features>
<features module="ਨੋਟਸ:" type="end">
<feature>1. ਇਸ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਨੂੰ ਇੰਸਟਾਲ ਕਰਨ ਨਾਲ ਤੁਹਾਡਾ ਨਿੱਜੀ ਡੇਟਾ ਪ੍ਰਭਾਵਿਤ ਨਹੀਂ ਹੋਵੇਗਾ, ਪਰ ਤਾਂ ਵੀ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਕਰਨ ਤੋਂ ਪਹਿਲਾਂ ਤੁਹਾਡੇ ਡੇਟਾ ਦਾ ਬੈਕਅੱਪ ਲੈਣ ਦੀ ਸਿਫ਼ਾਰਸ਼ ਕੀਤੀ ਜਾਂਦੀ ਹੈ।
2. ਜੇ ਤੁਹਾਨੂੰ ਅੱਪਡੇਟ ਦੌਰਾਨ ਕੋਈ ਸਮੱਸਿਆ ਆਉਂਦੀ ਹੈ, ਤਾਂ ਸਹਾਇਤਾ ਲਈ ਕਿਰਪਾ ਕਰਕੇ HONOR ਸੇਵਾ ਦੀ ਹੌਟਲਾਈਨ 'ਤੇ ਕਾਲ ਕਰੋ ਜਾਂ HONOR ਗਾਹਕ ਸੇਵਾ ਕੇਂਦਰ 'ਤੇ ਜਾਓ।</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pl-pl" code="1045">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Ta zalecana aktualizacja wprowadza Magiczną kapsułę. Ponadto jest wymagane uwierzytelnianie użytkownika podczas przełączania celów połączenia USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magiczna kapsuła">
<feature>Magiczna kapsuła oferuje trafnie dobrane i efektywne usługi. Jest wyświetlana w formie kapsuły i prezentuje bieżące zadania. Dzięki temu można łatwo sprawdzać status w czasie rzeczywistym i szybko wykonywać operacje lub przechodzić do aplikacji.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Wymagane jest uwierzytelnienie użytkownika podczas przełączania celów połączenia USB. Monit o weryfikację lub monit dotyczący bezpieczeństwa pojawia się po wybraniu opcji Transferowanie zdjęć lub Transferowanie plików / Android Auto zamiast opcji Tylko ładowanie, zapewniając bezpieczniejszy transfer danych.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Uwagi:" type="end">
<feature>1. Zainstalowanie tej aktualizacji nie wpływa na dane użytkownika, jednak zaleca się wykonanie kopii zapasowej przed aktualizacją.
2. Jeśli podczas aktualizacji wystąpią jakiekolwiek problemy, zadzwoń na infolinię firmy HONOR lub odwiedź punkt serwisowy firmy HONOR, gdzie uzyskasz pomoc.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-br" code="1046">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Prezado(a) usuário(a), esta atualização recomendada apresenta a Cápsula mágica. Além disso, a autenticação de usuário passou a ser necessária ao mudar o propósito da conexão USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cápsula mágica">
<feature>A Cápsula mágica fornece a você serviços precisos e eficientes. Exibida como uma "cápsula", ela apresenta tarefas em andamento, facilitando a visualização do status em tempo real, a realização de operações rápidas ou a entrada rápida em aplicativos.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>A autenticação de usuário é necessária ao mudar o propósito da conexão USB. Uma mensagem de verificação ou segurança aparece quando você seleciona Transferir fotos ou Transferir arquivos/Android Auto, em vez de Carregar apenas, garantindo uma transferência de dados mais segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Observações:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não afetará seus dados pessoais, mas um backup prévio ainda é recomendado.
2. Se você encontrar algum problema durante a atualização, ligue para a linha de atendimento de serviço da HONOR ou vá à Central de serviços de atendimento ao cliente HONOR para obter suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="pt-pt" code="2070">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Caro utilizador, esta atualização recomendada apresenta a Cápsula mágica. Adicionalmente, é necessária a autenticação do utilizador quando se alterna a finalidade da ligação USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Cápsula mágica">
<feature>A Cápsula mágica fornece-lhe serviços precisos e eficientes. Apresentada sob a forma de uma “cápsula”, apresenta as tarefas em curso, facilitando a visualização do estado em tempo real, a realização de operações rápidas ou a introdução rápida de aplicações.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistema">
<feature>É necessária a autenticação do utilizador ao mudar para a ligação USB. É apresentado um comando de verificação ou segurança ao selecionar Transferir fotografias ou Transferir ficheiros/Android Auto em vez de Apenas carregar, garantindo a transferência de dados mais segura.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notas:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalar esta atualização não irá afetar os seus dados pessoais, mas continua a recomendar-se a realização prévia de uma cópia de segurança.
2. Se encontrar quaisquer problemas durante a atualização, ligue para a linha direta de assistência da HONOR ou dirija-se ao centro de apoio ao cliente HONOR para suporte.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ro-ro" code="1048">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Stimate utilizator, această actualizare recomandată introduce funcția Capsulă magică. În plus, este necesară autentificarea utilizatorului atunci când schimbați scopul conexiunii USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Capsulă magică">
<feature>Funcția Capsulă magică vă oferă servicii precise și eficiente. Afișată sub forma unei „capsule”, acesta prezintă sarcinile în curs, facilitând vizualizarea în timp real a stării sistemului, efectuarea de operațiuni rapide sau accesarea rapidă a aplicațiilor.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Autentificarea utilizatorului devine necesară atunci când schimbați scopul conexiunii USB. Un mesaj de verificare sau de securitate apare atunci când selectați Transfer de fotografii sau Transferare fișiere/Android Auto, în loc de Doar încărcare, asigurând un transfer de date mai sigur.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Note:" type="end">
<feature>1. Instalarea acestei actualizări nu va cauza ștergerea datelor dvs. personale, dar vă recomandăm totuși să realizați în prealabil o copie de rezervă.
2. Dacă întâmpinați probleme în timpul actualizării, apelați linia de asistență HONOR sau vizitați un centru de servicii pentru clienți HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ru-ru" code="1049">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Уважаемый пользователь! Мы разработали это рекомендованное обновление, чтобы добавить функцию Magic Capsule. Кроме того, теперь при переключении USB-соединения требуется аутентификация пользователя.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Функция Magic Capsule предоставляет точные и эффективные службы. Она отображается в виде капсулы и содержит текущие задачи, что позволяет удобно просматривать их статус в режиме реального времени, выполнять быстрые операции и легко входить в приложения.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>При переключении USB-соединения требуется аутентификация пользователя. При выборе режима «Передача фото», «Передача файлов/Android Auto» вместо режима «Только зарядка» появляется запрос проверки или безопасности, что обеспечивает более безопасную передачу данных.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примечания:" type="end">
<feature>1. Установка этого обновления не затронет ваши персональные данные, но мы рекомендует сделать резервную копию данных перед обновлением.
2. При возникновении каких-либо проблем при обновлении обратитесь на горячую линию обслуживания HONOR или в службу поддержки клиента HONOR за помощью.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="si-lk" code="1115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>හිතවත් පරිශීලක, මෙම නිර්දේශිත යාවත්කාලය මැජික් කැප්සියුලය හඳුන්වා දෙයි. මීට අමතරව, USB සම්බන්ධතා අරමුණු මාරු කිරීමේ දී පරිශීලක සත්‍යාපනය අවශ්‍ය වේ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="මැජික් කැප්සියුලය">
<feature>මැජික් කැප්සියුලය ඔබට නිවැරදි සහ කාර්යක්ෂම සේවා සපයයි. "කැප්සියුලයක්" ආකාරයෙන් සංදර්ශනය කෙරෙන එය තත්‍ය කාලීන තත්වය බැලීම, ඉක්මන් මෙහෙයුම් සිදු කිරීම හෝ ඉක්මනින් යෙදුම් වෙත ඇතුල්වීම පහසු කරමින් දැනට පවතින කාර්යයන් ඉදිරිපත් කරයි.</feature>
</features>
<features module="පද්ධතිය">
<feature>USB සම්බන්ධතා අරමුණු මාරු කිරීමේ දී පරිශීලක සත්‍යාපනය අවශ්‍ය වේ. ඔබ ආරෝපණය පමණි වෙනුවට ඡායාරූප මාරු කරන්න හෝ ගොනු හුවමාරු කරන්න / Android Auto තෝරාගත් විට, වඩා ආරක්ෂිත දත්ත මාරුව තහවුරු කරමින් සත්‍යාපන හෝ ආරක්ෂක ප්‍රේරණයක් දිස්වේ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="සටහන්:" type="end">
<feature>1. මෙම යාවත්කාලය ස්ථාපනය කිරීම ඔබගේ පෞද්ගලික දත්තවලට බල නොපානු ඇති නමුත් තවමත් යාවත්කාල කිරීමට පෙර ඔබගේ දත්ත උපස්ථ කිරීමට නිර්දේශ කෙරේ.
2. යාවත්කාල කිරීමේ දී ඔබට ගැටළු කිසිවක් ඇති වුවහොත්, කරුණාකර HONOR සේවා හොට්ලයින් අමතන්න නැතහොත් සහය සඳහා HONOR පාරිභෝගික සේවා මධ්‍යස්ථානයට යන්න.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sk-sk" code="1051">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Vážený používateľ, táto odporúčaná aktualizácia pridáva funkciu Magická kapsula. Okrem toho sa pri prepínaní na účely pripojenia USB vyžaduje overenie používateľa.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magická kapsula">
<feature>Magická kapsula vám poskytuje precízne a efektívne služby. Zobrazuje sa vo forme „kapsuly“ a predstavuje prebiehajúce úlohy, čím uľahčuje zobrazenie stavu v reálnom čase, vykonávanie rýchlych operácií alebo rýchly prechod do aplikácií.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Systém">
<feature>Pri prepínaní na účely pripojenia USB sa vyžaduje overenie používateľa. Pri výbere možnosti Prenos fotografií alebo Prenos súborov/Android Auto sa namiesto možnosti Len nabíjanie zobrazí výzva na overenie alebo zabezpečenie, čím sa zaistí bezpečnejší prenos dát.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Poznámky:" type="end">
<feature>1. Inštalácia tejto aktualizácie neovplyvní vaše osobné údaje, ale aj tak sa odporúča pred aktualizáciou si ich zálohovať.
2. Ak sa počas aktualizácie vyskytnú problémy, podporu môžete získať zavolaním na zákaznícku linku HONOR alebo návštevou Centra služieb zákazníkom HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sl-si" code="1060">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Spoštovani uporabnik, ta priporočena posodobitev uvaja funkcijo Čarobna kapsula. Obenem je pri preklopu povezave USB potrebno preverjanje pristnosti uporabnika.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Čarobna kapsula">
<feature>Čarobna kapsula zagotavlja točne in učinkovite storitve. V obliki »kapsule« prikazuje opravila v teku in omogoča enostaven pregled sprotnega stanja, izvajanje hitrih postopkov ali hitro odpiranje aplikacij.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>Pri preklopu povezave USB je potrebno preverjanje pristnosti uporabnika. Ko izberete možnost Prenos fotografij ali Prenos datotek/Android Auto, se namesto možnosti Samo polnjenje prikaže poziv za preverjanje ali varnostni poziv, s tem pa je zagotovljen varnejši prenos podatkov.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Opombe:" type="end">
<feature>1. Namestitev te posodobitve ne bo vplivala na vaše osebne podatke, vendar vseeno priporočamo, da podatke pred posodobitvijo varnostno kopirate.
2. Če med posodabljanjem naletite na težave, lahko pokličete odprto linijo za pomoč uporabnikom družbe HONOR ali obiščete središče za storitve družbe HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sv-se" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Bästa användare, den här rekommenderade uppdateringen introducerar Magisk kapsel. Användarautentisering krävs dessutom när du byter USB-anslutning.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magisk kapsel">
<feature>Magisk kapsel ger dig exakta och effektiva tjänster. Den visas som en ”kapsel” och innehåller pågående uppgifter, vilket gör det enkelt att visa status i realtid, utföra snabbåtgärder eller snabbt öppna appar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Användarautentisering krävs när du byter USB-anslutning. En verifierings- eller säkerhetsuppmaning visas när du väljer Överföra foton eller Överföra filer/Android Auto i stället för Endast laddning, vilket ger en säkrare dataöverföring.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Noteringar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installation av den här uppdateringen påverkar inte dina personuppgifter, men det rekommenderas ändå att du säkerhetskopierar alla data innan du uppdaterar.
2. Om du stöter på några problem under uppdateringen kan du ringa HONORs hotline för service eller besöka HONORs servicecenter och få support.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="sw-KE" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Mtumiaji mpendwa, sasisho hili linalopendekezwa linaleta Kapsuli ya Miujiza. Pia, uthibitishaji wa mtumiaji unahitajika unapobadilisha madhumuni ya muunganisho wa USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Kapsuli ya Miujiza">
<feature>Kapsuli ya Miujiza hukupa huduma sahihi na fanisi. Ikiwa imeonyeshwa katika hali ya "kapsuli", inaonyesha majukumu yanayoendelea, hivyo basi kurahisisha kuona hali ya muda halisi, kutekeleza shughuli za haraka au kuingia programu kwa haraka.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mfumo">
<feature>Uthibitishaji wa mtumiaji unahitajika unapobadilisha madhumuni ya muunganisho wa USB. Kidokezo cha uthibitishaji au usalama hutokea unapochagua Hamisha picha au Hamisha faili/Android Auto, badala ya Chaji pekee, hivyo basi kuhakikisha uhamishaji salama wa data.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Madokezo:" type="end">
<feature>1. Kusakinisha sasisho hili hakutaathiri data yako ya kibinafsi, lakini bado unapendekezwa kuweka hifadhi rudufu ya data yako kabla ya kusasisha.
2. Ukikumbana na matatizo yoyote wakati wa sasisho, tafadhali piga simu kwa nambari ya dharura ya huduma ya HONOR au nenda kwenye kituo cha huduma kwa wateja cha HONOR ili upate usaidizi.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ta-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>அன்புள்ள பயனரே, இந்தப் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படும் புதுப்பிப்பு மேஜிக் கேப்சூலை அறிமுகப்படுத்துகிறது. கூடுதலாக, USB இணைப்பு நோக்கங்களை மாற்றும்போது பயனர் அங்கீகாரம் தேவை.</feature>
</features>
<features module="மேஜிக் கேப்சூல்">
<feature>மேஜிக் கேப்சூல் துல்லியமான மற்றும் திறன்மிக்க சேவைகளை உங்களுக்கு வழங்குகிறது. ஒரு "கேப்சூல்" வடிவத்தில் காட்டப்படுகிறது, இது தற்போதைய பணிகளை வழங்குகிறது, இதனால் நிகழ் நேர நிலையைப் பார்ப்பது, விரைவான செயல்பாடுகளைச் செய்வது அல்லது செயலிகளுக்கு விரைவாகச் செல்வது ஆகியவற்றை எளிதாக்குகிறது.</feature>
</features>
<features module="சிஸ்டம்">
<feature>USB இணைப்பு நோக்கங்களை மாற்றும்போது பயனர் அங்கீகாரம் தேவை. பாதுகாப்பான தரவுப் பரிமாற்றத்தை உறுதிசெய்யும் வகையில், சார்ஜ் மட்டும் என்பதற்குப் பதிலாக, புகைப்படங்களைப் பரிமாற்று அல்லது கோப்புகளைப் பரிமாற்று / Android Auto என்பதைத் தேர்ந்தெடுக்கும்போது சரிபார்ப்பு அல்லது பாதுகாப்புத் தூண்டுதல் தோன்றும்.</feature>
</features>
<features module="குறிப்புகள்:" type="end">
<feature>1. இந்தப் புதுப்பிப்பை நிறுவுவது உங்கள் தனிப்பட்ட தரவைப் பாதிக்காது, எனினும் புதுப்பிப்பதற்கு முன்பு உங்கள் தரவைக் காப்புப்பிரதி எடுப்பது இன்னும் பரிந்துரைக்கப்படுகிறது.
2. புதுப்பிப்புச் செயல்பாட்டின்போது ஏதேனும் சிக்கல்களைச் சந்தித்தால், உதவிக்காக HONOR சேவை ஹாட்லைனை அழைக்கவும் அல்லது HONOR வாடிக்கையாளர் சேவை மையத்திற்குச் செல்லவும்.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="te-IN" code="1053">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>ప్రియమైన వినియోగదారుకు, ఈ సిఫార్సు చేయబడిన అప్‌డేట్ మేజిక్ క్యాప్సుల్‌ను పరిచయం చేస్తుంది. అదనంగా, USB కనెక్షన్ ప్రయోజనాలను మార్చుతున్నప్పుడు వినియోగదారు ప్రామాణీకరణ అవసరం.</feature>
</features>
<features module="మేజిక్ క్యాప్సుల్">
<feature>మేజిక్ క్యాప్సుల్ అనేది మీకు ఖచ్చితమైన మరియు సమర్థవంతమైన సేవలు అందిస్తుంది. "క్యాప్సుల్" రూపంలో ప్రదర్శించబడే ఇది జరుగుతున్న టాస్క్‌లను చూపుతుంది, ఈ విధంగా నిజ సమయ స్థితిని చూడటం సులభం చేస్తుంది, త్వరిత ఆపరేషన్‌లను అమలు చేస్తుంది లేదా త్వరగా అప్లికేషన్‌ల్లోకి ప్రవేశిస్తుంది.</feature>
</features>
<features module="సిస్టమ్">
<feature>USB కనెక్షన్ ప్రయోజనాలను మార్చేటప్పుడు వినియోగదారు ప్రమాణీకరణ అవసరం. మీరు ఛార్జ్ మాత్రమే కాకుండా, సురక్షితమైన డేటా బదిలీని నిర్ధారిస్తూ ఫోటోలను బదిలీ చేయండి లేదా ఫైల్స్ బదిలీ చేయి / Android Autoను బదిలీ చేయడాన్ని ఎంచుకున్నప్పుడు ధృవీకరణ లేదా భద్రతా ప్రాంప్ట్ కనిపిస్తుంది</feature>
</features>
<features module="గమనికలు:" type="end">
<feature>1. ఈ అప్‌డేట్‌ను ఇన్‌స్టాల్ చేయడం వల్ల మీ వ్యక్తిగత డేటాపై ప్రభావం ఉండదు, అయితే అప్‌డేట్ చేయడానికి ముందు మీ డేటాను బ్యాకప్ చేయాలని ఇప్పటికీ సిఫార్సు చేయబడింది.
2. అప్‌డేట్ సమయంలో మీకు ఏవైనా సమస్యలు ఎదురైతే, దయచేసి HONOR సర్వీస్ హాట్‌లైన్‌కు కాల్ చేయండి లేదా మద్దతు కోసం HONOR కస్టమర్ సర్వీస్ కేంద్రానికి వెళ్ళండి.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="th-th" code="1054">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>เรียนผู้ใช้ การอัปเดตที่แนะนำครั้งนี้เปิดตัวเมจิกแคปซูล นอกจากนี้จำเป็นต้องมีการรับรองความถูกต้องของผู้ใช้เพื่อวัตถุประสงค์ในการสลับการเชื่อมต่อ USB</feature>
</features>
<features module="เมจิกแคปซูล">
<feature>เมจิกแคปซูลให้บริการที่แม่นยำและมีประสิทธิภาพซึ่งแสดงในรูปแบบ "แคปซูล" ซึ่งแสดงงานที่กำลังดำเนินอยู่ ช่วยให้ง่ายต่อการดูสถานะแบบเรียลไทม์ ทำการดำเนินการอย่างรวดเร็ว หรือเข้าสู่แอปอย่างรวดเร็ว</feature>
</features>
<features module="ระบบ">
<feature>จำเป็นต้องมีการรับรองความถูกต้องของผู้ใช้เพื่อวัตถุประสงค์ในการสลับการเชื่อมต่อ USB การยืนยันหรือข้อความแจ้งเตือนความปลอดภัยจะปรากฏเมื่อคุณเลือกถ่ายโอนรูปภาพหรือถ่ายโอนไฟล์ / Android Auto แทนที่จะชาร์จเท่านั้นเพื่อให้แน่ใจถึงการถ่ายโอนข้อมูลที่ปลอดภัยขึ้น</feature>
</features>
<features module="โปรดทราบ:" type="end">
<feature>1. การติดตั้งอัปเดตนี้จะไม่กระทบต่อข้อมูลส่วนตัวของคุณ แต่เรายังคงแนะนำให้สำรองข้อมูลของคุณก่อนที่จะอัปเดต
2. หากคุณพบปัญหาใด ๆ ในระหว่างการอัปเดต โปรดโทรติดต่อสายด่วนการบริการของ HONOR หรือไปที่ศูนย์บริการลูกค้าของ HONOR เพื่อขอการสนับสนุน</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tl-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, ipinapakilala ng inirerekomendang update na ito ang Magic Capsule. Bukod pa rito, kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag lumilipat ng mga layunin ng koneksyon sa USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Nagbibigay sa iyo ang Magic Capsule ng mga tumpak at mahusay na serbisyo. Ipinapakita sa pamamagitan ng "capsule," at nagpapakita ng mga kasalukuyang gawain, na nagpapadali para matingnan ang real-time na katayuan, magsagawa ng mga mabilisang pagpapatakbo, o mabilis na pumasok sa mga app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag lumilipat ng mga layunin ng koneksyon sa USB. Lalabas ang isang pag-verify o panseguridad na prompt kapag pinili mo ang Maglipat ng mga larawan o Maglipat ng mga file / Android Auto, sa halip na Mag-charge lang, na tumitiyak sa mas ligtas na paglilipat ng data.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="fil-ph" code="1124">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Minamahal na user, ipinapakilala ng inirerekomendang update na ito ang Magic Capsule. Bukod pa rito, kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag lumilipat ng mga layunin ng koneksyon sa USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Nagbibigay sa iyo ang Magic Capsule ng mga tumpak at mahusay na serbisyo. Ipinapakita sa pamamagitan ng "capsule," at nagpapakita ng mga kasalukuyang gawain, na nagpapadali para matingnan ang real-time na katayuan, magsagawa ng mga mabilisang pagpapatakbo, o mabilis na pumasok sa mga app.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>Kinakailangan ang pag-authenticate ng user kapag lumilipat ng mga layunin ng koneksyon sa USB. Lalabas ang isang pag-verify o panseguridad na prompt kapag pinili mo ang Maglipat ng mga larawan o Maglipat ng mga file / Android Auto, sa halip na Mag-charge lang, na tumitiyak sa mas ligtas na paglilipat ng data.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Mga Tala:" type="end">
<feature>1. Hindi makakaapekto sa iyong personal na data kapag na-install ang update na ito, pero inirerekomenda pa ring i-back up ang iyong data bago mag-update.
2. Kung makaranas ka ng anumang problema habang nag-a-update, pakitawagan ang hotline ng serbisyo ng HONOR o pumunta sa customer service center ng HONOR para sa suporta.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="tr-tr" code="1055">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Değerli kullanıcımız, önerilen bu güncelleme ile Sihirli Kapsül eklenmiştir. Ayrıca, USB bağlantı amacı değiştirilirken kullanıcı kimlik doğrulaması gerekliliği eklenmiştir.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sihirli Kapsül">
<feature>Sihirli Kapsül size etkin ve verimli servisler sunar. Bir "kapsül" şeklinde görüntülenen bu ekran, devam eden görevleri göstererek gerçek zamanlı durumu takip etmeyi, hızlı işlemler gerçekleştirmeyi veya uygulamalara hızlı bir şekilde girmeyi kolaylaştırır.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sistem">
<feature>USB bağlantı amacı değiştirilirken kullanıcı kimlik doğrulaması gerekliliği eklenmiştir. Sadece şarj yerine Fotoğraf aktarımı veya Dosya aktarma / Android Auto'yu seçtiğinizde bir doğrulama ya da güvenlik istemi görünür ve bu da daha güvenli veri aktarımı sağlar.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Notlar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu güncellemenin yüklenmesi kişisel verilerinizi etkilemeyecektir, fakat yine de güncelleme yapmadan önce yedekleme yapmanız önerilir.
2. Güncelleme esnasında herhangi bir sorunla karşılaşmanız durumunda destek için lütfen HONOR servisi yardım hattını arayın veya HONOR müşteri servisi merkezlerinden birine gidin.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ug-cn" code="1152">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>‏ھۆرمەتلىك ئىشلەتكۈچى، بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاشتا چاققان لەيلىگۈچ قوشۇلدى، USB ئۇلاش ئۇسۇلىنى ئ‍ۆزگەرتكەن ۋاقىتتا ئىشلەتكۈچى سالاھىيىتىنى دەلىللەش باسقۇچى قوشۇلدى، يېڭىلاش تەۋسىيە قىلىنىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«چاققان لەيلىگۈچ»">
<feature>‏مەشغۇلاتتىكى ۋەزىپىنى «لەيلىگۈچ» شەكلىدە كۆرسىتىپ تۇرىدۇ، بۇ ئارقىلىق ئەمەلىي ۋاقىتلىق ھالىتىنى كۆرەلەيسىز، تېز مەشغۇلاتلارنى ئېلىپ بارالايسىز ياكى ئەپكە تېز كىرەلەيسىز، پۈتۈن جەريان ئىنتايىن ئۈنۈملۈك، توغرا ھەم قولاي.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏«سىستېما»">
<feature>‏‏‏USB ئۇلاش ئۇسۇلىنى ئۆزگەرتكەندە ئىشلەتكۈچى سالاھىيىتىنى دەلىللەش باسقۇچى قوشۇلغان بولۇپ، «پەقەت توكلاش» تىن ​«ھۆججەت يوللاش/Android Auto» ياكى «ھۆججەت يوللاش» ھالىتىگە ئالماشتۇرغاندا دەلىللەش كۆرۈنمە يۈزى ياكى بىخەتەرلىك ئەسكەرتمىسى پەيدا بولۇپ، مەلۇمات يوللىشىڭىزنى تېخىمۇ بىخەتەر قىلىدۇ.</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏يېڭىلاشتا دىققەت قىلىدىغان ئىشلار:" type="end">
<feature>‏1. بۇ قېتىملىق يېڭىلاش ئىشلەتكۈچى مەلۇماتلىرىڭىزنى ئۆچۈرمەيدۇ، ئەمما يېڭىلاشتىن بۇرۇن يەنىلا مەلۇماتىڭىزنى زاپاسلىۋېلىشىڭىزنى تەۋسىيە قىلىمىز.
2. يېڭىلاش جەريانىدا ھەرقانداق مەسىلە كۆرۈلسە، روڭياۋ ماركا مۇلازىمەت قىزىق لىنىيەسىگە تېلېفون قىلىڭ ياكى روڭياۋ ماركىسى خېرىدارلار مۇلازىمەت مەركىزىدىن ياردەم سوراڭ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uk-ua" code="1058">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Шановний користувачу! В цьому рекомендованому оновленні представлено додаток "Магічна капсула". Крім того, тепер вимагається автентифікація користувача під час перемикання цілей підключення через USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Магічна капсула">
<feature>"Магічна капсула" надає точні та ефективні послуги, відображається у формі "капсули" та представляє поточні завдання, що дозволяє легко переглядати стан у реальному часі, виконувати швидкі операції або швидко відкривати додатки. Ця функція надає точні та ефективні служби.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Система">
<feature>У разі змінення цілей підключення через USB вимагається автентифікація користувача. Якщо замість цілі "Тільки заряджання" вибирано ціль "Передавання фото" або "Передавання файлів / Android Auto", з’являється підказка для проходження перевірки чи контролю безпеки, що зменшує ризик під час передавання даних.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Примітки" type="end">
<feature>1. Установлення цього оновлення не вплине на ваші особисті дані, але перед оновленням радимо створити їхню резервну копію.
2. Якщо під час оновлення виникнуть якісь проблеми, зателефонуйте на гарячу лінію служби підтримки HONOR або зверніться по допомогу в сервісний центр для клієнтів HONOR.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="ur-pk" code="1056">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>‏محترم صارف، یہ تجویز کردہ اپ ڈیٹ میجک کیپسول متعارف کرواتی ہے۔ مزید برآں، USB کنکشن کے مقاصد کو سوئچ کرتے وقت صارف کی تصدیق کی ضرورت ہوتی ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏میجک کیپسول">
<feature>‏میجک کیپسول آپ کو درست اور مؤثر سروسز فراہم کرتی ہے۔ ایک "کیپسول" کی شکل میں ڈسپلے ہوتا ہے، یہ جاری ٹاسکس کو ظاہر کرتا ہے، جس سے حقیقی وقت میں حالت کو دیکھنا، فوری آپریشنز کرنا، یا جلدی سے ایپس میں داخل ہونا آسان ہو جاتا ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏سسٹم">
<feature>‏‏‏‏USB کنکشن کے مقاصد کو سوئچ کرتے وقت صارف کی تصدیق کی ضرورت ہوتی ہے۔ جب آپ ڈیٹا کی محفوظ منتقلی کو یقینی بناتے ہوئے، صرف چارج کریں کی بجائے، تصاویر منتقل کریں یا فائلز منتقل کریں / Android خود کار کو منتخب کرتے ہیں تو تصدیق یا سکیورٹی اشارہ ظاہر ہوتا ہے۔</feature>
</features>
<features module="‏نوٹس:" type="end">
<feature>‏‏1. اس اپ ڈیٹ کو انسٹال کرنے سے آپ کا ذاتی ڈیٹا نہیں متاثر ہو گا، لیکن پھر بھی اپ ڈیٹ کرنے سے پہلے سے اپنے ڈیٹا کا بیک اپ لینے کی تجویز دی جاتی ہے۔
‏2۔ اگر اپ ڈیٹ کے دوران آپ کو کسی مسئلے کا سامنا کرنا پڑتا ہے، تو تعاون کے لیے براہ کرم HONOR سروس ہاٹ لائن پر کال کریں یا HONOR کسٹمر سروس سینٹر پر جائیں۔</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="uz-uz" code="2115">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Hurmatli foydalanuvchi, ushbu tavsiya etiladigan yangilanishda Sehrli kapsula taqdim etildi. Bundan tashqari, USB ulanish maqsadlarini almashtirishda foydalanuvchi autentifikatsiyasi talab qilinadi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Sehrli kapsula">
<feature>Sehrli kapsula sizga aniq va samarador xizmatlarni taqdim etadi. U “kapsula” shaklida chiqariladi va bajarilayotgan vazifalarni taqdim etadi. Bu real vaqt rejimida holatni koʻrish, tezkor amallarni bajarish yoki ilovalarga tezkor kirishni osonlashtiradi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Tizim">
<feature>USB ulanish maqsadlarini almashtirishda foydalanuvchi autentifikatsiyasi talab qilinadi. “Faqat quvvatlash” oʻrniga “Suratlarni o‘tkazish” yoki “Fayllarni uzatish / Android Auto” tanlaganida, maʼlumotlarni xavfsiz uzatishni taʼminlash uchun tasdiqlash yoki xavfsizlik haqida ogohlantirish oynasi ochiladi.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Eslatmalar:" type="end">
<feature>1. Bu yangilanishni oʻrnatish shaxsiy maʼlumotlaringizga taʼsir qilmaydi, lekin yangilashdan oldin maʼlumotlaringizni zaxiralash tavsiya etiladi.
2. Agar yangilash paytida muammolarga duch kelsangiz, yordam uchun HONOR xizmat markazi tezkor raqamiga murojaat qiling yoki HONOR mijozlarga xizmat markaziga tashrif buyuring.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="vi-vn" code="1066">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Người dùng thân mến, bản cập nhật đề xuất này giới thiệu Magic Capsule. Ngoài ra, cần xác thực người dùng khi chuyển đổi mục đích kết nối USB.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Magic Capsule">
<feature>Magic Capsule cung cấp cho bạn các dịch vụ chính xác và hiệu quả. Được hiển thị dưới dạng "nang", chức năng này hiển thị các tác vụ đang diễn ra, giúp bạn dễ dàng xem trạng thái theo thời gian thực, thực hiện các thao tác nhanh hoặc truy cập nhanh vào ứng dụng.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Hệ thống">
<feature>Cần xác thực người dùng khi chuyển đổi mục đích kết nối USB. Một thông báo nhắc xác minh hoặc bảo mật sẽ xuất hiện khi bạn chọn Truyền tải ảnh hoặc Truyền tệp tin/Android Auto, thay vì Chỉ sạc pin, giúp truyền dữ liệu an toàn hơn.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Ghi chú:" type="end">
<feature>1. Nếu bạn cài đặt bản cập nhật này, dữ liệu cá nhân của bạn sẽ không bị ảnh hưởng. Tuy nhiên, bạn vẫn nên sao lưu dữ liệu trước khi cập nhật.
2. Nếu bạn gặp bất kỳ sự cố nào trong quá trình cập nhật, vui lòng gọi điện đến đường dây nóng dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR hoặc đến trung tâm dịch vụ khách hàng của HONOR để được hỗ trợ.</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-hk" code="3076">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的用戶，本次更新新增靈動膠囊，更改 USB 連接方式時增加用戶身份驗證，建議您更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【靈動膠囊】">
<feature>以「膠囊」形態顯示，展示進行中的任務，方便檢視實時狀態、執行快捷操作或快速前往應用程式，高效服務、準確觸達。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>更改 USB 連接方式時增加用戶身份驗證，從「僅充電」切換至「傳輸檔案 / Android Auto」或「傳輸檔案」模式時，彈出驗證介面或安全提示，讓您的數據傳輸更安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的用戶數據，但仍建議您在更新前做好數據備份。
2. 更新過程中，如果遇到任何問題，請致電榮耀品牌服務熱線，或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="zh-tw" code="1028">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>親愛的使用者，本次更新新增靈動膠囊，變更 USB 連接方式時新增使用者身分驗證，建議您進行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【靈動膠囊】">
<feature>以「膠囊」形態顯示，展示進行中的工作，便於查看即時狀態、執行快捷操作或快速進入應用程式，高效服務、準確觸達。</feature>
</features>
<features module="【系統】">
<feature>變更 USB 連接方式時新增使用者身分驗證，從「僅充電」切換至「傳輸檔案 / Android Auto」或「傳輸檔案」模式時，彈出驗證畫面或安全提示，讓您的資料傳輸更安全。</feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事項：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不會刪除您的使用者資料，但仍建議您在更新前做好資料備份。
2. 更新過程中，若遇到任何問題，請撥打榮耀品牌服務專線或前往榮耀品牌客戶服務中心尋求支援。</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
