<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<root>
<component name="TCPU" version="CMO内部使用，商用发布不用关注，设备不会显示"/>
<default-language name="en-us">1033</default-language>
<language name="zh-cn" code="2052">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>亲爱的用户，本次更新新增 AI 消除、AI 笔记、AI 文档以及魔法修图中的 AI 扩图、AI 风格功能，新增三方应用通话录音和全局任务栏功能，提升系统性能和部分场景功耗体验，合入安全补丁，推荐您进行更新。</feature>
</features>
<features module="AI 消除">
<feature>•  新增 AI 消除功能，智能消除照片中的路人、杂物等，一键拯救废片。体验路径：图库 > 选择图片 > AI编辑 > 魔法修图 > AI消除。</feature>
</features>
<features module="AI 扩图">
<feature>•  新增 AI 扩图功能，支持旋转扩图和自由比例扩图，让照片秒变大片。体验路径：图库 > 选择照片 > AI 编辑 > 魔法修图 > AI 扩图。</feature>
</features>
<features module="AI 风格">
<feature>•  新增 AI 风格功能，使能多样的创意风格，让照片重焕新生。体验路径：图库 > 选择照片 > AI 编辑 > 魔法修图 > AI 风格。</feature>
</features>
<features module="AI 文档">
<feature>•  新增辅助阅读功能，支持多文对比，快速总结多方观点，一键生成思维导图，高效输出论文框架。
•  新增辅助写作功能，支持智慧润色、扩充/缩短篇幅、风格改写、智慧排版，轻松完成内容创作。体验路径：荣耀文档 > 打开一篇文档 > 左下角“文档助理”。</feature>
</features>
<features module="桌面">
<feature>•  折叠屏展开态全局任务栏，沉浸式切换应用。应用内手势导航上滑呈现全局任务栏，方便您快速切换应用，还可拖拽应用变为悬浮窗或分屏，为您提供更高效的桌面交互。</feature>
</features>
<features module="系统应用">
<feature>•  新增微信、QQ 三方应用通话录音功能。体验路径：设置 > 辅助功能 > 第三方应用通话录音。</feature>
</features>
<features module="系统">
<feature>•  分屏场景下，支持按应用进行选择截屏。
•  优化系统性能，让您的手机运行更流畅。</feature>
</features>
<features module="续航">
<feature>•  优化部分场景功耗体验。</feature>
</features>
<features module="安全">
<feature>•  合入安卓 2025 年 2 月安全补丁，增强系统安全性。有关荣耀软件安全更新内容的信息，请访问荣耀官方网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/support/bulletin/2025/2 </feature>
</features>
<features module="更新注意事项：" type="end">
<feature>1. 本次更新不会删除您的用户数据，但仍建议您在更新前做好数据备份。
2. 更多精彩功能介绍，请访问“玩机技巧”应用。
3. 如果您在使用过程中遇到任何问题，请访问“我的荣耀”应用或访问荣耀官方服务网站 https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us 寻求支持。</feature>
</features>
</language>

<language name="en-us" code="1033">
<features module="" type="header">
<feature>Dear user, this update introduces AI Eraser, AI Notes, AI Doc and enhances Magic Retouch with AI Outpainting and AI Style. It also enables call recording in some third-party apps. Moreover, this release includes Global Taskbar and improves the system performance. Additionally, it reduces the power consumption in some scenarios and incorporates a security patch. Update to enjoy the new features and improvements.</feature>
</features>
<features module="AI Eraser">
<feature>• The new AI Eraser can help you intelligently remove the passers-by and other unwanted elements from images with a single tap. Try it out by going to: Gallery > Select an image > AI Edit > Magic Retouch > AI Eraser.</feature>
</features>
<features module="AI Outpainting">
<feature>• AI Outpainting allows rotation or adjustment in a free ratio, instantly turning your photos into masterpieces. Try it out by going to: Gallery > Select an image > AI Edit > Magic Retouch > AI Outpainting.</feature>
</features>
<features module="AI Style">
<feature>• AI Style offers a variety of creative styles to give your images a new look. Try it out by going to: Gallery > Select an image > AI Edit > Magic Retouch > AI Style.</feature>
</features>
<features module="AI Doc">
<feature>• Assisted reading supports comparison of multiple texts and quick summarization of diverse viewpoints. Furthermore, it can generate mind maps with a single tap, and efficiently produce paper frameworks.
• Assisted writing now features AI text refinement, Expand/Shorten text, Change writing styles, and AI Format, making your content creation smoother. Try it out by going to: HONOR Docs > Open a document > Doc Assistant in the lower left corner.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Home screen">
<feature>• In the unfolded state, Global Taskbar brings you immersive switching between apps. Swipe up within an app to display Global Taskbar for you to quickly switch between apps. You can also drag an app to view it in a floating window or enable App Extender, creating efficient home screen interaction.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System apps">
<feature>• Call recording is available in third-party apps like WeChat and QQ. Try it out by going to: Settings > Accessibility features > App call recording.</feature>
</features>
<features module="System">
<feature>• You can take screenshots of individual apps in split-screen mode.
• Optimizes the system performance to make your device run more smoothly.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Battery life">
<feature>• Reduces the power consumption in some scenarios.</feature>
</features>
<features module="Security">
<feature>• Android security patch (Feb 2025) has been incorporated for system security. For more information about HONOR Security updates, please visit our website https://www.honor.com/global/support/bulletin/2025/2 </feature>
</features>
<features module="Notes:" type="end">
<feature>1. Installing this update will not affect your personal data, but it is still recommended to back up your data before updating.
2. Discover more information on product features in the Tips app.
3. If you encounter any issues during use, please get support by going to My HONOR or visiting our website: https://www.honor.com/cn/contact-us.</feature>
</features>
</language>

</root>
